[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://i.imgur.com/cXTRBqS.png" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Julian Cotterelli Banagher[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b] Ju-lee-en &nbsp;Cot-er-el-e &nbsp;Ban-uh-ger
[b]nickname:[/b] Ju
[b]age and birthday:[/b] 17, December 25
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b] male, he/him

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b] half-blood, werewolf&nbsp;
[b]sexuality:[/b] bisexual
[b]wand:[/b] 10 1/4 inch, red oak, dragon heartstring&nbsp;
[b]playby:[/b] Bill Skarsgard&nbsp;
[b]appearance:[/b] 6ft, lanky, scar on the back of his neck from the werewolf bite.&nbsp;

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling &amp; status[/b] Slytherin, Sixth Year&nbsp;
[b]current occupation:[/b] n/a

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b] the beach, being outside, care of magical creatures class, chocolate, being alone&nbsp;

[b]dislikes:[/b] amateur theatre, being a werewolf, his mother, quidditch, apologies (giving &amp; receiving)

[b]overall personality:[/b]
Julian has always been something of a loner, going out of his way to poke and prod at his classmates' insecurities. He didn't have friends prior to the bite and he didn't feel like he needed them. After the bite, he is more aware of the fact that he can't go it alone in the world, especially as a werewolf. As a result, he's trying to make amends with people that he bullied in the past, but finds it difficult.&nbsp;This is because while Julian will go to bat for those he is close to, he's also very emotionally closed off. He'll jump into the fray for those he cares about, but other than that, he struggles with being vulnerable and showing someone how he feels about them.&nbsp;

Julian has a very sarcastic, dry sense of humor, and doesn't actively try to make others laugh, just himself. He can occasionally be self-deprecating, but this has developed primarily as a defense mechanism as he deals with the intense feelings that have been brought on by the werewolf bite. If someone else were to say the same things toward him, he wouldn't hesitate to lash out.&nbsp;



[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b] Folkestone, England - born and raised&nbsp;
[b]relations:[/b]

Sharon Banagher - Mother, also born and raised in Folkestone. Half-blood, Slytherin when she was at Hogwarts. She's incredibly strict, and has grounded Julian more often than she hasn't.&nbsp;

Raphael Cotterelli - Father, originally from Italy. Muggle, disappeared during the spate of murders that were eventually attributed to the Purifiers.&nbsp;

Audrey Leanne Banagher - Little sister, 13, currently a third year Gryffindor. Prior to becoming a werewolf, Julian picked on her constantly.&nbsp;


[b]pets:[/b] n/a
[b]history:[/b]

Early Life - Julian was born into a family where he was both aware of magic and expected to go to Hogwarts when he turned eleven. From a young age, his mother had a lot of high hopes pinned on him - namely that he would end up being a top student just like she was. Except, he never had much of an interest in academics, and tended to hide from the tutor that his mother hired as much as possible. 

He soon proved to be a difficult and willful child. Julian spent more of his birthdays grounded than not, and as his younger sister Audrey got older, he picked on her too, frequently breaking her toys just to see her cry. His mother was quickly at her wit's end, because punishing Julian never seemed to work well. In fact, he seemed to like being by himself. 

Teenage Years - 

At Hogwarts, things continued very similarly. Julian skipped lessons as much as he possibly could, and got a reputation as a student with middling to incredibly poor grades. He spent a lot of time sitting at the back of classrooms, flicking enchanted spitballs at other students. He didn't have any friends, and frankly, he wasn't interested in having any. He was fine on his own.

When students were found dead in his second year, he wasn't particularly afraid - and he even mocked other students who were afraid themselves. The only murder attempt that really got to him was Ethan's - because Ethan survived, it suddenly seemed far more ghastly and terrifying, and suddenly he wasn't making very many jokes anymore. 

When his father disappeared before Christmas 2022, Julian drew some looks of sympathy from other students, but reacted by being increasingly standoffish and rude. The last thing that he wanted was for other people to suddenly act like they needed to console him. 

The summer before sixth year, things changed again when Julian was bitten by a werewolf. He'd snuck out, and even he doesn't remember why anymore, when he was attacked in his family's backyard. His sister was the one who found him. 

Julian began the school year by trying to make amends for his behavior, but has found this difficult - especially since right before the winter holidays, a fellow Slytherin intercepted one of his letters from home and discovered that he was a werewolf, meaning that now - everybody knows. 

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b] Bird
[b] pronouns:[/b] she/her
[b]age:[/b] 27
[/div][/div]