[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" alt="" src="https://66.media.tumblr.com/08ac9154b54b646d49041e486c81f049/tumblr_p7uzabP7Wx1x0a0g9o1_500.gif"]
[/div]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]lulu anne blishwick[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]Loo-Loo Ann Blish-wick[/blockquote][b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Loo.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]16

October 30. Scorpio baby.[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]



[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]

[blockquote]Pureblood[/blockquote][b]sexuality:[/b]

[blockquote]Demisexual[/blockquote][b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]10" Oak wood with unicorn hair core[/blockquote][b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Billie Eilish.[/blockquote]

[b]appearance:[/b]

[blockquote]Lulu stands at precisely 5'2" and is petite in stature. Don't be fooled by her vertically challenged appearance, she packs a mean punch. Lulu Blishwick looks identical to her playby Billie Eilish. Her hair is a different color every week and she could often be seen expressing herself through her unique sense of clothing and jewelry - often banned items from Hogwarts due to being too distracting or "loud" in class.&nbsp;She is considered a "Tom Boy" but she has many "girlie girl" quirks when it comes to appearance, such as her obsession with perfectly manicured nails and a different hair color from day to day. Her clothes are at times baggy but she’s a believer of being comfortable rather than impressing people with appearance, even if that means she's rocking too long of robes or frumpy looking joggers half of the time.

[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]

[b]schooling[/b]
[blockquote]Slytherin.
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]

[blockquote]Sixth Year.

[/blockquote][b]current occupation:[/b]

[blockquote]Part Time Receptionist for Blishwick Matchmaking Services during summer holiday


[/blockquote][div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]+ Oddities and strange things
+ Getting into people’s business
+ People watching
+ Singing for anyone that will listen and pretending she can rap
+ Dancing crazily
+ Making the ugliest faces possible across the classroom
+ Manicures
+ Giving advice she doesn't follow
+ The idea of love&nbsp;
+ Quidditch
+ Small Animals
+ Shopping
+ Snakes
+ Art
+ Work ethic[/blockquote][b]dislikes:[/b]

[blockquote]-&nbsp; Tea (she only likes to spill it)
- Bullying
- Her bad memory/forgetfulness (she often forget when she's 'mad' at someone)
- Not doing something perfect the first time
- Cousin Jimmie's negativity
- People who take quidditch ~too seriously~
- The smell of citrus
- Lack of creativity or imagination
- Boring people
- Blood purists
- Old men telling her to smile
- Being told "no"[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]+ Marrying rich so she doesn't have to work hard forever
+ Living in Spain on a beach 
+ Leading a humanitarian group or maybe cult[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]

[blockquote]+ Cherry Blossom, coffee and freshly mowed grass.[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]

[blockquote]Drowning or burning alive
Hissing cockroaches[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]

[blockquote]Lulu is a young woman with a heart of gold and a thirst for adventure. She has a good head on her shoulders and isn't easily influenced by her peers. Lulu has never cared about being 'cool', never afraid to go against the flow or march to the beat of her own drum. She has a good work ethic and is very achievement oriented. School has never been easy for Lulu because she's often caught with her head in the clouds but she does well when she applies herself. She's eager to learn but not very successful at retaining information. At times her bad memory has gotten her into trouble because she told a secret she wasn't supposed to tell or can't remember important information. Random trivia and other pointless information in stored in her noggin forever instead. There had been instances where her views could be "too strong" when she feels she's right, is passionate about something, or if someone isn't being treated properly. Lulu won't stand for bullying or blood purists under her watch. She isn't a fighter but she will certainly use words to try to make someone feel stupid for treating someone less fortunate badly. She hasn't gotten into a physical altercation but she kind of wants to, just to see if she'd win.

Most of the time Lulu has a pretty 'chill' demeanor but there are also times she goes through hyper spazz moments where she needs a hamster wheel to get the energy out. Sometimes in class she's too chatty and the teachers move her assigned seat around to deter the actions. What the teachers don't realize is they're only helping her make new friends in class by having her sit by someone she doesn't know.

Quidditch has helped Lulu release her energy and thrive in a team setting, but she doesn't always see eye to eye with her Slytherin teammates. She doesn't like to play sports too seriously,&nbsp; but she enjoys the intensity of quidditch and getting high on her broom. Lulu is currently seeker but enjoys playing keeper as well.

Lulu Blishwick strives to be known for saving the world - or maybe starting a cult. She wants to be a part of something really big. She's a leader and could easily influence others with her passionate nature, genuine personality, and willingness to connect with others. Lulu is extremely nosey and loves knowing every detail about everyone's business. Some people may find her invasive but she truly likes to know things. She considers herself an open book so she forces others to be by prying information out of them. She also gets a thrill at being an attention whore. There's nothing like having a room full of eyes captivated by the sound of her voice, or pupils&nbsp; intrigued by what she has to say. Whether if they think what she's saying is inspirational or stupid.

Lulu loves the idea of love but she doesn't feel like she is worthy of being loved by someone fully. She's confused when it comes to the playing field so she enjoys living vicariously through people she sees at Blishwick's. She enjoys helping out Uncle Jimbo because he pays very well for her to sit on her bum scheduling meetings and listen to peoples business... Oh, and added bonus: Uncle Jimbo's Dad jokes.

[/blockquote]


[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]



[b]origins:[/b]


[blockquote]London, England. Somewhere new Horizont Alley..[/blockquote]

[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Eliza Blishwick - Mom - Aurologist

Harry Blishwick - Dad - Broom Maker

Oli - Brother - 13&nbsp;

Sid - Brother - 14

@jimbo                - Favorite [s]and only[/s] Uncle&nbsp;

@jimmie                - Cousin


[/blockquote][b]pets:[/b]

[blockquote]A cat named Bob
Bearded dragon back at home named Lenny[/blockquote]

[b]history:[/b]


[blockquote]Lulu Blishwick was born in&nbsp; London, England on October 30, 2011, to Eliza and Harry Blishwick. She was raised in an upper-middle class Pureblood household where magic was used heavily. Since a young age she anticipated attending Hogwarts where she'd learn to hone her skills, and more importantly, where she'd be able to play quidditch. Lulus parents have never been enthusiastic for her playing the sport since it's considered dangerous, but since she made the team and has shown steadfast passion they have decided to support their daughters dreams.

As a child Lulu was homeschooled and she hated it. Eliza and Harry hated it too because she was hysterical and very hard to handle when cooped up inside. Lulu was too social of a child to have such a solitary method of learning. She had too much energy and needed an outlet. Lulu found out that singing was a great way to get her emotions and pent up energy out. And she was pretty good at it too. Her parents signed her up for a performing arts school in their surrounding neighborhood of Horizont Alley. However, once she got her acceptance letter from Hogwarts, singing was put on the backburner for a while.

Lulus family life was always a bit chaotic. Mostly because of Lulu's theatrics. Since she was young, she struggled at getting along with her younger brothers because she always wanted the attention on her. They have recently done better in school than her, which she finds very frustrating but she will always be the best quidditch player in the family. During her forth year she tried out for the team and held the position as keeper. Since the older kids graduated, she was able to play with the idea of playing seeker. She loves it but hopes to dabble in other positions as well. This upcoming school year she hopes to hone deeper into quidditch and sharpen her skills.

Love has always been a weird subject for Lulu. Her family is known for their 'Blishwick' name. Unfortunately, since&nbsp; her father didn't inherit the Blishwick gift, neither did any of his kids. Lulu honestly felt jipped in that department but at least Uncle Jimbo had mercy and hired her part time for reception and other duties. She hasn't been into anyone enough to want to date them but she's open minded to the idea if the right guy or gal comes around.

Lulu isn't sure what she wants to do for work in the future. She's very gung ho about quidditch at the moment but she knows it's not really a realistic profession. Lulu is working on connections now so she hopefully won't have to work hard her entire life. She hopes to meet a rich man or woman. All she wants is to be able to live comfortably and travel to some nice beaches in her lifetime. At the moment she's happy helping Uncle Jimbo and comfortable with the idea of working for him until she figures out what she wants to do the next couple of years.&nbsp;

[/blockquote]

[b]site events reaction:[/b]

[blockquote]Lulu was attending the quidditch event when the explosions happened. She was concerned about getting her panicking friends out. She's currently suffering from slight PTSD from the event and nightmares.&nbsp;

Lulu doesn't mind the Ilvermorny kids joining Hogwarts. It's a lot more crowded but the days are never boring. The American kids don't seem to care much about quidditch so she doesn't feel threatened by them taking her position on the team.

During the dragon attacks Lulu was working at Blishwicks Matchmaking services so it was frightening. She suffered minor injuries from broken glass.&nbsp;

The murders had her quite shaken up but she doesn't believe in living life in fear though and she has enough street smarts to get her by. She didn't know anyone that died by the murders.

[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]

[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]dez[/blockquote][b] pronouns:[/b]

[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote][b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]29[/blockquote][b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]PST -CA![/blockquote][b]reference:[/b]

[blockquote]I live here[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]

@tobias                , @joseph                , @simon                , @gideon                , @travis               [/div][/div]