
[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://i.pinimg.com/originals/af/77/41/af7741cf1a706777bc39e6a786787018.jpg" alt=""]
[/div]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]Isabeau Audra Boothby[/font][/div][hr]

[b]pronunciation:[/b]

[blockquote]Is-ah-bow boot-by[/blockquote]

[b]nickname:[/b]

[blockquote]Isa (most frequently)
Issy
Beau[/blockquote]

[b]age and birthday:[/b]

[blockquote]17
23rd March 2009[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]

[blockquote]Female
She/Her[/blockquote]



[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]

[b]blood status:[/b]

[blockquote]Half blood, even if her father does think otherwise.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[b]sexuality:[/b]

[blockquote]Straight[/blockquote]

[b]wand:[/b]

[blockquote]	13 ¼ inch elm, dragon heartstring[/blockquote]

[b]playby:[/b]

[blockquote]Ann Kuleshova[/blockquote]

[b]appearance:[/b]

[blockquote]160cm small and petite, Dark features. Usually a displeased look on her face; a scowl or cold glare. Or at the very least a very forced neutrality leaning more towards the cold side.&nbsp; Very well put together and well dressed. Never a hair out of place or not well presented. No scars or distinguishing features as such. In school when in uniform she often wears her hair in some sort of braids to keep her silky locks out of her face.&nbsp;[/blockquote]



[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]

[b]schooling &amp; status[/b]

[blockquote]Sytherin, Sixth Year&nbsp;

[/blockquote]

[b]current occupation:[/b]

[blockquote]N/A.[/blockquote]



[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]

[b]likes:[/b]

[blockquote]Cuthbert her cat
Herbology
The Greenhouses at Hogwarts
The Library at Hogwarts
Hiding away&nbsp;
People watching
Shopping
Money
Make up
Clothes&nbsp;
Wine&nbsp;
Nights out&nbsp;
School (not that she'd admit it)
Putting effort into her looks&nbsp;

[/blockquote]

[b]dislikes:[/b]

[blockquote]Socialising/Having to deal with people and their problems or emotions
Idiots&nbsp;
Purifiers
Muggleborns (or she at least has to pretend to)
Demi-Humans (again, has to pretend to, more conditioned to this)
Poor People (also heavily conditioned)
Being trotted out like the show pony at society events like her Father likes to do
People being mean to her cat

[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]

[blockquote]Once upon a time Isa would have been childish and carefree, unfortunately it was fairly quickly schooled out of her. With a controlling father and a mother who has trained Isa to rely heavily on her looks; she has become vain and all about keeping up appearances. She is very shut off from her actual emotions, rather than showing them she keeps them in a neat little box in the back of her head, hardly ever actually addressing them.&nbsp;

Isa is overall cold and distant. She doesn't have many friends at all and she's not sure if she even wants them really. She works better alone. She's selfish and self preserving to the extent where she would barely put you out if you were on fire, and that would only if there wasn't too much effort involved. Isabeau is not an open and friendly person at all. She sticks to herself, because it's simply easier than getting involved. However if she does really have to interact, she sometimes doesn't care too much of what she is saying and can be overly direct. Enjoying to people watching Isa is observant and gathers intel to use later on. She very much floats about in the shadows watching but never really interacting unless directly unless invited.&nbsp;She comes across as very meek and mild in school towards figures or authority, but really she's not bothered fighting them and preserves her energy for other endeavours. She's studious and gets brilliant grades, annoyingly so.&nbsp;

She doesn't exactly outwardly agree with her parents societal views, but it is easier in her mind to feign ignorance to whatever they do behind the scenes and enjoy the parties, rather than speaking out against them. She very rarely goes against her parents wishes and finds it easier to just stay in confined uncomfortable silence.&nbsp;[/blockquote]



[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]

[b]origins:[/b]

[blockquote]Kensington, London UK[/blockquote]

[b]relations:[/b]

[blockquote]
[i]
Richard Boothby.[/i] Father. 51. Half-Blood. Purifier. Head of Department of International Magical Cooperation. Born and bred Wnglishman. Stiff upper lip a lot of the time. Cold. Works a lot; if he isn’t out schmoozing diplomats or travelling for work.&nbsp;Old money from the Broom industry. Still has shares in the business.  Fairly good relationship with Isa. Generally distant from the family. Pays attention to Isa when she gets good grades, or catches the attention of some Pureblood family who are interested in having her marry one of their sons or the likes.&nbsp;


[i]Celeste Boothby [/i](neé Moreau). 46. Pureblood. Trophy Wife. French. Always looks immaculate. Comes from an affluent French Pureblood family based in the Alps. Substance abuse issues as far back as Isa can remember. The show pony her father wants to turn Isa into. Married Celeste for her connections for the most part, just a bonus they had two beautiful children. Good enough relationship with Isa. Treats her as more of a friend, very little boundaries 


[i]
Hugo Boothby.[/i] 21. Brother. Graduated from Hogwarts three years ahead of Isa. Played Quidditch. Briefly played professionally before a shoulder injury took him out altogether last year. Currently working an entry level job at the ministry but doesn’t care much about it. He doesn’t need to when he’s spending the family’s money. Currently being pressured to find a good Pureblood wife by his father, and start popping out more Pureblooded offspring. Isa would have liked to have been closer with him, but he always saw his little sister as an annoyance and didn’t have much time for her. 

[/blockquote]



[b]pets:[/b]

[blockquote]Cuthbert the Cat; big, fat, white fluffy Persian cat with bright blue eyes. Generally a utter prick of a cat personality wise. Lazy. Does nothing but annoy the people in Slyth common room by lounging around and leaving white hair on things, or rummaging through people's things looking for food.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[b]history:[/b]

[blockquote]Isabeau Boothby and her older brother Hugo are the product of a very well brokered business deal. Although from the outside looking in it seems like a fairly loving Marriage it isn’t always. Both parents have their own separate issues with various forms of substance abuse and at times cannot stand each other. Celeste often resents Richard and the life she was trapped in, in saying that she seemed to get lucky. It’s a comfortable life all the same. Sometimes she tells Isa that she would be lucky to find a life like this. Isabeau knows her parents' plans for her and detests them.

From a young age there was always immense pressure on Isa to be perfect. To be perfectly manicured, primped and polished. To act perfectly well mannered. To be a perfect little Pureblood Princess that will grow up and be married off to her own Pureblood Prince who can then start having their own little Pureblood babies. Which is ironic, as she’s probably not as Pure-Blooded as her Father likes to think. Yes the Moreau line was kept fairly pure, but the Boothby line was definitely watered down and mixed throughout the decades. Still, they have money and are in a position of power so that will do, for now. That is until they can continue climbing up the social ladder, and gain even higher status. As far back as she can remember she was brought to all sorts of parties and mixers, banquets and fundraisers and trotted out for show by her parents. What a gorgeous little girl, what good grades she gets, what fine manners. Isa hated all of it, but she went along with it because it was the right thing to do. To please her parents. Over time the bright young girl she had been, dulled with age as she bent to the will of her parents, refining herself bit by bit. 

When she graduated on from her basic education at home tutor, to Hogwarts she was sure she would be away from them, and free. Free like Hugo. Except she wasn’t. At school Hugo wouldn’t even look at her. It hurt at first, but she grew used to it. Acting cold and indifferent as she had been so used to seeing from her Mother. It was easier that way, to pretend it didn’t get to her. Quickly enough it was easier to do that with all her emotions, shut them off. Deal with it later when it was more convenient, for now being more refined and stoic. 

When her parents decided how her life would fall before her, Isa wasn’t so sure about it. Always the dutiful daughter, she did nothing to upset them and carried on with it. Even if she wanted more for herself. A romantic at heart she dreamt of more for herself, maybe even Muggle University like she had read about in the books Hugo mercilessly teased her for that she read when she was a pre-teen, or else maybe she could travel the world, without her parents looking over her shoulder. Her Ambition and resourcefulness to make this happen was how she ended up being sorted in Slytherin House. She was used to putting pressure on herself in every other aspect of life, why wouldn’t grades be any different? She flourished at school, but kept the fact to herself. She didn’t want to be seen as a swot or a teacher's pet, but still, she wanted to succeed. Quickly enough she figured out her surprising green thumb and affinity for Herbology, it became her best subject, along with Potions, and the Greenhouses became one of her favourite places to hide away in the castle grounds. 

As the years have gone on and she has move up through the school, she's discovered this. With students going missing and more recently the devastation over the Tri-Wizard Tournament. Although she enjoyed the spectacle of the whole thing at the time, the discourse it caused and the ripple effect it set off it something she has never really gotten over.&nbsp; Instead she uses it as an example of why Isabeau has learned to stick to herself. She finds it hard to deal with people, especially when there was so many transfers from Ilvermorny into her year. These strangers didn't make any of it any easier, even if they were going through similar horrors. She never found the nerve to branch out and befriend any of them. To Isa, hiding away from people is always so much more preferable to facing reality. Especially when the reality is so ugly. 

In the summer prior to beginning her sixth year, she discovered the uncomfortable truth about her father, after coming home early from shopping one day. A truth she had suspected for a few years, but never really wanted to face; he was a Purifier. And by the sounds of it a fairly high up one. Silently she hated everything the Purifiers stood for, she wanted to break out of the old Pureblood society, and here was her Father trying to preserve it all. By the looks of it her mother and Hugo had known too. Hugo even in training for the same. How long had she been so stupid? So ignorant? It shook her to her core, but in a way made her even more ambitious to break out of the circle. It just made sure she had to do it in a more sly way in future. However, staying under the radar of different fractions within the school and the wider wizarding world has not proven easy even if she is feigning a level of indifference to it all.&nbsp;

For now she lives her life on the frayed edges, mostly lurking in the shadows of the castle. Sitting on the edge of a group people watching is a lot easier than being the centre of attention.[/blockquote]



[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]

[b]name:[/b]

[blockquote]Dra[/blockquote]

[b] pronouns:[/b]

[blockquote]&nbsp;she/her[/blockquote]

[b]age:[/b]

[blockquote]old enough[/blockquote]

[/div][/div]