[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" alt=" " src="https://i.pinimg.com/originals/85/26/c2/8526c2f3ef29851d9cd0ca26e474e0a6.jpg"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]nessa abigael byrne[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]first name: ness-uh
last name: burn [/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]n/a[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]16
September 5th, 2009[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Female
she/her/hers[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Muggleborn[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Straight[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]10 ½ inches, English oak, Phoenix feather, Stiff.[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Florence Pugh[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]5’4”. Same as playby for everything. A faded scar on the top of her right hand where she was bitten by dog when she was five.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts. Slytherin.
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Going into 6th year for 2025/2026 term. Will graduate in 2027.
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]n/a[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]tigers, documentaries about places around the world, being outside, collecting small stones, museums, cookies, urban exploration (includes breaking and entering into anything that even looks interesting), Nate[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]dogs, getting caught while exploring buildings, rainy days and being cooped up inside in general, romance novels/movies/anything, heights/climbing/flying[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]To be free of the orphanage so that she can travel to wherever she pleases and without anyone or anything holding her back. To become a cursebreaker so that she can take advantage of that dream and make money at the same time.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]leather, cigarette smoke, musty buildings[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Terrified of heights. She hates having to climb the stairs at Hogwarts and she actively avoids the Quidditch Pitch and Astronomy Tower because of this. If she’s exploring a building and has the choice of being caught or climbing higher to find a way out, she would rather be caught. Nessa also has an extreme fear of dogs and will cross the street just to avoid them. The little ones are the scariest.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Nessa likes to think that nobody else understands or wants her, and therefore isn’t the warmest individual in the world. She has extreme difficulty in forming attachments with other people, and only has a couple of close friends because of that. With these friends she has no problem being thick as thieves with them, and expects that in return. Dropping people who aren’t invested in a meaning relationship with her aren’t worth it in her eyes. For everyone else, she doesn’t really care unless it benefits her in some way. Being curt with people is pretty common with her because she doesn’t want to waste time on pointless conversations.

Creating bonds with adults is even worse, because she’s always afraid they’ll just abandon her again. Despite being at the orphanage her entire life, she only views the caretakers as that: caretakers. They aren’t her friends or her parental figures. The same could be said about the professors at Hogwarts, but she’s noticed over the years that they don’t really care about her as long as she does the required work and stays quiet in class. 

Being the rebellious little orphan that she is, Nessa also tends to have issues with following the rules. She doesn’t see anything wrong with breaking into abandoned buildings to explore (because who’s even using them to care in the first place?) and she has been told a number of times over the years that her name should be Trouble instead. As aforementioned, she doesn’t exactly respect adult figures and has no problem with talking back when she’s caught lying or doing something she isn’t supposed to be doing.

The only time her tough exterior is going to falter is if she can’t escape from an oncoming dog or is stuck on some inescapable ledge high up, reducing her to a bubbling mess. 
 [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Dublin, Ireland. Lives at Pupillus Dorum Orphanage [/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Mother – Willow Byrne, 36, muggle, whereabouts unknown
Father – Connor Murphy, 43, muggle, whereabouts unknown
No siblings
[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]n/a[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]The product of a one-night stand and born to a young, single and struggling mother, Nessa has always been under the impression that she was never really wanted. She has fleeting memories and a few photographs from her infant years where her mother really did try, but that is about it. The young Willow Byrne couldn’t continue raising her child, the only alternative being to put her up for adoption. As a toddler, Nessa bounced around between families and soon became locked in the system, only to be yanked out of the muggle one and placed into the magical one the second sparks of magic started appearing whenever she sneezed or toppled over. 

As far is she is concerned, Pupillus Dorum Orphanage is the only real home she has ever had. Before going to Hogwarts, there were a few families that approached to see if she would be a good fit or not as a new addition, but it never worked out. Most of the families already had children, some her age and some much older, but they also always had dogs. A chance encounter with a roaming pup on the edge of the orphanage grounds when she was five had left her terrified of the animal. It had only been a small nip at her hand to get her to back off, but that was enough for Nessa to never want to be near one again. Having her in a home with pets struck a lot of contenders for new families, but she was fine with that. Even at a young age, she unconsciously knew that the only permanence she was going to have was by staying at the orphanage. At least she had other kids just like her there. That ended up meaning more than some new family trying to take her in and make her their ‘own’. 

Like all other eleven year olds, the year to start Hogwarts was a long one. With her birthday falling immediately after other kids her age left, Nessa spent the entirety of the year moping around and waiting for her friends to return for breaks, being regaled with stories of the freedom she had started to long for. Her restlessness during the school year though led her to wandering outside of the orphanage’s property at all times of the day, mostly just so she could stretch her boundaries and see what she could get away with. It was here that her love for exploration and going places where she wasn’t started. By the end of that long year, the orphanage was more than happy to ship her off to Hogwarts in September. She was finally free!

The first two years were probably as standard as they could get: classes were hard to stay awake in and doing homework was boring. The castle was great though! Nessa spent all of her free time (and then some) wandering around the corridors and busting into unused rooms just because she could. The grounds were equally as amazing, though after being dragged out of the forest by prefects a few times the professors started to take note and stop her before she could even get close. Getting sorted into Slytherin with her best friend from the orphanage, Nate Forrester, made the transition a lot easier, though they were only bound for more trouble from there on.
 [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Enter third year: 2022. Nessa had never really cared much about the status of her ‘blood’, though that quickly changed when muggleborn students like herself started turning up dead. Her quick and easy answer was that she had no idea what her real blood status was, being abandoned and an orphan. That also meant that nobody would miss her if she was offed. She started to stick closer to the few friends she had made over the previous two years and wandered less, knowing that if she put herself in positions of danger, it would follow. 

The culmination of her third year eased some of those worries, only to reignite them once again the next year during the Triwizard Tournament. The extra security for the tournament meant that they were safe at school, but there were all the headlines still floating about. She enjoyed watching the events and talking to the students from Beauxbatons and Durmstrang (mostly to try and convince them to let her sneak onto the boat and carriage so she could explore). If anything, the end of the tournament reminded her that wanting any sort of permanence was a folly, as her new friends she had made from the other wizarding schools were snuffed out of existence.

Nessa decided then to adopt her own personal policy of not letting anyone else in that wasn’t already there. She knew there would be less hurt there in the end, and if she happened to go in one of the seemingly routine attacks, there wouldn’t be as many people to worry about her either. The Azkaban issue only upped those odds. Her prior decision to hide away was lifted and she has started to not really care who she pisses off or gets in the way of. Letting others force her to fear for her safety will not keep her from doing what she wants.

Except, with the end of the school year, she returned back to Pupillus Dorum Orphanage with all of the Ilvermorny students that were locked inside the country because of the mysterious illness going around. At this point, she just wants to get her final two years of school done so that she can get the hell out.
 [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@colin [/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]he/him[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]25[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]EST[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]A long time ago in a galaxy far, far away[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@grey  @cordelia  @mina  @lily  @cara  @nottingham  @jimbo  @steve  @blaise  @harper  @renard  @nell [/blockquote][/div][/div]
