[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://i.imgur.com/iFZvKGf.gif" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]

hello there, my name is [b]nathaniel david forrester[/b] but you can call me [b]nate[/b]. i'm a&nbsp;[b]student&nbsp;[/b]and [b]16&nbsp;[/b]so that makes me a [b]sixth year[/b] at [b]Hogwarts[/b]. You could say I'm [b]cunning, resourceful and ambitious[/b]&nbsp;but I personally think that I am [b]calculated, sarcastic and obstinate[/b]. People say I look a lot like [b]finn cole[/b], but I don't really see it...

[div align="center"][font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][i][b]nathaniel david forrester[/b][/i][/font][/font][/div]

[b][i]pronunciation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]nah-than-yul for-est-er[/blockquote]
[b][i]nickname:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]nate, more often than not. but will correct you if he doesn't like you very much.[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]16[/blockquote]
[b][i]date of birth:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]25th October, 2007[/blockquote]
[b][i]gender &amp; pronouns:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]he/him[/blockquote]
[b][i]blood status:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]half-blood, though presumed muggleborn.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b][i]sexuality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]big sloot (bi)

[/blockquote]
[b][i]schooling:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts, Slytherin

[/blockquote][b][i]occupation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]full time student, part time pickpocket.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b][i]wand:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]13 1/2 inches, holly, phoenix feather, reasonably supple.[/blockquote]
[b][i]playby:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]finn cole.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b][i]appearance:[/i] [/b]
[blockquote]nate looks an awful lot like his playby, though he is slightly taller at 5'11". he has dusty brown hair and green eyes. his fair skin is dotted with freckles and a few moles and he is unlikely to be found smiling, except after a win. he dresses rather typically for a teenager, and is often found with the hood of his robes pulled over his head. he does, however, strive to one day dress incredibly smart. he understands that for success you must display yourself in a particular manner. this will only be seen on nate at formal events for now, as school isn't really the place for it he reckons.&nbsp;

nate does have a few nervous ticks. he will often be found chewing on an assortment of leather bracelets found on his right wrist at all times. he loves to draw in charcoal and it shows with the lingering stains on his fingers. he keeps a box of stolen artefacts procured over time, tucked safely under his bed and practises locking charms on the box for fear of being caught. his sketchbook is incredibly private to him and he will not show anybody unless he trusts them.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personality[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]likes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]
[ul type="disc"]
[li]nightfall[/li]
[li]silence[/li]
[li]drawing with charcoal[/li]
[li]winning[/li]
[li]being right[/li]
[li]stealing[/li]
[li]menthol cigarettes[/li]
[li]a joint&nbsp;[/li][/ul][/blockquote]
[b][i]dislikes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]
[ul type="disc"]
[li]large crowds[/li]
[li]being wrong[/li]
[li]losing an argument[/li]
[li]lack of control[/li]
[li]failing a class[/li]
[li]small talk[/li]
[/ul][/blockquote]
[b][i]erised:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Nate wants to be The Best. He is easily lured by the idea of a position at the Ministry, but his core desire is just to succeed beyond his wildest dreams. Money, comfort, quiet. He needs a thrill as much as he needs silence. It's why he'd never pursue a career with his art, it wouldn't be immediately gratifying.[/blockquote]
[b][i]amortentia:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]menthol cigarettes, maple syrup and clean linen.[/blockquote]
[b][i]boggart:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Nate's biggest fear is failure, though he often worries about losing his one genuine friend, it takes root as the former. He must succeed, failure is not an option.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b][i]overall personality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Nate has always been mistrustful. This is perhaps bred from abandonment and a lack of personal attachments at a very young age. He treats others as enemies until proven otherwise, which doesn’t make him the friendliest of individuals. He is quick to sarcasm, and will use this tone with others no matter if in jest or judgment - he is fond of both. Though, if you are not considered a friend, you may not get much out of Nate at all, unless you are arguing with him. A pastime he has always been fond of. Never one to take the advice of others he’s quick in trouble. Though Nate knows how to blend in to the background. Growing up in an orphanage, he’s learned how to paint himself into the backdrop with relative ease. It makes him an exceptional thief, a skill he flexes whenever he gets the chance. He enjoys the thrill of it. Of one upping somebody without them ever knowing it. Another notable delinquent skill Nate possesses is his ability to pick locks. A necessary talent for any budding criminal. Though, that is not the path that Nate favours, he just does it because he can.

Nate wants to be a great one day. To succeed beyond what the naysayers predicted. To surpass the statistics and outrun every other witch and wizard on the board. He’s intelligent and articulate, though his mouth has a way of getting him in to trouble whenever he uses it. His mind works rather analytically, avoiding emotion whenever he can. His fury is a cold thing that he often keeps under wraps for fear of it being used as his weakness. It ices over his entire being when provoked. He has gotten in to more than one fight because of it. If Nate can’t succeed in a high position within the Ministry, he will most definitely turn his talents toward more criminal outlooks. He’s self-driven, and without his partner in crime Nessa keeping him under wraps he may be entirely insufferable, but she is his balance. Her existence at the orphanage with him has bonded them. His loyalties lie with her and only her.

While Nate’s core interests lie with DADA and Charms at school, he does have a great passion for drawing. Having enjoyed the calming effect of it at a young age, he has taken this with him to Hogwarts. Often found with charcoal smudging his fingertips, it would be incriminating if he had many friends… Nate prefers the company of silence and can often be found walking alone with muggle headphones in, sneaking cigarettes in the cover of shadows. If caught, Nate naturally looks like he’s up to no good. Though he does his best to avoid this at all costs. 

 [/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personal history[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]mother:[/i][/b]
[blockquote][i]biologica[/i]l: lauren devon, unknown, unknown.
[/blockquote]
[b][i]father:[/i][/b]
[blockquote][i]biological:[/i] Ulrich Slughorn, unknown, unknown.[/blockquote]
[b][i]siblings:[/i][/b]
[blockquote][i]NONE known to him.[/i][/blockquote]
[b][i]pets:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]there are no pets permitted in his wing of the orphanage.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b][i]history:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Nate doesn’t know where he began. Nor where he is headed. All he wants is better; more. Though, so the record may show, Nate was the one and only child of muggle - Lauren Devon and Pureblood, Ulrich Slughorn. The consequence of a teenage love affair, of which Ulrich was forbidden from and Lauren was used for. The relationship did not last throughout the pregnancy, in fact upon learning about the fact Ulrich disappeared entirely. The fear of a half-blood child out of wedlock driving him from his muggle lover and leaving Lauren in a situation where an abortion did not appeal to her. Nathaniel was born without a name, or a family. Lauren said goodbye to her son in a hospital somewhere in Wales and though she may have looked back it was never far enough to find her son. 

Immediately placed between foster homes as an infant no family seemed the perfect fit for Nathaniel. He was named by the first family who took him in, veteran fosterers who welcomed Nathaniel in but did not intend to keep him. They didn’t have the resources for an infant anymore and by the time Nate was two years old he’d been skipped from foster family to foster family, none seeming able to keep the young, and rather troublesome child. As even as a budding toddler, Nate found trouble. He was quick to present as a fast learner, the kind of child who grew tired of tasks the moment he mastered them. Constantly searching for something new and challenging. At three, he was placed in his first residential home with dozens of other children in much the same boat as he was. It was at this age that Nathaniel began to display magical properties more prominently. In ways that could no longer go unnoticed as his mood swings had potent repercussions. 

Overseen by a volunteering wizard, Nate was transferred to a more appropriate home where budding wizard’s and witches were welcomed with open arms. It was at this orphanage that Nate would remain until he was of age to leave. He dreamed often of running away, stealing everything worth having and running for the hills. But, of course, he was a rather pragmatic child. Even he knew he wasn’t likely to survive. So, he found refuge in the cold heart of a fellow orphan named Nessa. Similar in circumstance and nature, they soon gravitated towards one and other. Claiming each other as their raft in the endless sea of miserable, snivelling orphans. Nate had always saw himself as better than the rest, but he didn’t necessarily think he was better than Nessa. They were two of a kind, cut from the same cloth. It wasn’t long before the orphanage realised that the two had bonded. Picking on their roommates together, lording themselves above. They were deemed a ‘problem pair’. It was only when they were alone that they spoke of their plans to escape. Nate would get a flat, she could come live with him. It was a childish dream. 

Though very closely bonded with his Nessa, Nate did not assimilate well with the other residents. Not outwardly friendly and immediately suspicious, he did not always make good company. Never one to beat around the bush, Nate often made this fact known with little regard for feelings. He was very opinionated and judgmental. It made him wildly disliked at the home, though Nate didn’t mind. He often found his peers simple minded and theatrical. Except for Nessa. Instead, he read. Often alone, it was during this that he showed promise with drawing. Always pursuing knowledge and perfection. It helped that he was told of the likelihood of his attending Hogwarts. A school ranted and raved about, for bright and promising children. He couldn’t think very many who’d be calibre enough to join him, right enough. It was during his self-imposed exile that Nate found a taste for stealing and perfecting the act of it. 

Though he never called it stealing, that is quite exactly what it was. Adults always had shiny things. The best trinkets and food and bags. Nate quickly deduced that if you were quiet enough… smart enough, you could talk any man or woman out of their belongings. It was thrilling, rewarding and as long as you didn’t get caught, harmless.
 
Though he was in a magical orphanage for magical children, Nate had to attend primary school with muggles. They didn’t have the facilities to home school every child and there wasn’t much prepubescent magic sanctioned to learn. It was there that Nate met some of his worst friends, the kind of boys who spray painted underpasses and spat groggers of phlegm on the heads of passers-by from bridge. Nate found refuge in their unruly wildness, the fact that they were so below him in intellect that he could be the worst of himself. Of course, soon enough he came of age. Soon enough, , he received his letter of admittance. Leaving Nessa behind was perhaps the hardest thing Nate had to do, but his desire to excel as a fully-fledged wizard far outweighed his undeniable attachment to the girl. 

He was sorted in to Slytherin, a house for the cunning of which he certainly was. And ambition rang straight in his veins. Still somewhat reserved, though, Nate buckled down and became extremely competitive. From starting incendiary arguments over trivial academic subjects, to the occasional sabotage, he still had a lot to learn. Though, his prowess for classes like DADA and Charms was undeniable. A talent he did not show as much competitiveness for, but was rather a private delight, was art. Painting and drawing, though he preferred the mess of charcoal. 

Nate coasted through the next few years with a relative amount of grace. Though he was no stranger to detention and the unusual punishments set for his unusual behaviour. If he wasn’t caught nabbing things, he was docked points for being naturally insolent towards others. And more than once he’d been grabbed for fighting, the muggle boys taught him a mean right hook. And a taste for scabbed knuckles. It was as if he was still trying to prove himself. The better, the best.  

It was from his place in Hogwart’s that Nate began to witness the changes in the wizarding world. First the murder of the Minister of Magic - a harrowing and unexpected event. Then the killing of innocent muggle students. It made Nate a target, or so he thought, as a presumed muggleborn. He was concerned for himself, even Nessa. And as the death count rose so did Nate’s anxieties. He stopped drawing attention to himself as much as possible, but sometimes he simply couldn’t help himself. Luckily, he was not targeted and when the true killer came to light Nate was shocked. A girl from his own house. And then the mysterious disappearance of several of his fellow students. Nate was lucky, but even Nate could see that it was only the beginning. 

The attack at King’s Cross was not as surprisingly to Nate as he supposed it might have been. A seemingly natural progression of violence he saw coming for some time. They called themselves Purifiers, and Nate wondered if that made him some kind of disease. His parentage made him a half-blood, but that was all unbeknownst to him. However, a distraction soon developed in the shape of the Tri-wizard Tournament. Nate had never been terribly interested in sports, preferring to draw, but the intense and aggressive nature of the tournament appealed to him in a way that Quidditch did not. His school was soon inundated with new students from the participating schools - which was a stipulation he did not appreciate in the slightest. He already shared his holidays at the orphanage with enough unwanted roommates.

Nate could tell that the entire community proceeded with the Tournament with held breath. As if one wrong step and another attack would occur. Even he could see that it was the perfect opportunity for the ultimate blow. Though the first, second and third task commenced without issue. It seemed that all was well when the departing students were targeted. The bloodshed was vast, so much so that even Nate cringed away from it all. Death count the largest yet, it was the biggest blow given by the Purifiers. A game changer. And suddenly Nate began to wonder if he was still safer on the right side. 

The summer before Nate’s sixth year commenced in the wake of the foreign disaster. Nate’s fear propelled him toward new and creative ends. He reconnected with a few muggle delinquents. Began distancing himself from the orphanage even more, even if this meant alienating himself from Nessa. His biggest mistake occurred when he was caught in the driver-side of a stolen car. Sixteen and arrested on suspicion of grand theft auto. The orphanage helped bail him out, though Nate refused to give away the kids who had put him in that position in the first place. A magical lawyer and it being his first official offense, Nate was let off with a warning. 

This did not, however, stop the necessity of a disciplinary hearing within the Ministry. Was Hogwarts still a good fit for him? As he was caught using magic outside in an attempt to flee from the police, it made them immediately aware of his crimes. The orphanage supported in any way they could, though it was weak, but with the correct character witnesses, Nate was thankfully allowed to attend Hogwarts for his sixth year. Though, under extreme scrutiny. The sensitive approach was perhaps brought on by the fact that the Ministry was in uproar following the disappearance of infamous Auror Harry Potter. Nate thanked his lucky stars. He’d never been more afraid in his life. Hogwart’s was all he had, his ticket to a better, successful future. He attends his sixth year tentatively, though how long this will last is really dependent on his patience for it. Which is almost non-existent on the best of days. 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]alias[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]name:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]chanel[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]21[/blockquote]
[b][i]time zone:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]GMT[/blockquote]
[b][i]reference:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]can't get rid of me...[/blockquote]
[b][i]other characters:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]tia finch, ondina weasley, elijah fleming, aaron milen, jimmie blishwick. no more after this for a while, i think. xD[/blockquote][/div][/div]
