[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;background-color:#B6B6B4;border:4px solid #B6B6B4;border-radius:10px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt="Maxima Greyback / PB Rowan Blanchard" style="max-width:100%;" src="http://49.media.tumblr.com/bf1305ecab589225db270fe55927317a/tumblr_nsfveaoCys1sih7c7o1_540.gif"][/div]

hello there, my name is [b]Maxima Greyback[/b] but you can call me [b]Max[/b]. i'm [b]15[/b] so that makes me a [b]5th[/b] year at Hogwarts, where I reside in [b]Slytherin[/b] house. You could say I'm [b] ambitious, cunning, and resourceful,[/b] but I personally think that I am [b]cautious, reserved, and moody[/b]. People say I look a lot like [b]Rowan Blanchard[/b], but I don't really see it...

[div align="center"][font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][i][b]Maxima Ruqayyah Greyback[/b][/i][/font][/font][/div]

[b][i]nickname:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Max[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]15[/blockquote]
[b][i]date of birth:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]June 22, 2008[/blockquote]
[b][i]gender:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Witch[/blockquote]
[b][i]blood status:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Half-blood (werewolf father)[/blockquote]
[b][i]sexuality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Asexual[/blockquote]
[b][i]house:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Slytherin[/blockquote]
[b][i]occupation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]
[b][i]wand:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]10 ¼ inches, cedar, dragon heartstring, solid[/blockquote]
[b][i]playby:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Rowan Blanchard[/blockquote]
[b][i]appearance:[/i] [/b]
[blockquote]Max is 5’6” tall and has a slender build. She has brown hair and eyes and an olive complexion. Her nose is relatively flat and widens towards its tip, and she has dimples in both cheeks. Both of her ears are pierced once on each lobe.

Not overly fond of frills, Maxima’s style is fairly tomboyish. She doesn’t care much for fashion or the latest trends, and most of what she wears—aside from her school robes—is chosen for comfort. She would rather die than be caught in a dress, and it isn’t uncommon to see her in a baggy sweater with holes worked away from the knit for her thumbs.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personality[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]likes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Music, being left alone, sour foods, oversized clothing, animals, rain, butterbeer, Wizard’s Chess, autumn, drawing in the margins of her schoolwork[/blockquote]
[b][i]dislikes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Small talk, relying on others, neat freaks, rejection, chalk dust, Quidditch, crowded rooms, the heat, public speaking, the idea of being in a physical relationship[/blockquote]
[b][i]erised:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Before she graduates Hogwarts, she would love to learn how to become an Animagus. In the long term, she thinks that she might want to become a Healer.[/blockquote]
[b][i]amortentia:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Pistachio, vanilla bean, and rose bushes[/blockquote]
[b][i]boggart:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Turning into her biological father[/blockquote]
[b][i]overall personality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]At school, Maxima has a tendency to keep people at a distance. Understanding how she is viewed because of her surname, she is distrustful of others’ motives and purposefully isolates herself to avoid rejection by her peers. As long as she has the ball in her court, so to speak, she feels more in control of her interactions with others and the image she projects, which—more often than not—is of a girl who is brooding and angry at the world. On the rare occasion that she does speak out—or lash out, as the case may be—it’s because she’s been angered. The girl has a quick temper, and she isn’t always able to keep it in check.

Additionally, Maxima is incredibly clever and very rational in her thought process. Because she prefers to remain independent, however, she simply does her work without a word. Forget tutoring others, though; she’s impatient and doesn’t want to have to deal with explaining concepts to those who don’t understand.

At home, her behavior is quite different from the way she portrays herself at school. Because she doesn’t have to put up walls—although still quiet—she is much more pleasant to be around. In particular, she has a deep affinity for animals and enjoys spending a great deal of time both with her pets and at her stepfather’s veterinary office.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personal history[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]mother:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Khadija Khoury Donovan, 38, Apparition Test Centre employee, half-blood witch[/blockquote]
[b][i]father:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]
[b]biological:[/b]
Fenrir Greyback, unknown, werewolf

[b]stepfather:[/b]
Michael Douglas “Mike” Donovan, 45, veterinarian, Muggle[/blockquote]
[b][i]siblings:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]
[b]by Khadija:[/b]
Simon Ibrahim Donovan, 7, primary school student, half-blood wizard, twin to Sarah
Sarah Mariam Donovan, 7, primary school student, half-blood witch, twin to Simon

[b]by Fenrir:[/b]
Aaron Carter McClendon, 23, Seeker for Puddlemere United, werewolf
Odette Willow Greyback, 20, Curse Breaker, half-werewolf 
Jamie Marianas Greyback, 16, Hufflepuff, werewolf 
Adrian Christoph Greyback, 16, Gryffindor, werewolf[/blockquote]
[b][i]pets:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Oscar, 6, male blue Cornish Rex, at Hogwarts
Bella, 2, female Yorkshire Terrier, at home
Barney, 10, male Yorkshire Terrier, at home
Polly, 3, female cockatiel, at home 
[/blockquote]
[b][i]history:[/i][/b]
[blockquote] 
Maxima Ruqayyah Greyback was born on June 22, 2008, in Devon, England, to a Lebanese British witch named Khadija Khoury. From an early age, Maxima—or “Max”, as she was more often called—was well aware of her father's identity: Fenrir Greyback, whose surname she shared. She had never met Fenrir, though she had no need to meet the man; by her toddler years, Maxima had a father figure of her own. He was a Muggle veterinarian named Mike Donovan, and he worked not far from Ottery St. Catchpole.

In time and without fanfare, Mike and Khadija married, and Max was given a stepfather. Khadija was honest with Mike about who Maxima’s father was, though the knowledge that Fenrir was a werewolf with a criminal history did not deter him, nor did the knowledge that Khadija herself was a witch. Not even a year to the date of their anniversary, Khadija gave birth to a set of fraternal twins, Simon and Sarah. The twins were a welcome addition to the family, which always seemed to have a few additional members of the furry or feathered variety.

However, it was only once she began school at Hogwarts that she became aware that she had half-siblings by her father, too. Greyback wasn't a common name, and the stigma attached to being the daughter of a werewolf who had associated himself with none other than Lord Voldemort followed Maxima into Slytherin House. She didn't particularly care for the fact that her father was most probably a murderer, especially not when Slytherin House had a reputation of its own as a breeding ground for Dark witches and wizards. And, although she was not a werewolf herself, Maxima chose to allow the other students to maintain their rumors that she was; if they were foolish enough to believe it in spite of the fact that she was in bed in her dormitory every night, she wasn't about to stop them. Honestly, she didn't think that it would have been a bother to her if she had been bitten, and part of her was disappointed that she wasn't afflicted. It was easier, she felt, to play into what other people wanted her to be, because it kept her from having to explain otherwise.

As Maxima grew older and moved from one school year to the next, tensions in the world outside of Hogwarts gradually increased. Being in Slytherin, she knew that many of her classmates' families were likely involved in the goings-on in some fashion or another, which was hardly reassuring. Numbing herself to the constant flow of awful headlines and student deaths, Max tried to go about her life as she always had, though her strategy only managed to work until a group of students were kidnapped from Hogwarts. She knew that she would have to make a decision sooner or later about where she stood, keeping herself from flying under the radar as she had tried to do for the past four years.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]alias[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]name:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Audrey[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]18[/blockquote]
[b][i]time zone:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]US Central[/blockquote]
[b][i]reference:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Current member[/blockquote]
[b][i]other characters:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]@lucian         [/blockquote][/div][/div]