[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://i.pinimg.com/originals/54/13/28/541328fe70469f0e738cd6ebe17587ac.gif" alt="(image here of playby)" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Thomas James Hughes
[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote] 	th AW - m uh s  	j AI m z  	h y OO z[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Tom
[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]16
February 8th, 2010[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Male, He/him
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Half-blood
Demi human: half - Vampire[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Straight[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]10 inches, Blackthorn, Wampus Hair
[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Nick Robinson
[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]
Thomas like all half vampires as a pale complexion with a reasonably athletic body if a little gaunt looking. With brown hair and eyes, Thomas stands five foot ten inches. His hair typically short and mess, not much effort is put toward his appearance besides the bare minimum. 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling & status[/b]
[blockquote]Ilvermorny: Wampus: First to fourth
Hogwarts: Slytherin: Fifth to present.
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Video games.
Technology.
Horror movies and scary stories.
Being away from people.
Music.
Webcomics.
Time to himself.
Dark magic.
Dueling.
Nocturnal animals.
Dark places, nighttime, and staying up late.
The taste of blood.
Exploring and going places at night.
Drawing and painting nature, wildlife and the rare person from time to time.[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Bright lights.
Crowded places.
Annoying people and random people trying to get in his business.
Sliver and garlic.
His parents when they are trying to be annoying.
Waking up early/ getting out of bed in general.
Very hot weather.
Small annoying bugs. 
The word Moist.
Brain freeze.

[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Thomas in general dislikes most people he has to deal with. He has very few friends or people he would consider himself close to. Preferring it this way. Finding more enjoyment in time spent alone. Time to himself to do whatever he wants without being dragged into other people’s drama. Finding most people’s issues just a hassle he’d rather avoid.

It’s not that Thomas is shy or couldn’t handle social situations. He’d speak up when he needs to given the situation. Just that he can’t stand annoying people or situations when he’d just much rather be doing something else. He’s a very closed-off person, letting very few in. Not many have stuck around long enough for Thomas to warm up to them and it hasn’t been something that’s ever bugged him. Just more time for Thomas to sketch the world around him.

Underneath all the sarcastic comments and dry humor used to drive people away is a good heart in Thomas. He just doesn’t show it to many nor does he make an effort to either. He’s fine with the incredibly small circle of friends he’s maintained over the years. Typically people much like himself. People who don't care for the craziness and drama that life and the school offered. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Portland Oregon, USA[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Alan Derek Hughes - father
Mallory Jane Hughes - mother (Vampire)[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]A Striped owl named Archimedes
[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]In a quiet, unassuming section of Portland Oregon. Lay a small magical neighborhood surrounded by the No-Maj world. There Alan Monroe lived. He was a writer for The New York Ghost. Typically writing articles on what the No-Maj people were up to in America. On one such outing at night to investigate a story of No-Maj’s coming upon magic somewhere in America he met Mallory. A striking woman, if a little pale and thin. She had almost attempted to oblivate Alan before he could explain that he was a wizard. He was there for a story but she was sent by M.A.C.U.S.A to erase and cover up any magical incidents. Mallory had attempted to apologize profusely but Alan was lost in her features and alluring voice. She’d claim it was because she was a vampire but Alan knew he was in love.

Just a few years later they were married and she was with child. Thomas was born and the family finally felt complete to the both of them. Thomas grew up just like every other normal child. The only differences being his need for human blood once a month and his aversions to the same things as full vampires. Garlic, sliver, and bright lights especially the sun. As he entered Ilvermorny he was sorted into Wampus. He liked his house and the friends he had made in the first few years. As he got older he started to enjoy being alone and spending time by himself. Finding a passion for art.

It was most notable in his fifth year. Ilvermorny was destroyed to the point that the school had to be closed. The American students that chose to go were sent to Hogwarts and to live in Europe. While his parents decided it was best for him to go to Hogwarts. Most of Thomas’s friends found other arrangements. His fifth year was spent with fewer friends than he had before and it was already a small number.

His parents annoyingly kept asking if he was being bullied and picked on. This wasn’t the case, he just found himself preferring to be alone most times. Especially now that he had lost many of the close friends he had. He didn’t exactly feel like making new ones. Instead diving further into his attempts at art and drawing. He wasn’t sure exactly if he was going to make a career out of it one day. Thomas just enjoyed sketching wildlife and sometimes people. His parents were once again concerned with their son. They felt he should have some direction in life. His father kept talking about becoming a writer while his mother wanted him to seek some career with M.A.C.U.S.A. Neither appealed to Thomas all too much.

The move didn’t help either when he caught Hag fever, it wasn’t as severe as some others. He just turned the room he was in different colors whenever he sneezed. He spent much of the summer in the hospital or alone at home which didn’t help with how closed off he had become. He spent much of that time sketching and reading in peace. This fever turned into a nice excuse to be left alone.

Thomas heard the news of the purifier's leader being killed. His only reaction being good riddance, people like her were why he was in Europe anyway. The same type of people that attacked Ilvermorny. While he didn’t hate being at Hogwarts, he would have still rather finished his school years in the place he had already known for four years. Followed by the accidental explosion at the Quidditch championship. Which he didn’t believe one bit was an accident. From what she heard the purifiers just loved blowing things up.

This was followed up by the sudden appearance of druids and some crazy island off the coast. He just felt like half this stuff wouldn’t have happened back home. Most of it wouldn’t have. It was all nonsense he didn’t exactly want to deal with. Yet the rumors of the creepy island did entice him ever so slightly. It might make for a good place to sketch new creatures or some interesting scenery.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@tj     
[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]he/him 
[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote][img src="https://img.buzzfeed.com/buzzfeed-static/static/2018-01/4/7/asset/buzzfeed-prod-fastlane-01/anigif_sub-buzz-27528-1515069690-8.gif?output-quality=auto&output-format=auto&downsize=360:*" alt="How old are you? (Must be 18-years-old or older)" style="max-width:100%;"][/blockquote]
[/div][/div]