[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;background-color:#B6B6B4;border:4px solid #B6B6B4;border-radius:10px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img]https://78.media.tumblr.com/63adb82bca71b6a101d87887d304c176/tumblr_oqirgbhWyW1w5wm1fo2_540.gif[/img][/div]

hello there, my name is [b]Kaylee Mahi'ai[/b] but you can call me [b]Kay, Lee, Kay Kay, Lee Lee,[/b]. i'm a/an [b]Slytherin[/b] and [b]16[/b] so that makes me a [b]6th year[/b] at [b]Hogwarts, transferred from Ilvermorny[/b]. You could say I'm [b]ambitious, cunning, and resourceful,[/b] but I personally think that I am [b]scholarly, responsible, and traditional[/b]. People say I look a lot like [b]Auli'i Cravalho[/b], but I don't really see it...

[div align="center"][font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][i][b]Kaylee Māhealani Mahi'ai[/b][/i][/font][/font][/div]

[b][i]pronunciation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]/ˈkeɪliː maːhejəˈlɐni ˈmɑ hiˈaɪ/[/blockquote]
[b][i]nickname:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Kay, Lee, Kay Kay, Lee Lee[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]16[/blockquote]
[b][i]date of birth:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]October 18, 2007[/blockquote]
[b][i]gender & pronouns:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Cisgender female; she/her pronouns[/blockquote]
[b][i]blood status:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Half-blood[/blockquote]
[b][i]sexuality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Heterosexual[/blockquote]
[b][i]schooling:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Ilvermorny - Horned Serpent (home institution)
Hogwarts - Slytherin (2024-2025 academic year)[/blockquote]
[b][i]occupation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Although currently a student, Kaylee is interested in becoming a historian so that she can preserve the contributions of her people to the wider magical community.[/blockquote]
[b][i]wand:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]12 ¾ inches, candlewood, shell core, sturdy (original; destroyed)
12 inches, larch, unicorn tail hair core, flexible (current wand)[/blockquote]
[b][i]playby:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Auli'i Cravalho[/blockquote]
[b][i]appearance:[/i] [/b]
[blockquote]Kaylee is 5'3" tall, with an average to slightly curvy build. As a Native Hawaiian, she has slightly tanned skin that darkens with exposure to the sun that comes primarily in the summertime. She has wavy dark brown hair that falls to the middle of her back, brown eyes, and a small, button-like nose. More often than not, she can be seen smiling, which gives her dimples in each cheek. Kaylee has a few small scars on the bottom of her left foot from where she once stepped on a broken glass bottle, and her ears are pierced in both lobes once.

In her daily wardrobe, Kaylee tends to wear brighter colors and patterns when at home in Hawaii. However, she gravitates towards more muted tones when at school in Massachusetts to keep from standing out too much. Now that she's headed for Hogwarts, she plans on wearing much of the same clothing that she's used to wearing at Ilvermorny—comfortably classic jeans and T-shirts, sweaters, and the like. While she would hardly consider herself “preppy”, having gone to boarding school in New England for so long has had an influence on her style.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personality[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]likes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]The ocean, her heritage, playing the ukulele, taking charge, caring for her siblings, sunshine, magical history, shave ice, Quodpot, loco moco[/blockquote]
[b][i]dislikes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Being far from home, snowy winters, hot beverages, large cities, Quidditch, procrastinating, Home Economics, the smell of smoke, anyone who messes with her siblings, dark places[/blockquote]
[b][i]erised:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]In the short term, Kaylee wants to settle into life at Hogwarts without any hiccups.

Ultimately, though, Kaylee would see herself back on her island and preserving the history of her people.[/blockquote]
[b][i]amortentia:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Kona coffee, plumeria, and chocolate chip cookies[/blockquote]
[b][i]boggart:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Kaylee's greatest fear is that she will lose touch with her culture while being in Britain.[/blockquote]
[b][i]overall personality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Overall, Kaylee is a fairly pleasant person. She doesn't intend to butt heads with anyone, provided that her family or close friends—but especially her siblings—aren't facing conflict. Far and away, Kaylee's family and heritage as a Native Hawaiian are what are most important to her, and she would do just about anything in her power to protect them. She takes her family and people's traditions very seriously while also remaining forward-thinking about how those traditions can remain alive well into the future, something that has driven her to want to become a historian.

She is very respectful of her elders, which has extended towards her teachers at Ilvermorny. Although initially hesitant about how she would fit in as a Native Hawaiian student, she quickly realized how much she had in common with other groups of students, including her fellow Asian and Pacific Islanders and the Native American and Alaska Native students there. This motivated her to get more involved at school beyond her studies, and she found that she was most comfortable in leadership roles, including executive roles in many clubs and running for Student Council. As a result, Kaylee can seem to be a “teacher's pet”, overbearing, and even bossy, but she simply sees herself as advocating for herself and her fellow students.

As a form of self-preservation, she tends to stick closest to those of similar backgrounds to her own. That isn't to say that she is rude or unfriendly towards those who aren't—far from it, in fact—but she knows that she can trust those who understand her background and culture more than anyone else.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personal history[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]mother:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Iwalani Abigail Kaʻanāʻanā, 45, herbologist, half-blood witch[/blockquote]
[b][i]father:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Tua Anakoni Mahi'ai, 48, former Auror (disabled), half-blood wizard[/blockquote]
[b][i]siblings:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]_____ Mahi'ai, 15, Wampus/Slytherin student, half-blood wizard
_____ Mahi'ai, 14, Pukwudgie/Ravenclaw student, half-blood witch
Kai Mason Mahi'ai, 9, elementary school student, half-blood wizard
Jaxon Kainoa Mahi'ai, 6, elementary school student, half-blood wizard[/blockquote]
[b][i]pets:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]
[b][i]history:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Born on Kauai, Kaylee Mahi'ai's time as an only child was short-lived. Following her came a brother and a sister, and she cannot remember a time before she was an older sister. Growing up as the eldest of three in a Hawaiian family, Kaylee and her siblings had nothing but love and support from their parents and community. Being magical, of course, that community was even more tightly knit than the average, which gave the Mahi'ai children a solid foundation on which to grow and learn.

Their father, Tua, was a former Auror for MACUSA who had returned to Hawaii after his legs were blown off by a Dark curse. While highly respected by their community, their mother, Iwalani, was the one responsible for making their day-to-day ends meet. Working as a herbologist and being the primary caregiver of her children—soon four, with the birth of another son—would have been a challenge without help from their community. Even Kaylee, in spite of her young age tried to help out wherever she could.

Attending a No-Maj elementary school, Kaylee quickly discovered how much she loved learning. Everything from reading to mathematics came easily to her, though she loved learning about her own culture the most. She sought out stories from anyone who was willing to tell them to her, took hula lessons, and learned to play the ukulele from one of her uncles. Her appreciation for her identity as a Native Hawaiian grew, and so, too, did her identity as a witch.

Kaylee knew that, one day, she would attend Ilvermorny, though she was apprehensive about going so far from home, to a place where she would be so different from her peers. She had never been to outside of Hawaii before and didn't know how anyone would react to her being Native Hawaiian. From what she understood, most of the Indigenous magic that was studied at Ilvermorny was based in Native American beliefs, which—while not entirely dissimilar to many of her own beliefs—was different enough that she expected to be shunned.

When she actually arrived at Ilvermorny, however, Kaylee found out that she had been worrying over nothing. Although it was still hard to leave her family, especially with another younger brother who was still an infant at the time, she settled in. Chosen for both Horned Serpent and Wampus Houses, she opted for Horned Serpent and never once regretted her decision. There, she made some of the closest friends that she had ever had and joined multiple student clubs. 

In her free time at Ilvermorny, she continued to play the ukulele, becoming quite skilled at it. She also began to gain an interest in Native American Magic and, as she grew older, advocated for greater inclusion of Native Hawaiian magic within the curriculum.

Although Ilvermorny wasn't "home", Kaylee was perfectly comfortable there, particularly as her younger siblings started school there, too. She was proud to be able to show them the ropes, and it made the transition back and forth between Hawaii and Massachusetts that much easier on them all.

By the end of her fifth year, Kaylee was excelling at school. Her grades were the best they had ever been, and she was thrilled to start her sixth year. The news of all of the dangerous things that had happened at Hogwarts was far from her mind. Nothing like that—the murders, the kidnappings, the explosions—would [i]ever[/i] happen at Ilvermorny, she thought, until the school was attacked by Chimera's Claw.

Already safely back at home on Kauai, Kaylee scrambled for any word that she could get from back in Massachusetts. Finally, she learned that she and her siblings had the option of going all the way to Hogwarts to continue their education while MACUSA continued its investigation. If Massachusetts was far, Scotland was a world away from Hawaii, but Kaylee knew that they needed to take the offer or risk never living up to their full potentials. As challenging as it would be—emotionally and financially—to send their three teenagers across yet another ocean for the year, Tua and Iwalani agreed that it was for the best, and Kaylee and her brother and sister began to pack their bags and make arrangements for their arrival in London.

Kaylee remains optimistic that Hogwarts won't be terrible and that she can continue her education just as she always has. Still, she has her worries. Without her wand, which was made custom for her, she is concerned about losing the vital connection that she has to her Hawaiian heritage. She has heard rumors that the Houses at Ilvermorny might not carry over to Hogwarts, either, because of their separate House divisions. At the very least, she finds comfort in the fact that her classmates are all in the same boat.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]alias[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]name:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Audrey[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]20[/blockquote]
[b][i]time zone:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]US/Canada Central/Eastern[/blockquote]
[b][i]reference:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Current member![/blockquote]
[b][i]other characters:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]@maxima, @parvati, @oona, @honey[/blockquote][/div][/div]
