[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/sarcasticmoth/proboards-templates/main/pics/evelyn/evelyn_app_header.jpg" alt=" "][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]evelyn rhea oliveira[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]Ev-el-en[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Ev, Evy[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]Seventeen
September 20, 2008

[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Female
She/her

[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]half-blood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]bisexual[/blockquote][b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]11 inches, cedar, werewolf hair, solid[/blockquote][b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]nicole wallace[/blockquote][b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]5’3”, green-gray eyes, light brown/dirty blonde hair

Ev was never afraid of getting dirty or running around outside, she has various small scars from falling out of trees and just tripping while running.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling &amp; status[/b]
[blockquote]hogwarts - slytherin 6th year&nbsp;
class of 2027[/blockquote][b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]her family, her nephew, charms, defense against the dark arts, astronomy, reading fiction, flying, dogs[/blockquote][b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]potions, being told what to think, studying, disloyalty, cats, people in her personal space[/blockquote][b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Being the youngest of five has its advantages and disadvantages. Some say life is easier for the youngest, which is true on some level, but the other side of that coin is a ten-year age gap with the oldest. Evelyn always held her oldest siblings in high regard despite their very different personalities. Her family was always the constant in her life, a source of stability for her. Still, she struggled to relate because she was so much younger, and that grew into a constant hope that she could be close to any of them. One might call her secretly idealistic, not that she’s shy about how she feels, but her constant stoic expression makes it hard to read her. 

Still, she was used to getting her way on most things. Perks of being the youngest, which in turn made her stubborn when things weren’t going in the way she wanted. But, as she gets older, she is learning when to dig her feet in. After her brother died, she noted the fractured state her family was left in around the void that Dakoda left behind. But, she internalized this sadness and grief and really found a way to live with high-functioning depression. The side effects of that were that she smiled less and found herself irritable most days. The unfortunate part is one might not even notice the shift as Evelyn was always available for a sarcastic comment or rude observation. She isn’t a bully, but it didn’t mean that landing the perfect insult didn’t feel good. 

Her love for her family taught her about loyalty, which is why learning what her sister had done really shattered some of those ideas she had thought were solidified. Maybe it was her naivety that let that happen, but she can’t help but hope that some of that idealism can still be good for something. Evelyn likes to think that she has her own little family at school, too—her friends. Because of the age gaps, her time only overlapped with Mina’s for a few years, but who wants to hang around with a first year? These are the people she is loyal to, and while Evelyn typically has that “what’s the point” resting bitch face vibe, that all shifts if you threaten anyone in that circle—family or friend. Her biggest fear is her family completely falling apart. Disharmony makes her uncomfortable and anxious still so to tide over those feelings she can open up but it might not always be to the right person. 

[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]england[/blockquote][b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Stella Oliveira, mother, werewolf
Deran Oliveira, father, Ministry Employee, werewolf

Dakoda Oliveira, older brother, b. 1999, deceased
@sarah  Oliveira, older sister, b. 2000, Ministry Employee
_____ Oliveira, older sister, b. 2001
@mina , older sister, b. 2003 Flourish and Blotts Employee

Sebastian Lestrange, nephew, b. 2021

[/blockquote][b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]snowy owl, hera[/blockquote][b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Evelyn looks at the events of the past few years. This mysterious island that appeared and had been discussed in the paper, the constant articles on Minister Krum and wonders what is going on in the world. It reminded her of some events spoken about in her History of Magic class, or at least that she’d bothered to pay attention to when all her energy wasn’t diverted into staying awake.  As if being a teenager wasn’t hard enough already. But, her family wasn’t entirely ever free from such events or drama. In fact, her parents nearly fought in the Battle of Hogwarts but only didn’t because her mother was pregnant with her brother Dakoda.

It all begins with Fenrir Greyback, though many have probably said that to start their story. Stella and Deran were part of Fenrir Greyback’s pack. They were werewolves, and while their loyalty was to the pack and Fenrir, it was also to one another. Not too long before the Battle of Hogwarts, Stella found out she was expecting, and this was a lightbulb moment for the both of them. Is this the life they wanted for their family? No. So, they left Fenrir and the others but of their own accord. The following year, Dakoda was born. Their life was far from typical, but it was now also quiet. The following year Sarah was born, followed by another sibling the year after. And things were quiet but not for long. Fenrir never forgot their abandonment of him, and as a result, Dakoda and Sarah were both turned one full moon.

They moved not long after that, fearing that Fenrir would turn their other daughter or worse. But again, things were quiet, and a few years later, Mina was born. Their quiet life was also simple, they had enough to get by and be comfortable, but there was a lot of sharing of rooms and toys and all that. Which didn’t always sit well with the now vast array of personalities under the same roof. And that’s how it continued for a few years. The threat of Fenrir Greyback was still looming. Her parents still heard rumors about all his activities and always kept an eye out for possible danger. And then, when their oldest was nine, they found out they were expecting again. Evelyn was born the youngest of the clan.

It had been years since they’d had a baby in the house, which was a challenge with four other children but manageable. It was also helped by Dakoda going off to Hogwarts and then Sarah, so outside of the summertime, they didn’t have to share the space as much. Evelyn got used to running around after whichever sibling was nearby. For a while, that was Mina until she also went off to school. By the time Evelyn’s letter arrived, she also ended up in Slytherin as Sarah and Mina had, Dakoda had graduated, and Sarah had been expelled. To be honest, Ev wasn’t totally surprised at Sarah’s expulsion, and yet it didn’t make her think any less of her big sister. It was remarkable how different each child behaved in and out of Hogwarts.

Despite everything, including the age gap, her older siblings were always kind to her—even Sarah. And that’s what always stuck with her from a young age. But her entire family was very important to her. It was the main constant in her life, and being able to depend on that was calming. She began Hogwarts during her sister’s final year, and she supposed it was as calm as first year could be, minus the natural anxiety of such a new experience. Unfortunately, she saw Sarah less, though she would pop in and out to visit the family. At least there were the other siblings. But before the beginning of her second year, she learned something cool, Sarah had a son—Evelyn had a nephew. While Ev didn’t know who the father was, she didn’t care either—it was a new family member, someone else to protect and keep close.

At the beginning of her third year, things began to change. Students had been found dead on the train and at school, and it was one of those things where the gravity of it all didn’t hit Evelyn until the latter half of her third year. This stuff wasn’t supposed to happen at Hogwarts, was it? During that time, her brother helped keep her spirits up. The following year was better. Everyone was focused on the Tri-wizard tournament where the Hogwarts champion won. And it seemed everything was going to be okay, at least until all those students were killed. It wasn’t just that, however. It was that year she found out her brother had died. Dakoda was dead. Evelyn remembered going home and just staring at his stuff. His old broomstick was in the corner. It had a thin layer of dust on it.

To top it off, she found out it was Sarah. Her sister had killed her brother. It wasn’t something that Evelyn could easily reconcile in her mind. In the same room was Sarah’s stuff next to Dakoda’s. But Sarah had grown cold over the years, so it was easier not to think about it so much and stuff down the grief of losing a brother. Though she often felt she’d also lost a sister. During her fifth year, Hogwarts received an influx of students from Ilvermorny, an adjustment for everyone. But even the family dynamic changed. Sarah seemed genuinely sorry for her actions, and while Ev was wary, she felt she had her sister back. Maybe this was a new normal? Or it had the potential, especially since the carnage didn’t seem to be done yet with the explosion at the Quidditch final that summer.

Now in her sixth year, Evelyn knows she still has time to figure out what she’s doing with her life and really figure out herself. And she’s found herself turning more and more to her older siblings, even if they all tell her something different. 


[/blockquote][div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]vanessa[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]jedi master[/blockquote][/div][/div]
