[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/sarcasticmoth/proboards-templates/main/pics/addy/addy_app_header.gif"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]addilyn elara slater[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]Ah-dee-lin Eh-lar-ah Slayder[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Addy, only her parents use her first full name[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]seventeen
august 24, 2008[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]female, she/her[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]half-blood[/blockquote][b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]bisexual&nbsp;[/blockquote][b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]Ebony, phoenix feather, 9 ¾, flexible[/blockquote][b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Madison Iseman[/blockquote][b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Addy is about five foot 3 inches tall, and appears very much like her playby. Her hair is blonde and usually styled long with blue eyes. She has an almost perfect posture, Merlin forbid she ever slouched in front of her parents. It didn’t show a strength of character. When not in her school robes she dresses very casually, but still appropriately. One can appear put together no matter the occasion. But regardless, she is typically smiling or quick to smile. [/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts - Slytherin[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]seventh year[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Technology (muggle &amp; magical)
Learning how things work
Reading
Quidditch
Being right
Winning
Butterbeer

[/blockquote][b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Divination
Losing
Haters
The ‘T’ in Horizont
Not being able to figure something out

[/blockquote][b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Be successful in a magical tech-related field and her parents being genuinely happy for her.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]hickory smoke, smell of an old book, white sage[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Not living to her family’s standards or receiving that validation. Not only her parents were disappointed but also her brother and sister.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]There are advantages to being the youngest of one’s siblings. While her parents’ pressure was there from the start, it was almost as if Claire and Grey acted as buffers for Addy. As long as she kept up with Claire and did better than Grey, they were happy with her. That isn’t to say she didn’t earn their acceptance and love in her own way. Addy did what she was told and did what was expected of her. She was never shy and found careful moments to speak her mind, her confidence never wavering. From a young age, it was clear that this Slater was not going to be the shy one. As soon as she could begin to speak words and then (to her parent’s delight) very quickly sentences, she never had an issue with conversation or asking many questions. Her curiosity did tend to get the best of her at times. She wanted to know how things worked and how they were put together, though her parents quickly became annoyed by the hundred questions Addy would ask. 

Still, she had goals. She wanted to succeed, and she took great pride when she would win and when she was right. However, rather than being argumentative, she preferred a strategy of patience and finding the right opening to speak or ask a question. Since her parents’ goals for their family were very transparent—they wanted their children to be the best, it wasn’t hard for Addy to find a calculated way to maneuver around their demands. Her strategy? Make them think something was their idea. They wouldn’t disapprove of that, would they? And part of those goals to strive for was her grades. With her agreeable personality, she found it easy to connect with her Professors though often her classmates would ask her for help on their assignments since she strived to meet her parents’ expectations and match the reputation that her sister had left as well. Her relationship with her family is important to her. She loves them dearly despite the obvious personality differences. She admires her sister and all her hard work though really it is how she receives that praise and validation from their parents that they all seek. 

Addy is a calculated person. When she is not reading, studying, taking apart her magical cell phone again, she is usually playing chess. The game of patience and forethought appeals to her, and she appreciates the nature of the game and how it is played. It is her approach to most things. Even in the fast-paced world of Quidditch, there is a need to think more than one step ahead. The last thing she wants is to act on impulsive behavior and end up in a situation that would only bring disapproval from her family. Also, patience tends to reap greater rewards, and Addy is the type that likes to win. All that being said, there is always the other side of the coin, and her competitive nature and uncompromising attitude toward being the best can tend to disagree with certain people. She has many friends, but in a way, they are in her life because they can help her move forward in one way or another. The majority of people will find her friendly and happy to help with a Transfiguration assignment, while others might find her sarcastic and, dare I say it, mean. While both her siblings were sorted into Gryffindor, Addy is a Slytherin, and she embodies the signature traits of ambition, cunning, and resourcefulness. 

Now in her final year of school, she feels she is still trying to make up for the disappointment of not being made a prefect and especially considering who was made a prefect instead. While she may not subscribe to her parents’ aged doctrines toward demi-humans or people from certain families, she’s only disappointed that the Hogwarts staff did not deem her ‘good’ enough for such a responsibility. 

[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]london, england[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]shela slater - mother, 48, works at gringotts, muggleborn.
tim slater – 50, works in the department of international magical cooperation in the international magical office of law (he’s a magical lawyer), half-blood.

claire slater – sister, 24, auror, former Gryffindor, half-blood.
grey slater - brother, 20, daily prophet quidditch reporter
[/blockquote][b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Snowy owl - Astraea[/blockquote][b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Addy was born near the end of Summer as the third and youngest child in the Slater family. Her older sister Claire was seven, and Grey was three when she was born, and like with any new addition to the family, it changed the dynamic. Addy could recall seeing her siblings disagree and argue at times, and when she got older, it wasn’t uncommon for her to do so as well. Though she quickly learned to follow by example. Her sister received praise and attention from her parents for doing ‘all the right things’ while her brother less so. It was an easy path to pick and follow in that regard, and that was what she did. Addy followed instructions, smiled when she was supposed to, didn’t argue with her mother and father, and it made her life that much easier. Still, it didn’t stop her parents from using them to motivate one another. [i]” Even your sister could play Quidditch better than that.” [/i] And tension existed where there might not have been any in the first place. 

However, unlike her siblings, Addy had a natural curiosity for how things worked. Seeing her parents wave a wand and something would move or action would occur, she would always want to know why. It was a difficult impulse to control when she was younger, asking a question every five seconds and speaking at the speed of sound until her father would close the book he was reading in frustrating with a loud [i]thump[/i]. And remind Addy that nobody liked someone who asked so many questions. They would wonder if she knew anything at all and if she was even capable. When Addy got older, she learned when to ask questions and time them to elicit such an adverse reaction. That was the goal, right? Do everything right, achieve some form of success, and her parents would be happy and smile.  But her curiosity still wouldn’t leave her alone. At least one incident of Addy actually took apart a book (fortunately not a valuable one) just to see how the pages were fit into the binding. How did this back part of the book hold all these pages in place? Unfortunately, it wasn’t something that she could quickly put back together as she could other items. 

When her siblings went off to school, she was the focus at home, and that became a shift in how she learned how to make sure she did everything right. She read books, tried to emulate her sister’s behavior, and asked her all the questions about what Hogwarts was like and what was taught there. But she still tried to remain as impressive as she could, whether it was learning something challenging in a book from her father’s library or practicing flying a broom in the afternoon. Her parents were quick to remind her that her sister consistently received top marks in her studies and her classes and that her time was coming soon just a few more years. There were big shoes to fill when she went to Hogwarts. It was a bit nerve-wracking when she was seven, eight, nine years old but hearing the same warning over and over again made it lose some of its meaning. Addy knew what she was capable of and that she was intelligent, and if she really wanted to do something, then she would. It became easier to communicate in her own way to her parents. They liked to be right, and Addy gave them that satisfaction, often finding a way to spin an idea until they made it their own. 

Finally, Addy received her coveted letter to Hogwarts. There had been a [i]tiny[/i] amount of fear that she wouldn’t get a letter. What if she was a squib and couldn’t do magic? What would her parents do with her then? Of course, it was a silly fear. She’d been showing signs of witchcraft since she was young, just as both her brother and sister had. But, the fear had always sat there in the recesses of the back of her mind and until she had that parchment in her hand. She brought the letter to her parents but held it carefully with both hands as if it were gold. Naturally, they were incredibly pleased and only repeated how they expected her to achieve top marks and become a Prefect and possibly Head Girl. She should strive for Gryffindor or Ravenclaw house as the traits from those houses were notable and considered ‘great’. So, Addy joined her sister and brother on the Hogwarts Express and though a bit nervous, was terribly excited as well. While she tried to talk to other first years as she found it easy to make friends, Claire wanted to give her all the ‘tips and tricks’ to success though perhaps she was happy to finally have a sibling who would listen to what she said on the topic. 

Finally, arriving at the school, Addy’s name was called. She glanced over at the long table in the Great Hall lined with the crimson and gold banners where her siblings were looking hopefully, and the Sorting Hat was placed upon her head. It paused for a moment, noting that Gryffindor [i]might[/i] work, but it noted her intellect. Still, another pause. The traits that made her driven to succeed was tiptoeing a fine line between the confident Gryffindor house and the cunning Slytherin. Much to the family’s surprise, the Sorting Hat shouted proudly, [i]’ Slytherin’ [/i]. Addy wasn’t sure what to think about the news, and she gave one last glance to her equally shocked sister as she walked toward the table with emerald-colored banners instead. A letter arrived quickly from home. Her parents weren’t very pleased with the sorting result and only continued to remind her of her goals while in school. She was to receive the best grades and make her family proud. Now that she was in this house with its low reputation in the past, she needed to be cautious about whom she chose to associate with. What Addy read from the letter that despite her house placement, rebellion was not an option, nor should the thought even pass through her mind. 

So Addy did what she did best. She pushed through. And though she was determined to prove a point and meet the expectations set before her, she would, on occasion, very stubbornly reach out to her older sister, who was in her final year of school, for help or advice. It was hard to ask for help, they’d been so focused as younger children to act independently as some sort of competition, but Addy thrived on it. She liked to win, and she wanted to be right, and in the one shared interest with her older brother, she joined the Slytherin Quidditch team in her second year. Unfortunately, and much to her and her parent’s dismay, she never made it to Quidditch Captain. Somebody else beat her to that, though she suspected the student’s part-veela background might have helped. While she waited to be eligible for the Quidditch team, she did join the Chess team as a first-year and quickly made friends with the other members from all different houses and years. As a child, she hadn’t plaid as much. Her father never cared for the mess of the broken pieces or wanted the expense of buying new sets when they had broken down too much. She enjoyed the game. The need to be calm and composed or your facial expression would give away your next move and then waiting for an appropriate time to strike. Perhaps let your opponent think they were winning for a few moments until you decided to let them in on the reality. 

Her sister graduated and entered the Auror training program. While she was happy for her sister, she felt the increased pressure from home. Her brother was still a few years older than her. However, his name began to come up more when her parents would persistently remind her of the expectations. He was the editor for the student paper, and that was a positive for them. Achievements in the form of Quidditch Captain, Newspaper Editor, Prefect—those were the words in letters that their parents wanted to read. Otherwise, school was relatively normal for Addy. However, she excelled in her subjects, such as Transfiguration and Charms. She barely achieved top marks in subjects such as Divination (which she absolutely abhorred). She was very interested in Potions as the idea that a seemingly random set of ingredients could be combined to form a potion with specific properties fascinated her. She continued her Chess club activities and Quidditch as well. However, she was shocked when her fourth-year students had been found killed at the start of her fourth year, and there was a growing sense of fear and anxiety. Her father remembered the scarier times of the past but didn’t stop their pressure. 

Before the start of her Fifth year, she was an uncharacteristic bundle of nerves as she awaited the letter’s arrival information that she was to be a prefect and the shiny green Slytherin badge to accompany it, but it never arrived. It was a similar feeling and knot in her stomach as she had been awaiting her Hogwarts acceptance letter, though this time she had failed. Her parents made their opinion on the matter known. The expression her parent’s eyes never wavered even when saying goodbye to her and Grey on the platform as they left for the school year. Being away from home helped deal with that lingering feeling of failure until she received another letter from home. Her parents had some….aged ideas about the Wizarding World though not as extreme as she heard of other families, but the knowledge that the prefect from her year was a rumored werewolf and child of Fenrir Greyback did not elicit a good response from her parents. Despite reading the words of disappointment in the letter, Addy was only grateful they hadn’t sent a howler instead. It was hard to fail, these were the things she was [i]supposed[/i] to achieve, and she hadn’t. 

Still, it was an exciting year! The Triwizard Tournament was being hosted by Hogwarts. Naturally, her brother submitted his name into the Goblet as he was of age—and their parents would have been over the moon had their one and only son been selected as the Hogwarts Champion. But alas, he was not—but even Addy knew the probabilities of that decision and doubted her brother really wanted that. Watching the tournament was exciting for her, and she enjoyed the atmosphere and excitement of it all. And in the end, she was glad for the experience, and it gave Addy some relief from the massive disappointment she had felt at the beginning of the year. After the tournament ended and her brother graduated, she realized she would be alone at school now. Receiving that pressure alone again though it never relented on her siblings either. Though students’ massive death and injury as they returned home to their schools left her shaken and a bit scared despite how much she tried to hide it. The school was supposed to be a safe place, yet it didn’t always feel like that. 

The beginning of her seventh year brought new changes as well. They would be receiving an influx of students from the American school and the pressure from her parents to not only impress and be better than her English classmates but now her new American ones, but at least Quidditch had returned. She had been made captain of the Chess Club though her parents barely commented on it. By this point, she had received several OWLs, which helped make up for her lack of a Prefect appointment with her parents. She was almost set to follow in her sister’s footsteps if she chose to do so. “Choosing” meaning if her parents insisted, of course. And she focused on those courses and that academic track because even if she didn’t go into Auror training, she would have the NEWTs to choose what career she wanted. However, she had many interests in mind, the Ministry being one of them. However, her concern about the world was only increasing. During the holidays of her sixth year, the Azkaban breakout happened, and she wondered what that meant. It had always been this long-standing institution, and now it was gone? 

The rest of the sixth year finished up without incident. Addy was excited that summer before her final year at school. She even opted to attend the Quidditch Final as a fan herself. It was going well until it wasn’t. Ministry Granger was killed, and she managed to get out unscathed though many did not. It left her a bit rattled, if she was honest. The rest of the summer, she threw herself into a new hobby. Technology. She couldn’t travel due to the Hag’s Fever quarantine. Still, magical technology had begun to spread in the UK, she’d heard about it from her classmates from America, but the Ministry hadn’t quite accepted it until now. It was fascinating how it all worked, and her parents did relent and get her a cell phone. She managed to take it all apart and put it back together again by the end of the summer. Naturally, she wanted more, but she’d be patient. However, it did present her with new opportunities, she felt after she graduated. Now she is in her seventh and final year, she knows she has to work extra hard this year to earn the NEWTs that are expected of her but that she also wants to achieve because she knows that she can. 

[/blockquote][b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]The events at school and around the Wizarding world have left her a bit shaken. Addy wonders what can be done and how this affects her after she will graduate. Her focus right now is on the growing usage of magical technology. When the students were killed and attacked, it scared her because Hogwarts was supposed to be safe. Still, she hid that fear away as she didn’t want to appear as though she was falling apart in any way. The students who died after the Triwizard Tournament made her feel vulnerable, especially since she didn’t have any siblings left at school. And the Quidditch Final was perhaps the scariest for her since she’d been in attendance and had been looking forward to attending since Hag’s Fever swept through the Isles. At least back at school, it does feel safe again. Still, she wonders what will happen next. She increasingly looks toward her brother and sister for some information or reassurance.
[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]vanessa[/blockquote][b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her&nbsp;[/blockquote][b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]i'm on the jedi council&nbsp;[/blockquote][b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]GMT-8[/blockquote][b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]I met a random stranger on craigslist[/blockquote][b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@vanessa , @anastasia , @layla , @leonardo , @cade [/blockquote][/div][/div]