[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img]https://imagesvc.meredithcorp.io/v3/mm/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fstatic.onecms.io%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2Fsites%2F6%2F2018%2F01%2Fkiernan-shipka2-2000.jpg&q=85[/img][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]luna lachesis trelawney[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]loo - na[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Lu to her family, otherwise just Luna[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]17 - 31 October[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]halfblood, seer[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]heterosexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]silver lime and dragon heartstring, 9 1/3 inches, brittle[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]kiernan shipka[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Luna looks identical to her other two triplet sisters, and her playby. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling & status[/b]
[blockquote]6th year Slytherin[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Student[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]competition
quidditch (particularly the Chudley Cannons)
winning
attention
her sisters
thesauruses
writing short stories
being called a witch or part of the heca-three[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]when she goes into a vision
losing
snails and slugs
simple minds
being called loony
her brothers - they are not gifted, nor really worth her time
[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]In a surprising turn of events, Luna can often be described as the most level headed of the three Trelawney triplets. While she is ferociously competitive, she is commonly grounded and the one to reel her sisters back to reality. She has the attitude of a leader, and is usually the one making decisions. Luna's gift means that she can see events happening anywhere in the world from a different point of view, but has no control over what events she sees or when they overtake her in a vision. For that reason, Luna secretly feels like the least useful of the triplets, but has never spoken aloud about her misgivings.

While not unkind, Luna is never overtly friendly. She is fiercely loyal to her sisters and her teammates, but tends to manipulate people to get her way. She will occasionally use her sister's gifts as a manipulation method - claiming that Selene saw something dire in their future, or that Phoebe knows something about their past. Luna is the main reason the triplets were placed into Slytherin - her ambition to be feared and popular, while leaning into the whole 'I'm a witch' thing make her a classic snake. Luna is polarising, either loved or despised, with no real proclivity for either. She is a focused individual, placing her own wants and needs above all others (even her sisters).

Luna knows that her sisters would move mountains for her, and while she would return the favour, Luna is an innately selfish and somewhat jealous person. She doesn't like when her sisters pay attention to other people, especially boys, but has no issue when her attention is grabbed by something else. Luna tends to collect people she thinks will be useful to her. She considers herself to be the best Quidditch player of the family, bound for super-stardom. However, Selene hasn't said anything about her bright and brilliant future... [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Ottery St. Catchpole[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Cassandra Trelawney- a famous Seer -great great great grandmother - deceased
___ Trelawney - great great grandparent
___ Trelawney - great grandparent

Mr Trelawney - grand-father
Mrs Trelawney - muggle - grand-mother

Sybill Trelawney - 63 - aunt - former divinations professor
Mr Higglebottom - ex-uncle - ex husband of Sybill Trelawney

Siilas Trelawney - 40 - father
Asteria Trelawney - 37 - mother

Older brother - 19
@selene -Older triplet sister
@phoebe - Younger triplet sister
Younger brother - 13[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]a barn owl called Megara[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Selene, Luna and Phoebe were born on a stormy Halloween night seventeen years ago. They were the second children of Siilas and Asteria Trelawney, descendants of the famed seer Cassandra Trelawney. From the moment they were born, the triplets had an affinity for one another, and even started showing signs of magic from that very first day - Selene knew to stop crying before her mother pleaded, Phoebe clung to her father and screamed if he let her go, and yet Luna couldn't do much of anything. She was just there to complete the set of triplets. The triplets grew up long after the shadow of war had left Britain, and stuck to one another like glue.

The triplets showed signs of their gifts from an early age, though Luna seemed to be the least special of them all. She grew jealous quickly of her more talented sisters, and though she loved them dearly, she fought them for her parents attention and affection. She discovered quickly that she didn't care what their elder brother thought of her - or subsequently their younger brother when he was born. They had shown no proclivity for the gift of sight, and therefore were not worth Luna's attention. Siilas was delighted that two of his girls were gifted seers, and Luna was determined to also prove herself gifted and useful. She picked up Quidditch and found she was a natural at the sport, and the family existed in their little bubble of life for years before things started to get a bit... difficult.

As the girls moved through primary school, their fellow students considered them weird. Asteria had insisted they attend, despite the fact that they were of magical blood. They were to be well rounded, like their older brother and their parents before them. The girls made few friends, though Phoebe was the one who was most affected by this. Selene couldn't give a rats ass about anyone else, and Luna thought her classmates were useless. Phoebe had always been the most sensitive and in tune with her emotions, her joy radiating outwards and painting everyone it fell on in a beautiful light. The girls were taunted for the way they acted, how sometimes they froze in the middle of speaking, overtaken by a vision. Whispers mounted, and they were soon dubbed the Heca-three, nicknamed after a story was told in their year two class about the Greek goddess of magic, Hecate. Luna leaned into the name, knowing the truth, holding her station above all else and offering to turn her classmates into frogs if they upset Phoebe, over whom she and Selene were most protective.

The triplets showed true, outwards signs of magic younger than normal, separating them even further from the norm. They were shipped off to Hogwarts instead of secondary school, and the three were sorted into Slytherin. Selene had foreseen this happening, and Luna was the first to be sorted. She knew the instant the hat touched her head, it would shout out her house, and Phoebe and Selene would request to be placed in Slytherin as well so they would not be separated. Though perhaps it was an odd fit, Luna felt like she flourished in Slytherin, especially with her sisters by her side. At last, she was the one who showed the strongest traits. She was the most powerful Slytherin of them all.

In their third year, things started to go awry again. There started to be murders at Hogwarts, to which Luna pointed out to Selene she did not foresee. Selene reminded her that the inner eye did not see on command, but Luna just rolled her eyes. Her own visions were infrequent, usually only happening as dreams that she then questioned the reality of. Eventually, it was discovered that Elaine Dupree was behind the trouble, and was expelled from Hogwarts. Phoebe had a flash of the older girl's murky past, but could make nothing of it. As they returned home that year, they were very nearly injured in the Kings Cross explosion, but thankfully made it out of the incident unharmed. Luna felt unsettled by it, especially since she had seen the explosion from the point of view of... someone involved. But she didn't know who. It had been her first waking vision in years.

In their fourth year, the Triwizard Tournament took place and Luna and her sisters and brother dutifully cheered on the Hogwarts champion. Three spots on the Quidditch team opened up, and Selene and Luna immediately tried out, forcing Phoebe along with them. The girls were successful, with Selene and Phoebe playing as chasers and Luna as a beater. She was glad to be different from her sisters, though she said nothing of the sort to them. Towards the end of the year, the girls were shocked by the explosion of the carriage. Again, none of the girls could see the explosions coming, despite their many gifts. Luna struggled to maintain a collected manner, especially when she knew that Selene and Phoebe should be more useful. 

The following year, Selene mentioned something about breaking out of jail, though no one paid her any heed. Months later, the mass Azkaban breakout occurred, but no one attributed Selene's foresight to this event. After all, she was just a fifteen year old girl at the time, making 'prophecies.' As Hag's Fever swept through the nation, Phoebe was able to connect various instances in patients pasts to their likelihood of getting the fever but again - no one really listened to her. After all, seers were so rare and unheard of. Even as the fever died down, Luna could see the adverse effects it was having on the nation, particularly in that people were terrified, and not in the way she liked. The girls started their sixth year in the midst of the epidemic, sticking closer to one another than ever. With the introduction of some far off island, Luna ensured that none of her sisters would venture that way - not even to find out the past or the future of the place. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]ana[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]it (she/her)[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]jedi knight[/blockquote]
[/div][/div]
