[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://i.pinimg.com/originals/e7/cd/f6/e7cdf6dfe3fb20e9358a6ad265510d94.gif" alt="(image here of playby)" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Selene Atropos Trelawney
[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]Seh-lean[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Sel, Lena, Atri, Heca-three, Weirdo, Trippy
[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]17
31st of October, 2009
[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Female, she/her
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Half Blood, clairvoyant
[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Panromantic, Demisexual
[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]Length, wood, core, etc if you own one.[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Kiernan Shipka
[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Selene usually dresses conservative in terms of how revealing her clothes are. Despite this her clothes are most easily described as odd and quirky and often not the most common for somebody her age. She's known to wear both knitted sweaters and dress pants, leading to a odd but quirky and strangely stylish combination of clothes. She's commonly covered in the hairs of her various cats, all of which are black. Selene has a pair of thick perscription glasses that she wears from time to time, although she likes to switch it up with lenzes to compliment her ridiculous outfits. She likes to keep her hair on the shorter side most of the time for practical reasons. 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling &amp; status[/b]
[blockquote]6th year Slytherin
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Cats, knitting, yoga, jigsaw puzzles, crosswords, baking, reading, sculpting, music (most of all her harp), her sisters, being called a weirdo, standing out, quidditch.
[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Things changing so fast she can't keep up, people being rude or mean to her sisters, people that are insisting she's playing some sort of part (while she's just genuine), disloyalty, dumb people, hospital wing visits, headaches.
[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Selene is most easily described as an old and cranky soul in the body of a young girl. From the day she was born she already was noticably different from her triplets in terms that she wasn't that keen to display the usual signs of emotions. She was reserved in her emotions, especially as a child. Older people in her community often found her to be a bit disturbing and peculiar, since she didn't often play well with any children but her own sisters. She's still not overly fond of people her own age and is more commonly seen befriending those multiple years older. 

That being said, Selene is a very active and spry girl, considering her granny like tendencies. She's collected a fair number of cats, sitting comfortably at three black ones currently and when she's not complaining or otherwise acting misplaced she can be found actively enganging in quidditch above all other sports. She's highly fanatic and even before she started playing she could be seen on the stands cheering her favourite teams on. 

One thing that should be said in favour of Selene is that she has a very strong connection to her siblings. She loves her two sisters dearly and is protective of them. Her eyes tend to be turned towards the future as her natural gifts as a clairvoyant in the little pack of three have her most inclined of all to actually have visions of the future, a gift she is keen to further develop. 

Selene doesn't care much about being popular, only ever about being seen as what she truly is, a unique part of a trio. She depends on her siblings a lot but will easily stand her ground. She's a bit of a stickler for oldfashioned romance and grand gestures but has few interests in the physical parts of a relationship. The way she sees it, a relationship is about far more and the connection between two people is what gets them through the many years in life. That being said she isn't opposed to physical intimacy at all, although she does tend to roll her eyes at public displays of affection.

Due to her gift of foresight Selene has a lot of difficulty with both concentration on the here and now, often being swept away by events that have yet to happen and by remembering things that already happened unless she saw them in advance to them actually happening. While she has relatively more control over her powers compared to her sisters she finds it a lot more difficult to keep her grades up and keep her attention in the here and now, where it should be. 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Ottery St. Catchpole, UK.
[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Cassandra Trelawney-a famous Seer -great great great grandmother - deceased 
---- Trelawney - great great grandparent
---- Trelawney - great grandparent

Mr Trelawney - grand-father
Mrs Trelawney - muggle - grand-mother

Sybill Trelawney - 63 - aunt - former divination professor
Mr Higglebottom - ex-uncle - ex husband of Sybill Trelawney

Siilas Trelawney - 40 - father
Asteria Trelawney - 29-35 - mother

Older brother - 19-25

@luna   triplet
@phoebe     triplet

Younger brother - 12-15

[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Onyx, black cat
Obsidian, black cat
Opal, black cat
[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Ever since birth, Selene and her sisters had been different. Her mother had been worried for while two of her children cried, much as babies should after being born, Selene was a quiet child, coaxed into laughter more easily than tears. She stood out and was easily seen as strange, even by the caretakers that delivered the three sisters. They were weird, strange and clearly different from most, this knowledge never bothered Selene. There were clearly more important thingsi n life than fitting into a mould.

As they grew up all triplets showed clear signs of Clairvoyance. Phoebe easily caught glimpses of the past and was prone to sleepwalking. Selene herself had her inner eye opened and exposed to the future and no place in the present was safe from Luna. They would be bullied for their peculiarities, Selene was quick to realise but she encouraged her sisters not to care too much. There were other and more important things. 

Selene probably got on best with her older brother out of the three siblings. Despite the age difference, Selene learned quickly and seemed to have an innate sense of maturity well beyond her years. The hobbies she picked up were often similar to that of the elderly and even before starting Hogwarts Selene was most likely of the triplets to sit around with their grandparents all day and discuss topics of interest to them, picking up skills such as knitting, jigsaw puzzles, baking (primarily cookies) and an appreciation of classical music. She learned to play the harp and still does so fondly. 

When the triplets received their nickname in primary school (the Heca-three) Selene felt a moment of pride at the title. They were strange and while Luna used this to threaten and bully their classmates, Selene choose a far more helpful approach. She at times glanced the future and warned her fellow students that their current path would lead them to illness or embarressment. She wasn't usually believed and her peers were keen to believe she cursed them. Luckily for the triplets, the muggle children had parents sensible enough to overlook the peculiarities of the girls as mere signs of them being... well, freaks. They knew magic wasn't real, so they had nothing to worry about.

It was shortly before Hogwarts that Selene started to understand the twisting pathways towards the future better. Choice seemed to be an important factor in many of the things she had seen that either did or did not come true, based on if she told them to people. Things happened as she'd seen them without her interference most of the time. If she spoke up, things sometimes changed. This awareness came barely on time, as it had almost separated the triplets that Selene didn't know.

Upon sorting, Luna was first and unsurprisingly ended up in Slytherin. With the utmost concentration, Selene had watched the events unfold and decided to tell her youngest sister that everything was going to be fine and they'd all be in the same house. By telling her, Phoebe believed it completely. Selene never lied about the future. As she predicted to her younger sister, she ended up with Luna in Slytherin. Her own turn came and she knew that she'd be sorted into Ravenclaw if she did not interfere. She pressed the sorting had to choose differently, focussing on all ways that she and her sisters were alike and putting her own priority towards her ambitions, permanently. Knowledge be damned if it'd separate her from her triplets. The sorting had was quite easily convinced as it realised that some things simply best left the way people saw them. While an apt fit for Ravenclaw, he also recognised her ability to fit into Slytherin at her cunning manipulation of events to ensure the trio could stay together. Slytherin it became. 

Third year was at best challenging for Selene. Bad things happened that she couldn't seem to get ahead of. People died and while Selene never admitted it to her sisters, she always made sure to take the paths that wouldn't lead to them discovering the bodies. Whatever was happening had to happen and Selene wasn't there to change it. Destiny could go hand in hand with prophecy to guide it but it clearly could also block the inner eye to keep on course. Selene grew more quiet and stopped sharing her visions with her sisters as much as she had before, in stead silently taking the reins from time to time since Luna had started questioning her abilities.

Kings cross was nothing short of a nightmare. Selene seemed like her normal self during the train ride but rather than actually read the book she was holding she was in a constant state of silent terror. She could see what was ahead and was planning their escape. She managed to lead her sisters towards locations where they wouldn't get harmed, but never actually told them what she'd seen. 

Fourth year came and the tournament was fantastic. Three spots on the quidditch team opened up and the triplets had joined, although Phoebe had needed more persuasion. Selene had felt a sense of dread and doom on the day of the carriage explosion but no visions had warned her. She saw nothing ahead of time and her nerves were frayed for weeks after. She dropped out of the quidditch team, telling her sisters she'd seen herself getting seriously injured if she kept playing. She would rather open up the spot for somebody else and she'd be back on the team when it was safe again, long before graduation.

She did foresee the break out, although none would believe her. She was young and not quite the most credible source. With her aunt loving to predict doom her own credibility as a seer was called into question and none listened to her warnings. Selene's confidence took quite a hit for a few months but she found strength in a letter to her grandparents. It was none of her concern what her peers or anybody else believed she could or couldn't do, only what she knew herself capable of. WIth that development, Selene stopped caring what other people said or thought of her or what she was capable of. It didn't matter. She kept quiet as the epidemic swarmed the world and merely encouraged her sisters to use their abilities. "Nobody wants to believe in a bad future." She told them and quite commonly stopped sharing visions. 

As the mysterious island was discovered, Selene figured Luna had seen things, as she was adamant none of them should go. Selene has little interest in going there, but a sense of dread had started to build in her. Perhaps there is more to the island, or her inner eye has been blinded again? 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Seph[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]She/Her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]29 and in denial
[/blockquote]
[/div][/div]