[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" alt="" src="https://64.media.tumblr.com/844d389da0d8454e27aa7ecdbf1a3936/50e1474f418915fe-c6/s1280x1920/026d7442b36e3ba25d769e3c443ea7db6ebe8059.jpg"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Phoebe Clatho Trelawney[/font][/div][hr]

[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]Fee-bee klaa-thow truh-laa-nee)[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Pixie - what her sisters call her, sometimes even some of their other siblings too
Pheobs (pronounced fee-bs), or Bee - what her friends call her
People in her home town call her and her sisters the Heca-three.[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]17
31st of October[/blockquote] 
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Female she/her[/blockquote]


[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]half-blood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Questioning, Phoebe isn’t quite sure, it isn’t something she’s really thought about before[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]13” Silver Lime, Fairy Wing(s)[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]kiernan shipka [/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Phoebe has short blonde hair, standing at 5’5 and is the perfect mirror image of her triplet sisters. She is rarely seen without a smile on her face.She has short blond wavy hair, and loves to wear headbands that compliment her mood and sometimes her outfits. When able to wear what she wants, Phoebe prefers bright or pastel colors. She loves clothes that are easy to move in, soft, and if she has to wear skirts or dresses, it is required that she can twirl, and the skirt must fan out. If it doesn't, she won't wear it. Most of her pants that cover the knee are usually stained, scrapped, torn, or grass stained, this comes from the many times she crawled on her knees, or tripped while running or walking.[/blockquote]


[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling &amp; status[/b]
[blockquote]Slytherin 6th year[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Herbology
Butterflies
Flowers
Song birds
cooking/baking
Being with her sisters
Rainbows
Sweets
Having a good time
Music
Dancing
cats
drawing
music
everything about her sisters
unicorns
[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Being told to focus
Being alone
Sensing danger
Getting stuck in a vision of the past
Getting lost after a vision, or waking up to something
Sleep walking
Spicy foods
Cold weather
People who harm people or animals (past or present)
being thought of as different
bullies
[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Phoebe has always been a positive girl. She has always been one to show her emotions as she is feeling them. As an infant, she was usually the first to start crying, as they grew up, she usually seemed to have a bounce to her step. She made friends with the neighborhood kids easily, that was, until their parents told them not to play with her or her sisters. The adults often thought of her as not quite there, or extremely immature. She’s always had a positive outlook on life, choosing to hope for a better future than the past. Because of her visions, Phoebe has a hard time thinking about the future. Not that she doesn’t try, it’s just that she has so many visions of dark and evil things that happened in the past, all she can  do is hop that the future will be better. When she does get sad, it’s easy to know. While she rarely gets sad, when she does, she tends to cry quite a bit. Phoebe has never been good at hiding how she is feeling.

Phoebe is a young soul, There is a part of her that believes that she will never truly “grow up.” She is easily distracted, and can often be found skipping, dancing or twirling around for no reason. She can get easily distracted, and much prefers to be doing something, rather than just sitting there. Because of this, she has a hard time paying attention in classes, and can normally be found doodling more than taking notes. With that said, she loves playing quidditch, especially with her sisters. Games are only fun if she’s playing them, not able to sit still while watching. Practices prove difficult if the captain is focusing on anything else, making the chasers sit out. When that happens, Phoebe can often be found picking the grass, wandering off, or chasing butterflies. But when it counts, she’s pretty good.

Romance isn’t a subject that the girl has thought a lot about, for herself. She loves a good romantic comedy, or a cute romance story, but for herself, she just likes having friends. Perhaps a sweet romance is just around the corner, or not. The girl loves all things nature, she loves plants and animals, and wishes for nothing but love and peace. Phoebe isn’t the most graceful of the triplets. She trips down and up stairs, always seems to fall when she runs, or even simply walking. If she isn’t  watching where she’s going, she’s most likely going to trip. Though it doesn’t end there, she often drops things or fails to catch. The only time this seems not to be true, is when she’s in a game.
[/blockquote]


[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Ottery St. Catchpole, Englandblockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Cassandra Trelawney-a famous Seer -great great great grandmother - deceased 
___ Trelawney - great great grandparent
___ Trelawney - great grandparent

Mr Trelawney - grand-father
Mrs Trelawney - muggle - grand-mother

Sybill Trelawney - 63 - aunt - former divinations professor
Mr Higglebottom - ex-uncle - ex husband of Sybill Trelawney

Siilas Trelawney - 40 - father
Asteria Trelawney - 29-35 - mother

Older brother - 19-25
@selene            -Older triplet sister
@luna   -Older triplet sister
Younger brother - 12-15[/blockquote]


[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Maine Coon cat named Buttons[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]On a particularly stormy Hallowen night, three special girls were born. Selene, Luna, and Phoebe were born to Silas and Asteria Trelawney. Being descendants to the famed seer Cassandra Trelawney, it was only a matter of time until another seer came along. It was clear from the moment the triplets were all out, that their connection was beyond normal, it was supernatural. Even as infants, there was a connection, and each girl started showing signs of magic. And from that moment on, they stuck with each other like glue.

From an early age, it was clear that the girls were special. Growing up, Phoebe was always a happy child. She made friends with the neighborhood kids easily. But when she really started to sleep walk around. It wasn't just around the house either, she was leaving home and wandering the streets. Waking up screaming from her visions. It wasn’t long for the village adults to start to perceive the triplets as weirdos and freaks. Once that started happening, no other child would play with her or her sisters. And if they tried, their parents would hurry them away. This didn’t bother the young girl, little seemed to get to her.

It seemed as though all three girls had the sight, while the Trelawney boys did not. As they grew, Luna took up quidditch, and seeing as no one in the town wanted anything to do with them, Phoebe started to play some too, though she wasn't anywhere as good as her siblings. 

Ateria insisted that the girls go to primary school, but rumors and comments had already gotten around. Phoebe found it harder and harder to make friends, so she began attaching more and more to her sisters. Though she still tried. Some kids would be nice to her, but soon hear stories from others, and the next moment, ignore, or call the girls names. Year two the kids started to call the girls the Heca-three, and while they said it in taunting tones, but Phoebe knew the truth. The girls really were witches, and seers. Luna seemed to love it, and while it took some more time, Phoebe learned to love it too. But that didn't mean that she had stopped trying to make friends. Though, her sisters always seemed to come to her rescue.

The time came when the girls received their letters to Hogwarts. The girls learned about the sorting process at Hogwarts. This left the triplets quite concerned, especially Phoebe. The last thing she needed was to be separated from her sisters. She knew she’d be lost without them. The girls gathered together and focused. Their goal, try to coax a vision out. Selene, the one who could see far into the future, saw the inevitable split. That was no good. With that, Selene ensured that they would all be able to stay together. Arriving at the hall, and the sorting ceremony, the girls were some of the last called. First Luna, then Selene, both sorted into Slytherin. Those seconds as the table of green and silver celebrated for the two, Phoebe felt the separation, it was torture. But then she heard her name. The girl walked up and sat on the stool. The ratted hat fell over her ears, covering her eyes. She heard the hat contemplating. She was made for Hufflepuff, that much was clear. But she didn’t want to be separated from her sisters. She begged the hat, please Slytherin. Please. In time, the hat called out the house she had wished for, and Phoebe joined her sisters at the table.

The house was a bit of an odd fit for Phoebe, but she was happy to be with her sisters. During their third year, bad things started to happen at school. Throughout the year, Phoebe was filled on and off with a sense of danger. She felt so on edge, choosing to stick as close to her sisters as possible. Being the only one who couldn't see anything to come. Heading home, they were nearly caught up in the Kings Cross explosion. The entire ride on the Hogwarts Express, Phoebe felt an overarching feeling of dread, so much so that she was made physically ill from it.

In the girls fourth year, three quidditch spots opened up on the house team. Selene and Luna were so excited about trying out, and Phoebe, not wanting to be left out, was forced to try out with them. She didn't mind, though she loved the game, she never felt as strongly about it as her sisters. It seemed as though she did play well enough, and made it on the team as a chaser. But, she did wonder if her better siblings had done something to ensure her success.

Throughout the years at school, Phoebe was able to make lots of friends. But none of that stopped her from sleepwalking. She would often leave bed, and even try to get out of the house common room. Once out, she would aimlessly wander the school, slow paced, as if in a trance. She would then often settle down and rest there until she woke up, but occasionally, she would simply start screaming. It all depended on what she saw in her visions. Phoebe, normally a happy girl, saw traumatizing visions. Many visions she didn't fully remember once the trance was over. So when she really had something to say, there was no surprise, that no one listened.

As their sixth year started, it seemed as though the girls were closer to each other than they had ever been.
[/blockquote]


[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Sophi[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her [/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]older than 18[/blockquote]
[/blockquote][/div][/div]
