[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" alt="" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/profile_images/1048716709568413697/LxrfJZUY_400x400.jpg"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]claudia eloise watkins[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]claw-dee-ah ell-oh-wees waht-kins[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Claud to few. Mostly just Claudia[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]16
August 20th 2008[/blockquote][b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]halfblood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Straight - probably[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]9 inches, red oak, dragon core[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]liana libreato[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Claudia is around 5 feet and 7 inches tall, she's taller than average and likes being so as it makes for straighter and longer lines while dancing. Her body is toned and athletic while remaining lean, a figure that she keeps up for the demands of her art form and sport. Claudia keeps her dark hair long and if it's not up in a styled and sleek bun on her head, she leaves it down to it's own devices and it falls in soft waves though rarely gets tangled. It's a blessing.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Slytherin at Hogwarts[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]6th year student[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]student&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]bodies of water
soup
storms
ballet and dance in general
her friends
her family (sometimes including her brother)
attention
flirting[/blockquote][b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]getting turned down/rejection
not being the favorite
forced socialization
people who ask too many questions
mud
humidity/muggy days
[/blockquote][b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Claudia wants to be a core or soloist dancer for the Royal Ballet in London England, but she'd settle for any other national company just about anywhere in the world&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]spring flowers, salt water, floral perfume, baby powder[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Injury, falling, being rejected or laughed at, major embarrassment&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Claudia is very protective of her friends and the people that she cares about. She's not afraid to make enemies, especially if they deserve it. She's fairly set in her own mindset and doesn't really listen to other points of view or opinions that she disagrees with. Claudia is also very hot-headed and easily gets upset and angry. She holds grudges and is hard to get through to. When she's gone off, only those who are close to her can bring her back down to Earth and reason with her. She's very aggressive and impulsive. She jumps to conclusions and would rather apologize than ask for permission. Though in that way she's also hypocritical because she'd rather others be the opposite way.&nbsp; When she was younger, she'd even hit and yell at her brother for even just touching her toys without permission.

Claudia is very creative minded and in some ways thinks of herself as a free spirit. She's been in dance classes since she was 6 years old and started dancing on pointe at the age of 12. She's tried not to let Hogwarts slow her down, but it has and sometimes that fact really frustrates her because when she goes back to classes and she feels behind. While she does all of her magical school work and is considering career back up plans that require Hogwarts and a proper education here, her main focus wants to be dance, and she tries to accomplish that. She's very dedicated and passionate about it. However, she addiction to dance has also turned her into quite a little perfectionist, a trait that she shares with her older brother.&nbsp;

Overall, Claudia is a nice girl and is easy to get along with, unless you get on her bad side or you don't know how to carry a decent conversation. She hates small talk and she hates forced conversation. What a necessary evil. Claudia could care less about a person's blood status or whether or not they associate with muggles, primarily, because she associates with them as often as possible in the dance world.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]winchester, england[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]harriett watkins, 40, healer - mother
james watkins, 45, department of magical games &amp; sports reporter - father

tobias watkins, 17, ravenclaw - brother
_____ watkins - forth year - slytherin
 - sister
_____ watkins - fifth year - ravenclaw - sister[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]pets are a distraction[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Claudia was born on the 2oth of august in 2008. She was born 9 months and 3 weeks after her older brother, Tobias was born. Her parents weren't exactly planning for another baby that quickly, and her mother didn't even think it was possible that soon, but it happened and here they were: Irish Twins. Two babies born in a 12 month period to one mother. This, oddly enough, made it so they two were in the same school year. Toby was older in the year and Claudia was younger in the year, but their Hogwarts letters arrived the same year and they ventured off on their first year together.&nbsp;

While her brothers magical abilities came through helping her from a bully in their muggle primary school, her own magical abilities came as a result of her dancing. She realized one day that she could slow herself down as we fell and not bruise her face or bloody her nose on the floor. that happened when she 8 years old, a late bloomer, she knew.

During her first two years of Hogwarts, Claudia took it all in and experienced everything that the castle and the classes had to offer, even to the extend of letting ballet slip to the back burner. But, come her third year she started to feel tired of it already and put more effort and attention back into her own training. She practiced everyday, even if all she had time for on particularly busy days was stretching and light cardio in the mornings before lessons. She had always been an early riser.

her favorite school subjects included charms, transfiguration and defense against the dark arts. She also enjoyed care of magical creatures a lot, about half of the time. It really depended on the creature that they were studying.&nbsp;

As Claudia grew older, she started taking more of an interest in flirting and boys and enjoyed the attention that they gave her. Claudia has had several boyfriends, but none of them has lasted more than a few weeks, they always annoyed her in someway, or, they didn't like that she was so unavailable most of the time when she was dancing. Overall, she's fairly promiscuous and doesn't view intimacy as an immoral act, though she can't stand her brothers lectures about "respecting herself".&nbsp;

Claudia doesn't cause a lot of trouble, at least not as far as the faculty or staff are concerned. But she loves personal drama as much as the next person and is never afraid of spreading it around, even at the cost of hurting someones feelings. It's all fun, isn't it? Well, until she's on the receiving end of it, of course. Then it's the end of the world.&nbsp;[/blockquote][b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]While Claudia has been at Hogwarts through all of the events thus far, she's not too bothered by most of them. She's unaligned, but would absolutely take a side if the war amped up further. She was saddened and scared by the tower explosion and the bombings last year, and of course she felt a bit of pain for the Ilvermorny students for their school, but none of it really effected her too much. She was not at the dragon attack in the village.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Ali[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]23[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]pst[/blockquote][b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]i don't even remember[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@rosie  @sav  @angie  @riley  @lucyweasley  @natalie  @lusie  @jack &nbsp;[/blockquote][/div][/div]