
[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://66.media.tumblr.com/6cd7638fc93ce10eed144329a0019982/tumblr_oxdpklTb8j1rw50e2o2_500.gif" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Penelope Raisa Bainbridge[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]Puh-NEL-uh-pee RYE-suh BAYN-brij[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Penny is the most common, but also Pen, Nell, Nellie, and ’Nelope[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]16
April 12, 2008[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Cisgender female; she/her pronouns[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Half-blood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Heterosexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]12 ⅝ inches, willow, unicorn hair core, slightly springy[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Lia Marie Johnson[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Penelope is 5’5” inches tall and of an average build. She has long dirty blonde hair, green eyes, and fair skin that tans in summer, as well as a mole just above her lip on the left side. She has her ears pierced twice on each lobe, though she plans to get a tattoo once she’s old enough.

Penelope’s style is generally more feminine. Even in her school uniform, she prefers to look nice, though she’s also not one to wear a face full of makeup on a daily basis. She wears jeans more than dresses, in general, but she doesn’t mind dressing up if the occasion calls for it. Overall, she prefers lighter colors to darker ones, and owns a lot of floral-patterned clothing, also.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts; Hufflepuff[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Sixth year[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Her siblings, in general; watching Quidditch; most animals, but especially cats; drinking tea with biscuits; a good book; yoga; peace and quiet, though it’s a little unsettling; liquorice allsorts, fuzzy socks, Divination[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Mediating fights within her family; being called one of her sisters’ names; when her belongings get “borrowed” and not returned; Skiving Snackboxes; Dark magic; the smell and taste of coffee; bullying; Potions; the sound of squealing chalk against a blackboard; thunderstorms[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Penelope desires to see her family’s dysfunction ameliorated, and she would like to travel the world eventually.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Peppermint, liquorice, and candle wax[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Penelope is terrified of being completely alone in the world, and she’s also afraid of ruining her relationships with her siblings for good.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote][b]accepting[/b]

Penelope is accepting of other people's differences, and she feels that diversity makes for a much more interesting world. She thinks that it would be boring if everyone in the world were all the same, and she has enjoyed getting to hear the perspectives of the students and staff who have come to Hogwarts from America and elsewhere.

[b]affectionate[/b]

Penelope is very much a physically affectionate person. She enjoys giving and receiving hugs, especially, and is overall what some might call "touchy-feely". She's always been that way, even platonically, craving physical affirmation from people rather than their words or gestures.

[b]anxious[/b]

Even if she won't admit it and tries to mask it to appear stronger than she feels, Penelope is very anxious, in no small part due to the multiple times that Hogwarts' safety has been brought into question. She thinks that her interest in Divination has only grown because it gives her a sense of knowing what might happen, even if she can't control the future.

[b]pacifistic[/b] 

Making sure that other people are happy—and happy with her—is important to Penelope. She is quick to forgive other people, especially her friends and family, for their wrongdoings, not wanting to cause further conflict. She tries her hardest to be a peacemaker, and it would take a lot to get her to intentionally harm anyone.

[b]loyal[/b]

Penelope is very loyal to her friends and family—all of them. She loves them and just wants to keep them all in her corner and safe from harm, though she has increasingly found that she's being stretched thin from not putting up boundaries. She just cannot bring herself to do it.

[b]sensitive[/b]

Penelope wishes that she could develop a thicker skin and not let people's thoughts and opinions bother her so much. No matter how much she [i]wishes[/i] that she could shake it off, though, she does get deeply affected by others' criticisms of her. She internalizes them much more than she should and is forced to wonder if she's the problem.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]England, UK[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote][b]mother:[/b]
Raisa Bainbridge, 43, [i]Daily Prophet[/i] reporter, witch of unknown blood purity

[b]father:[/b]
Eoin Bainbridge, 44, [s]some occupation that I can’t find anywhere[/s], Muggle

[b]brother:[/b]
Dustin Ariel Bainbridge, 20, former professional Quidditch player, half-blood wizard

[b]sisters:[/b]
@cara , 18, author and part-time Florean Fortescue’s cashier, half-blood witch, twin to Diana
@diana , 18, Curse Specialist, half-blood witch, twin to Cara

@kinsey , 17, Ravenclaw student, half-blood witch

@peytonbainbridge , 16, Hufflepuff student, half-blood witch, older triplet
@sephy , 16, Hufflepuff student, half-blood witch, younger triplet[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]From the beginning, Penelope Bainbridge never knew what it was like to be alone. She was a triplet, for one thing, and she and her two sisters were not their parents' first set of multiples, either. In order, there was Dustin, then Cara and Diana, Kinsey, Peyton, herself, and Persephone. Really, she had so many playmates that her childhood was never boring. There was always someone there, even if her eldest siblings could sometimes boss her around because she was little and naïve. The second youngest of the Bainbridge children never saw her siblings' behavior as malicious; she was just happy to spend time with them however she could.

As some saw it, Penelope had the best of both worlds. She had exposure to the Muggle world through her non-magical father, while her witch mother also exposed her to the magical world of which she would grow up to be a part. With four of her siblings at Hogwarts before her, Penelope's excitement for the school grew with each passing year. She began to gravitate towards the magical side of things, and she was always thrilled to hear about what school was like for her brother and sisters.

Eventually, it would be her turn to go, and her magic would be more than just a few mistakes that she couldn't control. When she finally did get her Hogwarts letter, Penelope wouldn't stop talking about it for weeks. She had waited so long, and she, Peyton, and Persephone were finally about to go for themselves!

Sorted into Hufflepuff alongside Peyton and Persephone, Penelope felt on top of the world. Everything was new and even better than Penelope had imagined it would be. She stuck close to Peyton and Persephone, especially at first, but gradually branched out and began to make friends with students who weren't her siblings.

As time passed, each of the triplets began to carve out their own identities. For Penelope, it wasn't exactly her academic performance that made her a stand-out. She did well enough to keep anyone from being concerned about her marks, but nothing really "clicked" for her until her third year. Divination, as it turned out, was her strongest subject yet. To some, that wasn't saying much; Divination had a reputation for being nonsensical for those who weren't Seers, but Penelope was happy to have found what she really enjoyed doing academically.

Outside of class, she spent her time on the grounds when it wasn't too cold to be outdoors—or wherever her siblings happened to be. Overall, she was content. There was nothing wrong. The occasional fight between her siblings was to be expected, but it was all life as usual.

Maybe it would have been better if she had been born a Seer, because Penelope just hadn't anticipated the many changes that were going to come. So many deaths happened that it seemed as though they were living in a nightmare. Penelope felt fortunate that she wasn't among the murdered or kidnapped. And, the more uncertain things became, the more distant her older siblings became from her and her triplet sisters. She tried to keep them all together; she didn't want to feel alone in the world. Her siblings had always kept her safe, she thought, and she didn't want to lose any of them.

The Triwizard Tournament was exciting, and it gave Penelope a distraction. It was fun to watch the tasks and to get to learn about the other countries from which the visitors to Hogwarts had come, but even that wasn't meant to last. Instead of a shift in a more positive direction, it became apparent that they had only been in the eye of a hurricane: Most of the visiting delegations were killed upon their departure from Hogwarts, and what faith Penelope had that things would get better was shattered.

She began to cling to anything and everything that made life feel safe again. Whatever she could do to reach out to her siblings, Penelope tried it. She kept herself as busy as she could, trying not to break down. She wanted to be the glue that held them all together—somehow.

As the news came that students from Ilvermorny would have to attend Hogwarts until the vandalism of their own school could be repaired, Penelope was just thankful that it hadn't been Hogwarts. She just wanted a year where things could go back to how they had been once, before the madness.

The return of the Winter Festival to Hogsmeade seemed to bring back that dose of nostalgia that Penelope so craved, and she spent as much time as possible in the village. That included during the time that the dragons were present and wreaking havoc. In the resulting chaos, she was spared physically but not psychologically: Every fear that she had managed to suppress had been reignited by the news that it hadn't been just dragons; Azkaban was also destroyed.

With that in mind, Penelope returned to school, grateful for the extra security that had been promised by MACUSA and hopeful that her fears would stay inside her head and that everything would be alright.[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Having been at Hogwarts since things first started happening with Elaine and the murders of Muggle-born students, Penelope has been cautious not to mess with anyone—not that she has ever been a confrontational person. She has always felt bad for the students who have been caught up in the murders and the kidnapping, though she’s also tried to be thankful that she hasn’t been a direct target. So far, Penelope has remained largely out of harm’s way, though she knows how many close calls there have been, including at King’s Cross, and that pattern has deeply worried her.

The Triwizard Tournament seemed like the opportunity for Hogwarts to turn things around, but it hit Penelope just how little she could know anything for certain when most of their visitors from Durmstrang and Beauxbatons never made it home alive. With that so fresh in her mind, as well as reports that Harry Potter was dead, she was worried about the students from Ilvermorny and their coming to Hogwarts. She didn’t think that any of them were a problem, but anyone who wanted to harm students, specifically, would not have had to look far, she felt.

One term in with the Ilvermorny transfer students at Hogwarts, Penelope had begun to feel at ease—until the apparent serial killings of both wizards and Muggles came to light. With her parents’ being a Muggle and a witch, the thought that maybe they would be in danger from whoever was doing the killings wasn’t the most comforting thought that she had ever had.

And then came December 28 and the dragons’ rampage through Hogsmeade, coupled with the news the next day that Azkaban had fallen while everything had been going on in the village. Inside, she’s truly terrified about what might happen next, but she’s trying to stay strong for everyone around her and hope for the best.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@audrey [/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]21[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]US/Canada Central/Eastern[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]Current member![/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@maxima , @parvati , @oona , @honey , @kaylee , @ezekiel , @clarence , @priscilla , @tamatha , @samira , @brody , @camila , @sepideh  [/blockquote][/div][/div]