
[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img]https://66.media.tumblr.com/ad044d07de5f1b56aa26eb2c02ecb9dd/tumblr_p5ke06lVee1skdj1oo1_540.gif[/img][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Brody Christopher Dubois[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]/ˈbɹoʊdi ˈkɻʷɪst.ə.fɚ dy'bwɑ/
BRO-dee KRIS-tuh-fur doo-BWAH[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Sometimes he's called "Bro", "Brods", or "Brodster", though those are mostly from his family.[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]14
May 23, 2010[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Cisgender male; he/him pronouns[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Half-blood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Heterosexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]7 ⅞ inches, tamarack, phoenix feather core, quite bendy (original)

8 ⅝ inches, chestnut, unicorn tail hair core, reasonably supple (replacement)[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Levi Miller[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Brody is 5'9" inches tall and has a slim build. He has some muscle, though it's not very well-defined. He has short brown hair (which would be more noticeably curly if he grew it out), fair skin, and bright blue eyes. He hasn't lost his "baby face" quite yet, as well, so his height doesn't quite match his appearance otherwise.

Because Brody enjoys spending time outside, aside from his school uniform, his clothing is usually pretty practical. Anything that's easily cleaned is generally his preference, which means jeans and sneakers with some sort of T-shirt most of the time. In the winter, it's flannels and fleeces.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Ilvermorny (2021-2024); Horned Serpent

Hogwarts (2024-); Hufflepuff
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Fourth-year[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Creature Care/Care of Magical Creatures, color-coded notes, competition, hands-on learning, the Fitchburg Finches, the color blue, magical creatures, hiking, being outdoors, owls[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Being cooped up inside, peanuts (not allergic; they're just gross), tobacco smoke, the color orange, disorganized people, theory-based material, animal/magical creature abuse, the taste of coffee, the sight of blood, bullying[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Brody plans to do something involving magical creatures in the future, whether that's magizoology or working for MACUSA in that area.

In the Mirror of Erised, Brody would see himself standing outdoors somewhere in Maine, along with his brothers and the de Snaijers… and probably a couple of owls.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Blueberries and molasses, saltwater, and pine trees[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Brody most fears the death of his twin brother, because he can't imagine living without him.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote][b]compassionate:[/b]

Brody is a generally good kid with his heart in the right place. He's empathetic and one to put the needs of others before his own. He'll happily lend a hand to someone in need without thinking twice, though some might say that that's too self-sacrificing of him.

[B]loyal:[/b]

Brody is also very loyal. He's someone who tries his best to stick by those he cares about—family or friends—through thick or through thin. He operates by the idea that he should treat people as he would want to be treated by them, and he knows that he would want support in a tough situation. At the same time, he would hate to leave a friend behind and doesn't really know when it's okay to let go of people.

[B]hardworking:[/b]

As another true-to-Hufflepuff trait, Brody is a hard worker. He gives his all, especially where school is concerned, though he might border on being perfectionist at times. He feels bad when he knows that he hasn't put forward his best effort towards something, and he's still trying to figure out the right line between doing something to completion and taking it too far.

[B]intelligent:[/b]

Some would certainly guess that Brody might belong to Ravenclaw House, given his intelligence. He's very smart, though he prefers to apply his knowledge and do things for himself rather than simply theorizing about them. It's one of the reasons why he likes Care of Magical Creatures so much; that, and he's pretty partial to the beasts.

[B]protective:[/b]

Especially where his family and closest friends are concerned, Brody is protective. He isn't a fighter—much more of a pacifist, if anything—but he would raise his wand in defense of someone he loves.

[B]introverted:[/b]

While some might take this to mean that Brody is shy or unfriendly, the way he sees it is that he's simply just not the kid who's going to go to every party, and he doesn't mind that. He values his alone time, when he can get it, and there is also a good chance that—if he's nowhere to be found—he's in the company of owls.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Lewiston, Maine, USA[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote][b]mother:[/b]

Katherine Dubois, 38, owlet trainer, half-blood witch

[b]father:[/b]

Rodney Dubois, 42, owlet trainer, half-blood wizard

[B]elder brother:[/b]

_____ Dubois, 16, Wampus/Gryffindor student, half-blood wizard

[B]twin brother (younger than Brody by five minutes):[/b]

_____ Dubois, 14, Thunderbird/Hufflepuff student, half-blood wizard

[B]paternal uncle:[/b]

Randy Dubois, 39, metal charmer, half-blood wizard

[B]paternal grandfather:[/b]

Charles Dubois, 68, retired owlet trainer, half-blood wizard

[B]paternal grandmother:[/b]

Cynthia Dubois, 65, former homemaker, half-blood witch
[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote][b]at home:[/b]
Assorted owlets being trained by his parents for the post office or as pets

[B]at school:[/b]
Hoot, 4, male great horned owl

[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Growing up in Maine, Brody and his brothers had never had much to worry about. Although their family technically lived among the non-magical community, they had a large enough piece of property and enough enchantments placed on it to avoid suspicion. To the outside world, the Duboises were wildlife rehabilitators, which explained the owls when the No-Majes saw them. Maybe it wasn't especially "normal" to grow up handling birds of prey, but the Dubois boys were used to it. Their parents trained owlets to carry mail and packages for the magical community, though some ultimately became pets rather than full-time mail carriers.

Brody especially took to the owls. Even as an infant, his parents noticed that he seemed to have a real connection with them. He would wail if he was kept away from the birds for very long, only to smile and coo when he saw them again. As he grew older and was able to talk, he would say things that utterly perplexed his parents. He knew when an owl wanted something, or when it was unhappy—even when it wasn't apparent. Maybe, his parents thought, they just had a very empathetic child on their hands, but it seemed as though he actually could read their minds.

In elementary school, Brody and his brothers went to school with the local No-Maj population. They didn't exactly fit in, of course, but they made do. Aside from a fixation on owls, which he learned to tone down by about the first grade, Brody was well ahead of many of his peers, something that his teachers couldn't help but notice. They had to wonder if Mr. and Mrs. Dubois were right about not having a television or computers in the house. It was unorthodox, especially considering how often children sat in front of screens or went to coding or robotics camps, but maybe it had worked.

There were some odd things that went on with the Dubois boys besides their slightly unconventional home lives, though their teachers were sure that they had only imagined them. Of course, the twins had tried to switch places a time or two, but that was normal "kid" stuff. No, there was always something going on with the three of them—nothing that would result in suspension or expulsion, of course—but things would happen that they couldn't explain. For Brody, this once meant that he had to go to the principal's office to explain how the class turtle had ended up materializing in his pocket at recess.

As the boys grew older and got their acceptances to Ilvermorny, things got easier. Even when the twins were still at home, with their older brother off at school, they looked forward to receiving letters about the boarding school that they would soon attend. And, once they got there for themselves a short time later, Brody was [I]ready[/I].

Sorted into both Horned Serpent and Thunderbird, Brody chose the former, though his twin went to the latter. They had never been very far apart from one another, and getting to experience new things with new people in a place where they could still see each other frequently was the perfect balance. Brody, the more academic of the twins, enjoyed being in Horned Serpent and being challenged by his peers' knowledge. Some people might have found it frustrating, but it was fun to him.

What was even cooler was that there was another set of twins in his and his brother's year, both girls. They hadn't really met the de Snaijer twins before, though their elder sister was just in the year above their own elder brother, though it wasn't too hard to get to know them when one was in Horned Serpent and the other in Thunderbird. The de Snaijer twins, for what it was worth, were really cool… and also really pretty.

The more time that he spent with Yvonne de Snaijer, the twin in Horned Serpent with him, the more Brody liked her. She was smarter than he would ever be, and—as much as girls were a mystery to him—still relatable because of the whole "twin" factor.

As time passed, though, that began to change. Their second year was solid, and Brody could safely say that he no longer felt like "fresh meat" at Ilvermorny, though he'd have a way to go before he'd be anywhere near cool at school. Third year started off alright, and Brody had nearly worked up the courage to admit to Yvonne that maybe he wanted to be [I]more[/I] than friends with her.

And then, towards the end of the year, the unthinkable happened. The de Snaijers' parents had been killed, and the girls were sent to London to live with their grandmother. Brody was devastated for them—and also for himself because he hadn't had much time to say goodbye. The remainder of the school year felt ten times longer without Yvonne there, and it didn't help that people had kept spreading rumors in her absence. Brody tried to quash what he could, but it was hard.

When he learned that he and his brothers would have to attend Hogwarts from September, Brody was thrilled. Otherwise, he didn't know when he would get to see the de Snaijer girls again. He knew that Hogwarts had had significant problems for the past few years, but he had faith that everything would be fine, especially because the de Snaijer girls would have been at the Scottish school to face it all on their own. At least they would be back together, and it would be just like old times.

Brody, his brothers, and their parents arrived in London shortly before the start of the school year so that the boys could get what they needed for school and be seen off on the Hogwarts Express. From the very beginning, Hogwarts seemed like it would be an interesting place. The castle was so much older than Ilvermorny's, but it was beautiful. 

Finding out, however, that he wouldn't be in the same House as Yvonne at Hogwarts was disappointing. Brody tried to get the Sorting Hat to put him in Slytherin House, but it was to no avail. He was Sorted into Hufflepuff, and thus began his new life at Hogwarts alongside so many of the people he had known from Ilvermorny. Suddenly, it was back to classes and studying, along with meeting new roommates and classmates and teachers.

Being apart from Yvonne, though, was the biggest challenge. The Yvonne Brody knew had become withdrawn, and he wondered if it was because of the rumors that people had been spreading about her for months. He knew that it was only because people had nothing better to do with their time, but it still hurt him that she seemed to have been so affected by it. Nevertheless, he continued to stand by her. Things were different, but that didn't mean that they had to be any different between [I]them[/I].

Overall, Brody doesn't think that his first semester at Hogwarts was too bad. He has settled into a routine, and he's looking forward to the next semester and what it will bring. His concern, though, is for what will happen after that. He and his brothers have been trying to convince their parents to allow them to stay in Britain for the de Snaijer girls' sake, but he knows that the chances of that happening are slim.[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Brody had heard about the murders and kidnappings at Hogwarts but had never been too concerned about them before. Britain was light years away from the United States, in his mind, so the political side of it and the murdered Ministers of Magic barely even registered with him. His parents seemed more worried, but what happened in London wouldn't ever affect them, [I]never[/I].

It started to register with him a bit more as he got older, though. Especially once his friends, the de Snaijers, moved away, he became more interested in—and concerned about—what was happening across the ocean. The disaster that had happened with the Triwizard Tournament was probably the biggest shock that Brody had experienced, because so many people who weren't even from Hogwarts had died.

The vandalism of Ilvermorny was bad, but Brody was mainly just glad that no one had been hurt. He didn't mind having to go to Hogwarts, since he would get to go to school with the de Snaijers again, but Britain didn't stay peaceful for too long.

Harry Potter—who was famous even in America—had gone missing and then was presumed dead. In addition to what had already been happening, it was kind of scary. It wasn't as though Harry Potter had a low profile anywhere he had ever gone, though, so maybe it wouldn't be too bad for people who were—well, pretty ordinary.

As the serial killings of No-Majes and magical people alike started happening, Brody was glad that he was relatively safer at Hogwarts. With the latest news of the dragons in Hogsmeade and the breakout from Azkaban, he's especially glad that MACUSA is bringing reinforcements to Hogwarts. It's some peace of mind, anyway…[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@Audrey[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]21[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]US/Canada Central/Eastern[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]Current member[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@maxima, @parvati, @oona, @honey, @kaylee, @clarence, @ezekiel, @tamatha, @priscilla, @samira [/blockquote][/div][/div]