
[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" alt="(image here of playby)" src="https://64.media.tumblr.com/8621f3d10d08829f3994fcc8001e0490/7a29c351da6788d7-d9/s540x810/573aa3a74644623dc593a1f8995567a8f9dbdf26.gif"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Newton Connor Finkley[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]New-ton | Con-ner | Feenk-lee[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Newty, Newt, Dat New New Finkley[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]17
February 19th (Pisces)

[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b][blockquote]Male
He/him/his[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Muggleborn[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Heterosexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b][blockquote]11" Oak, Dragon Heartstring
[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Donald Glover (Community era)[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b][blockquote]Newt stands at about 6 feet tall with a dark complexion, brown eyes, thick brows and a smile that can brighten any room. He has a slender build with a small amount of muscle from playing sports.

In class he wears glasses. Newt has a very expressive face and wears his heart on his shoulder. People can usually tell how he feels by the way he presents himself. His style is more relaxed when he's not wearing his school uniform and robes. Newt looks identical to his play-by Donald Glover in the series Community.

[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling &amp; status[/b]
[blockquote]Hufflepuff
Sixth Year[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Part Time at Blishwicks Pizza Parlor[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]+ Friendship 
+ Solitary moments
+ School (what a nerd)
+ Quidditch
+ Football, sports, being active
+ Herbology/foraging
+ Science
+ Art
+ People trusting him
+ Video games
+ Making people laugh
+ Dancing
+ The great outdoors
+ Pizza[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b][blockquote]- The friend zone
- Fighting
- Hostility
- Materialistic shallowness
- Smoking
- Constant negativity
- How he gets awkward around cute girls
- Public speaking
- Television
- People taking his kindness as weakness
- Snow or freezing cold[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b][blockquote]Newton is kind, caring, compassionate, and a bit of a mixture of awkward and goofy. He has a heart of gold, always willing to give a stranger in a need the shirt off of his back without hesitation. However, he isn't a pushover.  Known to be typically even-tempered, the badger can be surprisingly vicious when provoked and capable of putting up a fierce fight. As much as Newton hates confrontation and can have a shy streak, he won't let people abuse his kindness or use him. He has no problem cutting people off - although at times he may forget about being mad at certain people.

As a Prefect, Newton is more easy going. More often than not, he will allow his peers to go with a warning. He isn't power hungry and doesn't wish to use his badge as a tool to upset anyone, but he will if he feels the need to.

Since transferring to Hogwarts from Ilvermorny, Newt has learned how to play quidditch. It has quickly become one of his favorite sports, ever. He joined the Hufflepuff team this year as a Beater and has quickly grown as a player. Before moving to the UK he played QuodPot for his Ilvermorny house team. Don't tell anyone, but he prefers quidditch now...

Newton is easily friendzoned by just about every girl he has ever liked and it frustrates him because he notices the vicious cycle every time. He has never had a first kiss or girlfriend because girls see him as an 'amazing friend' and 'don't wanna ruin it'. Awkward. That always ruins it. He isn't too concerned about dating because he's devoted to school and quidditch at the moment, but if the right girl came along he'd try to make her the happiest girl in the world.
 
Some of his favorite activities include: long, romantic walks on the beach...wait, wrong profile.
 
Newton enjoys being outside, being active, Herbology, learning new things, making new friends, and questioning everything. Newton is horrible at public speaking, instantly getting shy when he has to talk in a room full of people, even when he thinks he's prepared. He has no problem playing quidditch with spectators because he doesn't have to talk to them. At times he's an accidental class clown by his nervous mannerism and babbling in class when called upon, his mind goes completely blank and he kind of just laughs and mumbles nonsense. Newton enjoys when people are comfortable around him and could be their true selves. He's authentic to himself so when he feels like he has to hide he doesn't like it and often gets awkward due to it.

Newton hopes to pursue a career as an Herbologist so he can use the skills to find cure for illness. He strives to make his parents proud of him and he's extremely hard on himself when it comes to his academic endeavors and achievements.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Oakland, California[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b][blockquote]Shay (Nee. Musk)- Mother - Doctor/Scientist - Muggle
Christian - Father - NASA Astrophysicist - Muggle
[/blockquote]
[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]owl[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b][blockquote]
Newton Finkley grew up in Oakland, California, as an only child in a upperclass household to a family of scientists. His mother, Shay, a doctor, and his father, Christian, is a Astrophysicist for NASA, found magic an incredibly hard concept to believe.&nbsp;It was a complete surprise to Newts parents. Being natural critical thinkers, it made zero sense to them. They thought they were being pranked so they didn't believe the people who arrived at the door requesting their sons attendance to some magical school in Massachusetts called Ilvermorny.&nbsp;

They &nbsp;begrudgingly allowed their only son to attend this magical school. He flourished amongst his peers, quickly finding his place at Ilvermorny and being sorted into Horned Serpents, the house of Scholars. He's been a dedicated player on the QuodPot team since his 3rd year.&nbsp;Once Ilvermorny blew up, it took a lot of convincing his parents to allow him to go to the UK to this mysterious school called Hogwarts. They were against it, but Newt begged them, and they wanted to see their son happy...&nbsp;

Ilvermorny taught him that he had a green thumb he never knew he had. Newton had a knack for the outdoors, foraging, and making his way around a greenhouse. He has been a dedicated member of the Herbology and Horticulture Club since day one. His parents consider it gardening, but he will prove them one day when he finds a cure for major illness and other ailments through the power of plants.

The past two years at Hogwarts he has gone through a lot of changes having to transfer from Ilvermorny to Hogwarts. Learning how to play quidditch, rather than the traditional QuodPot back in America. Attending a completely new school with new traditions, accents his ears barely understood, and being so far away from home. It hasn't been easy. He has gotten by with a lot of help from his friends, new and old. Newt has come to enjoy Hogwarts but it took a year of adjusting from a bit of culture shock, cold weather, new customs.&nbsp;

During the explosions at the quidditch match he was there spectating at his first official quidditch match. It was a terrifying experience but he was able to take cover and help his friends who were in danger. He suffers from a bit of PTSD in crowds and he doesn't think he will wish to attend another match in a long time. He prefers to play anyways.

Currently Newt is a Beater on the Hufflepuff House team and a Prefect. He is involved in many extra curricular activities because he wants to be stand out when applying for future schooling and career. Next year he wants to go for Hufflepuff team Captain but he doesn't wish to pursue quidditch when he graduates. As much as it's hard to be so far from home, he hopes to finish his seventh year at Hogwarts since he's made so many new friends and connections.

[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]dez[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]old enough[/blockquote]
[/div][/div]