[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://66.media.tumblr.com/5401755ccc1141459c86f3cbf517f306/tumblr_inline_nxx3r01Tzm1rifr4k_500.gif" alt=" " style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]katiya mahaila krum[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]kat-ye-a ma-hay-lia krum[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]mostly kat but sometimes kit or kitty.[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]seventeen.
18th october.[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]pureblood.[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]heterosexual.[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]hornbeam, unicorn tail, 10", unyielding.[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]sophie turner.[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]born with bright red hair and light blue eyes, kat grew up thinking she was mismatched. she's not sure where she gets the red hair from because everyone in her family has brown hair but her dad just calls her the family throwback, with affection. she stands at 5'9 which comes in handy when she's on the back of a broom, she's got a longer reach. she likes to dress like she pays attention to fashion but she really doesn't. she lives in jeans and boots, sometimes shorts in the summer but mostly jeans. she doesn't like to spend too much time fussing about what she wears because the odds are no one's going to notice anyway but she likes to be neat. she hates wearing a tie for school so it's always tied a little looser than it should be and it does sit slightly askew out of rebellion for the constricting contraption.  [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]hufflepuff.
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]seventh year.
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]student.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]movie nights, hanging with her siblings, asking her dad for money, irritating any guys interested in her sisters, trashy tv, loud music, playing the piano, all animals, reading, cool weather, her collection of bed spreads, flirting, serial killer documentaries, being in a crowd, drawing, feeling excited, hanging out with friends, jeans that fit well, wearing boots with a heel, finding out about people, studying people, singing in the shower, early mornings, sunrises, the beach.[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]most herbs in food, staying up too late, loosing, rock hard pillows, when she can't read people, classes where she learns from a book, splinters, clowns, when people judge her, the fact she chews her nails, suburn, soggy foods, when lead pencils snap, when he siblings are mad at her, when her parents are disappointed in her.  [/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]to work with the ministry to try and find out what goes through the minds dark wizards.
to develop a way of preventing dark wizards from going bad. 
to find someone to travel the world with.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]leather, cheese and freshly washed sheets.[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]clowns.
lobsters.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote][b]wiry[/b] | one way to describe kat is wiry. she's always been a lithe child, able to slip into spaces she shouldn't, escape the grasp of someone barely touching her and outrun almost anyone in her family. her father once described her as quicksilver, darting here and there without ever stopping for breath. she's kept that up as she's grown, though now it's her mouth that's joined in. she can talk as fast as she can run. 
[b]honest[/b] | honest to a fault, everything that comes out of her mouth is the truth. she was brought up with strong morals, right was right and wrong was wrong but she's never been able to tell a lie. if she got into trouble when she was a child she didn't hide it. she'd own up to it, dob on her siblings if they tried to blame her for something and even as she's grown up she's kept that trait, some might call it a flaw but she thinks of it as a virtue, no one she loves will ever doubt her word. 

[b]loyal[/b] | her family is her life. at the moment they are the be all and end all that she has to live for. her sisters and her brother are the people she trusts the most, value's their opinions the most and if anyone tries to talk bad about them to her she'll cut them down in a second. it takes her a little longer to build up a loyalty to her friends than the average hufflepuff, just because she knows that sometimes people aren't what they seem, thanks to her parents warning about people trying to be friends with people who had famous names. 
[b]tough[/b] | she can't remember the last time she cried. she hardly cried as a child, her parents like to remind her of that fact every so often. she just carries on, no matter how she's feeling she carries on. she's a firm believer in her problems are her problems and she doesn't need people to bail her out, she can work through things on her own. tears are a weakness she doesn't let herself show. that's not to say she doesn't feel things. she feels things deeply, it's the showing those feelings that's hard for her. 
[b]fiery[/b] | red hair. she was born with the ability to strike fear into the hearts of men with a single glance. okay she's not that bad but she is quick to anger, slow to calm down and her voice can raise three octaves in one word so it's never a quiet anger. 

[b]curious[/b] | she's always wanting to learn things she doesn't know. if someone tells her to stay out of a room she'll try and peek. if someone tells her not to go somewhere she can't help but go. it's like the big red button. she gets this almost itch that's unbearable and before she knows it she's doing what she knows she shouldn't. she loves talking to people and learning about them, knowing all the things that make them tick. 
[b]gossip[/b] | she loves a good bit of gossip. she's not gonna try and hide that fact. she doesn't spread it, because she can't be sure if it's true or not but she loves hearing other peoples perceptions and opinions on other people. 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]england.[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]viktor krum - father - 48 - retired quidditch player.
elena krum - mother - 40 - retired quidditch player.

edrik krum - brother - 20 - quidditch player.
irina krum - sister -  19 - cursebreaker. 
iliana krum - sister - 18 - football player.[/blockquote]
[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]a calico kitten named matjik. [/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]katiya is the youngest of viktor and elena's children. she fits that position in the family well. she was born stubborn, ready and willing to keep up with her siblings and do everything she saw them doing. as a child there was nothing she was afraid to try. she'd climb shelves, she'd follow her siblings up tree's. her mother once joked that if they jumped off a bridge that kat would be right there behind them. it wasn't untrue, she would. her siblings were her people. at least until she was old enough to start forming her own identity and had the chance to start making friends outside her family circle. though, given the choice she'd still hang out with her siblings over anyone else. 

if there was ever a moment in her life that defined her as stubborn, it was when her father tried to put her on the back of a broom. she resisted, strongly. refused to even try it. she wasn't afraid of heights, she wasn't afraid of falling she just didn't want to fly on a broom. much to her parents dismay they were never able to bribe, convince or make her siblings talk her into flying. she was quite happy to watch her siblings fly but she never took much notice while they were at quidditch games. much preferring to draw in a sketchbook or talk to the people that were sitting around them. 

one of the most upsetting things in her life so far was watching her siblings go off one by one to hogwarts. while she still had irina and iliana at home, it wasn't as bad. because there was someone else to talk to, someone else to hang out with but when it was just her in the house she felt a little lost. she'd always had her siblings around and suddenly the house felt empty. it was then that she really got into the books their house was filled with. books about people, the history of her father's home country and to her dismay a lot of books on quidditch, which somehow she should have expected but it never crossed her mind until she sat down to read them. 

soon it would be her turn to join her siblings on the train and she was excited. her siblings had told her all about the school and their houses and she couldn't wait to get there. she wanted to be placed in a house with one of her siblings though, she didn't want to go to ravenclaw or slytherin. while ravenclaw would be okay, she'd be on her own and that wasn't what she wanted. she was glad and a little surprised when she was put into hufflepuff, she'd always thought of herself more as a gryffindor if anything but she wasn't upset by the choice. she was with anna so she was happy. it didn't take her long to start prying into the students in her year and dorm. some accepted it, some didn't like it but she wasn't bothered. she'd never really cared if people liked her or not, if they didn't it was their problem, not hers. 

she spent the next six years learning about magic, learning about people and trying to figure out what she wanted to do when she left the busy halls of hogwarts. she knew she wanted to work with people, to study the way people thought the way they did, if there was more to nature and nurture than people thought, after all it was one of the most fascinating things to her. why people did the things they did. maybe it was because of all the horrible things happening in the world, the attacks on the students leaving hogwarts, the girl who had been killed on the train years before and all the other wrong doings in the wizarding world. why couldn't they figure out how to stay ahead of them, if they knew how they thought. they might have had a chance at stopping things before they started. 

[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]kat didn't really know about the goings on in the world until the attack on the students. she'd always been interested in people but that attack jumpstarted her interest in the minds of dark wizards and the thought process and reasoning for their actions. she was devastated when the students died, angry that it had happened and sorry for the people she knew that lost loved ones. she can't understand why they're doing what they're doing and that bothers her more than anything. the attack on the quidditch match has made her certain she wants to hunt dark wizards down when she leaves school, hunt them to study them and find out why they are the way they are. to see if there's a way to stop future attacks before they happen. to try and help find a way that will make the world an almost safe place to live in again. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]shadow..[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her.[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]27.[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]awst.[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]guess.[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@luke         , @edward         , @sunday          &amp; @calder         .[/blockquote][/div][/div]