
[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt=" " src="https://static.fabrik.io/u3x/a65ad2c76fbb59d7.jpg?auto=format&amp;lossless=1&amp;w=2880&amp;h=5120&amp;fit=max&amp;s=f1c85bfc626526ab5eef7916ae467452" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]charlie darwin weekly[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]char-lee[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Chuck – by her family members and she absolutely hates it whenever non-family calls her by it[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]16.
December 17, 2008.[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Female. she/her/hers[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Half-blood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Homosexual [/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]Fir with phoenix feather, unyielding, 10 ¼ inches
Description: A proud wand that requires mutual respect. It allows for strong, formidable spells that will keep its owner safe in the direst of times. Transfiguration spells and protection charms are favorable specialties of this wand. It has a piece of black marble engraved at the end of its hilt. Made by Nell Ollivander in 2023 and sold to Charlie in June 2025. [/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Elizabeth Wheeland[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Charlie is 5’5”. She has both ears pierced multiple times, and generally dresses just like her playby. Money can buy a lot of things, so she takes advantage of that, so that she can fit in with the ‘crowd’, whatever that may be. Appearances mean everything, after all (according to her mom).[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Ilvermorny: Wampus (Years 1-4)
Hogwarts: Hufflepuff 
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]6th Year
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]n/a[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Snakes and most reptiles, animals (magic and non), being outside, eating healthy, drawing/sketching animals/birds/bugs, doing things on her own, reading comics, divination, palm reading, astrology (and ironically this fits with the family business of calendar making), meditation, lots of natural things[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Having a large family, her middle name (really? Charlie Darwin?), having to keep up the appearance of being a ‘vegan’ in front of her fad freak mother, a deep hatred for puns, being cooped up inside with all seven of her siblings, being dragged around to every sibling’s extracurricular activities, paparazzi, bad reviews of her mother’s movies, having her picture taken[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]To work with animals in some capacity. She doesn’t care if it’s as a vet or magizoologist. 
To not be seen as just another member of her family. She seeks individuality more than being a non-adopted sibling and not having a weekday for a name.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Freshly cut grass, wood chips, wood-burning stoves [/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Being viewed as pretentious and snobby, despite being just a little bit of each. She dislikes having it pointed out.
Being suffocated by her own pet snake.
The irrational fear of being forgotten amongst her family members.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]When it comes to her interests in animals of all sorts and other passions, Charlie really shines the brightest. Like her namesake, she sort of fell into the role of wanting to know anything and everything about the natural world. She is extremely passionate when it comes to telling others about these sorts of things, sometimes coming across as a tad bit aggressive with her almost encyclopedic memory.

To that same affect, she’s unbelievably pretentious in the way that she delivers this knowledge. She has been trying to dial it back as she’s realized it makes her out to being sort of a nature freak and unapproachable, but that’s still a work in progress. More often than not though, she leaves a sour impression with her ramblings and takes other’s responses to her as personal as humanely possible. 

Being compared to her siblings and their multitude of goals and achievements, the real root of her inferiority complex rears its ugly head. While she enjoys all of their company equally, there are times where she certainly feels inadequate and more like an accident than having a real purpose in the family. Her siblings were adopted because they were wanted, and she sort of popped up into the picture happenstance. Charlie unknowingly compensates for this by taking care of animals and learning how she can help them.

Her other interests lay in the more occult, though she reasonably fits in well in the astronomy and divination communities of magic. Like her fanaticism with animals and nature, Charlie can go a little overboard when it comes to palm reading and tarot cards. She’s exceptionally good at it, devoting maybe just a little too much time into it. Overall, she enjoys when others take an interest in her interests, and she has no problem sharing as long as they are willing to learn.
 [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote] Beverly Hills California, USA[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote] April Weekly - mother – actress
August Weekly - father – heir to a magical calendar company

Jeremiah Weekly - grandfather - founder of a magical calendar company

Monday Weekly – adopted sister, 17, Current 7th Year Gryffindor
Tuesday Weekly – adopted brother, 17, Current 7th Year Gryffindor
Wednesday Weekly – adopted sister, 17, Current 7th Year Slytherin
Thursday Weekly – adopted sister, 16, Current 6th Year Ravenclaw
Friday Weekly – adopted sibling, 16, Current 6th Year Gryffindor
Saturday Weekly – adopted brother, 16, Current 6th Year Hufflepuff
Sunday Weekly – adopted brother, 15, Current 5th Year
[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Alfonso, a male reticulated python that unfortunately has to stay home in California[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]The sole, biological child of April and August Weekly, Charlie Darwin was graced with easily the most normal of her family’s names – but not without extreme resentment years later. By the time she was old enough to really comprehend her family’s situation, she knew that she had two older sisters (Monday and Wednesday) and a sister and brother around her age. But they also weren’t like her, because they were all made members of the family after she was born. That didn’t change the fact that they were her siblings, but they were definitely different and had varying degrees of odd quirks that she had trouble coming to terms with as she grew up. Like having a brother that also turned into a werewolf every month, or a sister that had to drink blood. She knew that normal families weren’t like that and that her family certainly wasn’t normal because they had magic and children named after the days of the week. But they were still pretty weird even for magical families.

On top of having a bunch of adopted siblings, there was also the limelight of her mom being an actress. Seeing her on the movie screen or tv was pretty cool while growing up, and at an early age she definitely got confused about why mom was suddenly inside the television. All of this was taken in stride as she got older, understanding that they were all part of the same team and needed to get along. 

Things were good and all was swell, until she was seven and suddenly the family adopted two more kids. Seven year old Charlie was more of a go-getter, one-hundred percent invested in her future career as an animal doctor (as she called it until she learned how to pronounce veterinarian). She also knew how to call out injustices when she saw them, and she grew to resent that more attention was being placed on Saturday and Sunday than her and the rest of her siblings. It mattered more now than it did with Thursday and Friday, because she actually knew how to vocalize her worries.

Digging into her passions and gaining a pet reticulated python for her 9th birthday, Charlie became obsessed with snakes and reptiles, almost forgetting that in two years’ time she would be following Monday and Wednesday off to Ilvermorny to learn magic at school. That sort of thing didn’t necessarily interest her yet. 

Until her sisters came back and told her about magical creatures, and how they were literally everywhere. Then it was a waiting game until she could go to school too. During this time, another boy joined the family, and completed her parents’ obsession with weekday names, becoming Tuesday. Charlie didn’t really know what the extent of this would be like until starting school the following September, and that was where it got really hard for her.

Being the only non-weekday named Weekly kid immediately had her singled out, especially with six of her seven siblings attending Ilvermorny. Why was she called Charlie? Why was she excluded from the family naming scheme? Why did her siblings call her Chuck (which even she didn’t understand, they just did)? Why was she named after Charles Darwin? That was a stupid name. It wasn’t necessarily bullying, more so an endless game of twenty questions that she didn’t really have the answers to. And kids knew who her mom was too. And they had the magical calendars that her dad’s company made. She quickly learned what it meant to be seen as a circus sideshow, and felt like all of this was became her parents had to have their guilty pleasures and adopt seven kids to give them quirky names. She didn’t like being part of a trend, but was forced into it without much say.

The next three years ticked by slowly, and Charlie started to feel like the odd one out in her family. She took part of her mom’s fads, whether that was going vegan or subscribing to whatever the most recent fashion trend was to appease the media and her mom’s publicist. The media liked that the daughter named Charlie Darwin had a pet snake and studied animals in her free time. That ticked all of their famous kid boxes in all the right places.

Her quick fix to getting people to back off? Becoming so engrained in zoology and nature studies that she became a snob in the field. People eventually got tired of her incessant blithering about saving the rainforests (which is important!) and the best methods of rebuilding the still faltering koala populations, that they stopped paying attention to her. She liked this for a while, but then realized that purposely driving people away was different from unknowingly doing so, and when she really wanted others to listen to her, she came across as the pretentious, entitled rich girl who could bother to do what she did because she had the money for it. 
 [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Moving to the UK to attend Hogwarts was a blessing. Even with all of the other Ilvermorny students attending as well, she had a fresh batch of people that she could test herself on. Ones that she could actually try to befriend without sounding like a snob. It also meant escaping her parents, and being able to finally eat whatever healthy food she wanted, instead of just vegan this, vegan that, like she had for the last few years. The downside was having to leave her python behind in California, but that made trips home that much better. Plus, showing people pictures was just as awesome as rolling out with Alfonso draped around her neck.

After spending fifth year at Hogwarts, Charlie expected that the Weekly clan would head home and go back to Ilvermorny. Until the UK became quarantined and they were forced to stay for at least another year. She didn’t dislike it, because there were plenty of interesting things that the British school had that Ilvermorny didn’t. The Hag’s Fever also doesn’t bother her that much because her family has money, and money solves a lot of things. Especially sickness and private hospitals and medication. Her concerns are more with not being able to go home and see her snake.
 [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@colin     [/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]he/him[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]25[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]est[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]I’m too lazy to look at an old app to see, but somewhere.[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@grey     @cordelia     @mina     @lily     @cara     @nottingham     @jimbo     @steve     @blaise     @harper     @renard     @nell     @nessa    [/blockquote][/div][/div]
