
[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;background-color:#B6B6B4;border:4px solid #B6B6B4;border-radius:10px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt="" src="https://data.whicdn.com/images/10108645/original.png" style="max-width:100%;"]
[/div]

hello there, my name is[b] lusitania katherine windsor[/b]&nbsp;but you can call me [b]lusie[/b]. i'm a/an [b]hufflepuff&nbsp;[/b]and [b]15&nbsp;[/b]so that makes me a [b]5th year[/b]&nbsp;at [b]hogwarts[/b]. You could say I'm [b]hard working, patient, &amp; loyal[/b]&nbsp;but I personally think that I am [b]kind, thoughtful &amp; studious[/b]. People say I look a lot like [b]georgie henley[/b], but I don't really see it...

[div align="center"][font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][i][b]lusitania katherine windsor[/b][/i][/font][/font][/div]

[b][i]pronunciation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]l-oos-eh-tan-aye-a kath-er-in wind-sor[/blockquote]
[b][i]nickname:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Lusie only (pronounced Lucy)&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]15[/blockquote]
[b][i]date of birth:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]October 8th 2008[/blockquote]
[b][i]gender &amp; pronouns:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]She her hers[/blockquote]
[b][i]blood status:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]muggleborn[/blockquote]
[b][i]sexuality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]heterosexual&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b][i]schooling:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts - Hufflepuff house

[/blockquote][b][i]occupation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Lusie is considering a job as a healer - but often wonders and questions what she should be doing. She has, in no way, completely made up her mind yet regarding her career.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b][i]wand:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Maple wood, coral core, 10 inches,&nbsp;reasonably springy
[/blockquote]
[b][i]playby:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]georgie henley[/blockquote]
[b][i]appearance:[/i] [/b]
[blockquote]Lusie has dark hair and green eyes, like her playby. She's about 5 foot 5, but likely done growing.[/blockquote][div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personality[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]likes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]tea
cakes
creatures/animals
family
friends
school
learning
fun
fire
travel
privacy[/blockquote]
[b][i]dislikes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]conflict
large bodies of water
natural disasters
muggle weapons
failing
press/being in the public eye
invasions of privacy[/blockquote][b][i]erised:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Lusie wants to meet people who love her for her. She wants to be able to trust those around her and to eventually find The One.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b][i]amortentia:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]roses, baby powder, warm tea with honey, a well tended fire, fresh spring air, lavender[/blockquote]
[b][i]boggart:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Lusie is afraid of drowning. She has never learned how to swim and isn't sure she ever would.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b][i]overall personality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Lusie likes to think of herself as an extroverted-introvert. She is very kind, sweet and outgoing, however, she also doesn't make friends easily and she really treasures her privacy and time spent alone to recuperate from her social activity. She'll happily talk to anyone, she just worries that people who would want to talk to her want to talk to her because of her last name and because of her family rather than who she is as a person. She is slowly coming into her own person and finding her own voice. People who know her say that she reminds them of Susan when she was younger. over the years, Lucy has made some friends that she knows are there for her and not for her last name, and she is extremely loyal to them.

Lusie has always loved travel and loves being in new places. She loves meeting new people and learning about new cultures. As a child, she learned French, German and a touch of Latin as necessary. Lusie wants to learn more languages, but those types of studies have been put on hold while she continues her wizarding education.&nbsp;

Luise isn't much of a risk taker and values safety and security over most others. She's a very cautious person and doesn't ever want to risk injury or pain in the emotional or physical sense, which sometimes gets in the way of her making deep, personal relationships. However, she's still the first one to greet a new person when they enter a room or are introduced to her. She tries to make everyone around her feel comfortable regardless of whether or not she likes the person or is friends with them.[/blockquote][div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personal history[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]mother:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Prewitt, Hannah, 43, in hiding, lawyer, muggle[/blockquote][b][i]father:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]windsor, william henry, prince, 4th in line for the throne, deceased, muggle
[/blockquote][b][i]siblings:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]William Peter - 21
Susan Victoria - 18&nbsp;
Edmund Michael - 17[/blockquote][b][i]pets:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Long Eared Owl named Charlie
[/blockquote]
[b][i]history:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Lusie Windsor was born in London England on a cold, Autumn evening in October of 2009. Lusie was the youngest of 4 children and always felt like the youngest. She was the baby of the family even now that she was growing up and getting older, her family still sees her as the baby. Lusie was born into the English Royal family and knew nothing of the wizarding world until her oldest brother, William, and her sister, Susan went off to Hogwarts and were sorted into Gryffindor and Ravenclaw house respectively. Lusie was still fairly young at the time and didn't entirely understand it all, not to mention that she was still dealing with the death of her father, which was just as hard for her to come to terms with.&nbsp;

Lusie grew up with her siblings and parents in a modestly sized house in the English countryside, away from the city and away from the palace - away from being royalty. Their mother insisted that she didn't want the children to grow up spoiled or feeling too entitled. And while none of them ever wanted for anything, Lusie felt like she had grown up similarly to most of her classmates. She was made to help around the house, help cook meals and always had to go to bed on time no matter how much she'd beg for "just 5 more minutes." Growing up, Lusie loved her siblings and saw all of them as role models for how to act and behave. William was always so composed and put together, Susan was so sweet and smart, and Edmund was adventurous and fun-loving. She took little cues and traits from all of them and put them together in her own way to make the person that she was. Lusie always felt she was closest with Susan and Edmund, simply due to the fact that they were slightly closer to her in age.&nbsp;

One year, we were staying at the palace for a big party my grandparents (the king and queen) were throwing. I had always thought the parties, fancy dresses, hair styles, and the make-up were a bit frivolous, but this one seemed different. After we were ready to go my dad said he had something he needed to take care of and would meet us there. We arrived at the party and sat down for dinner. It was always my dad's job to give some sort of speech before dinner and so we looked for him. He wasn't there yet. My grandma sent someone to look for him. When the guard came back his face was pale. The next few hours were a blur. My mom rushed me and my siblings into a different section of the palace and told us not to leave the room. Then she left. I didn't even find out until the next day that my father had been assassinated. 

The palace put the whole royal family into protective custody for a few weeks while they figured everything out. We were moved to a summer home on the coast. That was when things started to get strange. Again, being of muggle decent, no one expected William to have magical powers, or Susan, or Edmund, or even little baby Lusie. But they all did, 4 muggles borns in the same family.&nbsp;

Lusie was the last to go to Hogwarts but eventually she did make it. Edmund had gone two years ahead of her and had been sorted into Slytherin house. Lusie, now having a siblings in 3/4 houses wasn't sure if she'd end up following one of her siblings, or if she'd end up on her own, and sure enough, there seemed to be room enough in Hufflepuff house for the young princess. Lusie rarely thought of herself as a princess, however, it was sometimes really hard to forget, especially since every student in the castle knew her last name.&nbsp;

Lusie had always been a studious girl and loved her tutoring sessions with their private tutor as a girl. She soon realized that she loved most of her classes in the same way that she loved her tutoring lessons. She excelled mostly in the more academic classes, such as astronomy, arithmancy and history of magic. During her 3rd year, muggle borns began being attacked, which, obviously, sparked a huge fear in the rest of the muggle students, but particularly in those tied so closely to to royal family. Lusie barely wanted to leave her common room, however, she knew she was safe in the castle, or, at least, she wanted to believe that she was. At the end of her 3rd year, a group of 7th year students were kidnapped and taken by a group of wizards and witches who wanted purebloods to regain control over the wizarding world. Lusie spent that summer in her muggle disguise where she felt the most safe. At least she wasn't alone in her fears since Susan and Edmund would be going back to school with her next year.

In her 4th year, it was announced that Hogwarts would be hosting the Tri-Wizard Tournament and two other schools would be joining them at the castle to partake in the events. Lusie, being someone who loved learning about other cultures and religions was happy to welcome the guests and get to know them, however, her being younger than them didn't grant her much of an opportunity. The year seemed family calm at Hogwarts, which, Lusie felt, was odd given the events of the previous year. The tournament went on with no interruptions and the Hogwarts Champion, Anna Weasley came out the victor! What great fun! As the other schools departed and the year began to whined to a close, the brunette couldn't help but think that it was too good to be true. And indeed it was, for just hours later they school got news that both the ship and the carriage had been attacked on their journeys back to their home countries and a majority of the students and professors on-board had been killed. A very small handful had survived but were in critical condition. Lusie, an emotional person, took the news pretty hard.

Now, as the summer months ticked on, Lusie spent the time with her family who still lived at home getting ready to return to the castle for her 5th year at Hogwarts. This year to come would be Edmunds' last year and then Lusie would find herself the last remaining member of the Windsor family at the magical school for wizards and witches. She felt the anxiety and weight of that fall on her, but at least she had one more year with her brother before that happened. And, hopefully, even with the addition of the American students, the year would come and go without too much fuss.&nbsp;[/blockquote][div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]alias[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]name:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Ali[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]21[/blockquote][b][i]time zone:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]PST[/blockquote]
[b][i]reference:[/i][/b]
[blockquote][img src="//storage.proboards.com/5647952/images/4Y59kkqjrlv5qH4AMIaH.gif" class="smile" alt="<3" style="max-width:100%;"][/blockquote]
[b][i]other characters:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]oh so many, Rosie, Sav, Riley, Angie, Cray, Luke, Bern, Fiona, Brooke, Lucy&nbsp;[/blockquote][/div][/div]