[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt="" src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/sarcasticmoth/proboards-templates/main/pics/diana/diana_app_header.jpg" style="max-width:100%;"]
[/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]diana eoina bainbridge[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]dye-ana[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]none really, her sisters may call her dee[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]nineteen
07 June, 2006[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]female
she/her/hers[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]half-blood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]bisexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]10 inches
red oak
dragon heartstring[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]christina perri[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Diana is a Metamorphmagus, which gives her the ability to change her appearance at will. However, on a typical day, she stands about five foot eight inches or nine inches if she isn’t slouching. She has naturally dark eyes and dark hair, though she sometimes has blonde hair to match her sister and siblings. The other distinction between herself and her fraternal twin is she has many tattoos all over her body, mainly her arms but a few on her back and chest. Her mood tends to affect her abilities at times.[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling &amp; status

[/b][blockquote]Hogwarts - Ravenclaw
Graduate - 2024[/blockquote][b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Curse Specialist[/blockquote][div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Dark arts
History
Reading
Her twin
Quidditch
Experimenting, tinkering
[/blockquote][b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Cooking
Not knowing [i]why[/i]
Failing
People in her bubble
Asking for help
[/blockquote][b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Being born a twin always had its advantages. Diana was never alone. She always had a friend and someone to talk to. Despite being the older twin, she was not the bossy one of the duo and preferred to stand in the background and quietly observe. However, this didn’t always translate into ‘good behavior’ by any means. Diana was always the type to wander off in public because she saw something interesting and much to her poor parents' chagrin, especially her Muggle father if they were ever in a Wizarding area such as Diagon Alley. To add to their stress, Diana would often change her appearance as a child because she thought it was fun and exciting, and she was curious to see how extensive this ability was. However, it wasn’t helpful to find a kid that had wandered off in a crowd because they were watching the magical mechanisms in a shop window and wondering how they worked. Despite this, it was clear from a very young age that Diana was very intelligent and loved to learn, and it came relatively easy to her as well.

Whether it was reading or testing the limits of her Metamorphmagus ability, she would always persist until she either absolutely couldn’t figure it out, or she finally did. This determination always stuck with her, like a hidden drive and ambition that one typically saw from Type A personalities rather than someone more introverted. As Diana learned more in her school years at Hogwarts, she would use this determination to practice different spells (especially Charms) or Transfiguration. It reminded her of her own abilities. It wasn’t a surprise to sometimes find Diana in the Hospital wing. Not with any serious injuries, but mainly some side effects of a modified potion that had backfired. Or how she had modified a charm to have a jinx effect, but in the end, she’d lost her eyebrows and not even being a Metamorphmagus could return them. The only time Diana wasn’t getting in relative trouble was when she was reading, mainly History of Magic and history of anything. If one needed a person for a trivia competition—Diana was the person. Despite her intellect, she might forget something basic in Care of Magical Creatures. Still, she could tell you precisely when the first Peruvian Viperooth was discovered because she’d read it offhand in some book.

It was a strange combination and didn’t always translate to the best grades despite her evident ability. And entering a classroom, Diana could easily be found sitting in the back. Something was unnerving about knowing people were sitting behind you and their eyes staring into the back of your head—she wasn’t a fan of crowds or talking to many people at once. It was exhausting, and she preferred her alone time or time with her siblings if she had to choose. Diana could also be seen as relatively calm unless she was excited about some new (albeit small) jinx she had created, and it takes a lot to anger her to the point of reaction. But people themselves typically didn’t elicit this reaction. Diana likes to know how something works, but how it [i]completely[/i] works, and she has been brought to the point of frustration several times in her life.

Her goal in life is to hopefully contribute something helpful to the Wizarding World—create a new charm or potion that can help many people, and her name would be attached to that. She has a different perspective on magic and its uses, in her mind it is all just about the tools and that studying the Dark Arts as the students in Durmstrang did could produce useful results. Naturally this was pushed back, one did not study the Dark Arts for any reason. But Diana would argue that magic was just a tool, the intent was up to the user.  With technology making its debut, she hopes that perhaps that can be an option as a venue to create something. In the meantime, her good-natured and curious disposition has been replaced with that of someone almost emotionless and cold. Sarcastic and distant as well. With Diana’s sixth year's events weighing on her, she has coped by pushing those closest away from herself. Including her twin and her sisters. She tells herself that she is protecting them and herself in the process, although with Kinsey’s ability, she has had to work toward putting walls up, if only to hide her secrets from her. The change isn’t a subtle one, even with her already quieter nature. The only happiness she finds anymore is when she gets her hands on chocolate, her favorite sweet treat along with coffee.
[/blockquote][div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Godric's Hollow, England[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Raisa Bainbridge, mother, Daily Prophet Reporter
Eoin Bainbridge, father, muggle
Dustin Bainbridge, older brother, Quidditch Player
@cara   , twin, Author &amp; Fortescue's Ice Cream Parlor Cashier
@kinsey   , younger sister, Merlin's Mystical Museum of Magic Guide
@penelope   , younger sister, 7th year Hufflepuff
@peytonbainbridge   , younger sister, 7th year Hufflepuff
Persephone Bainbridge, younger sister, 7th year Hufflepuff[/blockquote][b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote][b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Diana was born the older twin (fraternal) in a family that already had a boy. But soon, the Bainbridge family would grow to seven children. After Diana and Cara, Kinsey was born and followed by [i]triplets[/i]. Despite being older, it was clear that Cara had the more dominant personality. Despite this, they were the best of friends—they were two halves of a whole after all, and Diana wasn’t bothered by the differences in their personalities. The siblings all got along well, even with Kinsey ability being discovered at a young age. It was tricky when the children were younger as emotions would run high in different situations, but they grew older and began to understand it as best they could. However, she wasn’t the only Bainbridge with an ability. Diana is a Metamorphmagus which gives her the ability to alter her appearance at will, while Kinsey and the triplets also had their abilities. 

Aside from that, their childhood was relatively normal, and she never felt alone with the commotion of so many siblings around. And she would mostly read and tinker with things, her magical ability showing up randomly as a child as she tried to explain [i]how[/i] a book flew across the room without provocation. Her older brother was very much into Quidditch and would make his sisters join him, and while Diana enjoyed it, she didn’t enjoy it to the extent that her brother did. Preferring to watch while sitting alongside Cara. It was common during her younger years to find Diana in her mother or father’s offices, reading whatever book she managed to climb and reach on the bookshelf or magical item from her mother’s office to inspect. If not that, she’d wander off in public because she saw something interesting and couldn’t stop her curiosity from driving her. 

Finally, her older brother entered Hogwarts, and she was eager to also attend. But her and Cara’s letters wouldn’t arrive for a whole year, and naturally, she was excited about this. The twins were sorted into Ravenclaw, which was no surprise for Diana. Her first five years at Hogwarts felt normal. She went to class, would get caught not paying attention and trying different spells instead of the one they were supposed to be practicing on the unassuming item in Transfiguration, or she’d test other potion ingredients to the potion at hand based on what she had read about their effects. Her teachers were frustrated. She was brilliant but seemed driven to modify anything should to create a new result. As a result, her grades on paper might not have been the highest, but that didn’t dissuade Diana either by any means. 

However, sixth year brought a very different experience. A student had been found dead on the train by the oldest Potter boy and had dampened the usually excitable mood of the first day of school and the initial train ride to Hogwarts. When another student was found dead, it became clear there was some muggle connection, and Diana herself feared for her family. All of them were enrolled at Hogwarts at this point, and their father was a muggle. Did that make them a target? She focused on what she could control, and that was the ordinary everyday things about school. But later in the school year, she encountered a fellow student, one that was a year older than her, but she had seen her around—Elaine. While what transpired that night is not something that Diana had ever told anyone or explained in any detail, she almost doesn’t quite believe it happened. An unbreakable vow—and one that required her absolute loyalty to Elaine, which meant an inherent commitment to her cause. 

It was a horrifying experience, and even worse because she couldn’t share what was bothering her to anyone—not even her partner in crime, her twin. There was a clear change and shift in her personality after this, but she brushed it off to the stress of the year's events. Ethan attacked and then later killed by Elaine and the mercenaries running through the school and kidnapping students who were later rescued. It was stressful, as it might have been on any sixteen-year-old who had lived a carefree life up until that point. But, Diana could never talk about the actual source of her stress—it became easier to begin to shut herself off slowly and especially avoid her younger sister as it wasn’t something she could hide in terms of intent. It was difficult. She cared about her sister but had to keep her physical distance which caused a sort of rift. 

Then seventh year began, and Diana still had no idea how to get out of her situation, but at least the school and everyone seemed to be distracted by the Triwizard tournament, and that was everyone’s focus. Diana could still blame the trauma of the past year on her current behavior, not that the flimsy explanation helped anyone. Though she had to admit she did feel a tiny bit of relief when one of the Purifiers was killed by an Auror. But that was quickly gone when after the tournament when an explosion killed many Durmstrang and Beauxbatons students. Soon after that, [i]the[/i] Harry Potter was announced to be missing. It was a lot, and after they graduated, there was hardly time to celebrate as the unbreakable vow she had taken was called upon. Diana herself just took off, and while her family had no idea where she was with only a note left behind, indicating she was alive and well but with no explanation. During that time, she regrouped with Elaine and her group—the Purifiers. Her Metamorphmagus ability was helpful to them as well as her intellect. 

Diana entered the world of the Dark Arts. And while Diana had studied them during her time at school out of purely an academic angle, she never thought she would be made to use them or create new spells and such things in her life. The thing was, she had a knack for it, and she just told herself it was for that same academic purpose she had pursued in school and not for what it was actually for. During this time, she became acquainted with a Purifier master Legilimens and Occlumens, who spent the next few months training Diana under a, particularly grueling schedule to train her mind. Close it off. They knew about Kinsey's ability, and Diana needed a way to put up an absolute wall against it. And so she trained, and she learned to close it all off, everything. The further shift in her personality made her cold and distant, and soon after Harry Potter was assumed dead, she reentered the world but did not immediately contact her family in any way. All that time away and all that training had helped her push away what she felt, or at least most of it, so life was manageable. 

Especially since there was work to be done. Diana continued her black market work and activities for the Purifiers. It was easy since she could change her appearance. Dragons were used to attack Hogsmeade village while she joined in the fall of Azkaban. Her appearance changed, of course. The item they were after was destroyed, and Diana even had to admit she was upset since it would have been a valuable item to just inspect and learn about. Such ancient magic, it pulled at her curiosity. However, with the quarantine afterward in the UK due to Hag’s Fever, it became increasingly difficult to avoid bumping into people she knew from school or even her sisters and brother. Still, she had closed herself off by that point, and it didn’t feel as difficult. Then the news reached the Wizarding World that Elaine Dupree had been killed. This meant the end to the Purifiers, right? An end to the unbreakable vow? Was Diana free? 

Nope. Elaine wasn’t dead, and then the explosion during the Quidditch final occurred, which kills Minister Granger and many others in the process. Even Diana felt that, fortunately, her family was safe, but he forced herself not to think about it—not to feel it. She couldn’t. Now that the quarantine has lifted, Diana can travel and work more freely wherever she pleases. Although the main hot topic is the emergence of an island which new and unknown magic. This intrigued Diana. She was eager to explore the new and unknown and wondered what the plans were for the island, or at least before the Ministry controlled its borders. This compounded with the rumors that Harry Potter was alive and had returned…well, 2026 was already beginning to be an interesting year, and the month had only just begun. [/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]vanessa[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]jedi master[/blockquote]
[/div][/div]