[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://missbish.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/how-to-find-balance-in-life-with-model-and-health-activist-alexis-ren-5-810x800-888x590.jpg" alt=" "][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]cara june bainbridge[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]car-uh[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]n/a[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]19
June 7th, 2006[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Female. She/Her/Hers[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Hhalf-blood.[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Bisexual.[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]7 ½ inches, red oak, kelpie hair, rigid.[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Alexis Ren.[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote] 5’9”. Dark blonde hair, brown eyes. Two piercings on each ear. Likes wearing relaxed, yet fashionable clothing when out of school uniform.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts. Ravenclaw.
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduated 2024
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Cashier at Fortescue’s Ice Cream Parlor. Author.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Reading, going for jogs and fitness in general, getting her way (by telling others what to do, mostly her siblings), writing short stories, her twin, light music, rigid schedules and deadlines, personal space, playing the ukulele.[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Being talked back to, failing, not understanding something, losing sleep, snoring, being sick, rest of the family and their attitudes towards her (when they don’t listen to her, etc.), loud noises/distractions, afraid of heights.[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]To complete her book and get published.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Baked bread, damp cellars, pumpkin.[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Failing at everything, losing Diana.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Cara likes order, rigidness, and everything in working order. Life obviously decided to have a fun time and throw four more siblings after her and her twin, and that was both a blessing and a curse. By being granted younger siblings, that meant she could coerce and tell them what to do, and they would mostly listen to her. This characteristic carried over into school, and now it has become something of an enigma. She prefers getting her way as much as possible, though will not use it for purposes beyond her moral reasoning. Typically that means ordering her younger siblings around, getting other students to be quiet, and overall being the typical bossy smart girl who thinks she is right, and you are wrong.
 
She is extremely critical of other’s intelligence, as well as her own abilities as a witch. Failure isn’t an option in her mind, and she has to work extremely hard sometimes to achieve that level of perfection in every aspect of her life. Having control over things is her way of making sure she isn’t slipping into complacency. This coincides with her bossy nature, and isn’t afraid to mince words if she thinks one of her siblings or friends isn’t living up to their aspirations, especially if she knows that they are capable of doing it on their own. Her self-criticism, while healthy in some doses, can end with her reaching some extremely high levels of stress. She doesn’t deal well under stress and can easily blow a fuse over this, thus achieving a full on meltdown. While like this, her own advice would probably suit her well.

Not a state that Cara reaches often, but she can be extremely helpful and calm around others if they have the will to learn. It’s even better if she manages to “persuade” the other person to let her teach them. Since teaching takes time and patience, she’s more likely to be like this over her normal critical self, since she understands that not everyone gets things immediately. She’s not a horrible person deep down inside, as much as it can seem like that sometimes, so there are moments where this comes through. Friends and acquaintances are more likely to see this side of her more than her family, since they’ve lost that privilege (in her mind). Her twin is the only one that can break down the hard outer-shell that is formed by her high and mighty personality and bring her back to this level. This side of her is more prevalent after a huge meltdown or if a big assignment is recently off her back. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Godric’s Hollow, England[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Raisa Bainbridge, 44, daily prophet reporter
Eoin Bainbridge, 45, muggle
Dustin Bainbridge, 20-22, Professional Quidditch player
Diana Bainbridge, 19, twin
@kinsey        , guide at Merlin’s Mystical Museum of Magic
@peytonbainbridge     , 7th Year Hufflepuff
@penelope        , 7th Year Hufflepuff
Persephone Bainbridge, 7th Year Hufflepuff[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]n/a[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote] Being the second (or third depending on who you ask) child born to the Bainbridge family, Cara quickly showed that she was the alpha sister. It was hard to enact superiority over her brother or her twin, but the next four sisters were much more influential at a young age, and they were perfect to boss around. She was the oldest of them after all. Cara enjoyed having a partner in crime in her twin; while they got along the best out of all of the rest of the siblings, it was nice to know that she had someone getting her back at all times no matter what.
 
Aside from cementing her role in the family as early as possible, Cara enjoyed embracing her father’s muggle world. A deviation from the hustle and bustle of the magical world, being able to fit in with the rest of humanity was (and still is) fun. Understanding the differences between magical and non-magical folk only deepened her interests in finding common ground between the two, even at a young age. Of course, going to Hogwarts at the age of 11 with her sister meant that she had to re-learn that not every kid was like her family. Things like movies and computers didn’t matter to them as much as say, blood purity or the amount of spells one knew did. Cara had a hard time understanding this at first, but soon pushed it to the side as her studies took precedent. Ravenclaw was meant for excelling in school, and having the competition of her housemates was more than enough to distract her from silly muggle things. That was for home, and magic was for school.

Studying at Hogwarts was an itch that she didn’t even know she had. Dustin was a year ahead, and had glorified it. Rather, he had talked non-stop about Quidditch, which Cara was disappointed to find was not a class she could take, and actually all about flying around in the air. That didn’t exactly settle too well with her, and the uncertainty of falling off a broom was too much for her to handle. Instead, she found that lounging around in the library where she could read and write at her own pace was much more to her liking. Not every subject was an instant click for her though, but learning how to properly study and teach herself how to do work and learn spells all became part of her work ethic, and from there she started to excel in as much as she could.
 
Over the next few years, she also developed an affinity for playing the ukulele. Having wandered around the corridors one day after getting out of class early one day, Cara found herself in one of the music rooms, and in it, a number of different instruments. The ukulele in there spoke out to her the most, and it was quickly in her hands. Something about the small size of it and the sounds that it created intrigued her. Taking lessons from one of the professors, she perfected it, as her nature dictated, and she quickly had her own purchased once she had saved up enough allowance money. It meant going without her weekly candy at Honeydukes on Hogsmeade weekends, but she could do without that if it meant playing music.

Sixth year brought some untasteful events though. Apparently some believed blood status was more important than one’s education, and muggleborn students started getting killed. It was disturbing that someone, a student to boot, could get away with murder so easily, or even have the ability to want to do that in the first place. She understood that accidents happen with magic, and sometimes people died, but offing students based on their blood status was ludicrous. To make it worse, they were all her housemates. There was so much potential taken away by one person. In her mind, it wasn’t fair. There were plenty of obnoxious Gryffindors or lazy Hufflepuffs that could have gone. The first death hit her hard, but each consecutive one and then the subsequent kidnappings left less of an impact. Normalizing it probably wasn’t a smart thing to do, and instead she focused on school work, writing, and playing the ukulele. It all had to stop eventually.

The seventh and final year brought on another new surprise: the Triwizard Tournament. Cara debated for a long time on whether or not she wanted to enter, and eventually decided against it for various reasons. One was that she wanted to focus more on her studies, seeing as this was her last year and all, and that took precedent over everything else. The tournament would interfere with those plans, and thus was deemed not as important to her. Still, she understood the general premise of it, and after the previous school year, bringing together two other schools to form stronger magical bonds seemed like a good idea. If only the Hogwarts champion had been someone other than a Gryffindor though, then maybe they would be in first place right now. Like a Ravenclaw, for example.
 
Upon graduation, Cara immediately set about to write a book she had been planning over the last few months of school. She gave herself until the following Christmas holidays to make progress on it, at which point she would reevaluate whether or not she could make a life out of writing. Failing with this goal, she scrapped her entire story and decided to get a part-time job at Fortescue’s Ice Cream Parlour for the time being, so that she can make money and work on her book.   
[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Hag’s Fever was a pain to deal with while at the ice cream shop. Cara has started to grow increasingly frustrated with peoples’ inability to keep themselves at a distance or clean up after themselves. As for the explosion at the Quidditch match, she was happy that her brother’s team wasn’t in the finals this year.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@colin        [/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]he/him[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]26[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]EST[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]Support[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote][a href="https://alohomorax0.proboards.com/thread/5759"]Link To Plotter[/a] [/blockquote][/div][/div]
