[div align="center"][font size="1"][B]TW/CW:[/B] Depression, self-harm (cutting), child loss, drowning, mentions of blood[/div]
[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img]https://66.media.tumblr.com/b7caf269ba35dc43f703a0b85f127569/tumblr_pf95nfB7Hk1uijsn1o1_540.gif[/img][/div]

hello there, my name is [b] Tamatha Berg[/b] but you can call me [b]Tammy[/b]. i'm a/an [b]adult[/b] and [b]27[/b] so that makes me a [b]graduate[/b] of [b] Ilvermorny[/b]. You could say I'm [b]ambitious, cunning, and resourceful,[/b] but I personally think that I am [b]blunt, protective, and self-critical[/b]. People say I look a lot like [b]Brie Larson[/b], but I don't really see it...

[div align="center"][font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][i][b]Tamatha Josée Berg[/b][/i][/font][/font][/div]

[b][i]pronunciation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]/ˈtæmɪθə ʒoˈze  ˈbɛərɡ/[/blockquote]
[b][i]nickname:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Tammy, Tam[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]27[/blockquote]
[b][i]date of birth:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]January 6, 1997[/blockquote]
[b][i]gender & pronouns:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Cisgender female; she/her pronouns[/blockquote]
[b][i]blood status:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Half-blood (Veela mother)[/blockquote]
[b][i]sexuality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Heterosexual[/blockquote]
[b][i]schooling:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Beauxbatons (2008-2012)
Ilvermorny - Wampus House (2012-2015)
[/blockquote]
[b][i]occupation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Tamatha works as a News Coordinator for the British and Irish Quidditch League.[/blockquote]
[b][i]wand:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]11 ¼ inches, poplar, Veela hair core, reasonably supple[/blockquote]
[b][i]playby:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Brie Larson[/blockquote]
[b][i]appearance:[/i] [/b]
[blockquote]Tammy is 5’7” in height and of a slim to average build. She has fair skin, which isn’t as tanned as her play-by, and wavy dirty blonde hair that is just past shoulder length. Her eyes are brown, and her jaw is square in shape.

Tammy’s earlobes are pierced once on each side, and, while she has no tattoos, she has considered getting her siblings’ names tattooed somewhere. She also has a few small scars from injuries here and there, but nothing too noticeable.

Although she’s a half-Veela raised by a model mother, Tamatha’s wardrobe has become less and less formal over the years. She still enjoys looking nice and certainly never looks like a slob, but Tamatha is more likely to be found wearing Muggle clothing than dress robes when not at work and having to maintain an air of professionalism.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personality[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]likes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Writing; poutine; her family (even if she hasn't always shown it); being outdoors; wintertime; morning jogs; white wine; butter tarts; neat handwriting; flirting[/blockquote]
[b][i]dislikes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Swimming pools, lakes, and similar bodies of water; red wine; unreasonable deadlines; illegible notes; men who don't understand the word "no"; broken fingernails; summertime; hard liquor; cigarette smoke; being cooped up inside[/blockquote]
[b][i]erised:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Tamatha's main goal is to repair her broken relationship with her younger sister and to see Cameron happy in life.[/blockquote]
[b][i]amortentia:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Maple syrup, apple pie, and black coffee[/blockquote]
[b][i]boggart:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Following the accidental drowning of their baby brother, Tamatha most fears the death of her younger sister, Cameron.[/blockquote]
[b][i]overall personality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]In her younger years, Tammy was self-centered and even rude, and she relished the attention that she received from others. As time passed and her outlook began to change, her personality did, too. From her teenage years, Tamatha learned what it meant to care for other people. If anything, Tamatha has matured enough to reflect upon how she used to behave and feels guilty for the way she once was. She genuinely wants to improve herself, but she is her own worst critic at times, giving in to the voice in her head that points out everything she’s done wrong.

If one were to look at Tamatha now, the woman they would see tries to portray herself as having it all together—the textbook example of a "Type A" personality. Really, though, Tamatha is merely  a perfectionist, which carries over into her work life, and capable of compartmentalizing long enough to get her work done. She wants to do the best she can, and work sometimes feels like the only thing in which she has found true success.

That isn't to say that Tamatha hasn't found success in other areas of her life. She has—namely, with men—because of her Veela charm. The excitement of getting anyone she wanted has worn off, in her mind, though, and she's started to think about finding someone with whom she can settle down.

Hampering Tamatha's attempts to "better" herself is the fact that she has never been an outwardly emotional person, for the most part. She tends to internalize how she feels even when she shouldn’t, until the point at which her feelings come out as being harsher than she intends. She's trying to do better in that department, however, especially now that her sister is living with her.

In truth, she would lay down her life for her family, not that she wants such an occasion to arise. Although she wouldn't admit to it, she's terrified of losing her parents or Cameron. Although Tamatha is aware that that might make her look like a stick in the mud to her teenage sister, she is determined to keep her safe while she's in her care. Especially after everything they've been through, the last thing she wants is to fail her, too.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personal history[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]mother:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Ines Berg (née Caron), 49, model, Veela[/blockquote]
[b][i]father:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Arthur Berg, 53, businessman, half-blood wizard[/blockquote]
[b][i]siblings:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Cameron Daya Berg, 17, Pukwudgie/Ravenclaw student, half-Veela witch
Arthur Berg, Jr., 2020-2022, half-Veela wizard[/blockquote]
[b][i]pets:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]
[b][i]history:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Born in Bourges, France, Tamatha Berg spent most of her childhood as an only child. Besides her half-Veela blood, she was a precocious child and outgoing, always eager to meet new people and to explore the world around her. Her parents doted on her, to the point—some would say—of spoiling their little girl, who almost exclusively went by “Tammy”. Her youngest days were spent playing outside and running errands alongside her mother, who would scold her for getting her dresses dirty but never hold it against her daughter for long.
 
As Tammy grew, her focus turned from playing to school. She knew that she would attend Beauxbatons, and she looked forward to it. Fleur Delacour, who had since become distinguished in her native France, was also part-Veela—as Tammy understood that she was—and so she hoped that she would one day become so honored, too.
 
Before she could ever set foot at Beauxbatons, however, her parents gave her a sister. The baby, whom they named Cameron, took away the Bergs’ attention from their older daughter, and—from the beginning—Tammy resented her younger sister. Too old to treat Cameron as a doll and too young to watch her, Tammy kept her distance. That distance was increased once Tammy then went off to school.
 
Tammy's time at Beauxbatons was exactly as she had imagined it. The school itself was beautiful beyond anything she had ever seen before, and getting to learn magic for herself was a thrill. She was a strong student, and she made fast friends with her classmates from the start. Popular and pretty (if not downright entrancing because of her Veela blood), Tammy loved school and was always more reluctant to return home. Her toddler sister made it difficult to have friends around, and spending time with any of her crushes was out of the question without risking embarrassment. 
 
When she learned that she would be leaving Beauxbatons at the end of her fourth year, Tamatha balked. Boys were starting to notice her as something more than a friend, and she was just beginning to see the benefits of it. She couldn’t leave her school, she protested, or France, but her parents had other ideas in uprooting the family to her father’s former home in Canada so that they could care for his ill mother.
 
To say that Tammy hated moving to Quebec would be an understatement. She loathed her first weeks there and blamed her parents for cutting her off from everyone and everything that she had ever known. In essence, she felt, they had ruined her life by relocating. Reluctantly, though, she agreed to give Canada a chance, if only for the sake of her dying grandmother.
 
By the time that she was preparing to start her fifth year of schooling at Ilvermorny, Tammy felt some sadness to leave Canada for the United States. No, Canada wasn’t like anything she had known in France (nor could she understand the Canadians’ horrendous accents half the time), but it was suddenly familiar enough. At least Quebec was Francophone; Massachusetts was in [i]America[/i], and school wouldn’t be the same without her friends from Beauxbatons. The one bright side, she noted, was that there would be boys at Ilvermorny, and she would be the mysterious new girl. That would do.
 
When she first arrived at Ilvermorny and was Sorted into Wampus House, Tammy played into that role as planned, and it was easy enough for her. She didn’t have to try too hard to get boys, since she knew they would be drawn to her, regardless. Tammy didn’t care, either, if she made other girls jealous, since she couldn’t exactly help her Veela charm. She tried to do her best in school, but she found it even more difficult to focus once her grandmother died. The woman had been the reason why she hadn’t just taken a broom and attempted to fly back to France and had actually learned to [i]like[/I] life in Canada.
 
Accepting Canada as her home became even easier once Tammy saw what it was like in winter. It became brutally cold, sure, but it looked like a snow globe. She even tried her hand at skating, although she fell more than she glided across the ice with the grace she expected. She grew to appreciate maple syrup and poutine, too, in time, even though the thought of fries smothered in gravy and cheese curds made her stomach churn initially.

As Tammy adapted to her new life, she tried to keep a more open mind. She put effort into her schoolwork again and made friends who valued her as a person beyond her attractiveness as a half-Veela. She was brutally honest at times and occasionally a little mean because of that, but they knew that that was how she was and accepted her despite her flaws.

It was because of the friends she made at Ilvermorny that she chose to remain in Canada with her parents and younger sister upon her graduation. Rarely, either, had she spent quality time with them, and especially not Cameron. Her little sister had grown up as she had been figuring out her own adolescence, and the baby who had once annoyed her with her cries had become a little girl who had her own life and friends beyond needing their parents’ attention at every waking moment.

Directly out of school, Tammy took her first job as an intern with the local magical newspaper. It wasn't too exciting, but it gave her some spending money and a career path if she chose to follow it. The most exciting stories Tammy covered were Quidditch and Quodpot scores when the sports’ respective seasons became heated, or maybe that of a warlock who had misused magic in Manitoba, but she stuck with it through the most monotonous workdays in the hope that it would pay off eventually. She kept at that for a few years, and, by the time that Cameron was ready to go to Ilvermorny, she had been promoted to a staff reporter.

About a year later, Tammy learned that she would be an older sister for the second time. Although she was surprised that her mother had gotten pregnant again after so many years, Tamatha was thrilled for her parents. She wasn't sure how Cameron would take being the middle child as an adolescent, but she hoped that her younger sister would have a better relationship with the unborn child than she had had with her.

Learning that her mother had given birth to a healthy baby boy was wonderful news, and Arthur, Jr., was the cutest thing Tamatha had ever seen. Being that she was so much older than her younger brother, she loved him almost as though he was her own child, always eager to take care of him when she wasn't working. There were times when she was mistaken for his mother while in public, given their age difference, but she didn't mind. The little Arthur seemed to be the missing link that their family needed, after so long.

That was, at least, until his death at the age of two. Tamatha’s recollection of the day her younger brother died is that it began like any other. She had had a piece to write and, secure in the knowledge that Cameron was meant to be watching him, had left to finish her work before its deadline. The sudden screams coming from elsewhere in the family home had sent her running, but it was already too late. Arthur, Jr., had slipped into the swimming pool while he was unsupervised and drowned.

Tamatha blamed herself for her brother’s tragic death. She shouldn't have trusted Cameron to watch him, she told herself. She shouldn't have gone and finished her work until she knew that their parents were there to keep an eye on him. Everything that she could have done to save the poor baby's life filled her head, and every step she took past the swimming pool filled her with a grief and an anger that she couldn't describe.

She knew that she needed to leave before the tragedy consumed her. Her first thought was New York City—close, but not so far away. Still, Tamatha realized that the competition for jobs there would be unlike anything she had experienced. France was her next choice and the one with which she was most comfortable, truly. Although she had lost touch with many of her classmates from Beauxbatons, she reached out to them for any leads that she could.

After a few weeks, Tamatha found one, although not where she had planned. The British and Irish Quidditch League needed a news coordinator, and she had enough experience that she decided to send her CV via owl the day after she learned of the opportunity.

To her shock, she got the job. Tammy left Canada a short time later and didn't look back, feeling that she couldn't for her own sanity. She dove into her work, writing to her parents occasionally to stay updated on how they and Cameron were doing. Things in Britain weren't as great as she had hoped, either. She had gone there to avoid death, but that was what was in the paper every few months.

After nearly two years abroad, Tamatha used her vacation time for something less selfish than the weekends she had admittedly spent with whatever man had caught her eye at the time, and she returned home to Canada to surprise her parents and sister. They all seemed like strangers to her, but it was the least she could do.

It seemed like such a small thing at the time, knocking on the bathroom door to see if her teenage sister was ready to go to dinner. In hindsight, Tammy wasn't sure if it was the sight of the blood or what Cameron was doing to herself that had brought her to tears first. She knew how much it had seemed to Cameron as though she was breaking what little trust remained between them, but it was for her sister’s own good that she told their parents about the razor in her hand.

Cameron was placed in a program to get her the help she needed, and Tamatha—because she couldn't lose her job—returned to London. Her sister never left her mind, and especially not when the news broke about Ilvermorny and how its students would have to study at Hogwarts until MACUSA could get everything back in order.

Tamatha didn't hesitate to open her flat to her younger sister, though she didn't think through how awkward it would be for the both of them. She and Cameron hardly knew one another, and Tamatha was sure that her sister must have hated her for speaking up about what she had seen. While her sister is at Hogwarts, though, Tammy hopes that she can get to know her better and to be the support that she failed to be for so long.[/blockquote]

[b][I]site events reaction:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Trying to escape her own grief at the time, the flood of horrible news that Tamatha found upon her arrival in Britain did little to help her feelings of security. Every death that was reported shook her, but none more so than the deaths that followed the Triwizard Tournament from her former school, Beauxbatons. Although the damage done to Ilvermorny was horrifying, too, Tammy was comforted to know that none of the students or staff were put in any danger.

Now that her own sister is attending Hogwarts, however, Tamatha is scared for her. She trusts that their parents have made the right decision in having her be responsible for Cameron’s safety while she’s in Britain, but that doesn't mean that Tamatha doesn't question herself.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]alias[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]name:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Audrey[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]21[/blockquote]
[b][i]time zone:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Time is a social construct.[/blockquote]
[b][i]reference:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Current member![/blockquote]
[b][i]other characters:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]@maxima, @parvati, @oona, @honey, @kaylee, @clarence, @ezekiel, @priscilla[/blockquote][/div][/div]
