[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" alt=" " src="https://www.gannett-cdn.com/presto/2019/09/04/USAT/2a8203c9-6241-4344-a7d0-66dde0a2a27e-Neil_Patrick_Harris_Photo_Cred._Mark_Veltman.jpg"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]jimbo brian blishwick vi[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]gym-bow blish-wick [/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]jim[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]43
14th February, 1982[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]male. he/him/his[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]pureblood [/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]heterosexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]10 inches, rosewood, veela hair, flexible. the wand is normally inserted into a cane also made of rosewood, that has a cupid firing an arrow on the handle.[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]neil patrick harris[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]6’2”. everything else same as fc. jimbo likes wearing suits because it’s ‘classier’ than every day clothes and gives his business a more legitimate feel to it. He needs to be a professional after all. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts. Ravenclaw.
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduated Class of 2000.
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]owner of blishwick matchmaking services. Professional matchmaker. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]jameson (the alcohol and his daughter), matchmaking, milkshakes, suits, people watching, social gatherings, veelas and vampires (he’s a huge sucker for their allurement charms due to his ability), potion making [/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]use of love potions (but doesn't mean he's against telling people to use them), lying to oneself, rom-coms, the idea of 'true-love' in the media sense, being put on the spot with his ability, people telling him how to do his job (he’s obviously pretty good at it), messing up a match, february, valentine’s day, being lied to about the love potential clients have with another[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]for the family business to be passed on to his daughter.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote] ocean air, peppermint, smooth jazz [/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]his business failing due to his own problems/his daughter dying [/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]jimbo brian blishwick vi. most would think a certain level of arrogance would be attached to someone with such a long, dedicated family history when it comes to his business. not jimbo though. the class clown while at hogwarts all those years ago, jimbo hasn’t exactly changed much since becoming an adult, married man, and a father. he likes to find humor in everything, devolving to self-deprecation just to get a laugh. taking him seriously in anything but his matchmaking services would be the first mistake, because even he doesn’t take himself seriously enough. despite the goofing off, his work is still highly important because it deals with people’s futures. when it comes to business, the straight face comes on and he’ll get down to it.

because of his great job and wonderful ability to match couples together, that obviously makes jimbo one of the more…attractive individuals out there. at least that’s what he thinks about himself. only an attractive person can put others together in what is normally perfect harmony. not being able to use his power, whether in the presence of demi-humans, during the month of february, or while being put on the spot, automatically sends jimbo into a dark place. to him, his perfect matchmaking is everything, and not being able to properly use it makes him feel terrible and not attractive. it’s a very ‘him’ thing, because he’s still actually a hot dad.

while in meditation to determine matches, jimbo can become extremely irritable if individuals are giving him trouble. since the ability works more as a sixth sense, those that are harder to read eventually cause blocks in his head while trying to pair them (see aforementioned demi-human abilities). getting stuck on pairing, or trying to pair via letter, causes him a great deal of stress, which is one of the reasons why he doesn’t work during the month of february. instead he spends time at bars playing a game where he matches people up based on body language and the drinks they have. he usually gets it right in the end. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]London, England[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]wife - charlotte blishwick (née allen), 32, deceased (2014)
@jimmie           , 16, 7th year Gryffindor

mother - elizabeth blishwick, 73, retired, potioneer
father - jimbo blishwick V, 75, retired, former store owner

brother - harry blishwick, 39, broom maker
sister-in-law - eliza blishwick, 38, aurologist
@lulu           , 16, 6th year Slytherin
sid blishwick, 14, 4th year student
 oli blishwick, 13, 3rd year student


uncle - gerard blishwick, 73, retired potioneer
aunt - alice blishwick (née armstrong), 73, retired potioneer

cousin - arnold blishwick, late 30s, open job 
              orion mullens, late 30s, muggle
              ____ blishwick, 5th year student
              ____ blishwick, 4th year student

cousin - phoebe blishwick, early 40s, open job
              bradley mooney, 40s, open job
              ____ blishwick, 5th year student


cousin (from jimbo blishwick jr. line) - @bobby          , 32, magical tattoo artist


[div align="center"][a href="https://www.familyecho.com/?p=SMSRC&amp;c=3qigr3fghw&amp;f=928218438535420705"][font size="4"]FULL BLISHWICK FAMILY TREE[/font][/a][/div]
[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]n/a[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Jimbo is the sixth first-born male in the Blishwick matchmaking dynasty. His brother Bernard missed out on only a few years, which was sad for Bernard, but a great thing for Jimbo. That meant he was the one due to inherit the family ability. The Blishwick clan is known for their matchmaking store located in Horizon Alley, and has been a popular establishment when it comes to pairing together young pureblooded couples. The first few Jimbo Blishwick’s were sometimes called into question about betrothals they made, the integrity of their ability on the line for several decades. Then stepped in Jimbo Blishwick IV, our very own Jimbo’s grandfather. He had the highest success rate of all the Jimbos, and brought fame back to their store once again. It became a hot thing to match together school-aged purebloods, hoping that their time spent together at Hogwarts on top of their betrothal would be enough to push them towards marriage at the end. Jimbo IV and V continued doing this throughout their years, and then it became Jimbo VI’s turn once he graduated from school.

Taking a few steps back though, Jimbo’s school years were definitely interesting. He had the chance to be their during the second wizarding war. Having been placed in Ravenclaw, the majority of his formidable years were spent learning anything and everything about potions, specifically love potions. He wanted to figure out how they differed from his family’s ability, and why they were becoming increasingly more popular than Blishwick Matchmaking. Delving into deeper levels of potineering, he eventually realized that the unnaturalness of the love potion was a disgusting thing; what he had was the ability to lead people in the right direction of a potential partner, not something that forcefully used lust. Thus his years at Hogwarts went by quickly, and the events of the wizarding war went by almost unnoticed. His job was the aftermath, after all. People were dead and broken apart. Sending them towards a person that would understand them was what he was designed for. Joining his father and grandfather at the store immediately after graduating, Jimbo began his official career.

Love was an interesting topic for Jimbo. Having such a unique talent for placing people with who they belonged wasn’t always a good sign for the Blishwick boys, their ability granting them insight on things that were normally personal. Jimbo knew that he could use his father and grandfather’s ability to find him ‘the one’, but that wasn’t him. That meant having to go out into the wild and finding a partner instead of utilizing their natural talents. Jimbo had a long string of awful relationships in his early 20s, most of which ended up with pissed off veelas and vampires chasing after him. The poor man was a sucker for their allurement charms, but also didn’t know what he was getting into when dating them. By the time he met Charlotte, his future wife, he was burned out from chasing countless women around. Things moved quickly, and they were married and expecting their first child within a year. Jimbo couldn’t have been happier, knowing that all those failures ended with two successes. Once he was married, his father retired from the family business and everything was placed on Jimbo, getting him ready for when his own son was born and the ability was inevitably passed on.

Except that didn’t happen. Instead of having a first born son like the last five Blishwick men had, Jimbo became the first to have a daughter. Agonizing over the fact that Jimbo VII was actually a little girl led him to heavily drinking the night of her birth. When it came to naming her, he thought the nurse was asking if he wanted another drink, in which he responded ‘Jameson’, his alcoholic choice to drown his sorrows in. Charlotte didn’t chastise him for it, thinking it was funny how passionate he was for the family business, and was fine with the name choice. At least he would still have a little Jimmie running around. And so began the next generation of Blishwicks. 

All was well for the first six years they were married. Then Charlotte got sick. A nasty strain of dragon pox had been making the rounds that year. She seemingly won the first round, but she got a second one soon after, and that was it for her. Soon Jimbo was a single father running a business on his own. His father offered to come back from retirement and help him out, but working was the only thing that could save Jimbo from himself. The hardest years were the first few his daughter was at school. There was still no telling if she would manifest their ability, and if she already had, she hadn’t said anything about it. Concerns were brought up that the store would have to be shut down upon Jimbo’s retirement, his father and grandfather solemnly accepting that their love matchmaking dynasty was finally at its end.

Then interesting things started happening again in their world. Deaths at Hogwarts once again. While Jimbo was initially disturbed by the killings, mostly of students in his former house and the one that his niece occupied, he realized that this was also the time to start promoting the store once again. That was what his grandfather had done during the last war, and that was exactly what Jimbo did as well. Promoting love in hard times was what he was all about, even if it took away from the problems at hand. The Triwizard Tournament became the perfect chance to get three school’s worth of students in one place. Spending countless Galleons on advertisements to be delivered to the school, he figured out a plan to get people talking once again. What he didn’t realize was that he was also promoting the connection between pureblooded families. The attention from the rich, noble families of the wizarding world has made him interested in what else they have to offer in their premiere social circles, if they’re willing to accept someone like him. With the deaths from the previous year behind him and the Tournament taking his full attention when it came to business, Jimbo, like many others, watched in wonder as the students from Durmstrang and Beauxbatons were killed. It was horrible. So many potential connections lost, then and there. Lights snuffed out in a blink of an eye. Returning to work and thankful that his own child is still alive, Jimbo awaits to see what comes next. [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Jimbo has been taking most of the things occurring in the magical world in stride. He still has a business to run and people that he can help in his own way. The Hag’s Fever has him more on edge than anything else, only because that has the propensity to shutter his business for an unknown amount of time. Thankfully, the newly introduced combination of magic and technology has helped him push a phone app of his own, which could possibly be used to fight against the decrease in foot traffic into his store.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@colin           [/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]he/him[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]26[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]est[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]the old app says proboards support, so we’ll go with that[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote][a href="https://alohomorax0.proboards.com/thread/5759"]Link To Plotter[/a][/blockquote][/div][/div]
