[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://data.whicdn.com/images/272384692/original.gif" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Camila Calderón[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]ka-MEE-lah kahl-deh-ROHN[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Cami, Mila (for those who know her by her stage name)
Carmen (for those who knew her pre-fame)

[b]birth name:[/b]
María del Carmen Kirchner Calderón
[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]18
November 27, 2006[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Cisgender female; she/her pronouns[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Half-blood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Heterosexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]11 ⅖ inches, jacaranda, unicorn hair core, quite flexible[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Martina "Tini" Stoessel[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Camila is 5'5" tall and of a thin build. She has olive skin, brown eyes, and wavy dark brown hair, which is presently about to her shoulder blades. She has her ears pierced once on each lobe but has no scars of note or tattoos.

Camila’s style depends, more than anything, on what she’s doing. Since she’s constantly in the public eye, her wardrobe is most reflective of the current trends, whether that’s streetwear or what she’s wearing to some event or another. Her looks are, overall, very feminine, though her wardrobe for concerts is flashier and much more extravagant than anything that she would choose to wear in her everyday life. It isn’t that Camila hates the way she dresses anymore, but there are times when she wishes that she could just roll out of bed and be ready for the day.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Castelobruxo[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Drop-out (as of December 2023)[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote] Wizarding musician/vocalist (2023-present)
Student (2017-2023)[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Singing, performing for an audience, traveling, writing her own songs, meeting fans, enchanted non-magical technology, dulce de leche, following Quidditch, special effects charms, British accents[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Never having any downtime, artists who lip-sync, learning choreography, invasive paparazzi/press, laryngitis, people who wear too much cologne/perfume, Caipora, becoming distrustful of people, alcohol, running late[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Camila is, as she sees it, living her dream; the only thing more would be to win some major singing awards and to become known worldwide.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Caramel coffee, nail polish, and aloe vera[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Camila’s greatest fear is losing her voice permanently and never being able to sing again. Aside from that, ending up with a stalker is also on her list of fears.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]
[b]respectful:[/b]
Camila is a respectful person, both to those in a position of authority over her and to those who might be seen as below her. She's never been someone concerned with matters of blood purity, especially since her own father is non-magical, but she knows that there are still people who can't look beyond that, unfortunately.

[b]humorous:[/b]
Camila has a sense of humor, though it's been stifled somewhat in the public eye. When she is able to let her hair down, proverbially speaking, she does joke around quite a bit, though not at anyone else's expense.

[B]hardworking:[/b]
Although she was never a stand-out student academically, Camila has always put the effort into what she does—whether that was in her life before fame or presently as a singer. Sure, she doesn't always succeed, which can be a little frustrating, but she tries her hardest nonetheless.

[b]naïve:[/b]
Carmen/Camila, being relatively new to the music business, is still learning the ropes, and, with that, has come a huge learning curve. She relies on her "people" and trusts their judgment more than she probably should, and she doesn’t really know how to handle the whole "fame" thing quite yet. She’s still trying to find her own voice—literally and figuratively—to make her career what she really wants it to be, rather than selling out.
 
[b]friendly:[/b]
Camila—on stage or off—is a very friendly, down-to-earth person. She’s not a "diva" like many other celebrities, and she plans to stay that way. She tries to make time for all of her fans, and she feels that being nice to other people is likely to get her a lot farther than being demanding.

[b]creative:[/b]
Aside from her talent as a singer, Camila is very creative and is always coming up with new song ideas. Whether those actually get recorded has been up to her label, so far, but she’s almost always jotting notes down—song titles, lines of lyrics, and anything else that catches her attention that might make for an interesting song.

[b]clumsy:[/b]
Camila is a vocalist and not a dancer for a reason. In an ideal world, she would stay stationary on the stage; she’s terrible at picking up choreography and has what some would call "two left feet”. She’s tried her best to become more graceful, but she still has her moments.

[b]humble:[/b]
Camila knows that a lot of the reason why she is who she is came down to luck. At the end of the day, she still feels that she’s María del Carmen from Córdoba, and she’s genuinely grateful to all of the people who have helped her to get to this point in her singing career.

[b]nervous:[/b]
Although she’s good at looking put-together in public, Camila does worry considerably about making missteps in her career. Sometimes she gets a sense of impostor syndrome—as though she shouldn’t actually be as famous as she is—and has her moments where she questions if she’s really doing what she should be. Still, she’s determined to make it in spite of her doubts.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Córdoba, Argentina[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]
[b]mother:[/b]
Lucila Calderón Vidal, 53, Argentinian Council of Magic employee, half-blood witch

[b]father:[/b]
Ernesto Kirchner Alonso, 56, banker, Muggle

[b]manager:[/b]
Germán Miranda Sosa, 65, talent manager, half-blood wizard[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]María del Carmen Kirchner Calderón was born and raised in Córdoba, Argentina, as the only child of a witch mother and a non-magical father. Her early childhood was unremarkable, though she began singing shortly after she could speak. She attended a non-magical primary school, where she first began performing. It wasn't anything major—just the typical school concerts—but Carmen realized that she really enjoyed being on stage.

Eventually, her primary school life came to an end, and she left Argentina to attend Castelobruxo, the South American wizarding school in Brazil. She didn't mind going to school in the rainforest, but she never really had the same knack for Magizoology and Herbology as many of her peers. It wasn't for lack of trying, though; the subjects just didn't come easily to her, and schoolwork became something of a struggle because of it.

Carmen pulled through on a combination of her other coursework and a few marks that barely passed in Magizoology and Herbology and continued to deal with life at Castelobruxo. She was always eager to leave school at the end of each school year, though, to return to the city. It was back home in Argentina that she felt most comfortable, taking trips to Buenos Aires and Mendoza with her parents.

By the time that Carmen had reached her teens, she had started singing again. She had no intention of becoming hugely famous—Castelobruxo was surrounded by forest—but her friends encouraged her when they realized how talented she was. It seemed completely ridiculous to try to get anywhere with a music career; singing in the shower or the occasional jam session with her friends didn't really count. 

In July of 2023, however, that changed. On the urging of her friends, Carmen entered a singing competition in Buenos Aires. She wasn't sure how far she would get, but she did it with the hope that she might get a few paying gigs out of it. Getting her name out there didn't sound like a bad idea, and neither did a little bit of spending money of her own. With that in mind, she put her best foot forward—and, with a cover of "This Is the Night" by the Weird Sisters, won the competition.

Carmen was immediately approached by a talent manager and a record label, and—after discussing it with her parents—decided to sign a recording contract. She was immediately swept up in a whirlwind of activity and was advised to take a stage name—something that would resonate with a global audience—and thus took on the name Camila Calderón for her music career. 

Before she returned to Castelobruxo, Carmen—as Camila Calderón—recorded her first demos, though she didn't remain at school for long after that. The demands of her team and her career became too difficult to balance alongside her school schedule, which was increasingly difficult and frustrating. Although her parents were displeased with her choice to leave Castelobruxo permanently at the end of the academic year in December, they accepted it because Carmen had a plan and a contract.

Shortly thereafter, Carmen returned to Argentina and recorded the cover of "This Is the Night" that had led her to win the singing competition, which was then released as her first single. Not only did it hit radio stations in South America, but it hit the airwaves around the magical world. It seemed as though Carmen—or, rather, Camila Calderón—was an overnight sensation.

It was equal parts scary and thrilling, and Carmen/Camila was excited for the ride. She began doing interviews—not only in Spanish and Portuguese, the two languages with which she was most comfortable—but also in English. People were actually listening to [i]her[/i] on their radios in countries that she had never even visited! Her parents, too, were thrilled for her. Who would have thought that their daughter would actually become a star?!

With that success, of course, Camila's team grew motivated to pick up the pace. The next few weeks were a blur of meetings and songwriting and recording and more meetings, as it was decided that Camila Calderón needed to release her first album. Camila insisted on writing at least some of her own material, which got whittled down to two songs: "Beso del Dementor" and "Dueling Hearts", her two biggest hits to date in Spanish and English, respectively.

Her self-titled pop album, [i]Camila Calderón[/i], was released in March 2024. It was received well by music critics and the general public alike, which was exactly what Camila and her team had hoped for. A Latin American tour, her first, was announced for the following months, which even took Camila to Los Angeles, California, for two additional dates beyond her previously announced schedule. The work that she had to put in was considerable. Wardrobe fittings, dance lessons, and choreography sessions filled the time that she was used to spending just on singing.

Following a number of incidents globally, Camila's security was kept tight to ensure that nothing would go wrong. While the Auror presence was occasionally a little intimidating, Camila appreciated it, especially when nothing went wrong. As far as she could tell, she had really been able to connect with her fans, and she ended her tour in July ready to spend some time with her parents and friends from Castelobruxo—and return to songwriting.

With how well her tour had gone, Camila's team was eager to see her branch out to more English-language markets. Camila, who had never thought of herself as being very good at English, was hesitant. She could cover English-language songs, sure, but write an album of them?

Her team thus managed to get ahold of some music executives in Britain who would be willing to work with her, and it seemed to Camila to be a good opportunity to brush up on her English, too. It would be something of a working vacation, she thought, and she wasn't too concerned about spending the next few months in London. She'd still be writing and recording music, and she would have security around almost all the time.

As word began to spread of a possible serial killer in the country, Camila and her management locked down her schedule even more than they had, which was again increased in the wake of the destruction of Azkaban shortly after Christmas. With Camila as one of Argentina’s biggest stars, they weren’t going to take any chances with her safety.[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Carmen was never really too worried about the goings-on elsewhere in the world, but—now that she’s [i]the[/i] Camila Calderón—she has no choice but to care. She knows that she has a high profile, and she and her management have been doing everything in their power to keep her safe, especially as she travels abroad. She does worry about what would happen in the event of a serious incident, particularly at one of her own concerts, but she trusts her team to make the right decisions for her and her career.

The incidents at Hogwarts had never concerned her too much, given her distance from the school when she was still attending Castelobruxo, but the explosions of the Beauxbatons Carriage and Durmstrang Ship as those students were about to return home was perhaps the first time that she felt truly uncomfortable about something that had gone on outside of South America. They had been students her own age, and it had happened right as she was beginning her first tour. The few times that she had been asked about it in interviews, she had expressed her condolences and concerns—but, still, she knew that her team had put measures in place to keep her and her fans safe at her shows… and the shows had to go on.

It was after the incident at Ilvermorny that Camila had had her tour dates in Los Angeles, though nothing much changed from a security standpoint. Her fans were already subject to a clear bag policy, and there was nothing else to suggest that the group that had targeted the American wizarding school had any intention of disrupting her concert.

With the events of the past few months in the United Kingdom, especially, Camila has considered leaving London for Argentina again. There has been a potential serial killer, for one thing, plus the destruction of Azkaban and dragons in the wizarding village of Hogsmeade—all of which have led to increased security and restricted movement for Camila. 

As much as she wishes that she could just leave, she knows that she has commitments to uphold and an album to record, so she’s trying to make the best of the situation without feeling too stifled… and get back home as soon as possible.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Audrey[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]21[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]US/Canada Central/Eastern[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]Current member[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@brody, @clarence, @ezekiel, @honey, @kaylee, @maxima, @oona, @parvati, @priscilla, @samira, @tamatha [/blockquote][/div][/div]