[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://media1.giphy.com/media/ghOZWpn1xO0j4K0SU2/giphy.gif" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""]
[/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]noah william corner[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]No-uh[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Erik Esper - his stage name

[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]23-years-old
October 3, 2002
[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Male
He/him[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Half Blood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Pansexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]10 3/4 inches, Hornbeam, unicorn hair[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Conan Gray[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Height: 5'10
He looks like his playby. Keeps his dark hair longer and has a very casual dressing style.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts - Ravenclaw[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduate[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Musician
Madam Puddifoot's Barista[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Writing music
Playing instruments (piano and guitar)
Singing
Being alone/with only friends
Camping
Spending time outdoors

[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Parties/big events
Performing in front of people
Being in the spotlight
Sports
frivolous and unnecessary spending[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]To be honest? He truly wants to live a quiet life. Where he can still make and share his music but he doesn't have to worry about the paparazzi or anything like.
He'd like his younger siblings to grow up without any more trouble in the world.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]vanilla, pine, campfire smoke. coffee[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]losing his ability to write music/sing
Being rejected (romantically)

[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Noah is a quiet boy most the time. He's the sort to be consumed by his own thoughts and ideas. He is definitely an introvert, and doesnt' really go out of his way to be social. He does have friends, of course. but he's just not a social butterfly. He's the type that will sit on a couch alone at a party. There, but not actively participating.&nbsp;

He's very reserved and tends to keep things about himself to himself. This is especially clear with his music. While he's a very talented musician (singing, guitar and piano) few people actually know it. Well... They don't know it as "Noah". You see, he puts out all his music under the alis "Erik Esper". His identity is something that the label has come to see has a very closely guarded secret. To the point where only the producers and managers taht work directly with him know what he looks like. No other employees, or other musicians know his face. Just his music. Though his music is known for being deep and meaningful. His lyrics are impactful and will move the audience.&nbsp;

He is a very deep person, even when it's not music related. He has a philosophical outlook on life. He isn't the sort to be drawn into meaningless drama. But he will be there to support you when you fall if he considers you a friend. Sort of like a silent guardian.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]England[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Michael Corner - father (divorced)
Sue Corner nee Li - mother (divorced)

____ ____ CORNER S/7th&nbsp;
____ ____ CORNER R/4th[/blockquote]
[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]None[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Noah is the eldest son of Michael Corner and Sue Li. He was a honeymoon baby, born almost 9 months to the day after their marriage. Obviously, getting pregnant so quickly hadn't been the plan, but his parents made it work somehow. Thankfully, they waited many years before having another child. Though it did mean that Noah is quite a bit older then his other siblings.&nbsp;

From a young age he was a quiet one. He tended to gravitate to solo activitie. Then, when he was a toddler his parents got one of those cheap toddler music toys and he took to it like glue. Realizing that he clearly enjoyed music his parents soon enrolled him in piano classes. He was a natural. He took piano lessons all growing up.&nbsp;

Eventually his siblings were born. He loved being an older brother but he didn't always know how to play with them after being an only child for so long. But, he loved them none the less.&nbsp;

When he turned 11 he got his letter to Hogwarts, where both his parents had gone, and was sorted into Ravenclaw his first night. While not necessarily the "smartest" Ravenclaw, he was definitely a philosophically minded individual. He had a bright mind. THough, he didn't always know how to express himself. To him, that was where music came in. He would play the piano to express himself. And, as he got older started to sings and learn the guitar. He was soon writing his own music and was quite good at it. During his school years though he did not share any of it with others except his siblings and parents.

During his years at Hogwarts his parents got divorced. They'd been having marital issues since the youngest had been born, so it wasn't too surprising, but it help solidify Noah's difficulty to be open about himself. He turned fully to music.&nbsp;

After graduation he started a job at a cafe. He didn't really have any ambitions to get into music. It wasn't his intention. But his parents encouraged him to send a demo to a label. To his surprise, the label loved it and wanted to meet him.&nbsp;

During that meeting the made it clear they wanted to sign him. Noah, of course, made it clear that he wanted to produce music, did not want people to know who he was. He just wasn't a fan of the spotlight. He was also worried about how that sort of publicity might affect his younger siblings. While reluctant at first, the label decided to try it. It turned out to be a major success. His first cd did exceptionally well. They used the name "Erik Esper". As time went on fans became more and more curious about this Erik, as the cd didn't have anything about the singer. Nor, were there any live performances. Soon, this mystery became a part of his identity. While his label would make him do concerns they would take extreme precautious to ensure that no one ever saw Noah's face. Mystery and Erik Esper soon became synonymous. Not even other performers knew what he looked like, as the label guarded the secret with their life.&nbsp;

Now a days he still works in that little cafe, keeping up his simple life, though writes and produces music on the side under the mysterious alias that no one has ever seen...[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Of course, Noah is worried about how certain events affect himself, the world, and his family. He's even more cautious about things now then ever. He especially keeps a closer eye on his younger siblings.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Sora[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]29[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]Mountain[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]I live here[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]too many.[/blockquote][/div][/div]