[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://www.chicklit.nl/ckfinder/userfiles/images/Chicklit/acteurs%2C%20actrices/Jon%20Kortajarena.gif"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Auguste Benoît Collingwood[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]Like the month but with the emphasis on Gus rather than Au.
[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Gus[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]23
August 24th.[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Male, he/him[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Pureblood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Omnisexual. (Pan)[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote][/blockquote][span]&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;[/span][span]&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;[/span][span]&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;[/span][span]&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;[/span]Sycamore wood with a dragon heartstring core, 14 ¼ and quite bendy flexibility

[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Jon Kortajarena.[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Uhm, tall? Probably like 1.90m tall.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Beauxbatons alumnus[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduate.[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Superstar (current)
Private detective agency (2 years after graduation, quit when his singing career took off)[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Apples! Alcohol, smoking, flirting, apple picking, singing, playing guitar, saving people, writing songs.[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Pushy people, judgemental people, unattractive press, freeloaders, people using him for money or career or just.. using him at all.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Hugging his mother and seeing her happy. That's all.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Flower fields in bloom, apples, Phil's fur.[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Growing old and sad, going deaf.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Gus is what one might call a bit of a typical bad boy. He cares deeply but has such severe commitment issues that he's more likely to push all those that care about him away than he is to truly connect to anybody on a level. He is composed of mostly bad habits and flirtation and finds it very easy to talk to people although it usually results in flirting. 

Gus is fond of liquid courage in almost any bottle and it's more common for him to breathe smoke than clean air.&nbsp;Due to due death of his mother he has a severe feeling of guilt that he drags around everywhere he goes. He's previously been in a very dark depression but after some very dumb actions he's slowly beginning to mend. His behaviour usually counteracts exactly what he wishes to do but he is extremely charming and avoids lying even if that means he hurts people before getting what he wishes from them. He tries to be sincere at all times but lies to himself every single day of the year. 

He carries some minor bitterness and resent towards his father, although this mostly got cleared after his father encouraged him (forced him really) to pursue his musical talents after he'd failed to get the grades required to become an auror. All he wants to do is make the world a better place but he's not very good at seeing how to do this. [/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]France.[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Amaury - Older brother, curse breaker, gryffindor alumnus
Alix - slightly younger sister (almost twin), beauxbatons alumni

Adriana Eloise Courtemanche née du Lac - mother, deceased
Gregory Apollo Courtemanche - father, Ministry official

Sienna Linslee - ex girlfriend and best friend in the universe[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Phillipe the Tiger[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]cw/tw: death of a loved one, suicide, depression, substance abuse.&nbsp;

Gus was born as the second son to the Courtemanche household. His childhood was relatively easy. He grew up a normal regular rich pureblood, without most of the prejudices common in those circles. Perhaps that had more to do with his mother that suffered from a severe depression. She always did her best and was a kind and caring woman. Gus was particularly close to her and she was the center of his universe, along with Alix, his younger sister by less than a year.&nbsp;

His brother loved caring for little Gus and usually ended up doing so when his mother was suffering from her bouts of depression and their dad was off at work. Their mother had long since quit her job to take care of the children. With Amaury being six years older than the near-twins he was often expected to be an authority figure. Still life wasn't all that bad and Gus often made music with his mother, who taught him to play the guitar. The two often could be found singing together and Gus started to feel like he could make his mother happy, if only he tried hard enough. Much to his disadvantage, nobody noticed him taking on full responsibility for the mental welfare of his mother until it was much too late.

At eleven, Gus was sent off to school at beauxbatons, something that seemed not to do much good for his mother. Her purpose for caring for her children reduced as nearly all her children were off to school. His first year was okay, but everybody in the family started to grow desperate as the second year meant a steep decline for the health of the mother. At first Gus tried to show his mother all was going to be fine by being on his best behaviour. When this didn't work, he argued endless hours with his father to have him stay home and be homeschooled in his third year. Not managing to convince his father, he started to grow the reputation of a rebel. Something that seemed to amuse his mother no matter how much it worried her.&nbsp;

During an outing in his third year of school, Gus snuck into a local circus and stole a young tiger cub, feeling sorry for it being locked in a cage. He managed to sneak it back onto the grounds of Beauxbatons where it remained undiscovered for a while. Disaster struck when the owl came to school to inform Gus and his sister that their mother had finally (although it had long since been anticipated) taken her own life. Upon hearing the news Gus had ran off into the woods on the school grounds and had sought out Phillipe, as he'd named the tiger. The bond the two had built meant he'd spent hours upon hours crying near his little tiger cub that playfully attempted to cheer him up.&nbsp;

For several days he refused to go back to the school until finally he was found with Phillipe in his little hide out. Gus was handled with delicacy at first. Phillipe had to be off and after a heated discussion and multiple threats on Gus' part, his father agreed to getting the required permits and keep Phillipe on the grounds of the Courtemance mansion. Gus received only detention at first but due to the chaos he constantly caused at the school they eventually suspended him for a month, saying he could come back after he'd dealt properly with the loss of his mother.

At home he and Phillipe spent nearly all their time together and while he was with his tiger, Gus was as happy as he could manage. He calmed down and came to terms with the fact his mother was gone, although he felt to blame for her death, something that worried his father greatly. There was nothing that seemed to be able to be done about that and several therapists later it was clear it was something Gus needed to figure out on his own.&nbsp;

Eventually he returned to school, something that caused his mental health to take somewhat of a hit. While he'd gotten to the point he meant to continue with his life despite his mother being gone, he didn't take well to the change in his life. He started to cultivate the reputation of bad boy and lived his life in constant defiance of the rules. While he did his work for school and his grades surprisingly didn't suffer too much, the teachers found they had a nightmare on their hands in terms of his behaviour. He didn't care enough about social convention and the moment he figured out that men could love men, he started to explore his sexuality only to find out that he liked men just as much as woman. This lead to him flirting with nearly every single member of the student body.&nbsp;

He eventually had a few relationships but nothing lasted. The fear of losing those he grew to love and care about led him to always push people away. He made one dear friend though, a girl by the name of Sienna Linslee. A girl beautiful beyond compare, Gus found her heart was as beautiful as her face and breaking her heart caused him severe regret. She forgave him effortlessly and assured him they wouldn't make a proper match in that part of their lives. He started to build a bond with her that would eventually save his life.

In his seventh year, bad news hit the Courtemanche household again. His aunt, the only living relation to his mother, had died in a tragic accident. All ties to his mother severed now, Gus fell into a deep darkness. He couldn't sleep for weeks on end and grew too tired. Eventually he stole a lot of sleeping potion from the hospital wing, determined to get the rest he felt he needed.&nbsp;

Thankfully Sienna had been keeping a careful eye out on him and along with his sister Alix they ensured that he would wake up again. At that point things deteriorated. He slipped into substance abuse and broke down for several months. With the careful guidance of Sienna he eventually got past it, in time for the final exams. Due to his circumstance he didn't get the required grades to try and become an auror, a path he'd chosen for himself in hopes of helping others avoid the losses that he'd suffered. Apart from that he actually enjoyed the prospect of dying a heroic death. It just seemed like an added bonus.

When that fell through he got himself a small apartment where he locked himself up and refused to come out for weeks. Eventually he and his male best friend Thierry managed to start a detective agency. In their time, they managed and Gus was okay, although far from thriving.

Sienna spoke to his father and eventually his father spoke to Gus at great lengths and at long last made a deal with Gus. He was to play a song he'd written but never managed to play out in public. At that point his father would back off. Naturally his father didn't bother to tell him he'd lure in headhunters for a life of fame for his son. Music had always made him happy in the past and these days the only creature that heard him play music and sing was Phillipe, something many of the humans in his life envied.&nbsp;

Gus played and was instantly offered many opportunities to start making music for a living. Sienna was the one to convince him that it was as good as anything. That music could pierce the hearts of many and often help them through tough times. Gus accepted the deal the next day and started his rise to fame.&nbsp;

Due to his good looks and flirtatious character he rapidly gained popularity and within a year he was a sensation in France. From there he started to expand his audience to Europe, eventually spreading to the UK. Constantly being on the road was something that suited Gus rather well and he finally managed to start enjoying his life again. Every song and performance was dedicated to his mother in silence. Recently he's been doing much better although his vices are still a vital part of his bad boy image.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Gus felt a sense of rage upon reading people escaped from the prison. Once upon a time it had been his greatest ambition to put people behind those bars. What good was a jail meant to keep criminals in if they could get out? He was quite grumpy and complained endlessly to his friends and staff. Since most knew of his previous ambitions it was not much of a surprise. They mostly worried he'd abandon his work as an artist to try and join a ministry in hopes of chasing after criminals. It would greatly affect their lives as well, they wouldn't have jobs. Still, Gus was well aware of this and resisted the temptation to go knock on the door of the ministry in the closest place to ask to join in the effort of bringing criminals back to join, although he did up the security on all of his venues to ensure no disasters could take place while people were supposed to be enjoying themselves.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Seph[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]27[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]GMT+1 (or 2)[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]the searching.[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@seph  [/blockquote][/div][/div]