TW/CW: parental suicide / sibling attempt

[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/617321779089899530/848766376163803216/R090e62db33dd96e1e6d1dd120af31ec3.png" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]alix eloise courtemanche[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]ah-licks eh-low-ease cour - tee - man - che[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Ali, sexy babe, Shrink,[i] 'f--- off-out-of-my-head'[/i], P’tite Poupée (by her parents),[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]23 years old
Born September 15, 2002[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Cis-gendered female
She/Her[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Pureblood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Pansexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]11 1/2" beech wood, phoenix feather core.[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Adelaide Kane[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Alix likes to stay on trend like that and ever since a child, she's enjoyed makeup. In fact, it was one of her earliest memories, sitting with her maman and getting all beautiful for the tea parties. Like her brothers, she's tall and lean... at the Academy, she sometimes felt inadequate as the other girls all seemed to blossom in the bosom area. However, she soon began to enjoy the freedom that came with her naturally lithe body.

She still puts a lot of effort into the way she looks, although sometimes she's heard remarks that she looks a little beyond her age when she forgets to drink enough water during the day. See, Alix is pretty sure that most people would have the same worry lines she had if they'd been through her tragedies. For her job, she still wears heels unlike many other healers - her area of expertise is the psychiatric maladies, after all. The moment her shift is over, though, she sheds the healer's robe quickly enough and particularly enjoys fashionable ensembles that highlight her long legs. She's got them, so she flaunts them.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling &amp; status[/b]
[blockquote]Beauxbatons
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]- began training at St. Mungo's in the psychiatric ward straight out of the Academy. She chose this over the French equivalent because she wanted to be "closer" to her brother.
- currently works as a psychiatrist on the ward
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote] being surrounded by people
- the feel of her hair on her back (it's the main reason she keeps it long)
- vegetarian lifestyle
- a good party with wine, music, dancing, fun people
- preferably natural fibres
- studying the way people think and how she can make them see the world with more... perspective
- jewellery
- her family &amp; family in general. She's of the persuasion that people are happier when they're grounded and have a strong familial bond.
- showers
- the idea of lavender fields. You'll not likely ever find her in one though. Bugs and … no, fields aren't exactly beautiful heel friendly.
- firewhiskey because it keeps her accountable for drinking alcohol (ie she doesn't drink too much because she'd wake with a raw throat the next morning and that's just unprofesh)
- those druids because they're so … different. Fascinating. She has no idea how they live without modern conveniences, but she adores that for the most part they're a cohesive unit and covets their sense of community.
- receiving owls from friends and family. Her love of it, if you ask her, stems from when Meric left for Hogwarts and she used to live for his letters, even as they became less frequent. There's just something so heartwarming receiving a letter and she stores all of them chronologically in a specially enchanted chest in her apartment.
- the art of divination. She likes the psychology behind most readers; a decent portion of them have no actual seer ability over that of reading their clients well. She's sure if she ever needed a side-business she'd be just as effective..[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]- Ok don't tell her brother Gus this but... she's not a fan of the tiger. Like... no. Hard pass. Same as the big slobber machines that are Meric's bloodhounds. Merlin no[/]. They just look at her and she gets skeeved out.
- being alone. She will always be visiting friends, family, being in the pubs... more than sleeping.
- the terrorists that destroyed the students returning from the triwizard tournament.
- meat has a horrible texture that hasn’t agreed with her for a very long time.
- when people don’t listen to reason
- purists because honestly, there’s so many more things in the world to worry about than one’s magical inheritance
- people that chew with an open mouth
- when she sounds silly by misinterpreting from French to English, particularly when idioms do not match up between the languages.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Mental health has always been a [i]huge[/i] issue in the Courtemanche family and as a child Alix did everything she could to make her mother laugh, or in her darkest days… even smile. This had become quite a staple of her personality, always making every effort to bring sunshine to the lives of other people. As she grew older, she learned the ability to also sit to and listen to people’s complaints and so she became quite a popular young lady in Beauxbatons. People could confide in her and Alix always found it a lot easier to deal with their pain and problems than the ones that plagued her brother and mother.

Alix always feels a deep responsibility for the death and almost death of her family members. She drives herself to exhaustion as she works around the clock to keep herself from thinking or by partying. She understands the substance abuse that her brother has turned to because the temptation to fall into the same hole … it’s overpowering sometimes. In fact, if it weren’t for her deep love and fear for her brother, she might very well follow down the path. There’s been a few times when she’s gone a bit too hard on alcohol though and woken up in … interesting places and errr.. situations.

If you hadn’t noticed yet, Alix can be a little… vain. She’s not narcissistic, but she definitely can’t go outside without a full face of makeup. She’ll be the first to tell anyone that the best way to [i]feel better[/i] is to [i]look better[/i]. Alix fears abandonment above most things, so she’s always thrown herself into study or work or partying… so she’s never had any deep, emotional attachments to anyone romantically.

As much as she appears to be a confident young woman that tries to get people to talk through their problems… she's actually quite secretive about her own deep seated insecurities and troubles. This is evident in the fact that she doesn't even burden her brothers' with the knowledge that she cannot stand - is part grossed out and part terrified of - their chosen pets. No good would come of it, they'd no doubt just laugh and tell her she doesn't need to visit them. She's ultimately disposable.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]France[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]adriana eloise courtemanche nee du lac | mother | deceased
gregory apollo courtemanche | father | ministry official

aymeric thierry courtmanche | brother | 29 | Potions Professor at Hogwarts
auguste benoit courtmanche | brother | 24 | superstar

raphael enzo courtmanche | nephew | 3

ambroise du lac | uncle | curator
evangeline du lac née flamel | aunt | deceased
tatiana du lac née Thorne | aunt | tbc
aurum victoria du lac | cousin | 15 | ravenclaw
argentum odin du lac | cousin | 15 | ravenclaw

--- --- courtmanche nee loche | sister in law | 28 | tbc
--- --- loche | brother in law | 20 | wizard.
--- --- loche | sister in law | 17 | witch.
--- --- loche | brother in law | 15 | wizard.
--- --- loche | brother in law | 14 | non magical.[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Alix doesn't do pets. It's something that most people know... but Gus doesn't. He's too close to the edge and Phillipe for her to let him know that.[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Being the baby of the family can be both a blessing and a curse, depending on the person's ability to practice gratitude.
In Alix's youngest years, she remembers little more than fun times and a lot of love from her family members. She was only a year younger than her brother Gus, so she followed him around like they were attached at the hip which, in turn, meant that she spent a lot of time with their even older brother, Meric. She learned to walk and talk quickly because even as a toddler, she didn't want to be left behind.

When Meric went away, little Alix didn't really understand why but her parents encouraged her to "write him letters" although how many actually got sent to Hogwarts, we shall never know. Obviously as she grew older and better in her literacy skills, the more likely they were to be sent to him. She was only 4 when he left for the Scottish wilderness, after all.
Time passed with few notable memories until her brother Gus also left for school at Beauxbatons. This was … rough. Alix saw less of her mother, her father was busy at work and the little girl spent her final year of childhood mostly alone in the well appointed Courtemanche home. This is when the girl grew to dislike being alone and when the house elves were preoccupied she would slip out to explore the wider wizarding world that France had to offer. She would bring little gifts home for her mother after a day out and about, hoping that it would help her see what beauty lies just outside the drawn curtains.

Being able to attend Beauxbatons was like…. a weight lifted. A freedom that Alix felt entirely guilty about but… the moment she put on the tailored dress and little cap, pulled up her pretty white socks and tottered off to Beauxbatons she was all smiles and determined to enjoy herself. She hoped that getting good grades would be enough to assuage the guilt she felt. She made a great group of friends in her year who went on to stay her besties until this day - of course sometimes they go long periods without speaking, but not that long because Alix is… needy. In a good way, she wants to assure you all.
In her second year disaster struck and her mother passed away. It was made even harder because Gus broke down quite spectacularly. He went missing and Alix couldn't cry for her mother because she was too worried about him. The difference in the reactions of the two children were like polar opposites, many remarked at the time and even in less polite societies… still do. Alix rallied with her friends around her for support and there was a lot of ice cream and pedicures and pamper sessions had immediately following Gus' return and even more so when he was suspended.

With Meric remaining in England and Gus falling apart, the youngest did her very best to keep on the academic straight and narrow for her father's sake. She applied herself to her study, broke up with one of the boys she was casually "dating" (as a 14 year old will do when at school) and attended the counsellor provided by the Academy. Honestly, Alix felt like the woman was an angel - if she believed in such creatures - and this is where her career path began to form.

When her aunty passed away after a long sickness, Alix's brother's fragile mental health took a turn for the worst again and Alix spent many sleepless nights worrying for him. She became quite thin - yes, it was possible for even her slim frame to get tinier - but with the support of her friends and counsellor she pulled through once more. She was reminded by the smiling photos of her aunt and mother that they would not want her, Gus, Meric or their father to suffer.

She made the decision to honour them and be happy.

Alix graduated the year after with hard earned top marks and instantly decided that she needed a change of pace and… to reconnect with her older brother in England. She applied for her traineeship with St Mungo's, specialising under the psychiatric ward.
What. A. Ride.

She had taken on the ward because of her experience with mental health issues but the ward was something else entirely. Honestly, the brain and what it could do was such a weird, wonderful and often tragic thing that even three years as a fully trained healer, Alix is still learning new things. She loves her patients - unlike other wards, hers were often long turn or repeat visitors. Learning to communicate effectively with different ones has been a trip and she's thankfully quite an expressive person physically so she usually finds a way to get her point across. Even if she has to look like an idiot to do so.

In the past five years, Alix has been building on her relationship with her brother Meric and his wife, plus her younger siblings that they look after as if they were their own children. The eldest is similar in age to Alix and so they have a great friendship - she's almost like an aunt to the youngest, but far more of a friend. She loves talking about and learning muggle things from them and boy oh boy can muggles party in the UK. When she's not working, she loves nothing better than spending time in this family. It makes her heart soar and it recharges her batteries ready for the time she needs to handle more difficult patients…

Spending time with Gus is grand and boy does she love a great night out with him and the lifestyle he brings with superstardom. More than once a colleague has mentioned how she's wearing the same thing as yesterday - except they always think it's because she's scored the night before. Alix hasn't had a serious relationship, too married to her work and with the recent tragedies occuring - muggleborns killed, attacks at Hogwarts and escaped prisoners… Alix's case load is more than enough to excuse the lack of romantic relationship.

Anyone with half a brain can figure it's because Alix is too scared to lose another loved one. Not that they tell her that. Or perhaps they have and she just refuses to acknowledge it [img class="smile" style="max-width:100%;" src="//storage.proboards.com/5647952/images/rKJQTqXtCqHlMyypKBce.gif" alt=":)"] 

[b]Site specific reactions: [/b]

- Firework catastrophe: this was chaos at St Mungo's and was a testament to many of the healer's abilities. Even Alix was on hand to help with the injured when she wasn't assisting in treating people for shock, terror and unimaginable grief. During this time, Alix pulled very long hours and, when it was finally done, she passed out in her apartment for almost a full 48 hours.
- Brother Gus hospitalised with Hag's Fever: it was very hard for Alix not to spend 24/7 at her brother's bedside while he was hospitalised. Unfortunately, other patients are whom she's paid to look after and so it was only during her lunch break or after work that she could be there for him.
- Trials of the new wolfsbane potion: Alix hopes that the trials for the new potion works for the tortured souls that are cursed with lycanthropy. She fears that it will be unsuccessful and is merely a money-making tactic by the Slug and Jiggers.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]RoadRoo[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]31 uears[/blockquote]
[/div][/div]
