[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://64.media.tumblr.com/146fa791e9673d8b3b4fb10cfa6a766c/tumblr_inline_nlktdgFpyF1rxlhrp.gif" alt=""]
[/div][div align="center"][font size="5"]sacha de lapin[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]Sa-sha[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]eh, whatever you want to call him. He doesn't care.[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]27
August 21, 1998
[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Male
He/him[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Pureblood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Pansexual, but he does tend to lean towards men.[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]10' Pine Unicorn hair.[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Willy Cartier[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Height: 5'10
Willy has dark hair and eyes, with quite a few freckles scattered across his nose and cheeks. While he has a bit of facial hair he has a very androgynous look about him that doesn't really help since his hair is quite long.&nbsp;

His style is very laid back and casual. Much preferring loose loungewear that some would deem inappropriate for wearing outside the house.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling &amp; status[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts Graduate 2016 - Slytherin[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Professional Musician&nbsp;
(no, not that kind of musician. He's a classically trained and performing violinist)[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Classical music
Playing the violin
Operas/the theater
classic literature
rainy days
[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Doing anything that doesn't interest him.
Parties/crowds/events where he has to -gag- socialize
Pointless conversations
Sports (particularly participating in them)
Studying[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Sacha is a strange man for many to understand. He comes across as a very lazy, unmotivated person who has no drive to do anything. And in most instances you'd be correct. He is someone that will never do something he doesn't want. He'd rather do nothing at all then do something he doesn't want to do. This trait of his also makes him incredibly difficult to deal with as very few people have been able to successful in motivating the man.&nbsp;

Though if it is something he's interested in? Well he has unlimited focus and attention. He throws all of his time, attention, and energy into tasks he enjoys. Particularly music. But not just the noise people listen to today, classical music. He's been playing the violin since he was a child, and it's one of his few hobbies in life. It means that he's an incredibly talented and dedicated musician and plays for several orchestras.&nbsp;

Sacha can come across as a very cold and cruel man. Because of his unmotivation for anything unrelated to his own desires it means that he also feels no desire to be polite or put any unnecessary energy into something. Despite knowing social queues and manners he blatantly ignores them if they don't benefit his desires. He can be quite harsh in dealing with people because of this disinterest&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Born in France.
Raised between France and London, depending on his parents business.[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Louise de Lapin - Mother, 57. Socialite
Hugo de Lapin - Father, 60. Successful businessman

____ de Lapin - brother, 16. Hogwarts student
[/blockquote]
[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]He personally doesn't have any.[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Sacha was born to the de Lapin couple have several years of trying. A healthy baby boy. His life was quite ideal being an only child, especially as a pureblood child. His parents gave him whatever he wanted and never made him do something he didn't want. From a very young age he became obsessed with music and his parents paid for the finest violin tutor.&nbsp;

His parents had always wanted more children though. It had never been the plan for Sacha to be an only child. Unfortunately it seemed their luck didn't improve though. And so, for many years Sacha was raised alone. And spoiled rotten.

Finally though, around the time when Sacha was preparing to head to school his parents finally welcoemd a second child, a boy. Sacha, to his parents' surprise, took quite a bit of interest in his newborn baby brother and enjoyed spending whatever time he could with the brother. THough, unfortunately he was forced to attend school as well. Much to his distaste. For once his parents didn't give into his refusal to cooperate and forced him to attend Hogwarts.&nbsp;

Sacha's Hogwarts years were incredibly dull and boring. He cared absolutely little for school learning, or socializing with most kids his age. He made few friends but he didn't really care. He had his music, he had his brother, and that was that.&nbsp;

After graduation he returned to his family's home, with no real desire to really work or do anything. That was when his violin tutor recommended he meet with an old acquaintance of his, a conductor for a renowned orchestra. The rest was history. He was hired on by the orchestra officially, climbing his way through the seat ranks quickly. A very talented and dedicated violinist who wouldn't be satisfied just "being one of the musicians". HE wanted that first chair, and he got it.


The events of recent years have played little affect in his life past his concern of his brother attending Hogwarts at the time the events were happening. As long as they didn't affect him personally, he honestly didn't care.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Sora[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]30[/blockquote]
[/div][/div]