[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://ar.vogue.me/image_provider/?w=750&amp;h=&amp;zc=1&amp;q=80&amp;cc=ffffff&amp;src=https://en.vogue.me/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/Salma-Abu-Deif-Vogue-Arabia.jpg"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]yasmin zara el fayed[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]yaz - meen[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Yas, exclusively
Zaza (only by Emrys)[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]20; 18 Octrober 2005[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]female - she/her[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]muggleborn[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]heterosexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]Unicorn tail hair and acacia, 9 and a half inches[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Salma Abu Deif[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Yas has long, straight black hair and large, dark eyes. She is tall and willowy at 175 cm and often wears dark liner around her eyes, and will occasionally wear colourful headscarves and oversized wire framed glasses.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts - Hufflepuff
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduate
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Bartender at Hounds and Harriers pub
Digital Artist[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]+technology
+oil paints
+drawing
+painting
+chatting
+freedom
+sunshine
+raspberry white chocolate cookies
+the idea of falling in love again
+her sisters (and brother, but he's a bit irksome)
+waterfalls
+moving bodies of water[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]-fires
-monotony
-the status quo
-arranged relationships
-the taste of liquorice
-the amount of rain in the UK
-infidelity
-humiliation
-importance of upholding a certain reputation
-still water
-paying attention to lectures for a long period of time
[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]to have her artwork featured in a prestigious gallery, to find a love that she approves of as well as her parents[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]sandstone, oil paints, gardenia[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]to be set up in an arranged marriage with a horrible mate; to have her family pull their support and love from her; dying of thirst[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Yas is an effervescent, free spirited, head in the clouds kind of girl. She is fiercely loyal to her family and those who have won her affection (though won is a bit of a strong word - she loves easily). She's a typical Hufflepuff in the way that she is loyal and hard-working, though perhaps not in the classical educational sense. When something catches her attention, Yas is not easily distracted and focuses on things with a singularity not found in her daily life. She's known to obsess over different mediums of art, the way the light catches a flowing stream, and the very colour of the grass on a mid-summer day. She is idealistic and hopeful and very much a believer in fate.

Yas is overly protective and trusting to a fault. She didn't realise when she thought the boy who was the love of her life was actually... well, not. Since his betrayal of trust, Yas has tried to be more protective of her self, but it simply isn't her nature. She struggles to pay attention and did not perform well in school at all, barely managing the marks to past. She was much too distracted by the way the light bends coming through the warped old windows of the castle. It was a lucky thing, for that reason, that Yas had no intention of joining the ministry. Yas likes to joke that Yara got her missing portion of brains.

Easily forgiving, and practically allergic to confrontation, Yas is not a staunch holder of her own beliefs. She will bend to more forceful opinions in order to keep the peace. She normally will refuse to get into arguments, and will avoid those who pick fights for the sake of fights. Her blow up with Emrys was completely out of character for her.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]cairo, egypt[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Kaliph El Fayed -paternal  grandfather - 89
Aisha El Fayed - paternal grandmother - 81
Jafari El Fayed - father- 59 - business mogul
Hafiza El Fayed - mother -47 - housewife, painter
Yara El Fayed - sister - 19 - university student
Yrene El Fayed - sister - 10
Yahia El Fayed - brother - 10 [/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Nubia, a sphinx cat[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]The first born of Jafari and Hafiza El Fayed, a powerful arranged match in the Egyptian Arabic spheres, Yasmin was treated well from the onset. Though her parents were disappointed they had not fathered a son, they knew there were further opportunities to keep the family name. As the daughter of a wealthy and aristocratic line, Yasmin was trained from a young age to be a proper Islamic young woman, Allah fearing. Just a year after her own birth, Yas' younger sister Yara was born. The pair were close from the very start, sharing in childhood adventures. Yas was always the creative one, painting pictures of the worlds they imagined up for themselves. Yara was always more pracitcal than Yas, reminding her older sister that reality existed outside of her own little world.

As part of their upbringing, the girls were put into classes and Yas immediately took to art. She loved the way paints mixed together to create something so real and so beautiful at her own hand. She had a natural talent and an eye for capturing movement. Though the family was based in the bustling city of Cairo, they often travelled throughout the country, and Yas always loved their holidays up the delta, loving the lush greenery, the gentle movement of the wind through the palm trees and tall grasses, the way the rocks cut up the river current. 

It came as a complete shock when Yas received a letter from Uagadou, explaining that Yasmin was in fact a witch. None of the family knew of a magical person in their heritage, but considered it a blessing form Allah rather than a curse. They would be able to leverage Yas' magic for their own benefit, though Yas didn't want to admit she wouldn't make a very good witch. Her parents researched more into magical history and learned of the British school called Hogwarts, and decided to send their daughter to the renowned school up north rather than the African version. If their daughter was magical, she would get the best education the magic school had to offer. 

Despite the amount of work Yas' parents put into her getting a good education from Hogwarts, Yasmin rarely wasted time studying. Instead, she spent her time painting, flirting, and making friends. After all, that was much more important to her. As much as she missed her family back in Egypt, she was used to always having her sister by her side and missed her constant companionship. She frequently wrote to Yara and her parents, updating them on her life and 'forgetting' to expand on details. It came to a head in her fourth year, when her parents questioned whether she was doing her duty to her family and doing well enough to support their decision to send her to Hogwarts. She barely scraped past her end of year exams, but Yas was adamant that it wasn't her fault completely. After all, she'd been thoroughly distracted by something else.

Emrys. A Slytherin boy in her year had captured her heart so firmly and decisively. They spent almost all their time together, or at least when they could. Emrys encouraged her to follow her passion with her art, to not bend to the will of her more traditionally valued family. Yas loved Emrys fiercely, ignoring whispers that he perhaps wasn't the young man she knew him to be. After all, she was the one who knew him best. She trusted him fully, allowing him access to her mind, body and soul in a way that would make her parents furious in their sixth year. Their relationship was sweet, loyal and care free. He was her muse for paintings, and he was always in her head. 

In their seventh year, Yas could ignore those cruel whispers no longer. She investigated and found that to her horror they were true. It was the first time she had seen red, the first time she had felt sure raw anger. She blew up at Emrys for betraying her trust, for making a fool of her, for ruining her and her reputation. He had known how sacred certain things had been to her, and had completely ignored her. She had never felt so hurt and betrayed. She swore to herself that she would never fall in love again.

That promise to herself was shortlived however. Yas took her time to heal, immersing herself in her painting. After graduating she continued her art, becoming more interested in digital mediums at the behest of Yara. Still wounded by Emrys' betrayal, Yas has been reluctant to fully invest herself in another relationship. Every time she sees Emrys in the news, something within her shifts. There's no denying her lingering attraction, but the trust between the pair had been absolutely shattered. His upbringing was no excuse for the way he had treated her.
 [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Yas had withdrawn into herself after the Yule Ball and subsequent explosion of the carriage after the Tournament. She didn't personally know anyone who died, for which she was immensely thankful. It still devastated her to know the loss of life could have been avoided, and that students her own age had their lives taken needlessly. She stopped painting for some time due to the trauma, turning to spending time with her family after graduation before returning to England to pursue a career in art. Yas didn't think much about Harry Potter's disappearance, though it was a true shame that the boy who lived had died in an off screen death.

However, when she went into the Hounds and Harriers pub one afternoon to see if she could get a job to support her art career, she had been shocked to find that Harry was in fact still alive and fighting.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Ana[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]27[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]gmt[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]magic[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]felix, astrid, brígh, petri, harry[/blockquote][/div][/div]