[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://i.pinimg.com/originals/a0/ec/71/a0ec710ae2f4bfe14450de37e01a7f33.gif" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""]
[/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]clodagh elowen fitzpatrick[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]Chlo-dah.[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Clo, Chloe[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]25
May 20th, 2000[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Female
She/her[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Half-Blood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Pansexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]9 inches, phoenix feather, alder[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Dominique Provost-Chalkley[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]5'7 in height
Clodagh is a dark haired, doe eyed woman. There isn't anything she feels is 'remarkable' about her appearance in anyway, or anything that might make her stand out. Though, she is quite pretty. She doesn't do a lot for her appearance. If anything she dresses as if to be unnoticed.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts - Ravenclaw[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduate[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]author (starving really... She hasn't published much and nothing under her own name).
illustrator at Obscurus Books[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]peanut butter
american string cheese
reading
fairy tales
making up stories/writing
children
her family
oversized sweaters
swimming
flowers/gardening
drawing/art/illustrating[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]cats/dogs/birds/snakes(Basically ANYTHING that likes to hunt mice)
voodoo
dark alleys
swamps
sunset/night in general
being smaller then something
mouse traps (especially when they use peanut butter at bait! Seriously, how dare they tempt her like that!)
humidity
fire
her work (writing) being rejected by publishers)
peppermint[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]To break the curse
To go on a nice date at night.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]... peanut butter without a doubt, lavender, wild flowers, a certain someone's cologne.[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]That's she'll never break the curse the Witch doctor placed on her, or that the curse would worsen to where she is stuck as a mouse.
Cats - ever since almost being eaten/killed so many time she's developed quite a fear of them.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Ah, Clodagh. So loveably annoying. No, really. People that meet her think "she's sweet, but awkward.". She's like a baby deer learning to walk. All knees, and no coordination. She's clumsy, she's awkward, and she chronically lives in a state of either fear or embarrassment ( because her own doing, of course).

Clodagh is, first and foremost, a very creative individual. She lives with her heads in the clouds. She's all ideas, and not much logic. She's inquisitive, and loves to learn new things. She absorbs information like a sponge. Though... She also has a knack for letting her curiosity get the best of her. She eavesdrops. A lot. And gets into all sorts of trouble with her snooping.

Clodagh is.... awkward. She's extremely shy, and she's just as uncoordinated in conversation as she is when walking. She just doesn't communicate well. She's likely to insult you, ramble on endlessly, or just not talk at all. Her lack of people skills is actually insanely impressive. She can offend even the most forgiving of people without meaning to.

Clodagh is very skittish. She scares and startles easily (for obvious reasons). She jumps at every shadow, and acts like anything and everything can potentially kill her at any given moment (also for obvious reasons if you know her secret). The world in general is absolutely TERRIFYING to her, but somehow she still manages to survive.

Despite being scared of... literally everything, she is a very loving person that can see the best in people, even if they themselves can't see it. This also makes her very gullible and naive... Because she wants to believe people are good.&nbsp;

About the Curse:
Clodagh is cursed to turn into a mouse at night (sunset to sunrise). While it's considered an animagus, it's closer to a "werewolf" because she has no control over it. This curse happened in early 2023. She can't stop this transformation.

In the last year she's been actively trying to break the curse, only there's been a bad... side affect. It seems the more she tries to break it the worse it gets. Before, she as always able to retain her human mind as a mouse, but in recent months she's noticed that her human mind is weaker and weaker when a mouse and instead mouse instincts are taking over. Often times she'll wake up under furniture and hurt herself because said furniture didn't have human sized space where she was.

Likewise, she's noticed that leading up to sunset her mouse instincts that to try to take over, and it becomes a war to stat in control of her mind leading up to her transformations.

After changing back, it can take her up to an hour to really start functioning like a normal person as well.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Ireland (though her family moved a looooooot)[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Quinn Fallon Fitzpatrick, mother, &nbsp;55, magizoologist.
Declan Taidhg Fitzpatrick, father, 56, magizoologist.

Karney Fitzpatrick, 34, brother.
Mannix Fitzpatrick, 32. brother.
Cullen Fitzpatrick, 29, brother. 
Emmaline Fitzpatrick, 18, sister.
[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]She has enough problems, let alone taking care of another living being...[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]From the time Clodagh was born, it was obvious she was an independent and sometimes unsocial child. She loved her three older brothers dearly, but she was always off on her own somewhere, getting into her own adventures, only to return with fantastic stories of adventure. Of course, most of these stories were made up, she had a brilliant imagination. She could spin the most beautiful tales out of the most mundane events. But, thankfully, she did not live a mundane life. See, her parents were Magizoologists, traveling ones at that. Clodagh grew up on every continent, in jungles, forests, deserts, plains and mountains. Her home was in her heart, and her backyard the entire world. She met extraordinary people and creatures of all shapes and sizes. 

As she got older, she realized she had an important decision to make. One each of her brothers had made before her, and one her sister would make many years later. To go to Hogwarts to begin her magical schooling, or be home schooled by her parents. It wasn't odd, many of the Witches and Wizards the family had met around the world home schooled. In fact, the majority of them did. It was perfectly normal! But, Clodagh wanted to have a chance to learn with other Witches and Wizards her age, and chose to attend Hogwarts when she turned 11. 

Her years at Hogwarts were good, and uneventful. She was sorted into Ravenclaw her first night, and did her best to live up to the name. She worked and studied hard. Of course, Care of Magical Creatures came naturally to her. She'd already encountered many of the creatures they covered in the class. History of Magic, to no surprise was another class she excelled in. And finally, she showed a knack for Transfiguration. All in all, she did well through schooling. Not the top student, obviously, but high marks and even a few job offers at the Ministry upon graduation. With her background, she would have been an ideal fit for the Department for the Regulation and Control of Magical creatures, but she declined. During her seven years she'd decided what she wanted to do. And that was to write. She'd been telling stories since she was a little girl, after all.

A few weeks after graduating, she packed up all her belongings, and went out on her own. She wanted to have her own adventure, no parents or siblings. Over the next several years the only real contact she had with her family were through phone calls, letters, and emails. She never stayed any one place for long, having learned her nomadic ways from her parents.  Eventually her journey brought her to New Orleans, Louisiana, in the United States. Her family had never spent much time in the state, and for good reason. It had a bad reputation for the Dark Arts. Clodagh wasn't going to be persuaded out of going though. While there, she met and befriended a young witch. The young woman's family had been in the area for generations, and she was happy to help Clodagh with her writing. Helping her find out what was fact or fiction. It was during her time here that she started hearing rumors of trouble back home. Students being attacked at Hogwarts. Some murdered. Clodagh's only sister, Emma, was still a student during the time and Clodagh felt increasingly nervous for her safety. Was Emma okay? None of the letters she received said Emma was in danger... 

At least until she heard Hogwarts was attacked. Many students were hurt, one had died, many others were kidnapped. Clodagh knew she had to return home to make sure Emma was okay. Unfortunately, the young witch Clo had been working with had other plans. Clodagh hadn't thought that the woman would take her leaving as an abandonment. And she definitely didn't expect the woman to go to one of the Voodoo Kings. The very one the woman had always told Clodagh to stay far away from. One minute she'd been packing her things into a bag, and the next she was waking up in the middle of a Bayou. Only.. she wasn't quite... human.

Clodagh was a mouse.

It didn't take her long to realize that at dawn each day, she transformed into a human, and at dusk into a mouse. That blasted witch doctor had cursed her. Since being cursed, life has not been easy. She'd been almost eaten or killed over a dozen times, and finally decided it'd be best to return home to Europe and hope a healer there would know how to break the curse.

Upon returning home she, unfortunately, didn't find a cute. But she did find a boy. A gloriously handsome man who swept her clean off her feet. They dated for a few months. A few blissful and beautiful months. Until he found out about her curse. He encouraged her to go back to New Orleans, to try to break the curse once and for all...

And so.... with a heavy heart, she left this beautiful man and went back to where everything started.

She searched for a long, long time... But after 6 months with absolutely no leads on who had cursed her, she reluctantly gave up. She started to search for other remedies, investigating other magical cultures to see if anyone could help her break the curse. This is how she was, eventually led to the Druids. She'd known many growing up, and visited Hy-Brasil many times from her parents work. Perhaps one of them could help? So, In the summer of 2025 she visited the island, pleading their most experienced healers to help her. Unfortunately nothing worked....

Heavy hearted she returns to London near the end of summer, though couldn't bring herself to find Aerick after a year to tell him her failures. That was when they found her...

Outcasts from Hy-Brasil that said they could help break the curse. They brought her to their "gatherings" to meet their friends and leaders. Who took her in, promising aid in her blight. The Order of Eternal Gaia was kind to her, making her feel welcome and accepted. While they couldn't break the curse now, they promised her the, with time and dedication Gaia might bless her and remove this burden.

They just happened to leave out the whole "evil cult" part... As fall began she was integrated more and more into the cult, and realized just how messed up this organization was, and that she wanted out, but by then it was too late. This mousey girl was too afraid to leave...[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]She was very worried about her sister during the events over the years. Though, Clodagh has been pretty focused on her own issues of late, so while she's aware of everything it's sort of hard to focus on the world falling apart when you're being chased by cats every night.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Sora[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]She/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]29[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]Mountain[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]I live here[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]To many[/blockquote][/div][/div]