[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://static1.squarespace.com/static/56c346b607eaa09d9189a870/t/58a643306fd27c86d8e78439/1487292822944/01_Saoirse_Ronan_CreamBG_208.jpeg"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]calliope ivory fleming[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]kuh·lai·uh·pee fleh-ming[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]cal, li[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]19
11th august 2006[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]cis-woman, she/her[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]half-blood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]bisexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]honeysuckle, unicorn hair core. 11 inches long and is supple. lightly colored and is elegantly carved.[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]saoirse ronan[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]due to calliope being a metamorphmagus, no one except her family truly know of her identity, considering every minute, hour or day, she takes enjoyment in changing her hair colour, eye colour and different aspects of her appearance. the changes tend to follow her emotions so red colour usually signify her anger, blue: sadness, yellow: peace, and etc. in relation to her playby, calliope stands a little taller at 5"8, while her playby is 5"5. her "true" identity however is a brunette fair skinned girl who enjoys the comfort of casual clothes on most days and formal attire on others. calliope likes to pair some of her outfits with silver glasses, and even sports a few tattoos around her body. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]ilvermorny: thunderbird
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]graduated, class of 2024
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]current: [b]legal:[/b] record keeper for st mungos hospital 
[b]illegal:[/b] black market merchant
previous: magizoologist apprentice[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]magical creatures, books, drinking (heavily), smoking, muggle things (drugs, movies, the whole lot), adventures, her ability to change how she looks, her siblings, strangely enough: her illegal job[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]her dead-beat dad, animal mistreatment, her current /legal/ job, the fact her mother disappeared, her instant change of emotion[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]to become the magizoologist she always dreamed to become...and to hopefully earn enough to move out.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]bacon, the way some wines smell, sea breeze, flowers[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]being stuck in her record keeping job for life, small spaces, her father disappearing the same way her mother did (even if she hates him)[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote][i]wild, impulsive, flighty, funny, 'street-smart', silver tongue[/i]

out of all the Fleming children, calliope tends to believe she's the...odd one out. from a young age, all the middle child believed was, there was no reason to uphold her parents views or face responsibility. considering...that's what temperance was there for. from this, people view the morphing-girl as [i]flighty[/i], and rather chaotic, a [i]wild[/i]-child if you may, which was also evident from her times in ilvermorny and the friends she stuck with there. as the fleming continued to grow, her parents expressed their disappointment in her, always adding the mention of how...[i]impulsive[/i] and too adventurous she was. to some, being seen as adventurous was a good thing, but calliope always saw it as a bad thing when it came from her parents. it was the same for impulsiveness, as hearing that word always bugged her, considering she believed she always thought before taking action on something, but parents' disappointment always stuck more than the words of friends or professors. though she has always been rather [i]funny[/i], tying that in with her other many qualities to her personality. 

calliope is also rather claustrophobic, seen from her current job as a record keeper. she hates being commanded to sort out the filing in the back considering how bad of a tight spot it can be. after her mom disappeared during the summer before her fifth year, calliope's personality remained the same, up until she reached her seventh year and prior to graduation. she had always been one to push her friends into fun-like activies and help her brothers realise some goals while they were young but with the fleming ageing, she developed a sort of [i]silver tongue[/i] and [i]street smarts. [/i] the two didn't make an active appearance until calliope was active in the illegal businesses of the wizarding world, always seen in the black market attempting to help sell products for others. either way, her words of persuasion usually allowed her to see the benefitting side to a situation. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Los Angeles, USA[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote][b]mother[/b]: Luciana Fleming, 43, former Auror (Missing)
[b]father[/b]: Theron Fleming, 45, former Quidditch player, now dead-beat
[b]sister[/b]: Temperance Fleming, 22, Ilvermorny Alum
[b]brother[/b]: elijah theron fleming, 17 turning 18, ilvermorny transfer: hogwarts hufflepuff
[b]brother[/b]: ___ Fleming, former Ilvermorny student - current transfer to Hogwarts[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]none, (though she wants a heck ton)[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]during the afternoon of august eleventh 2006, theron and luciana welcomed their second child, a young baby girl that they decided to name calliope — after the greek muse which also means beautiful voice. from the mythic legend, calliope was also supposedly the lover to ares, the god of war, which is the same story calliope followed whenever someone mentioned her name. it was ironic for the second fleming girl, named with a beautiful voice when she was born screaming out and continuous changing-coloured hair within hours of her birth. amongst the nurses and the fleming parents, it was revealed that their second child was a metamorphmagus, the first in their family line, and while it posed no danger, it simply meant calliope had a slight advantage with her appearance. though from her crying, her hair sported a dark blue, the same way it had done so as she grew.

growing up with a sister three years her senior, most of the stress was laid onto her. but considering how controlled and serious temperance was, calliope rebelled in her younger years, ensuring she would show a complete and different side from her sister. being a metamorphmagus played fairly well into it, using her ability to shift her appearance to simply cause mayhem and chaos, outside and inside of the family home. no one was hurt though. [i]luckily[/i]. with years passing on and calliope's parents introducing two more children, elijah and ___, calliope hated the idea of sharing responsibility with her elder sister, or upholding a good image and was somewhat glad they had a few years before entering the wizarding school just like herself. the sorting ceremony was interesting for calliope, who was utterly confused when she received her letter from ilvermorny just after turning eleven. she remembered stepping on the gordian knot once her name was called, the aggressive beat of the thunderbird's wings indicating the house she was placed in.

calliope's time in ilvermorny was average, with grades not really exceeding expectations unless it was muggle studies or care of magical creatures, as well as charms, aside from those three classes, it showed the fleming's shining qualities of being a student. though, the middle child was sure there were times the professors hated her, considering her wild and impulsive nature. but during the summer before her fifth year, fifteen — going on sixteen — year old calliope was faced with...something she didn't expect. well. no one did. while her father was a retired quidditch player, her mother was an active auror in the american ministry, partaking in missions still that would render the children worried at times. temperance more than everyone. during one mission, their mom...disappeared. it was odd, unexpected and no story could be drawn towards it. the searches began with news articles, search parties from other aurors and eventually with time, everyone gave up. even their father, who resorted to being a complete asshole mixed with alcohol and laziness. calliope kept busy though, only being a newly fifth year, as if nothing happened and instead tried to focus on her last two years of ilvermorny. it was hard to keep the family morale up during the holidays but luckily for the metamorphmagus, changing her appearance seemed to bring joy for her brothers and a twitch of a smile from her older sister. 

despite her mother's disappearance and temperance moving out into a home of her own after graduation, calliope managed to graduate ilvermorny with a future idea in mind. her goal had been in order for her final years, and upon graduation she became a magizoologist apprentice. it was the dream job she wanted to follow, the similar job line she had convinced eli to follow because of his interest in it. being an apprentice was just the start, to build a career and save for a home of her own away from her deadbeat drunken father. following ilvermorny's destruction, the fleming' moved to london, where calliope's apprenticeship continued like normal. but it was six months in when calliope was faced with another hardship, this time presented by her father. she remembered his threats as if he spouted them yesterday, to choose her dream and face the possibility of being thrown out or find an actual job to help "provide for the family". considering she knew being a former player would only get their family so far. to carry the family responsibility now that temperance wasn't around, calliope took up a full time spot as a record keeper for st mungos hospital. it wasn't an ideal job for a nineteen year old who was terribly claustrophobic, but it was better than a boring office job. 

to keep her life rather exciting, calliope used her ability and silver tongue to her potential, taking on a role in england's black market. it helped bring in extra galleons alongside her legal job, while keeping the fleming girl fairly sane. sane for a failure anyway. even if she was truly found passed out on counters, bar tops or even her desk at home with a few bottles of alcohol nearby. for someone that hated her father's actions, calliope reflected them rather well.[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]from ilvermorny's destruction, calliope felt her heart break. in the fleming family, she was the last to graduate from the wizarding school and it crushed her when she discovered precious memories had been destroyed. the death of the students and the beginning attacks from the purifiers left calliope in a state of shock and fear as the days followed, showed from her constant hair changes which usually shifted to a dark blue. 

if things couldn't get worse, harry potter, a man who many seemed to love and worship went missing before eventually dying, leaving everyone in mourning. then came along the dragons and azkaban's destruction...it was safe to say, calliope couldn't wait until her father reconsidered moving back to america.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote][s]bc rissy baited me out[/s] haise[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]they/them[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]teen of the nine[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]gmt[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]first lisa and suzie kept me captive, then colin, now chanel[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]bc i never pussy out like rissy does:
[b]dana, edrik, zenevieva, sari, jiyu, yvonne, bryelle, ares, flora, veronica, miles[/b][/blockquote][/div][/div]