[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://64.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_m3bzvqVuqt1r7ifqv.gif" alt=" " style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]raleigh orion flint[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]rah - lee | o - ryan | flyn - t[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]leigh.[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]twenty.
19th janurary.[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]he/him.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]pureblood.[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]bisexual.[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]sycamore wood, doxy wing, 11".[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]colton haynes.[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]raleigh stands at 6 foot, he has dark hair that he keeps cropped short and he has piercing blue eyes that seem to start straight through a persons soul. he likes to dress in the finer fabrics purely because that's how he was brought up though he doesn't like flashy. he prefers understated class when it comes to clothes. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]hogwarts | slytherin.
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]gradute.
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]curse breaker.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]food, fire whiskey, pubs, travelling, most animals, being on his own, thinking, showers, being with a girl, a soft bed, fire, swimming, running, boats, sailing, music, playing the piano, suits, leather shoes, leather jackets, hotels, expensive wine, vintage scotch, the color green, soda, cool weather, busy days, getting in late, early mornings, walking on the beach, friends, getting lost in new places, owning his own place, egyptian cotton, the wind.[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]rain, blue clothes, old shoes, scones, flowers, being nice to everyone he meets, hard beds, four poster beds, low ceilings, small doors, small houses, beer, a dying fire, the dark, scratchy sheets, silk sheets, badly dressed people, splinters, running out of money, hats, his hair growing long, dirty plates, a messy room, looking down at shorter people, looking up at taller people, being barefoot outside, camping, roughing it, pink shirts.[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]to not turn out like his father.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]musk, vanilla, clean sheets and salt water.[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]his father.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote][b]detached[/b] | he doesn't like showing his emotions. he never has done. his mother used to tell him that when he was a child he hardly cried at times when he was injured. he'd fallen down the stairs at the age of five and broken his thumb, he'd showed a house elf, obviously in pain but with no tears and trying his hardest to convince her that he was okay as she'd fixed him up. showing emotion is something he associates with showing weakness, so any sort of pain he's in, be it emotional or physical he doesn't show it.

[b]musical[/b] | there is one way to tell when he is feeling stressed or upset. he plays the piano. he's been playing since he was four. he used the piano as his escape, what he focused on instead of his parents. he doesn't play much any more, but when he does it's to relax and let go of every thought in his mind, because when he's playing all he hears is the music. everything else becomes void

[b]refined[/b] | he likes to think of himself as refined. he likes classy things and to dine out in fine restaurants and he can't stand listening to or looking at what muggle teenagers call slang. honestly there are some people in the wizarding world that he can't stand to listen to because of the way they talk. he never looks less than good, his clothes are mostly always pressed unless he's wearing jeans. he can talk wine for hours and drink scotch by the glass and still keep his head. the finer things in life are his calling, thanks to his parents wonderful and vast bank account.

[b]organised[/b] | he doesn't like mess. it's something he can't stand even as a child he was always tidy. he doesn't mind getting dirty, but he has to keep things tidy. his dorm is always immaculate. books need to go in order and everything has to be stacked so the largest is at the bottom, smallest at the top no matter what the items, and things that are the same size, the sides have to be straight. he figures he's a little OCD.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]england.[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]marcus flint | killed by his wife. 
pansy flint | died of mystery causes.

@dusti    / sister / 19.
--- flint / sister / 19.
--- flint / brother / 18.[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]none.[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]leigh's life was planned for him the moment he was born. he was promised to be married to the oldest daughter of another pureblood family, his education was mapped out by his parents and the job he would take after graduation was already waiting for him. he resented all of it. he grew up lavished in expensive clothes, toys and possessions in an effort by his parents to keep him quiet, to stop him asking questions and to keep him from getting in their way. it was their belief that children should be seen and not heard and when they were heard, they were to be punished. though when their father was in a bad mood, it seemed all he wanted to hear were his childrens screams and they could often be heard echoing through the halls and into the spacious grounds of the flint manor. as painful as their father's abuse could be, it was nothing compared to the emotional abuse that their mother took pleasure in inflicting upon them. it was hard to tell truth from lie, her story would constantly chance and it seemed their confusion and sometimes hurt fuelled her. the flint house was an unhappy one but everyone who walked through the doors remained none the wiser thanks to pansy and marcus. 

as parents, they did a number on their children. leigh grew up with a warped view of the world. women were vicious and coniving creatures that couldn't be trusted, they were willing to hurt with a word and not care how deeply it cut. men were supposed to be cold, collected and put on a face but behind closed doors were violent, handy with their fists and mean. it was those role models that shaped leigh into the cold and unassuming teenager that he became. 

the day he turned eleven was the day he saw a slight light at the end of the tunnel. there was freedom there, there was months away from the house and company that wasn't his parents. though he was worried. he'd be leaving his younger brother and his sisters to the hands of his parents but he couldn't not go. his parents were counting on him to do them proud, to be sorted into slytherin and carry on their disgusting family legacy. which he did, once sat under the hat, it took all of three seconds to choose slytherin house for him. he wasn't unhappy with the choice, given what the other three houses were but he couldn't help but wonder what his parents reactions would have been had he been sorted into any other house. 

the next seven years were filled with classes, making somewhat friends throughout his school years and recurrent visits home during the holidays. his seventh year was his most eventful. it started with a murder, it ended with kidnappings and more death. he does his best not to remember what happened, after all he'd been rasied to carry on and not dwell on the past, his parents had drilled that into him enough that weakness was the one thing that would hurt more than anything else, so he hasn't dwelled on it. after he graduated he started working at the leaky cauldron, taken in by the longbottoms after he'd refused to go home once he'd graduated. he can't say it was his favourite job, dealing with people wasn't his forte but he'd lasted long enough to get a feel for the job. then had come the news about his parents. his mother had murdered his father. that hadn't come as a shock, the death had but the fact she'd finally killed him, hadn't. 

that wasn't the only news to come out at the same time. his sisters were only his half sisters. that hurt a lot more than the death of his father. he'd never been really close to  his sisters but he cared about them, loved them and for their world to be turned upside down, he didn't like that they had to go through it. of course he kept this quiet and to himself, after all they didn't need him fawning over them and it wasn't who he was. well he wasn't who he had been but watching the way people interacted at the cauldron has made more of an impression on him than he'd realized. then the news of their mothers death reached him and he couldn't help but feel an imense relief that they were both gone, they were both out of their lives and the siblings, while orphans were free of the people who had made their lives living hells. 

it seemed that in death his parents weren't the smartest. after all their boulster about not leaving their children anything, their will spoke different. so the money was split between the four children and the house they grew up in still stands, while they decide what to do with it. it was only a few weeks after that that leigh quit his job at the cauldron, moved into his own flat and started working at gringotts as a cursebreaker. that's what he's been doing since and even his relationship with his siblings is improving, he see's them more and gets more involved in their lives, it's a slow process but it's happening slowly. 

 [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]leigh's always been a bit cynical, he's never thought the world was a good place to begin with so the events of the wourld around him haven't really surprised him. he lived through abusive parents, murders and kidnappings so to him a quarantine, an attack on the quidditch match and the other events that have happened are all pretty much par for the course in the world they live in. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]shadow.[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her.[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]27.[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]awst.[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]magic.[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]lucas weasley, edward lupin, sunday weekly, calder mugwump, katiya krum, sutton avery, aymeric courtemanche &amp; elliot porter. [/blockquote][/div][/div]