[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt=" " style="max-width:100%;" src="https://i.pinimg.com/564x/fd/fc/ac/fdfcac06d0893a49f91e22183be54538.jpg"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]aurelia rusti flint[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]uh-RAY-lee-uh [/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]rusti/rust – while it is her middle name, it started as a joke because of her sister’s refusal to go by anything but dusti, and has stuck with closer friends and family members. it’s so normal to her now, that she actively goes by it over her first name now.
[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]19.
February 22nd 2006 [/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]female. she/her/hers[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]pureblood [/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]pansexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]10 ¼ inches, rosewood, unicorn hair, extremely bendy[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]scarlett leithold[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]5’9”. Same as playby for the most part. She has a large floral tattoo on her back that wraps around onto her left shoulder, and is typically covered by clothing. Since her job consists of taking care of plants, she wears a lot of tshirts and clothes she has no problem getting dirty. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]hogwarts, slytherin
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]graduated 2024
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]owner of Forget-Me-Knot Florist
herbologist  
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]flowers, plants, Herbology, dirt in her hands, being outside, spring, lemon &amp; ginger tea, working/pleasing others, drawing diagrams of plants and studying them, potion making, cats, small spaces, keeping to herself, staying in order, over-sized sweaters, quiet nights, the breeze over the tops of trees[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]being yelled at, fire, her parents, screwing up a customer’s order, long conversations, close relationships, sticking up for herself (but is working on this), having photos taken of her/photos of her parents[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]For her shop to become popular for herbologists and people looking to get both magical and non-magical plants[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]citrus, fresh dirt, morning air, anything floral[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Her shop burning down
Parents returning from the dead/ghosts. They’re gone, and she doesn’t want to deal with them anymore.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]A reserved individual, it took years of silent practice for the Flint girl to achieve her current level of normalcy. There were a lot of times growing up where she learned when it was the right time to talk, or when to disappear completely. Like her twin, Rusti also takes a cautious approach to virtually everything. This doesn’t mean she always shies away from daunting tasks or obstinate people that come blundering into her shop, though. Once upon a time she would have turned around and walked the other way, and while that still happens from time to time under specific circumstances, these days she is able to overcome her flight instinct more often than not. She understands that the only way to overcome what her parents put her through is by working on herself and breaking down all the insecurities that she built up barriers for. Disconnecting and checking out completely doesn’t exactly work in the real world and when dealing with people that don’t necessarily care about who she is or what she has gone through.

Unfortunately that doesn’t mean she is always quick to open up to others. General conversation and pleasantries are easy enough, but she views a lot of base level relationships as transactions. With her parents, that was how it worked. Positive results lead to positive interactions. As long as she did what was asked of her, she would be fine and that she wouldn’t have to retreat to her safe spaces or be looked down on by her parents. She ultimately tries to follow this same line of thinking at work, though flips it around: her positive interactions lead to positive results. It’s a slow process, but certainly a start to understanding how other people outside of her family function.

Nowadays, she is more confident in her discerning nature, and sees the value in thinking things through first over acting on instinct immediately. From the outside, this equates well with her ability to gently take care of her plants and shop, something an aggressive touch would never be able to handle. For those that knew her in school, long gone are the days of her accidentally looking down her nose at others. She no longer strives for the perfect everything that was required by her parents, and therefore has started rejecting many of the things she used to parrot from them. It never really kept her in their good graces to begin with, but desperation allowed plenty of bad habits to manifest. Understanding the value of money, as one example, has humbled her immensely. Making reparations for the things she has said or done in the past is part of her attempt to break free of her guarded, reserved shell that she had built up around her for eighteen years.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]England[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote] Pansy Flint nee Parkinson, mother, deceased, 43
Marcus Flint, asshole dad, deceased, 49
Ernie MacMillan, biological father, 44-45

@raleigh       (half sibling through Pansy), 20
____ Flint (half sibling through Pansy), 18
@dusti       (twin sister.), 19
@sav      (half brother through Ernie), 18
@shreya       (half sister through Ernie), 18 [/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Nibs – small black cat[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b] – TW but it’s the Flints, so like, anything involving with them is going to be like this
[blockquote]Growing up in the Flint household sucked. There really wasn’t any other way to put it, because it was a constant war zone. Her siblings all took their own versions of abuse: physical, verbal, and emotional - and Rusti was no exception. While she evaded the physical part of it as best as she could, the onslaught of snide comments, screaming, and general disorder was more than enough to make her realize at a young age that there were a few ways that she could minimize it all. The first was disconnecting completely and retreating to the safety of her bedroom, though that meant nothing when it came to angering her raging alcoholic of a mother. She was nine when she found a small door in the back of her bedroom closet, and that became her haven more often than not, leading to her name being screamed through the hallways whenever her parents couldn’t find her. There was never really any sort of cool down or point where they weren’t actively trying to ‘harden’ her or her siblings, so most of the time she tried to stay away until the attention was off of her.

Her other option, and the one that happened more often the older she got, was playing her parents game. She became a sort of ‘Yes-man’ to them, doing what they asked and as perfectly as possible, because that meant she wouldn’t be on the chopping block in that moment. This unfortunately carried over into her first year at Hogwarts, terrified to not return an owl immediately if they sent her a letter, and spending every waking studying, afraid of finding out what poor grades would mean during the holiday breaks. It really didn’t take too much imagination to figure out what the many possibilities could be, should that happen.

And so Rusti spent a lot of her time in school studying, and while she wasn’t an ace student, she didn’t do horribly either. She barely made friends with others, and was usually found in the library or one of the greenhouses. Both seemed to have an adverse effect on students congregating and she liked it that way. Her personal bubble didn’t feel threatened, and only half of the plants kept in the greenhouses wanted to kill her on a daily basis. Those were far better odds than dealing with her parents.

Eventually school had run its course, and seventh year arrived. While it should have been spent enjoying the Triwizard Tournament, it was hard to do that when it came out that she and her twin weren’t actually the legitimate children of Marcus Flint. Ernie MacMillan was. There was a lot involved, ranging from bribes to keep the secret, to the fact that she had two more siblings. She had a hard time processing the fact that she had spent her whole life trying to appease a man that wasn’t even her father, only to have it thrown back at her over and over again. Was that the reason things were the way they were? Were they only targeted because they were illegitimate? She wasn’t even sure who she could ask, and she felt like it wouldn’t be fair to ask her sister for help in understanding it, despite being in the same boat.

But just as fast as that revelation came crashing in, it seemingly fixed itself. Rusti hated the way she reacted to the news of her ‘father’ being murdered by her mother, and the irony of it made it laughable at best. It was the perfect example of the pot calling the kettle black, and her mother apparently couldn’t handle the harshness of Azkaban, dying only a week later. 

What started as tears of relief now that seventeen years of horror were done with, soon turned into the realization that she had no idea what to do from there. She still had to graduate, and then there was the fact that her and her sister weren’t even legitimate heirs to Marcus Flint. Somehow the inheritance worked its way out in four parts, but she felt dirty having it. Yes, it was a head start into whatever she wanted, but it seemed like blood money. So she did what any good Flint (or not) would do – spent it.

Opening the florist shop was a staggeringly difficult process, considering she had zero business experience and had no idea what she was doing. There was a market for magical and non-magical plants alike, something she had noticed every time she went to the shopping district while growing up. But there were also very few stores for it, if any. Finding a tiny nook of a shop in Horizon Alley, Rusti forked over her portion of the Flint fortune, and opened Forget-Me-Knot Florist. Her own new safe place, and a spot where she could start working on everything she felt like she hadn’t been allowed to have before then.[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]As horrible as it sounds, she very rarely cares about the things happening in the world. She has had too many things happen to her in the last two years, to the point where pausing and taking a hard look at the world hasn’t really been possible. Her own personal and family issues have taken precedent, and she believes them to be of greater importance than the issues at Azkaban, or the recent problem with the druid island that she had never heard of before. 
She has no problem admitting that her pureblood status and family name most likely protects her from the majority of the horrid things in the headlines, and aside from what occurred at Hogwarts while she was attending, everything since has barely affected her. Maybe a bit selfishly, she hopes it stays that way, because working on herself has been much more important as of late than anything else going on. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@colin      [/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]he/him[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]25[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]EST[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]idk[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@grey       @cordelia       @lance       @mina       @lily       @cara       @nottingham       @steve       @jimbo       @blaise       @harper       @renard       @madeleine       @nell       @nessa       @charlie       @mickey       @fae      [/blockquote][/div][/div]
