[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" alt="" src="https://66.media.tumblr.com/df288d75dbac022c8c9785186743b8e8/tumblr_pxd7s34v9j1s5hgwbo4_400.gif"]
[/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Drusilla "Dusti" Kessia Flint[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]Druh-sill-ah[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Dusti. Call her anything but Dusti and she'll stab you.[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]19-years-old
February 22nd 2006[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Female. She/her[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Pureblood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Demisexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]11 inches, ash wood, and unicorn hair[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Charly Jordan[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Height: 5'10
Dusti is tall and slim with blonde hair and almond brown eyes. While not intensely obsessed with her appearance Dusti does make sure to wear flattering make up and clothes, knowing what does and doesn't look good on her. She's also a bit more higher end in terms of fashion because of her high society upbringing.

Dusti has several scars from her parents, however most are easily hidden/explained away. The worst is the remnants of a burn on her upper back and right shoulder.[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts, Slytherin[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduate[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]St. Mungos Phlebotomist (Lab)[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Working alone
Being outdoors
Winter/the cold
Ice skating
Reading
Candles
Flowers/gardening/herbology
"clean living" (like sustainable living/zero waste)
hard sciences (where answers aren't subject to change because of someone's interpretation)[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Her name (call her Drusilla and she might stab you)
Mentions of her parents (it complicated)
Being a Pureblood
Water
Being touched without warning
Crowds
Dark arts
Night
Alcohol (Her mother was an alcoholic so she's seen the damage it does)
Talking about her "feelings"[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Deep down, Dusti dreams of a little cottage, surrounded by fields of flowers. And in those fields of flowers happy blonde haired children play.... Basically a life free from her parents' legacy and their way of life.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]lemons/limes, oranges, grapefruit... Okay, she just likes anything citrus![/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Dusti highly dislikes kitchens. Though while this was a full out fear for years, it's lessened to extreme discomfort.
 Confined spaces
the dark[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Dusti is.... troubled. Simply put, she's the product of an abusive and broken home. She has many of the classic signs of an abuse survivor (distrust, wary, guarded), and also the signs of someone from a physically abusive home (aggressive, trouble regulation emotions). Much of her past has come to define who she is today, despite the abuse being "over".



Dusti doesn't trust people. She's closed off and guarded, refusing to let people in no matter how hard they try. She fully believes that no one is "good" for no reason. Kindness, courtesy, generosity. To her they are all charades, hiding your real motives. No one does something for nothing. 



Dusti is not known for being "warm and fuzzy". In fact, you'll usually hear her name in the same sentence as "ice queen", "asshole", or "cold bitch". She's very straightforward and honest to a fault. If she hates you she'll tell you she hates you. She's also quick to insult others. So if she thinks you're an idiot and she'll tell you you have the intellectual capacity of a goldfish. She's cold, harsh, angry, and bitter. 



Dusti is a stubborn soul. It's all she really had growing up, trying to hold onto herself, or whatever parts of herself her parents didn't crush into a million pieces. She sticks true to herself, no matter the cost. This has, of course, gotten her in quite a bit of trouble growing up because sometimes that meant butting heads with authority figures. 



Growing up in an abusive home taught Dusti to always be on high alert. She had to to survive. She doesn't drop her guard easily and stays aware of her environment and those in it. Her abuse taught her to read certain emotions well, for her own protection. 



Of course, a few individuals have managed to get through Dusti's thick armor. For those lucky few, Dusti is still very guarded. She keeps most things to herself. But she isn't totally closed off. Since the deaths of her parents (well... the parents that raised her) she's been trying to be more "accepting" of new influences in her life. Better influences. Though... it's still very difficult.

 [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]England[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Pansy Flint nee Parkinson, mother, Deceased at 43
Marcus Flint, "father" (sort of. Not biological. believed to be father until Dusti was 17) murdered at 49
Ernie MacMillan, biological father (didn't find out until Dusti as 17) 44-45 ish

____ Flint (half sibling through Pansy), 20
____ Flint (half sibling through Pansy), 18
____ Flint (twin sibling.), 19
Savtaj MacMillan (half brother through Ernie), 18
Shreya MacMillan (half sister through Ernie), 18

ex-boyfriend, 19 (Shadow will make him eventually, haha)[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]A dark skinned sphynx cat named "Danny" that she adopted from a rescue[/blockquote]
[b]history: (TW - ABUSIVE CHILDHOOD, MURDER)[/b]
[blockquote]Marcus Flint and Pansy Parkinson were likely never in love, despite their long marriage. A man married a woman, probably for the political status of two pureblood families, to raise a new generation of perfect pureblood children. But it was never perfect. Marcus was obsessed with his career and "making his children strong", while Pansy was a serious alcoholic. 



From a young age there was intense conflict in the house. Her father, when angry, was quick to violence. Physical and verbally abusive was daily, all in hopes of "making his children strong". Pansy, likewise, was obsessed with appearances. She drank like a sailor and when drunk.... Well, things got ugly. The Flint manor was a constant warzone. One wrong step and they could set a parent off and chaos would reign. Dusti learned very young how to read her parents and when trouble was coming.



Unfortunately, Dusti wasn't the only child. As Dusti grew older, she came to the conclusion that she needed to protect her siblings. To try and focus the Flint parents wrath on her, to spare her siblings. She could take it. She was strong enough. Her parents wouldn't break her. So, she grew cold. She learned to deal with the abuse. One particular incident solidified her existence. Her mother, drunk (as always) scalded her with a pot of boiling water. Even to this day the scars remain.



Dusti's only real relief came from Hogwarts. Being able to go away to school. It was Dusti's first time meeting other kids her age in a setting where she could "be herself", though that was a very unpleasant person. She only made a handful of friends because of her attitude and the teachers had quite a bit of trouble keeping her in line. 



But, it was freedom. Just a small taste of it. And it was glorious. Dusti was sorted into Slytherin her first night, and as she progressed through the years her Slytherin traits started to shine.



Sixth year was when things started to change though. That was the year the murders started, and the kidnapping. While it was an emotional rollercoaster for the students, Dusti was fine. Though, Dusti did come to realize that she had very strong feelings for one of her friends. While she confessed those feelings in sixth year, it wouldn't be until the summer break that the two started dating.



Seventh year was a likewise rollercoaster, as the Tri-Wizard Tournament was in swing. But, Dusti was happy. She had a great boyfriend to keep her mind off things. But good things never seemed to last. At the beginning of the school year it was discovered that Marcus Flint wasn't her biological father. Her mother had had an affair with another man, Ernie MacMillan. Apparently Marcus had known for years as well, as Ernie had been bribing him to keep quiet. After all, Ernie had a wife of his own. And through that marriage, Dusti had two younger half siblings. 



Her Illegitimacy was a huge blow. How would you feel if your entire existence had been a lie? Though that was just the tip of the ice berg. Her biological father wanted nothing to do with her. It seemed no parents wanted Dusti.  By Christmas though, the trouble escalated. Marcus had apparently been having an affair and Pansy took it personally. She killed him, and, a week after being sent to Azkaban died herself. The parents that had raised Dusti were suddenly gone, ripped away without any warning. 



After graduating, Dusti took up a job at the hospital, working in the lab. While bright and very methodically minded, Dusti had poor people skills. The lab was the perfect place for her. Away from people where she could work in peace. 



She moved in with her boyfriend after graduation and things were good, for a time. But, again, good never lasts. They broke up, and Dusti struck out on her own.

[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]This whole mess started when Dusti was a 6th year, so she was at Hogwarts during the murders. Though, Dusti has never been "involved". She keeps to herself and prefers it the way. Even the most recent events have been largely ignored by her. The Azkaban break out hit a little close to home though, as that was where her mother died, but &nbsp;she pretends it doesn't bother her.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Sora[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]29[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]Mountain[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]I live here[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]Too many[/blockquote][/div][/div]