[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://64.media.tumblr.com/b2d97faa0c729bbfff5e11403e1a9962/tumblr_o7pw11ldYv1sagi1uo6_540.gifv" alt="(image here of playby)" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Ilija Cayden Fortescue
[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]Ih-Lee-Jah[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Ili, Caycay. 
[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]25
2000, 15 August
[/blockquote][b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Male, He/Him[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Half Blood
[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Straight[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]Fir and unicorn hair. 
[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Jake Hold 
[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Ili has many tattoos, mostly to cover up his many scars from his worst curse breaking accident. His right leg blew up from just above the knee and he has a golden replacement that he usually hides. 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts alumnus, Hufflepuff
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduated
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Curse breaker
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Old things, sunlight, ice cream, sand, druid culture, his siblings. 
[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Anything that explodes, loud noises, darkness, nightmares, questions about his past, ghosts, his limp in his walk, clicking sounds; especially those that pens make.
[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]He forgot. He wishes to see his siblings do well in life though. 
[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Ice cream
[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Being chased by somebody with a bottle of milk, any and all kinds of explosions, clicking sounds.
[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Ilija was once a perfectly happy and bubbly young man full of hopes and dreams. Now he's pretty much just a wreck. He keeps no bad habits and takes care of his body surprisingly well all things considered but there is more cheer to be found on a graveyard than around him these days. The only exception usually being around his family, where he feels more joy. Still even there he's very quiet and brooding, preferring to stay in the background and out of the way. 

Ili has a lot of anxiety and tends to sit still a lot when he gets anxious. He can easily get caught up in his own mind and his version of reality. He hasn't accepted the loss of his family despite it being several years ago. He's on average very calm despite his more moody and brooding presence and never lashes out because he hates loud noises. 

He's very protective of those he cares for most, wishing to save them from all kinds of harm, his own trauma included. He's by nature a helpful person and loves being productive. He doesn't enjoy days spent sitting still and when he's having a good day or period he usually is very active and always busy. When his depression takes hold he tends to brood, not doing much and choosing to interact as little as he can get away with, which is usually limited to a few sentences at best. 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]London (diagon alley)
[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Abigail Fortescue, 58-years-old, mother (cares for husband full-time)
Florean Fortescue jr, 62-years-old, father (terminally ill)
Vasilia Fortescue jr, 21-years-old, sister
Felix Fortescue, 19-years-old, brother

Hannah Webb, deceased, fiancee
Floyd Fortescue, deceased, stillborn son
[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]-[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]CW: death, ptsd and mental health issues in a broad sense. 

Ilijah found his childhood to be mostly unimpressive. He was four when he became the proud older brother of his first sister and several years later found himself with a second siblings, at first also presumed to be a sister. He loved his siblings and would often join mom in putting them to bed, even if it made little sense. He was very caring.

He himself was discovered to be allergic to cows milk at a very young age. It certainly complicated life for him and both his parents, as they had to be careful he wouldn't stuff just anything from around the shop in his mouth. While not immediately lethal it caused him immense pain and suffering to consume any products containing cows milk. Ice cream was... complicated.

School came and went without much of a hiccup. He went to school, made a lot of friends and was a generally cheerful, happy and bubbly kind of guy. He met his sweetheart, a girl by the name of Hannah Webb. They dated most of their teen years and after graduation pursued the same career, curse breaking.

It was exciting and a little scary! Ilija was thrilled to be out in the world with his Hannah but still wrote home as often as he could. He and Hannah truly lived in the moment and were at times a little careless. She ended up pregnant at eighteen and after the shock wore off the couple was delighted to no end with the idea of becoming parents. They talked about maybe looking into a safer career. They talked about buying a little house to live in and making a home for their family. Ilija often wrote home with little updates. 

Nine months passed and several weeks before the baby was due, Ilija proposed to his girlfriend. They'd just bought an adorable little cottage and had decorated a room for the child. Everything was perfect. That was the last night he wrote home to his family on a happy note. 

A few weeks later the first of the tragic events took place and they found their son, little Floyd, to be stillborn. Their hearts were heavy with grief, but at least they had each other. They found solace in each others arms and closed the door to the little nursery they'd built. It was sad, but Ilija knew it'd be fine. He'd started a long letter home in hopes of telling his siblings and father was they were going through. They decided to delay the wedding, first wanting to grief the loss of their child properly.

Grief was not an easy emotion to work through. After a month, both Ilija and Hannah were doing better again though. At times they got a little distracted but they had plunged into work, determined to get a good life going in case they were ready to make a family again. To get a nice fortune to build their life together in anticipation of another child, only this time planned. It wasn't meant to be, however. 

One day they were raiding an old tomb when everything fell apart. An explosion was triggered and Ilija watched as Hannah, the unfortunate soul to have triggered it, disappeared from the face of the earth in what felt like slow motion. He himself lost most of his right leg but his life remained in tact. Two days later he wrote from the hospital, the last his family would hear from him in a long time. "Something went terribly wrong." Nothing more, nothing less. No explanation. 

It took a lot of owls, six months of recovery in terms of physical health and several visits to the shared grave of his would have been wife and their stillborn son before he wrote. He wrote two letters, one for his father and one for his mother and siblings. He told his father everything in a long and heartfelt letter, begging his father to keep the truth from the rest of the family. He told the rest only that his son had passed away and that he and Hannah were no longer together. He never offered elaboration and changed the subject when asked, even going as far as to outright refuse to talk about it at all.

By this time it was obvious things had changed, since his personality was nearly a polar opposite of before. His cheer and joy replaced by a much more serious demeanour. He was no longer the person people knew him to be and the ones that knew of the accident respected his wishes and didn't speak of it to him or others near him.

He developed many nightmares, severe depression and started taking on a role of far more weight. He started acting like an older sibling when he was home. He had PTSD, most easily triggered by the inane clicking of a pen, every click like a drum vibrating through his skull, slowly eating away at his sanity. He often freezes, completely unable to move after hearing sounds that bring back the memories. He's known to cease moving and almost act like a statue, turning pale and stone cold as memories flood over him. 

He still went home for Christmas every year to keep the tradition alive but has never revealed even the physical changes to his family, apart from his father. The news that his father was terminal hit him like a blow. He was always the one that Ilija had relied on more than anything. Despite knowing he'll need his siblings and mother more than ever he hasn't figured out how to open up to them. He told them the limp was the after effect of a small work incident. He's often uncomfortable around them, nervous they'll find out the truth if they start poking around. 

When he's at ease he manages to forget for a while and things are almost good. He recently sold the little cottage he'd lived in for several years after the tragic events and the situation with his father had him moving back home, although he has no idea to break the news to his family. After keeping secrets that big for that long it becomes very hard to tell the truth and open up. 
[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Ilija follows the events of the world with a heavy heart. Due to his severe depression he's not overly concerned as he doesn't have the energy to consider things not close to him. He mostly worries more about the family he does have left, although the fear of losing them often addles his thinking and keeps him very unnerved by even the more mundane situations. He's terrified they'll suffer and while he'd never admit it, all the events are part of the reason he travelled back early to be around his family.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]hpes[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her 
[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]I was born at the dawn of the world.
[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]I could be in +2......
[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]This place found me.
[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]Heleen Arista Lisanne Oppedyk, Auguste Benoît Courtemanche, Melody "Lúthien" Perdita, Argentum du Lac, Shreya Dawn MacMillan, Byron Ray Blishwick, Virvatuli Lahti Taikalainen, Deva Samael di Angelo, Sergei Alfred Rohs, Ocean Orion Wildspear
[/blockquote][/div][/div]