[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://66.media.tumblr.com/1e7a826661cea87db11b16c1f1343105/tumblr_pvmmyugeaE1wuvctqo1_500.png" alt="Felix Image"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Felix Valentin Fortescue[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]FEE-licks Val-IN-teen FORT-ess-kew[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Usually just “Felix” or “Fortescue”

[b]dead name:[/b]
Felicity Valentine Fortescue (name legally changed upon turning 17)[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]18
September 21, 2006[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Transgender male; he/him pronouns[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Half-blood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Pansexual and polyamorous[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]14 ¼ inches, vine, unicorn hair, quite flexible[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Nathan Westling[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Felix is 5'10" with a thin but slightly muscular build. He is fair-skinned, with brown eyes, freckles, and curly red hair, which he has cut short. He has both ears pierced once on each earlobe and wears fake plug earrings when not in his Hogwarts robes.

Felix doesn't always keep his school uniform the neatest in the world, and he is usually found wearing Muggle clothing when he can. He prefers an edgier "skater" style, typically plaid shirts with jeans and the like.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts – Ravenclaw[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Seventh year[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Ice cream; his family; Diagon Alley; coming up with new flavor ideas; tattoos, which he intends to get eventually; being able to magically alter his appearance; Muggle technology; school and learning; Gobstones; social justice[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Winter, solely because it means less business for the ice cream parlor; customers who take too many free samples without buying anything; being misgendered; “ginger” jokes; homophobia and transphobia; the Dark Arts; those who look down upon Vasilia for being a Squib; being out in the sun for too long, because it means getting sunburnt; know-it-alls; Wandless Magic[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Felix's immediate goal is to finish his schooling at Hogwarts with his NEWTs to his name and then go to work at the family ice cream parlor. After that, he's not really sure, but he would see a much more masculine version of himself in the Mirror of Erised, for certain.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Caramel sauce, new books, and vanilla bean[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Felix most fears never fully passing as male. Second to that, he fears the closure of his family’s ice cream parlor.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]
[b]responsible[/b]

Felix is a fairly responsible kid. Although he doesn't always get the best marks, he does his best to do what is asked of him and usually delivers on that. He can be trusted to do things and to follow the rules—even more so now that his father is terminally ill.

[b]clever[/b]

He is also very clever. Whether it's whizzing through a book or finding an answer to some other problem, there's no doubt that Felix is intelligent and is very true to Ravenclaw in that sense.

[b]inclusive[/b]

Felix is inclusive, and he doesn't see any reason why he shouldn't be. His family runs an ice cream parlor, and he knows how happy ice cream makes people. If he can bring that same feeling to other people just by accepting them for who they are and being a friend to them, then why not?

[b]introspective[/b]

Felix is introspective, always looking within himself. This allows him to keep himself in check, especially where things like privilege are concerned. At the same time, this occasionally becomes a negative for Felix, who also tends to be rather critical of himself and his shortcomings. 

[b]anxious[/b]

Felix can be anxious, especially when it comes to how other people will react to his appearance. He knows that he doesn't always "pass" for male and that there are people who will still inevitably misgender him or call him by his dead name, but he looks forward to a day when he won't have to worry about that.

[b]perfectionistic[/b]

Unfortunately, Felix can be a bit of a perfectionist. He puts his all into things, and sometimes that means spending too much time on projects or assignments simply because he is so interested in what he's doing.

[b]procrastinating[/b]

Tied to his perfectionism is procrastination. Felix could definitely use some better time management skills, because he finds it easier to put things off than to think about doing them to anything but the best of his ability. Usually, this means that he can be found in the library late into the night, desperately trying to finish something that's due the next morning.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]London, England, UK[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote][b]mother:[/b]
Abigail Fortescue, 58, caregiver, half-blood witch

[b]father:[/b]
Florean Fortescue, Jr., 62, terminally ill, half-blood wizard

[b]siblings:[/b]
____ ____ Fortescue, 24, open

Vasilia Abigail Fortescue, 20, Squib
[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Although he was given the name Felicity Valentine at the time of his birth and socialized as female for the first sixteen or so years of his life, Felix had always had a suspicion that he was different. From his toddler years, he was drawn towards more "boyish" toys and activities. He loved running through Diagon Alley with his toy broomstick and climbing trees. He preferred trousers to skirts and dresses, and his parents never discouraged him from what some might have seen as too "masculine" for a little girl.

Likewise, they were never ashamed of his older sister, Vasilia, because she had been born a Squib; they had just taken it in stride, and Felix had never known any differently. Obviously, he understood that Vasilia was different because she couldn't use magic, but she was always just his sister. He had never known her any other way, though he was slightly disappointed that he wouldn't get to go to Muggle secondary school with her.

By the time he entered Hogwarts, Felix had accepted that he was simply a girl who was capable of being "one of the boys". With as gendered and antiquated as Hogwarts could be sometimes, he never openly questioned the binary options. It was confusing to him. As much as he loved school and learning all that he could, he wished that he knew where he fit in.

Otherwise, being at Hogwarts wasn't so bad. Felix was Sorted into Ravenclaw House, which he felt fit him. He was surrounded by other students who shared his same creativity and enjoyment of learning. He liked all of his classes, for the most part; they all provided him with different angles from which he could view the world. It wouldn't be until his third year that he would add his favorite subject—Muggle Studies—to the list of what he studied, but even just the basics were exciting to him back then.

By the age of thirteen, he thought that he might have been gay. That didn't feel right, though, because he had had crushes on people who weren't female. He then came out as bisexual, which seemed to fix that problem, and he stuck with that label for a while.

Then, as he was well into his fifth year of school, Felix had another realization: Maybe the reason why he didn't feel right about his identity was because he wasn't a girl. Initially, he wondered if all of the awful things that had been happening at Hogwarts and in the world at large were messing with his head, but those feelings remained. He was a boy; by that point, he was practically a young man.

He came out to his family and some of his closest friends first, asking them to call him by the name Felix and to use the pronouns "he" and "him" with him, although he didn't come out to the rest of the school as transgender until the start of his sixth year, when it would be less disruptive for him to request to be treated as any other boy at Hogwarts. Because his birthday fell in early autumn, he was able to change his name and relevant paperwork that same year, once he was seventeen and an adult in the eyes of the magical world.

Felix also joined the Gay-Straight Alliance when it was formed in his sixth year, eager to get to know other people who were either like him or weren't put off by the thought of learning more about the LGBTQ+ community.

As he established himself as male, the labels that he had put on his attraction to others also changed. He chose to identify himself as pansexual, rather than bisexual, to place emphasis on his openness towards being with anyone of any identity. A few more experiences also made him realize that perhaps he wasn't monogamous, either.

Having discovered from the Healers at St. Mungo's that transitioning with various spells and potions would be easier said than done—likely requiring him to continue recasting spells and taking potions all the time to keep the effects from wearing off over time without more advances in potioneering—he began to look into how transgender Muggles did things. While the thought of some of the procedures they had was frightening to him, it was all much more permanent than anything that the magical world had yet invented. Given that he couldn't exactly take time away from school for anything like that—and because he was still under the age of eighteen, anyway—the most that Felix was able to do at that point was purchase a binder.

Beyond all of the searching to figure out his identity, the rest of the world was sort of a mess, too. Although his family remained tight-knit, Felix grew worried as his father's health rapidly declined and led him to a terminal diagnosis. While Felix offered not to return to Hogwarts for his seventh year so that there would be that much less stress on his family, his mother and father encouraged him to stay in school. He did, and he was ultimately happy to have made that decision.

Now, with a few months left, Felix looks forward to finishing his Hogwarts education, continuing his transition, and beginning the rest of his life.
[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Life for anyone in attendance at Hogwarts has never been particularly "easy", although the past few years of Felix's schooling seem to have taken that to an unsurpassed level. While the dead Ministers for Magic were unsettling, the dead Muggle-born students were even more so—especially as a Ravenclaw. Then came the kidnappings and the attack on King's Cross. The more that all of this kept happening, however, the more that Felix grew desensitized to it. There was so much going on that he couldn't allow it to affect his ability to carry on. That was what the people who had carried out those killings and attacks wanted. They wanted people to fear them, and Felix decided that he couldn't let them do that.

The Triwizard Tournament seemed like an end to all of that. There were months of relative peace, until Harry Potter went missing and the students who had been visiting Hogwarts were killed upon their departure from the school. Felix barely had time to mourn them when news came of another attack on a different school. This time, it was Ilvermorny, in the United States of America, and their students were invited to attend Hogwarts.

Harry Potter was presumed dead around the time that the Americans began to arrive. Days and weeks blurred. Felix went back to Hogwarts. There were killings outside of the school, this time—possibly a serial killer, but who really knew for certain? Felix worried for Vasilia, that she might get mistaken for a Muggle and caught up in something, but that didn't happen.

What did happen next came all at once. Dragons in Hogsmeade, where Felix felt fortunate not to have been at the time. The next morning, though, the damage done was clear: Azkaban had been destroyed at that same time.

That fear that he had told himself not to feel came back. At least Hogwarts was secure; he considered himself lucky there. Putting a security troll in front of an ice cream parlor wasn't going to work, though, unfortunately, so he just had to hope that the Ministry would do its job to keep Diagon Alley safe until he could finish his NEWTs and be there for himself… just in case.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@audrey[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]She/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]21[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]US/Canada Central/Eastern[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]Current member![/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@samira, @chrissy, @clarence, @parvati, @brody, @ezekiel, @penelope, @kaylee, @maxima, @muffet, @oona, @priscilla, @camila, @honey, @tamatha[/blockquote][/div][/div]