[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt="GIF" src="https://66.media.tumblr.com/333b2651ff0f6e583dcdf04497a19599/tumblr_inline_ovjojj4vTY1smwr80_500.gif" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Claricia Anja Freund[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]KLAIR-eetz-EE-yah AN-yah FROIND[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Clara, Ricia, Ricky, Freund, Captain[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]37
March 30, 1988[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Cisgender female; she/her pronouns[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Half-blood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Homosexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]12 ⅞ inches, blackthorn, dragon heartstring core, hard[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Melanie Scrofano[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Claricia stands at 5'8" in height with a thin, athletic build. She has fair skin, blue-grey eyes and medium-length brown hair. She has her ears pierced once on each earlobe, noticeable dimples, thick eyebrows, and no shortage of scars from Quidditch accidents over the years.

At present, she has three tattoos. Her first, a blackwork tattoo of an anatomical heart on the inside of her right wrist, was done when she was twenty. Her second was a tattoo of the word "LIEBE" (German for "love") in black script on the left side of her ribcage under her breast, done when she was twenty-five. Her third and most recent—done in 2023 upon the announcement of her captaincy—was a blackwork tattoo of a wasp, located behind her right ear.

Prior to her retirement at the end of the 2024–2025 Quidditch season, Claricia could be most often seen in her Quidditch gear or other athletic clothing. Outside of Quidditch matches and practice, however, Claricia tends to opt for more masculine looks. She owns quite a bit of dragon leather, tends to go for neutral tones, and prefers trousers and suits over more feminine garments.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote] Hogwarts — Gryffindor (Autumn 2000 – Spring 2006)

Durmstrang (Autumn 1999 – Spring 2000)
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduate
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Quidditch scout (as of the 2025–2026 season)
Wimbourne Wasps – Captain (2023–2025)
Wimbourne Wasps – Chaser (2011–2025)
Heidelberg Harriers – Chaser (2006–2011)[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Quidditch; taking charge; Weisswurst; the feeling in her muscles after a tiring Quidditch practice; the catharsis of cursing in German; waking early; feminine women, in terms of attraction; drinking men under the table; rock music; the color yellow[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Incompetent referees; fruity cocktails; Erklings; being talked back to; the color pink; traveling via Portkey; wearing dress robes; playing Quidditch in the rain; folk music; admitting failure[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Claricia’s greatest goal in life is to move beyond her playing career and maybe, eventually, settle down with someone.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Dragon hide, pretzels, and broom polish[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Claricia’s greatest fear would be Fiendfyre; second to that, she fears never really being able to be vulnerable with other people.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote][b]confident[/b]

Claricia is, above all, confident. Especially when it comes to Quidditch, she knows what she’s doing and how to do it [i]well[/i]. Her self-assuredness, however, tends to come off as stubbornness: She doesn’t give in easily to anyone, and she’s known among her fellow Quidditch players as being someone who can be notoriously difficult to work with.

[b]talented[/b]

There’s no doubt, however, that Claricia is a gifted Quidditch player. She has spent nearly twenty years as a professional, and she has been described as “one of the smartest tacticians of the league” and was able to prove herself a formidable opponent as captain of the Wasps. On the side, she is also an avid broomstick collector.

[b]hard-working[/b]

Although gifted on the Quidditch pitch, Claricia is equally hard-working. She has put countless hours into Quidditch and has been driven by her passion for the sport, continuing on despite adverse weather conditions and—at times—physical injury to get where she is.

[b]demanding[/b]

Claricia has always given 110% of herself to her sport and expected the same from her teammates. While some of them likely considered her rules to be overkill, she has always tried to take a “tough love” approach. She’s blunt when needed, but she does truly care about other people—even if she’s maybe not the greatest at showing it.

[b]impatient[/b]

Even though she tries not to be, Claricia is also impatient. She operates on the view that time is of the essence. As a reserve player, she made a terrible Seeker—since she hated to wait for the Snitch—but her primary concern is with other people’s timeliness. Having to repeat herself constantly just because someone couldn’t be bothered to show up on time gets old… 

[b]regretful[/b]

The side of herself that Claricia has tried to keep separate from her work is how much she actually cares about other people—especially her fellow players—and the death of Edmund Windsor as well as numerous others hit her a lot harder than even she expected. She now carries with her a lot of survivor’s guilt and wishes that she were capable of doing more to express how much others truly mean to her.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Freiburg im Breisgau, Baden-Württemberg, Germany[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote][b]mother:[/b]

Henrike Freund, 59, German translator, half-blood witch, divorced from Manfred

[b]step-mother:[/b]

Sieglinde Freund, 62, homemaker, half-blood witch

[b]father:[/b]

Manfred Freund, 63, German Ministry of Magic employee, half-blood wizard, divorced from Henrike and remarried to Sieglinde

[b]sisters:[/b]

Constanze _____ (née Freund), 33, open occupation, half-blood witch
Crescentia _____ (née Freund), 31, open occupation, half-blood witch

[b]step-sibling:[/b]

_____ Vogel, 31, open occupation, half-blood wizard, son of Sieglinde

[b]extended relatives:[/b]

Various, on both sides.

[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Claricia Anja Freund was born on March 30, 1988, in Munich, Germany. She was the first child of her parents, Manfred and Henrike, who were both of magical heritage and employed by the German Ministry of Magic.

For the most part, Claricia's earliest years were uneventful. When her mother became pregnant for a second time, her parents decided that they should move out of the city, in order to give their children more space. They chose to settle in Freiburg im Breisgau—better known as simply "Freiburg"—near the Black Forest, and Claricia's first sister, Constanze, was born soon after.

Owing to her parents' schedules, Claricia was sent to a non-magical school in Freiburg for her primary education. She wasn't the best student in terms of her behavior; her teachers found her to be very hyperactive, but she was curious about the world around her. As she became older and started to exhibit signs of magic, her parents realized that she needed some way to channel her energy and gifted her a toy broomstick—probably the best decision they ever made, in Claricia's later opinion. She quickly grew to love Quidditch, though she found it a shame that her sisters—Constanze and Crescentia, the latter of whom was born when Claricia was six—were too young to form a team with her.

At the age of eleven, Claricia moved on from her non-magical school to Durmstrang Institute, one of the premier boarding schools in the magical world. As reputable as her new school was, she found it difficult to fit in with her peers—and even more difficult to live up to her teachers' expectations for her behavior.

Added on top of that was the fact that her parents had been having marital problems, and Claricia only lasted a year at Durmstrang before her mother and father divorced and she and her younger sisters moved to just outside of London, England, where her mother took a job as a translator. Although she was upset about not being able to see her father so often, it worked out well enough for Claricia, who was able to transfer to Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry in time for her second year of her magical schooling.

Starting school at Hogwarts, where Claricia was Sorted into Gryffindor House, was exciting for her. Although she understood some of what had happened in the war, it was never a concern for her. The rules were nowhere near as rigid as at Durmstrang, nor was the discipline as strict. It suited her much better, especially once she found out that she was old enough to try out for her House's Quidditch team. Even though she was only a reserve player for her first two seasons, she managed to learn a great deal from her older teammates—and hone her skills enough to know that she was best at playing Chaser.

Claricia and her sisters would spend the majority of their summers in Germany with their father and extended family members. It was important to her to maintain her German identity, being so far from "home" most of the time, though—in the summer before her fourth year—she learned that her father was seriously dating another woman. While it was difficult at first to adjust to the change, Claricia grew to realize that Sieglinde was by no means the "evil stepmother" that she had imagined her to be.

From her fourth year on, Claricia was playing Chaser on the Gryffindor Quidditch team. Although she was concerned that her academics wouldn't be sufficient for it, she made Captain in her sixth year, which continued on through her final year of school. She left school with NEWTs in four subjects—Defence Against the Dark Arts, Transfiguration, Charms, and Ancient Runes—though her focus remained on Quidditch.

Rather than join the British and Irish League, Claricia took up an offer to return to Germany in order to play for the Heidelberg Harriers. Her father remarried to his girlfriend, Sieglinde, and everything seemed as positive for Claricia as ever. She began to learn a great deal more from playing professionally, rather than at school, including that she certainly wasn't straight.

About a year into her career with the Harriers, Claricia began a relationship with one of her fellow teammates, another woman. Things between them grew serious quickly, and Claricia came out to her family as a lesbian. The relationship didn't last but ended amicably, a saving grace for Claricia's time with the Harriers. She continued to work towards being the best player that she could be, and she wound up with five seasons to show for it.

As time passed, Claricia began to feel that she needed a change. When the opportunity presented itself to move to England to play for the Wimbourne Wasps, she took it, beginning in the 2011–2012 season. Returning to England after so long felt refreshing, and it was. She had to work even harder to stay on top of her game in the British and Irish League.

The early years of her career with the Wasps were great, though things started to slow to a trickle when it came to any hope of further progression on the team. While she was a good player, Claricia knew that she had a tendency to come off as too abrasive with her teammates—and occasionally, too, with the referees—but she remained a strong player, through and through.

Before she knew it, Claricia was among the older players in the league. While she was eyeing retirement from the sport before injury ended it for her, she was announced as the Wasps' next captain before the start of the 2023–2024 Quidditch season. To say that she was elated was an understatement, and she gave the captaincy her all. She had, at long last, cemented her value to the team, although she was disappointed that the season didn't end with their winning the League Cup.

With 2024–2025 planned as her last season as a player before moving into scouting, she was even more determined to take the Wimbourne Wasps to the finals. The season started off horribly, with a devastating loss against their rivals, the Appleby Arrows. The Wasps could only go up from there, and so they did—obliterating the Fitchburg Finches 360 to 20. Although the rest of their matches weren't quite so perfect, it was enough to remain at the top of the leaderboard. The Wasps had proven themselves as one of [i]the[/i] teams to beat, and—what was more—they'd reached the finals against Yorkshire.

The blood, sweat, and tears of Claricia's entire career had led her to the finals match, on her team's own turf, and she was more prepared for that match than for any other in her life. She was eager to see what her team could do, especially with a player straight out of Hogwarts on the roster for such a vital match. It had been going well, too… until it didn't.

As explosions rocked the stadium and flames began to tear through the crowds of spectators, Claricia had the advantage of being on her broomstick. Terrified and angry though she was that the match had had to end that way, she was able to fly herself a safe distance away, the image of green inferno seared into her mind.

Learning that one of her own teammates, Edmund Windsor, hadn't made it out of the stadium alive devastated Claricia beyond words. Fearing for how self-destructive she might become if she didn't, she immediately decided to check herself into St. Mungo's for psychiatric treatment, where she remained for a few days before being discharged to outpatient care.[/blockquote]

[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]The events of the past few years in magical Britain thankfully spared the Quidditch world, for the most part. Claricia, although living in England again since 2011, was able to keep most of her attention on her sport through the tragedies.

As the dangers moved to Hogwarts and Muggle-born students were killed, however, she began to grow increasingly concerned. It was terrible, although she knew that there wasn’t very much that she could do about it, and it only got worse as the Triwizard Tournament came to an end and the visiting delegations from Beauxbatons and Durmstrang—the latter being her former school—were killed in explosions.

The devastation began to hit closer to home for Claricia from that point, and she questioned how Hogwarts planned to absorb so many students from Ilvermorny so soon after the previous tragedy, especially as Harry Potter himself went missing and more and more murders seemed to be occurring.

The biggest hassle related to the destruction of Azkaban in Claricia’s daily life was the increased security around matches, though she was grateful that nothing seemed to be amiss, really. Then, despite the Hag's Fever outbreak and subsequent quarantine measures, she was able to take the Wasps to the British and Irish Quidditch League finals. It wasn't as though she would have had time to leave for Germany, anyway, and her team's success could not have been more of a thrill for her.

Although she was able to make it away from the stadium alive following the "accident", Claricia has struggled with the knowledge that so many people—including one of her teammates, a rookie—died in the explosion, while she survived it. She immediately sought psychiatric treatment at St. Mungo’s, with the goal of working on putting her life back together in the aftermath.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@audrey[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]She/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]22[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]US/Canada Pacific (for now)[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]Current member![/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@brody, @camila, @chrissy, @clarence, @dasha, @ezekiel, @felix, @honey, @kaylee, @maxima, @monday, @muffet, @parvati, @penelope, @priscilla, @samira, @tamatha[/blockquote][/div][/div]