[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://i.ibb.co/t4cq4ys/Aaron-Taylor-Johnson-Source-on-Instagram-aarontaylorjohnson-aaronjohnson-nocturnalanimals-kickass-pi.jpg" alt="" style="max-width:100%;"]
[/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]rhys alexander greyback[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]reese alecksander gray-back[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]there are a handful that call him Alex, but not many[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]August 25, 2000[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]cisgender, He/Him[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Half-blood, werewolf[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Straight[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]10 inches, Blackthorn, Dragon heartstring[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]aaron taylor-johnson[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]5'11" , 

Rhys appears very much like his playby, he will tend to keep his hair shorter sometimes or a bit longer where you can see his waves and curles and pictures of himself younger will show much longer and wavy/curlier hair and less facial hair. He wears glasses at times for reading. Rhys also carries many random scars across his body, mainly his torso from existing as a werewolf along with a larger scar near his shoulder where he was bitten as a young child. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts, Slytherin[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduate, 2018[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Curse Breaker [/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]+ firewhiskey
+ reading
+ rainy weather
+ quidditch
+ music
+ his siblings
+ organization
+ museums[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]- full moon ([i]naturally[/i])
- chocolate
- limitations of being a werewolf
- clutter
- feeling inadequate 
- being dismissed/ignored
- people who can't step up when needed[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]to be accepted and respected, especially in a position such as an Auror. [/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Freshly brewed coffee, old book smell, peppermint, cinnamon[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Becoming the monster associated with his father and namesake, hurting his discovered family or anyone he is close to and loves. Also the pure rejection from society. [/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Driven to succeed, cunning, determined, resourceful. From a young age Rhys had to adapt to a world that did not accept him, did not want him. This injustice against an innocent left an impression him, but did not get in the way of his goals. From a young age Rhys learned to adapt, he had to especially with his upbringing and his name. Rhys is definitely more on the introverted side of things but when his temper gets the best of him (as it does often) he isn't afraid to speak his mind. All outwards appearance show a man of great constraint and self-control but brewing underneath the surface is something angry and something unyielding.  Rhys had been faced with an important decisions prior to entering Hogwarts at age 11, did he use his mother's name "Winchester" or continue to use his father's name knowing the two very different paths it would mean for him. He chose the latter, he wasn't going to let this man, this [i]beast[/i] define who he was going to become in this world. 

The Sorting Hat had actually sat on his young head for a moment, where would he place his boy? This quiet, observant, bookish yet driven and unhesitating in his goals. Rhys didn't mind either way even if the reputation of Slytherin house was well known and certainly didn't help his case with his public image issues. Overall, however, Rhys did not want to fit into that prototype expected of his name and instead he just wanted to get through school and learn as much as he could. Unfortunately, his upbringing hardly affording him tons of pre-existing knowledge as many of his house-mates had so he used his determination to study, read and absorb all he could. 

Rhys considers himself an intellectual, he wasn't much to get into trouble or receive detention. At least not at some rate to earn him a reputation, but while he didn't break the rules on purpose he chose to ambiguously follow those he perhaps did not agree with. However, as a werewolf he certainly did his best to follow those very specific rules give to him by the Hogwarts staff for his own and other student's safety. A professor had sat him down and told him the story of Professor Lupin, the previous DADA professor and how badly the families had reacted to the knowledge of his lycanthropy. 

Your average intellectual, if one does exist. Rhys was not made a prefect or Head Boy, the discrimination against his name was far too great no later than two decades after the last war. While it angered and frustrated him to be on the end of this senseless injustice he took it in stride. Any outburst from himself would only prove their point, so he kept calm and kept his cool and punched mirrors, walls and doors when nobody was looking. When he was older, in his final years at Hogwarts he discovered he had half-siblings. While this discovery was certainly unexpected it was not unwelcome. 

Family. Rhys liked the idea, it was something he'd never had and the idea warmed his heart. As the eldest he felt he had to help them or at least reach out, protect them if needed. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Caerleon, UK
[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Charlotte Winchester - witch - mother - deceased
Fenrir Greyback - werewolf - father

the various greyback half-siblings[/blockquote]
[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Screech Owl, Eris[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Fenrir Greyback, weapon to the Dark Lord and an infamous name in the magical community. With his goal of infecting as many young witches and wizards to create a lycanthrope population it only made sense if he not only bit but bred them too. Charlotte Winchester had been a young Witch and recent graduate of Hogwarts. Although she existed at the school during the time of the Golden Trio and even those Order of the Phoenix students who returned to Hogwarts to finish and education and NEWTS she was a bystander, a spectating Hufflepuff who was just happy for peace, but peace she would not get. The young witch was home from Hogwarts and living on her own as her parents had been victims of the war she was out and about her small village and not quite home as the sun was setting over the horizon. Fenrir, licking his wounds from his side losing the war was looking for a fresh victim, but not quite to bite but to have. 

Fenrir attacked Charlotte, but left her alive. Though I'm not sure how alive one can be so broken and beaten, and she found out just after the new year that she was [i]pregnant[/i]. A decisions was made, an important one. The terrified young woman would keep her baby, out of some kind of motherly love but also out of great fear if Fenrir decided to come back to claim his spawn. The thing with small villages, however, is people knew. People looked at her, they whispered when she walked by if their eyes locked there would be nothing but pity in them and shame back in Charlotte's. The wounds from the war were still too fresh, not there was hardly any redeeming qualities to the Greyback name. 

Rhys was born without incident in August of that year, he was a normal baby by all accounts and the only feature that sent chills down his mother's spine were his eyes, blue eyes that he most certainly inherited from his namesake. The village was concerned at first, but once it became clear that he was not a werewolf as his father was people settled down. Now, that didn't mean they accepted this child and were glad that he did not bear the name that brought much fear. That did change, however. The year when Rhys turned 5, he and his mother were walking back to their small cottage as the sun was setting and it was getting dark. Charlotte had an innate fear of being out too late, considering what she had gone through and was hurrying the distracted little boy along when she paused. She felt the hairs standup on her arms and the chill up her spine, she turned and there were those eyes. Those blue eyes and that decrepit snarl and she froze for a split second. But that split second was enough for Fenrir to attack her again, and again he had her but this time she did not survive. 

Rhys stood there and watched as his mother was attacked by this inhuman thing, he was so young and he didn't understand what was happening but then full terror took over and he ran. The only place he could think to run was the neighbors, a middle aged man and wife who's kids were all out of the house and they heard this screaming little boy approach them and as they went toward the crime scene they saw his mother's remains but Fenrir was nowhere to be found. The couple took Rhys in until they could find other arrangements, and the boy was traumatized. Nightmares plagued him, as they still do at times. 

One week later, Fenrir returned with his true purpose in mind. The moon was full and high and he approached the small cottage, transforming right in their front yard. 

Well, you know the rest. Before he knew he he awoke at St. Mungo's a few weeks later, and was force fed a wolfsbane potion. Once he had physically healed he was sent to a magical orphanage in Caerleon. The staff at the orphanage knew of his condition and the wolfsbane potion kept him from harming himself or others, save the rare few times he fully transformed and was let loose in a nearby forest. Growing up there was difficult, even without families the other magical children still had their views of werewolves and Rhys grew up knowing when people were staring and knowing when people were talking about him. But while he was angry as a young boy he learned that he had to push that aside. Yes, he was different but he could be better than that. 

When Rhys turned 10, it was [i]let slip [/i]who his father was and who [i]he[/i] really was and of course what had actually transpired that night 5 years prior that resulted in the death of 3 innocent people and his transformation. Well, it was devastating to say the least but Rhys knew he had to make a choice. If he kept his name "Winchester" he could go through life with merely the prejudice attained by being a werewolf, but as it usually does, people would find out who he was eventually and that kind of a fall would not be something he was sure he could handle. [i]But, [/i]if he owned it and carried it with him--well the challenge was there but he could make something of himself and try to lessen the hate that came with "Greyback". In a sense, it was the inevitability of society knowing, just get it out of the way and deal with it now. He was not the monster his father was. 

Rhys' heart was pounding in his chest standing in the Great Hall, he stood next to pretty girl he couldn't help but keep glancing at. She smiled at him and then continued chatting with her friends 

[i]"GREEN!" , [/i] "[i]RAVENCLAW!"  [/i]

Applause and cheering from the table with the blue banners. 

"[i]GREYBACK!"[/i] 

There seemed to be a pause from [i]everybody[/i] in the room, staff included. He went up to the stool and the sorting hat sat on his head for a moment, pondering the fine line this young boy walked.  

"[i]SLYTHERIN![/i]" 

There was some light applause from the Slytherin table as he found the farthest point in the back to sit among curious glances from all tables. 

His peers viewed him with a curiosity, those children of the war either hated him for his name, his blood status or b/c his namesake hurt one of their family members. Rhys certainly left his first year actually quite miserable, his only friends the books in the library and the knowledge they contained being his solace. Quidditch was also something that caught his attention and his his heart well in his chest, but alas his monthly sickness did not afford him the schedule to play on the team if he chose to the following year but he figured he might have been blocked from trying out as well. No matter, he wouldn't be a quidditch star but he could still succeed. 

In summary his time at Hogwarts grew better with time, after the initial shock of his name the other students and staff began to remember that despite the name he was still just a young boy. He made friends, in his own house and other houses, even had a short term girlfriend at one point though dating wasn't much of a priority for him, his introverted self seemed to come out more when around those he was attracted to. Rhys did very well in his classes, he enjoyed learning about different subjects and even the odd class such as Ancient Runes and Arithmancy that other students hardly took unless they knew they needed the OWL or NEWT. 

It wasn't until close to his final years at Hogwarts did he make an amazing discovery during the Sorting Ceremony that year. 

[i]"GREYBACK!" 

[/i]Again that sill pause in the Hall and suddenly he felt many eyes on himself, he turned to see a small girl walking toward the stool. The normally in control and self-composed Slytherin young man looked like he'd been confounded. He had....a sister? Greyback was hardly a common name in the magical community of the UK. It was also a turning point for Rhys as he watched the young girl head toward the table with the yellow banners, the students there auspiciously greeting their new housemate. A family. It wasn't something Rhys had pondered on, he had grown up essentially an orphan, and he felt drawn to her. Suddenly there was this void he didn't realize he had. 

Rhys befriended his younger sister, and later on he would befriend his other siblings as well. For someone who had grown up so alone it was something new and wonderful in his life. But, he still had his goals. His good grades had given him the OWLS he needed to finish the NEWTS he needed, but what was in store for this young werewolf after the safe haven of Hogwarts? Rhys had wanted to change Greyback image, if only to redeem himself and his newfound siblings. So, what about an Auror or a Hit Wizard or some cool Ministry Job? 

Well, i'm not sure about you but i'm sure they could count on one hand how many werewolves worked in the Ministry of Magic. Dreams aside, Rhys had to settle for his very wounded pride and chose to work as a Cursebreaker for Gringotts. His knowledge and eagerness to learn would work well and it reminded him of the place that had been his home away from home as a child in Caerleon, the museum. He wouldn't forget the snub nor the treatment of those in similar boats as him, it was always in his mind as he went through life planning his next move, his next step up. [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Rhys had only heard stories of the previous Wizarding Wars and never thought he'd live in a world with such instability himself. By the time the events at Hogwarts and King's Cross occurred he had already graduated, but he was able to visit Hogwarts once more during the Tri-Wizard Tournament, when it turned out another sibling was competing in the Tournament. He thought he had met all of them or would have figured they would have been in the UK and attending Hogwarts, so it was a fair surprise to meet a brother from Durmstrang. There had been a sense of pride in his brother, that he was [i]allowed[/i] this opportunity and positive attention and he did his best to push down the jealousy that also came with that. Especially after the tournament was over and he found out that his brother had been killed....[i]murdered[/i]. 

This enraged Rhys, this senseless act of violence took his brother away and now over a year later there had been no justice, just nothing. There was something on the horizon and Rhys didn't know what it was but he could feel it, and the attack on Hogsmeade and Azkaban breakout did nothing to settle those nerves. But if he was bothered he didn't show it, he observed, his demeanor always cool and collected. 

The events of the last few years, the death of Hermione Granger, the disappearance of Harry Potter, the attacks by this so called Purists group leaves Rhys uneasy and unsure of what to do about it, but only with the sense that something must be done one way or another. [/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]vanessa[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]t h i r ty , [i]ugh[/i][/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]GMT-8 [/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]ad on proboards.com[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]none at this time[/blockquote][/div][/div]