[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/862654302715904020/862655261898702848/malcolm005.gif"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Malcolm H. Hagrid[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b] 
[blockquote]Mal-com H. Hag-rid[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Typically goes by Hagrid by everyone except his parents.[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]21 (just)
April 3, 2005[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Cis-gendered male, he/his[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Part giant, halfblood. Please find the applicable [a href="https://alohomorax0.proboards.com/thread/10924/fee-fi-fum-giant-oneshot"]one-shot[/a] for the part-giant ability[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Heterosexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]12" English Oak, dragon heartstring core.[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Jared Padalecki[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]As the son of part-giants - although, his mother still does not concede to this heritage! - young Malcolm grew up [i]big[/i] and he grew [i]fast[/i]. Playing with kids twice his age in the village, the boy also matured mentally faster than other children his biological age. Now, Malcolm stands at an impressive 8'5"and he is entirely full of muscles. His father has told him on many occasions how much he reminds him of himself in his youth, though Malcolm cannot see how as Hagrid has let himself get chubbier in his married years. He has one bad scar down his thigh from an incident with a magical creature that even his giant-blood could not protect him from. The scarring is still healing, even years later it's a deep pink colour. Malcolm just thanks his lucky stars it wasn't 2 more inches to the left. He didn't like the thought that he could have lost his favourite appendage that day like Ili lost his leg. He does have a couple of magical warding tattoos, although the artist wasn't terribly happy about how many needles they went through to make it happen.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling &amp; status[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts, Gryffindor, graduate[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Trainee Curse Breaker since 2023 - traineeship has been extended due to needing more practice with the magical side of Curse-Breaking. The Goblins, Malcolm and his mentor, Ilija have discussed the need to extend the traineeship as a special access program for the diverse wizards.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]- Enjoys animals and magical creatures and is particularly good with them having grown up with Ruebus and Maxime and their myriad of exotic pets.
- Adores quidditch, though never pursued it as a serious hobby as he doesn't believe he's aerodynamic enough and that he'll do far too much damage if he were a beater. Besides, he couldn't become one professionally even if he wanted to.
- Learning new things, even though it doesn't always come easily to him. 
- Friends and family; although his little brother annoys him because he's done rather well on the school quidditch team. Arse.
- Stoat sandwiches because he grew up eating them with his Pa, even though Mamman was not a fan. 
- Riding bareback on the Abraxan that his mother breeds; there's nothing better than flying free and feeling the wind through his floppy locks.[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]- that his brother plays Quiddich. Wanker.
- when people ask him to do things that he clearly cannot... like intricate, delicate work with his hands. Don't ask him to do embroidery, he'll not talk to you for a good day or two.
- cabbage. It makes him fart the house down and [i]no one[/i] wants to experience part-giant farts.
- purists because they're muppets. As a part-giant, Malcolm has experienced a great deal of discrimination in the magical community.
- being asked about his giant grandparents. It's just [i]rude[/i].
- being told to 'be careful' because other wizards are such fragile creatures.  [/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Malcolm is a good part-giant, with the manners instilled by retired Headmistress of Beauxbatons Academy. He also knows how to muck-in, get dirty and work hard, which were skills he learned working alongside his father, Hagrid. He's friendly, although can be cautious in his approach with general wizard-folk as he was bullied terribly in his childhood for things completely outside his control, like being easily the size of the seventh years when he was a firstie. He has a temper that was inherited from his giant grandparents, although the careful parenting he received by two very loving people have given him the tools to [i]mostly[/i] control it. 

Instead, the temper shows mostly in his stubborn attitude. He's not yet as skilled magically as his mother, but he's a determined young wizard and so he does not let that fact get in the way. [s]He's not as old as her, so he knows he'll get there[/s]. He's fiercely loyal, which is another time that people will see flashes of the giant temper when people 'mess with' a friend, family member or innocent creature. 

He can be clumsy and careless, mostly because what his fellow wizards would be damaged by... well, doesn't affect him nearly as much. He's not ashamed to enjoy the positive aspects of his ancestry, often taking pride in being asked to help with the physical side of tasks or.... just showing off his impressive muscles. There has to be some perks to being a part-giant young adult, right?[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Scotland, United Kingdom and France during the summers.[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Fridwulfa - paternal grandmother - giantess - deceased
Mr Hagrid - paternal grandfather - wizard - deceased
Grawp - paternal uncle - giant - living his best gianty life in his own section of the Hagrid estate.
Ruebus Hagrid - father - part giant - retired, currently potters around looking after his wife's Abraxxan and his other creatures on their estate in Scotland.
Olympe Maxime - mother - [s]part giant[/s] witch - retired Headmistress of Beauxbatons Academy, known for her superior Abraxan stud stables
____ Hagrid - brother - part giant - Slytherin sixth year[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Many animals that are family owned, however his current occupation does not lend itself well to keeping pets himself. [/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]The first born of the Hagrid family, young Malcolm enjoyed a few good years of the sole attention of his parents. He would join Hagrid on his daily tasks about the estate, ensuring the various animals that found sanctuary were well looked after. Even as a little tacker, he could carry a big bucket of grain or water that even a ten year old human would otherwise struggle with. Though he was quite content with this scruffy lifestyle of sleeping in the pumpkin patches with the hippogryffs, his mother would also demand that he had the manners enough to 'pass' in polite society. He'd have to scrub up for dinner, leave his muddy shoes at the door and learn the difference between all the forks and knives before his half-decade birthday. When he became a big brother, let's just say that it's lucky the kid was also part-giant because the [i]amount of times[/i] he'd accidentally dropped his brother on the head as an infant is borderline criminal. It wasn't a purposeful act, though. His brother was a squirmer and Malcolm was always distracted by other things.

After the new addition to the family, they would always devote a good portion of their time to holidaying in France. Maxime was particularly fond of the culture of her homeland, as opposed to the wild vastness of the Scottish highlands. He learned early to 'fit in' with the different crowds, although found that both the magical folk of France and England were just as cruel as each other when it came to his being of diverse-decent (as his mother puts it, [i]rather than part-giant[/i]). He grew to be protective of his little brother in social situations, but when it came to defending himself... well he punched one child in a fit of giant-temper when he was 8 years old and they had to be rushed to hospital with broken ribs. Since that incident, Malcolm had to be very careful not to retaliate to the bullies.

Malcolm remembers listening to his parents hotly debate whether he should attend Hogwarts or Beauxbatons. It was one of the only times he remembered them actually raising their voices at each other. In the end, Hogwarts was decided upon because there was a change in leadership in Beauxbatons and his mother did not like the new Headmistress. Hagrid likes to joke that he won, but Maxime likes to remind her husband that is not the case. 

His years at Hogwarts passed relatively easily in the first few years. He did very well in most of the theoretical classes, however the practical magic classes such as Charms, Transfiguration, Potions and Transfiguration were a hard slog for the kid. He had to work four times harder to grasp the spellwork than his fellow students and many classmates were quick to point out he was a [i]stupid, slow giant[/i]. By second year, his family had employed a tutor for him who he grew very close to. In fact, by fourth year he probably had a burgeoning crush on the tiny girl. It didn't help that she was also the Seeker for the Gryffindor team. She was three years his senior and so he had to find himself another tutor once she graduated, unfortunately. Oh, the hidden tears he cried into his pillow the evening of that graduation.

In 2022, his sixth year, Hogwarts became [i]dangerous[/i]. For muggleborns, anyway. He was glad that his tutor had graduated in time to miss that, as she was a tiny muggleborn herself. Malcolm became even more protective of his little brother now that he was also boarding at the school. There was a period of time that he was called to the Head of House's office for his temper every other day, but by the seventh year he'd calmed down enough to focus on his studies. 

He was annoyed that he would graduate just before the Tri-Wizard tournament and miss out on a year with the Beauxbatons Academy students. Thankfully, he was accepted into the traineeship with Gringotts Bank to become a curse-breaker and so he was able to focus that disappointment into his new adventure. He spent his time being trained by Ilija - who often found Malcolm's disregard for the safety rules to be ... a cause for conern. However, his traineeship has been extended as he still works towards mastering the various magical aspects of his job... so he must be doing ok, if his trainer advocated for him with the Goblins, right? 

He particularly likes being involved in missions that may include handling dangerous creatures, because he's pretty darned good at that. On at least one occasion, he has had to be involved in a mission as a giant liaison - why the wizard folk think he'd have more rapport with them, Malcolm was not entirely sure. He was not brought up giant, after all. He did handle his Uncle Grawp well enough, although it wasn't a regular thing growing up around the miniture giant uncle because his mother was not particularly keen on Grawp. His father said it was because Grawp hadn't learned to use a fork.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]RoadRoo[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]She/Her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]31 years of age[/blockquote]
[/div][/div]