[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"]
[img src="https://i.ibb.co/fdn27yd/ezgif-com-gif-maker.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt=" "]
[/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]layla eleanor hendricks[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]lay-la el-eh-nor hen-der-ecks[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]just layla[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]22
August 31, 2003[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]female, she/her[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]half-blood, quarter veela [/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]pansexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]10 inches, hornbeam, unicorn hair, flexible[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Hayley Williams[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]5 feet 2 inches, looks very much like her face claim and she typically keeps her hair its natural blonde though over the years she has dyed it various colors depending on her mood. She also has a handful of tattoos. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts, Gryffindor[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduate[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Musician&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Playing Guitar and Bass
Singing
Reading
Long walks
Traveling
Rock, Classic Rock and Metal
Laughing 
Flirting
Partying
David Bowie
Tattoos 
[/blockquote][b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Boring people
Country music
The “I can play Wonderwall” guitarists 
Rude people 
Liars 
Killjoys 
[/blockquote][b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]To be a respected musician, respected for her talent versus her looks
[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Lavender, rain, fresh cut grass, popcorn
[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]not being able to play an instrument ever again, to lose her creativity. Her family injured in an attack.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Layla can definitely be described as a bit of a free spirit, but also an extrovert in all ways. One might say the life of the party that enjoys talking to people and the noise and bustle of a large crowd. She is aware of how her veela heritage, albeit only a quarter, can affect people and it doesn’t bother her much in terms of wondering if someone is being genuine or not. In fact she is a natural flirt who enjoys the attention to a point and enjoys the “game” of it. Her free spirited nature makes her less likely to enter something committed however if she does choose to she does it with her whole heart. This has definitely led to many situations of broken hearts since she does go all in but in the end she isn’t fearful of it. 

Despite her typically happy demeanor it doesn’t mean that Layla isn’t prone to her bad days, where she can be down in the dumps. Wearing one’s heart one’s sleeve constantly leaves the opportunity for a lot of pain, so when she is hurt she definitely feels it. She tries to hide it but she is more sensitive than she lets on. Sarcasm is also something that isn’t too uncommon for her but she likes to keep it in good fun versus being hurtful, she is a people person after all. There is a certain level of charisma not to be confused with whatever veela charm she inherited but she finds that people do in fact like to talk to her and she likes to talk to them and they tend to gravitate that way. 

Layla can be a bit of a rebel, when she wants to do something she does it with everything she has. It might be a bit stubborn but more she is willing to do something if she absolutely believes in it and this extends to people. When she has someone she is close to and trusts, she will do whatever she can for them. In a way she can be stubbornly un-selfish, which ends badly more than it does good.

[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]London, England[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Mother - Amelie Hendricks, half-veela, 47
Father - Michael Hendricks, 48 - Obliviator
[/blockquote][b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Little Owl - Angie[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Layla was born in late summer to Amelie and Michael, she was a beautiful baby girl though there was no doubt that this would occur. Amelie was a half-veela after all and a native of France where her family resided. She had met Michael who had been an Obliviator for the English Ministry while he was in France. Naturally, he fell head over heels for the half-veela although they genuinely had a loving relationship. This became the model for Layla as she grew older and most likely why she isn’t one to shy away from her feelings and sharing them with others as well, even if it doesn’t always end in a great way. The girl seemed to be running before she could walk and as soon as she was able to form words she just kept talking, she was a handful to say the least but it was a happy family after all. Amelie’s parents might have preferred she had married someone with a bit more prestige, an Auror or politician or someone with a bit more influence but Amelie wasn’t one to so easily give into her family’s ways. 

That small rebel streak was passed on from mother to daughter and the rowdy child showed herself to be fearless especially when she believed in something. Her parents tried their best to keep her somewhat contained, though it was futile most of the time and they tried different hobbies to keep her interested. The ones that seemed to stick were Quidditch and music. Quidditch because it was an outlet for the energetic child and music because she had a knack for it. The first instrument was guitar at around age 10, though when she got a few years older she did also learn how to play bass guitar. The concepts are similar (minus 2 strings) so it wasn’t hard for Layla to pick up. Her parents didn’t know a lot about the various genres of music that existed and as most members of the magical community did they listened to whatever music was available to the Wizarding world as a whole. It wasn’t until Layla entered her first year at Hogwarts and befriended muggle-born students that she was introduced to more artists and genres that muggles listened to and this formed her love of rock music as a whole. 

Layla turned eleven the day before her first year started, but that hadn’t gotten in the way of shopping for her textbooks and new robes and cauldrons and whatever other supplies she needed. Of course, her beloved guitar was coming with her to school. The sorting hat sensed the creativity the child innately had and her good heart but also her fearless nature and decided Gryffindor would be the best house for the young girl. Right away she noticed how people might treat her differently because of her Veela heritage, as another student explained to her the more Veela in her blood the more the effect was. In that sense she was spared the difficulty that full and half-Veela’s might have gone through but while it bothered her slightly after a while she learned to get by. The attention was unwanted, Layla enjoyed being the life of the party and hanging out with her friends and the large groups of loud Gryffindor's and students from other houses. Ideas such as pureblood superiority didn’t mean anything to her. 

During her time at school she made a lot of friends and continued her guitar skills, she also knew she could sing but actually preferred not to in lieu of just playing the instruments she loved. Other subjects she excelled in were Charms, Transfiguration and Flying while Potions and Herbology were the bane of her existence. Often she could be found skipping either class and instead using an enchanted MP3 player her father bought her for Christmas in her second year and listening to various artists. She found she really enjoyed what muggles refer to as “classic rock” but also a variety of artists from the rock genre. The rest of her years there went without a hitch, she played Quidditch for her house team for a few years though her skipping core classes didn’t bode well for staying on the team or even becoming a Prefect or being in any sort of student leadership position despite her personality to do so. 

After she graduated, she decided to pursue music full time much to the chagrin of her parents. They had hoped that she would find some kind of Ministry job or even work in a shop in Diagon Alley. Something with a little more foundation than just booking music gigs and hoping that it all works out. It was a slow start but she finally was able to join a group of musicians and quit the part-time cashier job she’d had in the meantime. 

[/blockquote][b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Many of the events and attacks that were credited to the Purifiers occurred after Layla had already graduated but it definitely left her feeling rather uneasy and uncertain. The quarantine has affected her the most since she wasn’t able to travel as she would have wanted and she felt a bit stuck which in turn certainly affected her mood as much as she tried not to show it. But it didn’t keep her from her bandmates , which was what was important to her. She has kept an eye on the paper when it came to updates regarding the prison break the previous year and she was fortunate that her and her family were not at the Quidditch match when that attack occurred but with her father working at the Ministry still she hopes for his safety. 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]vanessa[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]don't worry about it[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]PST[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]got in the wrong uber&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@vanessa  , @anastasia  [/blockquote][/div][/div]