[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt="" style="max-width:100%;" src="https://media.giphy.com/media/SUfpETzgiZa9O/giphy.gif"]
[/div]hello there, my name is [b]beatrice holmes[/b] but you can call me [b]tris[/b]. i'm a[b] journalist for the daily prophet&nbsp;[/b]and [b]28[/b] so that makes me an [b]alumni&nbsp;[/b]of&nbsp;[b]hogwarts[/b]. You could say I'm [b]ntelligent, knowledgeable, &amp; witty[/b] but I personally think that I am [b]passionate, quick-tempered &amp; curious[/b]. People say I look a lot like [b]jenna coleman[/b], but I don't really see it...

[div align="center"][font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][i][b]beatrice alexandra holmes[/b][/i][/font][/font][/div]

[b][i]pronunciation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote][/blockquote][blockquote] bea-tris [/blockquote]

[b][i]nickname:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]tris, bea (by her father) bebe (school nickname)[/blockquote][b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]28[/blockquote]
[b][i]date of birth:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]23rd may, 1996[/blockquote]
[b][i]gender &amp; pronouns:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]female, she/her[/blockquote]
[b][i]blood status:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]muggleborn[/blockquote]
[b][i]sexuality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]heterosexual

[/blockquote]
[b][i]schooling:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]hogwarts, ravenclaw

[/blockquote][b][i]occupation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]sportswriter for the daily prophet[/blockquote]
[b][i]wand:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]beechwood and dragon heartstring 11 3/4 inches[/blockquote]
[b][i]playby:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]jenna coleman[/blockquote]
[b][i]appearance:[/i] [/b]
[blockquote]beatrice looks exactly like her playby, but is a little taller at 5'4[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personality[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]likes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]christmastime, castles, bonfires, quidditch, her job, her dog, her family, tapas dinners, Spain, writing, cheesy Muggle rom-coms, fiction books, defending the underdog, gossip, [strike]her ex though if you ask  her she’ll deny it[/strike][/blockquote]
[b][i]dislikes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]being idle, thunderstorms, horrific injuries to athletes, loneliness, bullies, horror films, cruel rumors,&nbsp; nonfiction literature, being out of the loop[/blockquote]
[b][i]erised:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]editor in chief of the daily prophet, and to find that missing spark in her love life[/blockquote]
[b][i]amortentia:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]christmas trees, bonfires, [strike]her ex’s cologne
[/strike]
[/blockquote]
[b][i]boggart:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]An enormous poisonous snake, however her biggest fear that cannot be manifested is finding out second hand that her now ex-beau had been injured or killed.[/blockquote]
[b][i]overall personality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote][/blockquote]Beatrice is not a typical Ravenclaw; she is not that bookish, and she finds herself more to be the cleverly creative than the wise and witty sort.  She has a curiosity streak a mile long; she always asks why, how, what for, and what next.  She is also wildly passionate about the things she loves most and will fiercely defend them to a point of exasperation on the other party.   She loves a good argument or debate, and will like a person more if they're willing to engage her.  That passion includes defending the underdog, whether it be during Quidditch tryouts, classes or in the hallways.  She'll do something thoughtful for them as a cheer up, like find out their favorite sweet, or sit next to them at breakfast.  She does not try and judge a person by her first impression of them; if she did she would never have been with the love of her life.



 Beatrice has a flaring temper; her father would call her Hurricane Bea when she was on a warpath.  She has been known to say nasty and biting things when she is angry; something she always ends up regretting.  She would always come down quickly and turn back into her kind self, and will always apologize for being mean or rude when she knows she was in the wrong.  She's been able to keep her temper more in check now that she has a job she loves, but sometimes certain people will irritate her to a point of waspish quips.



[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personal history[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]mother:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]margaret holmes nee carmichael, 62, muggle, podiatrist[/blockquote]
[b][i]father:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]fletcher holmes, 65, muggle, sports broadcaster for the fulham football team in the british premier league[/blockquote]
[b][i]siblings:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]wallace holmes, 35, muggle (no signs of magic), neurosurgeon[/blockquote]
[b][i]pets:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]a long haired daschund named daisy &amp; a screech owl named barnabus[/blockquote]
[b][i]history:[/i][/b]
[blockquote][/blockquote]Beatrice is the second child born to Fletcher &amp; Margaret of London, who had a seven year old son named Wallace when she came into the world.  Fletcher and Margaret are both Muggles; Margaret a London-based podiatrist, and Fletcher the popular play-by-play sportscaster for the Fulham Football team.  Wallace had not shown any signs of magic, so the shock of the manifestation of Beatrice’s powers came as quite a shock.  It started with her flying off a long water slide in Brighton Pier, but instead of injuring herself, she landed like a cat on her feet.  They thought nothing of it though, until Beatrice’s eleventh birthday.  The Headmistress of Hogwarts, Minerva McGonagall, paid them a visit with Beatrice’s letter in hand.  She explained that Beatrice was a witch and that she was invited to attend Hogwarts that September.  While Margaret was initially quite hesitant, Fletcher was more than excited to be part of this part of the world he had never seen before.  He was the one who took Beatrice to get her schoolbooks, her wand and exchange some of their Muggle money for Wizarding coinage, all while incredibly fascinated by everything he saw.  Her brother Wallace was away traveling in Germany with his private schools’ football team when this all happened, and could not make it home in time to see Beatrice off on the train.  While Beatrice had been devastated by this at the time, she eventually got past it; he found the world to be as fascinating as his father did, especially with communicating by owl post.



Upon entering Hogwarts, Beatrice was Sorted into Ravenclaw house; the hat had debated for almost five minutes between Ravenclaw and Gryffindor before finally deciding on the former.  Within the first week, she had made fast friends with a Ravenclaw girl who had been brought up in an all-magical household.  Her friend taught her everything about Quidditch, and Beatrice soon realized there were plenty of similarities to soccer, a love she shared with her father.  She soon realized that her feet were far better put to use on solid ground; but her passion for the sport grew until it surpassed football.  She even convinced her father to buy tickets for their family for the Quidditch World Cup in England the summer before school one year to introduce them to the sport.  Beatrice also developed an affinity for Charms &amp; Transfiguration, but was abysmal at History of Magic; she just didn’t find it interesting.



Aside from Quidditch games, Charms Club and studying for classes, Beatrice was lucky enough to find the great love of her life when she was just twelve years old.  He was a Slytherin in her year, but they only interacted in her second year when the Charms professor paired them together for practice.  She found him a bit irritating of first; it definitely wasn't love at first sight for her.  But she found herself looking around for him during classes and somehow sitting next to him for most classes.  When he made the Quidditch team their third year, Beatrice ended up secretly rooting for Slytherin (except against Ravenclaw of course!).  Finally, fourth year, after a heated argument, they had their first kiss and were inseparable all the way up to graduation.  Sadly, their relationship came to a begrudgingly mutual end as their jobs took them to different places - hers landing her right in the fast paced offices of the Daily Prophet.  She started off as an intern, living at home with her parents while covering whatever the editors threw her way as a means to prove herself.  Finally, one day when the regular Quidditch reporter for the Chudley Cannons was taken ill, Beatrice was requested to go in their stead.  It was an abysmal game for the Cannons supporters - they lost 560-20 - but the article was the foundation that led Beatrice up the ladder into a cushiony job as a regular Quidditch reporter.  The job takes her all over Britain and Ireland to report on matches, giving Beatrice a passion for travel and discovering new towns and their quaint pubs.   Beatrice was even invited on a press pass to the most recent Quidditch World Cup, a sign that she took as really making a name for herself in the dog-eat-dog journalism world. 


[b][i]site events reaction:[/i][/b]
[blockquote][/blockquote]Beatrice was reporting on a Kestrels match in Ireland when she’d heard the news of the kidnappings.  Part of her was relieved that she didn’t have to report on it, but a much larger part of her was terrified, especially on her return to the office.  As is normal in any newspaper office, the rumors and gossip swirled wildly as to what really had happened.  The facts were that Elaine Dupree, an eighteen year old witch, had been the mastermind behind this plot, and it had been she who had tortured and murdered Muggleborn student Ethan Johnson.  This wasn’t the first death of a Muggleborn in the past year - another one had been found on the train in the beginning of the school year, the poor thing.  Worst of all, Elaine had not been caught, meaning she was still at large.  From what little attention Beatrice had paid in History of Magic, she knew this wasn’t the first time Muggleborn witches and wizards had been targeted, but this felt….different.  More personal.  She was placated by the fact that Elaine had the entire might of the Ministry searching for her, and as long as she wasn’t foolish, she should be safe.



Then came the Triwizard Tournament, and Beatrice got to go report on the Second Task, bringing her back to the very castle where she had loved and lost.  It brought back a lot of memories, both good and sad, but after the explosions that sent the carriage and ship plummeting to their doom, Beatrice realized that life was too short to not take chances.  So she reached out via owl to her ex-boyfriend, whom she had not seen in nearly ten years, hoping he was well and to let her know if he would be in the London are any time in the future.  She has had yet to hear from him, and with the Ilvermorny attack, the Daily Prophet has her working overtime to help cover the stories.  Perhaps one day though, she’ll get the closer she desires so much...



[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]alias[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]name:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Lisa[/blockquote][b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]29 (still in my 20s for now!)[/blockquote][b][i]time zone:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Eastern[/blockquote][b][i]reference:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]i live here[/blockquote][b][i]other characters:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]do i have to list them all?&nbsp; irina, hermione, susan, malakai, louis, ophelia, aerick, elaine[/blockquote][/div][/div]