[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" alt="" src="https://i.pinimg.com/originals/17/68/32/176832b9d9ec8202017866e4c6fd2244.gif"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]charlotta aino holopainen[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]Shar-lot-ah[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Char, Charlie, Lotti[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]30
March 15, 1995[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Female
She/her[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Half-blood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Lesbian[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]12 inches, vine, unicorn hair[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Taylor Momsen1[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Height: 5'5
Charlotta is an almost stereotypical Finnish woman with fair skin, hair, and pale blue eyes. Charlotta, while definitely more refined then her younger years, still has a very edgy and "rock and roll" look to her. She likes leathers and dark make up. But she can clean up when she needs to to impress people.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Durmstrang[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduate[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]WADA student: 18-21
Singer/Songwriter: 18-27
Co-Owner and Manager of HR Records: 27-Current[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Music/singing
traveling
parties
trying new restaurants
going to hole-in-the wall spots to try and find talent
coffee

[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Emrys'... antics and having to lecture him (CAUSE HE NEVER LISTENS)
bad publicity/paparazzi catching bad situations
Critics (bunch of prissy assholes that feel they can judge others on something they can't do themselves)
dealing with "difficult" musicians (she doesn't put up with it)
Being underestimated for being a woman in a primarily male dominated world (music management)
Cheap anything (food, clothing, goods... cheap is cheap. She has high taste)[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]to be extremely success in the music industry and someday become the greatest/most recognized magical music label in the world.&nbsp;

[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]her wife's perfume
the ocean
coffee[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]A huge scandal that will ruin her/her record label/her family
squids/octopuses
Losing one of her loved ones[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Charlotta has spent most her life in the lime light, so she's always making sure to say the right things and take the right steps. She's very conscious of herself, and what she is doing at all times. She's also mindful of those around her, and how they are acting. This is very apparent in how she deals with her brother's children and her wife's young siblings. She doesn't want the attention they get to go to their head and make them start acting outrageously without realizing what the consequences might be. In particular, she can come off as quite hard on Emrys, her nephew. Some people would think she's too hard on the boy, but he knows that she's looking out for him, and trying to make sure he stays safe. Though, his antics can be quite... exhausting.&nbsp;

Those that know her, and particularly her musical career, know that she wasn't always like this. She learned the hard way how to behave, as many of the actions of her youth were... quite rebellious. So many of the antics she tries to stop her musicians from getting up to are ones that she pulled herself. As such, she's quite adept at stopping them.

Charlotta is creative. While she may co-own and run the record label now she was much like her musicians in her youth. A musician herself, chasing the fame. She had a knack for music, like her brother and nephew. Music seemed to be in their blood. Though, Charlotta now channels her creativity in helping other musicians. Her love for music has made her realize that she loves helping other artists more, to see them flourish and blossom. She is very hands on with every musician at the record label, and will help them every step of the way. She's the type of owner/manager that will sit the artist down and read through the entire contract with them, making sure they understand every last bit before ever letting them consider signing. She's also very fair and generous, knowing that happy musicians will put out better music, so any contracts she does offer are some of the most lucrative for the musician.&nbsp;

Charlotta isn't necessarily "nice" all the time though. She's a woman in a male dominated world (music industry management), so she has a very thick skin. She will demand the attention of the room if she wants it and she will never let you talk over her. She demands respect from everyone she works with, and a mutual understanding that she won't work with you if you can't play by her (reasonable) rules. Respect her, respect her artists, respect her wife.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Finland[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Aino Holopainen, mother, 68
Rudolph Holopainen, father, 70
Radford Holopainen, 48, brother, famous rock musician
____ ____ ROSIER, 37 - brother-in-law
____ ____ ROSIER, 30 - brother-in-law
____ ____ ROSIER, 28 - brother-in-law
____ ____ (nee ROSIER), 26 - sister-in-law
PRISCILLA AMALIA ROSIER, 16 - sister-in-law

niece/nephew - 21
Emrys Holopainen - nephew, 20, musician and problem child
niece/nephew - 15
(any nieces/nephews from the Rosier siblings-in-law)

____ Rosier, 33, wife and co-owner of the record label
Jayli Holopainen-Rosier, adopted daughter (born 8/2/2025)

[/blockquote]
[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Frida, 6 year old&nbsp;Samoyed (female)
Flonder, 5 year old&nbsp;Samoyed (male)
(AKA, fur babies [img src="//storage.proboards.com/5647952/images/CqwApTvvQoNtPXRfTxg0.gif" class="smile" alt=":3" style="max-width:100%;"] )[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Charlotta was an oops child. Her brother, Radford, was quite a bit older then her. Her childhood, despite the age difference, was quite normal. Radford loved music, and he taught Charlotta everything he could while she grew up. Eventually, after he finished school, Radford went on to make quite a name for himself in the music industry. To be honest, she loved telling people she was his little sister. Charlotta was proud of her brother, and the musical heights he was reaching. He was her greatest role model growing up (though clearly he had a few issues, since he would go on to have a few children out of wedlock).

Charlotta attended Durmstrang when she was old enough. A dreary place, but she learned a lot and did decent. If was during her school years she learned about WADA and decided that, after graduation, she would attend the school. So, after graduation she packed her bags and moved across Europe to attend the famous school of the performing arts. While attending the school she also started to perform her own music in clubs, pubs and anywhere else she could. Eventually she was spotted by a scout, who offered her a contract with a record label. 

Charlotta fronted a magical rock band, and had quite the wild few years. She was a wild and powerful performer, like her brother. She also went through quite the rebellious phase, pulling all sorts of stunts and scandals. That is, until she met the woman of her dreams. The eldest Rosier daughter, who was just a few years older then Charlotta. It was quite the scandal when they started to see each other, as the Rosier girl left her arrange marriage to be with Charlotta. After the divorce between the Rosier girl and her husband was finalized, she and Charlotta started to date "officially". Eventually, Charlotta proposed. Charlotta was 25 when they got married in a small, intimate ceremony.&nbsp;

A few years after her marriage, Charlotta decided to step away from performing music herself and she and her wife founded their own record company. While she loved music and performing, she'd come to learn that she loved helping others with the arts more. She had a good ear. She was a natural at helping other artists improve their work, and bring out the best of them.&nbsp; That was when they founded Holopainen-Rosier Records (or HR records). While small at first, the name Holopainen was already huge in the musical industry (thanks to her own and her brother's work) It also helped that her brother openly supported the record label.&nbsp;

The past several years have been spent building their roster of artists, and work, taking the music industry by force. Over those years, Charlotta and her wife have also been working on adopting a child. In March this year, those dreams came true. An expectant mother was going to put her soon to be born child up for adoption and chosen Charlotta and her wife to be the parents.


When Jayli was born she was so... so tiny in August 2025 . Born prematurely due to the poor choices of the birth mother, Jayli spent the first two months of life in the hospital. Jayli would have a number of health problems growing up, something that might scare other parents. But not Charlotta and her wife. They were happy for their miracle baby and finally got to bring her hope in October.[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Charlotta is wary, about everything going on. As someone who works in the spotlight, she's always aware of the goings in the world and how they can affect her/her artists. She's definitely upped the security for all her artists in the last few years and tries to be extra precautious when it comes to the office and studio. The prison break in particular caused quite a bit of concern.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Sora[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]She/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]29[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]Mountain[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]I live here[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]... too many[/blockquote][/div][/div]