[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://64.media.tumblr.com/43f3e124c953bd7d499a5c18a0e5d1e3/7c939548cd9194ac-6e/s540x810/15cb2fad01935ff7bf401955144057c379f6515f.gifv" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""]
[/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]HANNA HORVÁTH[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]Haa-Nuh | Hor-Vathh[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Hanz[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]23
July 21st[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b][blockquote]Female
She/her/hers[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Half-blood
One-quarter Veela[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Heterosexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b][blockquote]10" Aspen wood, Dragon Heartstring core

[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Taylor Swift[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]
Hanna is slim and tall, at times a bit gangly, towering at 5 foot 10 inches. She has blonde hair that she frequently styles in a partial bob, straight, or soft curls. She's always changing her look depending on her mood. Her lips are normally painted red with perfectly manicured paws. She strives to always be the best looking person in the room, adorned in well put together outfits and ensembles with coordinated accessories. Hanna expresses herself through fashion and often makes her own clothes. She almost always has her face in her phone or is taking pictures of herself. Hanna looks identical to her play-by Taylor Swift.

- Light scars and scratches on her fingers/tips from when she first started used  sewing needles. 
- A scratch on her side from when Lyra got attacked by a werewolf. (more info in history)
-&nbsp;[a href="https://ugc.reveliststatic.com/gen/constrain/640/640/80/2018/05/02/13/zd/xw/phv49akpcc2qbwe.jpg"]Tattoo[/a]&nbsp;on ankle dedicated to Lyra.[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling &amp; status[/b]
[blockquote]Durmstrang, graduate.[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b][blockquote]Costume designer for a world renowned Magical theatre in France.
Socialite

Will relocate to London in search for work. Watch out London area employers.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]- Sewing
- Creating
- Languages: English, French, Hungarian
- Singing, guitar
- MAKEOVERS
- Fashion
- Being the best looking person in the room
- Crying (she's a cancer ok)
- Going out&nbsp;
- Her Enchanted Cellphone
- Socializing / gossip
- Being complimented
- Men with nice hair &amp; tattoos
- Underground Dueling
- Cats
- Cooking
[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]- Messiness
- Men telling her to smile
- Sandals with socks (excuse moi)
- People not complimenting her
- Plaid (like gross)
- Maths
- Being told "No"
- Mayonaise
- Losing
- Large breeds of dog
- Getting dirty
- Hard labor
- Flying (heights)

[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b][blockquote]Hanna is a person who brightens the room with her bubbly personality and spit fire attitude. Some would say she's emotional but it could be blamed on being overly passionate in everything she does. Nothing in her life is half-assed and she hates coming in second place, might as well be last. She's creative and always thinking of the next new fashion trends, or next "big thing". 

When it comes to friends and family, Hanna is a fearless protector, even when she shouldn't be. She will fight, cry and scream to get a point across. She's very caring (maybe too much), affectionate, and patient for those she loves the most. She will give a person in need the shirt off her back. She can be very dramatic and impulsive, especially with men who have done her wrong, or if her feelings are hurt. She wants love so badly, she tends to seek it out in the wrong places, and give the wrong people too much energy, later depleting herself. Leaving herself broken hearted and alone, again. She's working on that. 

When she goes out to have a good time she's easily influenced to do things she know she shouldn't do because she never gets to have fun. She tends to overindulge in those moments. Hanna could make a friend out of anyone, will always offer a shoulder to cry on, and enjoys making people smile. She's clean and organized to a point where it's meticulous and borderline psychotic. Her closet back home in France is color coordinated from floor to ceiling with a sewing section and entire mirrored wall with LED's. She's one step away from having a talking mirror.

Behind the happy facade hides deep sadness. Most wouldn't guess from looking at her, but Hanna is a very solitary and lonely person. It has been bothering her quite a bit lately. She has gotten so absorbed in her career and declining relationship that she doesn't go out with friends or see family nearly as much as she would like. Instead, she spends weekends getting ahead for work so she could get more done during the week. It's the vicious cycle of an over achiever. Hanna goes through major emotional shifts daily. One minute she can be happy-crying from a kitten in mittens on the net...the next she's lighting her cheating exes clothes on fire in the street of out of a fit of rage. She's not a force to be reckoned with when she's upset. Hanna can be very destructive in the moment and doesn't always have the big picture in mind when she reacts. She is part Veela and will use it to her advantage but she prefers to find something real. Hanna cannot turn into a harpy-like creature that throws fireballs, which is probably a good thing. But, she has a wand for that..
[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote][i]Born &amp; Raised:[/i] Pécs,&nbsp;Hungary
[i]Recent Residence: [/i]Saint-Jean-de-Lu,&nbsp;France
[i]Current:[/i] Couch surfing at Lyra's (technically Rob's couch)

[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]
@lyra                                                                 - Cousin (grew up more like a sisters)

Mata Horváth (nee Wojtanowicz) - Mother. Healer. Part-veela.
Czeke Horváth - Father. Ministry worker. Half-blood.

------ Horváth - Older Brother. Healer.
------&nbsp;Horváth - Younger Brother. School age.

[/blockquote]
[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]A cat named [a href="https://www.rd.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/GettyImages-1025449630.jpg"]Fluffy[/a][/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]
Hanna&nbsp;Horváth hails from&nbsp;Pécs, Hungary, to Mata and Czeke&nbsp;Horváth. The second out of three children, making her the awkward middle sister to two brothers. They grew up in a small wizarding town in Hungary, where they lived a lavish lifestyle in a big home with acres of land. Mata, a skilled Healer, and Czeke, a high ranking member of the Ministry. The&nbsp;Horváth parents ran a strict household and always expected the best from their children. Hanna grew up exceeding expectations of her parents, often leaving her brothers looking like under achievers, which she loved. A bit of a fathers girl, she knew how to talk her way out of trouble. Her Mum was okay with whatever she did as long as her father didn't care. Well, until she started back alley dueling for money. She loved that people would always underestimate her due to her looks.&nbsp;

Sibling rivalry and hate were a true factor in the pre and early teen years of the Horváth household. Hanna always wished she could switch out a brother for her cousin, Lyra. Instead, they had to settle for summers together, where they would wreck havoc in the city with back alley dueling and sneaking around with boys. It was a true thrill. Until it wasn't. One summer, she and Lyra snuck out as they normally would, finding a group of cute boys to drink with in a rural nearby field when a werewolf came rolling through. In the midst of the chaos, Hanna lost Lyra, and it's the moment she regrets the most in her life. She feels like a part of it was her fault, like she was selfish and let go of her hand when they were running. Hanna, being taller, with longer legs...had a clear advantage over her because she was the faster runner in the attack, built like a damn gazelle. She was able to hide inside a overgrown rotten log until the werewolf ran off.

Lyra and Hanna haven't dueled together since before the attack, because Lyra refuses to. Such a buzzkill. They started to drift apart, but Hanna adores Lyra more than anyone in the world. She will always be her best friend and fun-sized-soul-sister-cousin. Hanna would commit murder for Lyra, she feels like she owes it to her after she was useless during the werewolf attack. When Lyra started to slip at Hogwarts, she was offered to come to Durmstrang with Hanna for her sixth year. It was finally a dream come true for Hanna but Lyra didn't seem happy and she didn't mesh completely with her friends group at Durmstrang. Lyra dropped out of school and they drifted apart even more. Half the time, Hanna had no clue what Ly was doing or where she was, but she was always thinking of her. Writing to her often, understanding if she never got a response. 

Hanna was a great student and had a creative mind, she was admittedly a bit of an awkward dork, but her peers liked her because she was nice. She always wanted to learn new skills and was welcoming towards people. Some classmates would make fun of her height, which made her very insecure, but by her seventh year she learned how to use her height against them. (in a "shouldn't you pick on someone your own size?" kind of way). Shortly after graduating from Durmstrang, Hanna attended fashion school in France. Often modeling, or presenting her own creations. She has been employed for a world renowned theatre company in France for three years, where she's able to afford a flat on her own where she lives a grueling but satisfying work life.

Recently, her life has gone to shambles after a horrible breakup with her Muggle DJ boyfriend. They dated for a year and were very public. She gained clout on wizard social media but it doesn't transcribe to real life. She doesn't feel like she has any real friends in France, so she had a bit of a "pre-mature-midlife crisis" where she decided to drop everything and visit her cousin Lyra in London a week after being dumped. She couldn't take being alone another minute. Lyra had always been the one who could pick her up when she was down. &nbsp;Hanna was supposed to be in the Bahamas between show season for the theatre, so she was devastated and heartbroken when she arrived at the door of Lyra's boyfriends place. Rob. She's grateful for a couch to crash, but she's hesitant to trust anyone with her dear cousins heart. Experiencing their love and bond has exposed her to a strange mixed feeling of jealousy and loneliness.

Hanna hasn't done any underground dueling in London since traveling there recently, but she will try to convince Lyra, dangling the chance of making extra cash on the side in her face. She wants to feel excited about something that doesn't involve sewing needles again.&nbsp;

She's aware of the incidents that have happened at the schools, as well as the Azkaban prison break, but those things don't bother her until they directly effect her. She tries to ignore bad news because it makes her sad or scared, so an 'ignorance is bliss' lifestyle is how she lives when it comes in politics and issues.

[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]dez[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/hers[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]Jedi Council Member[/blockquote]
[/div][/div]
