[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center" style="font-size:10px;"][img src="https://i.pinimg.com/originals/bb/ac/4b/bbac4b7b5831209dd9c7738fff32d183.gif" alt="" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]bjorn alexander krok[/font][/div][hr style="font-size:10px;"]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]buh-yearn[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]Hook (inherited from his father.), Captain[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]30
April 6, 1995[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]Male
He/him[/blockquote]

[div style="font-size:10px;" align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr style="font-size:10px;"]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]half-blood.[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]Straight[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]wand:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]Blackthorn, dragonheart string, 13 1/3 inches.[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]playby:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]Ben Dahlhaus[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]Height: 6'4
A tall and well built man, Bjorn is an intimidating figure to many. Not just because of his size but also how he carries himself. He has the stance of someone that makes you feel small when you're around him.

Bjorn's dirty blonde hair is kept long, and he's grown out quite a bit of facial hair (Which suits his face well). His icy blue eyes are striking.

Bjorn has a number of tattoos as well, some professionally done, and some not.[/blockquote]
[div style="font-size:10px;" align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr style="font-size:10px;"]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]Durmstrang[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]Graduated[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]Officially: Smuggler and Thief

Unofficially: "Pirate Captain". Basically he's a modern day magical pirate.[/blockquote]

[div style="font-size:10px;" align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr style="font-size:10px;"]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]likes:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]History
Magical artifacts
Museums/Antique shops (He doesn't steal from them either! He has some moral lines)
Flying
Thunder storms
People's reaction when they find out what he is/does
Being in command
[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]Being on the ground to long
Clear weather
"slow days" (when they don't have any leads of Gringotts sites to raid)
Being around too much modern technology (He's a bit old school. It's nostalgic)
Magical authorities
[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]erised:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]To be the first Krok to successfully break into, and escape, a Gringotts bank.
To raise up the next generation of Kroks.[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]Rain
Rum
Old tomes/books[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]His grandfather's ship, which he's inherited, being destroyed/permanently grounded.
Being permanently grounded himself (not being able to be in the air)[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]Bjorn, if you didn't know him, can come across as a very scary and intimidating man. He's proud and confident. He's the sort of person that has an unbendable will, and the courage of a lion. He does not waver or cower before anyone, or anything. He is the sort of person that you do not want to make an enemy of, because he doesn't backdown.

When you get to know him though these same traits are what make him charismatic and likeable. Before of his will you know that he will never waver on his values, and would never betray you. His confidence makes him outgoing. His courage makes him an excellent defender, and someone you know will always have your back.&nbsp;

Bjorn works hard, and isn't afraid to get his hands dirty. He carries his own weight, and he will help out anyone he sees struggling. Bjorn is a very experienced person as well, and someone you would trust in a situation you know he's experienced. His confidence is reassuring and instills trust. He's also cautious and calculating. He doesn't do anything without thinking it through first and ensuring he's weighed all his options.&nbsp;

Bjorn isn't necessarily a nice person, he doesn't give compliments easily, and he won't just flash you a smile. He can come across as sarcastic, and sometimes a bit aggressive. But he isn't a mean person either. Instead, he's a hardened, street smart man. So a "bad boy" but not a "bad guy".&nbsp;

Bjorn is also a silent sympathizer and supporter of those in need. He helps those who need it. He'll leave money for families he knows can't make it. But he refuses to take credit for his deeds. He's just someone that doesn't like to see others suffer when they are seemingly decent people. So if he can do something about it without putting himself in a bad situation? He will.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center" style="font-size:10px;"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr style="font-size:10px;"]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]origins:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]Norway[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]relations:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]James Hook, deceased at 101, grandfather, was a pirate.

Olav Krok, 88, father, retired pirate (He's still kicking and having fun, just doesn't want to run the crew anymore)
Hilde Krok, 60, mother, seamstress.

Signe Krok, 29, sister, fellow pirate
Tove Krok, 23, sister, open profession (she's the blacksheep that isn't a pirate)

[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]pets:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]None.[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]history:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]The Krok family wasn't always "Krok". It all started with James Hook. Hook, of course, wasn't his real surname. James was found on the doorsteps of an orphanage shortly after birth. He was given the surname "Hook" by the orphanage, mostly just because it was the first word that came to mind when he needed paperwork done. James was a muggleborn wizard, and eventually, was found by the Ministry, and taken into a wizarding home as a child. His adopted family wasn't exactly the most pleasant people. The father, despite being a wizard, worked on a ship, while the mother was a witch who was a stay-at-home mother. The father was a mean drunk, and beat all the children that were brought into the home whenever he wasn't on the sea. During that era pirates were still a very common and dangerous adversary on the seas, and James' adopted father worked on a ship that tried to hunt them. 



James' relief came in the form of Hogwarts, in which he learned all about magic. He graduated with high marks, and was especially known for his enchanting skills. After graduation he fell in with the wrong crowd, pirates. Soon he was sailing, like his adopted father, but they were on opposite sides of the law. As he grew older, and became more experienced, James eventually had his own ship. Through his magical skills, and a LOT of hard work, he enchanted the ship to fly. His ship, the Jolly Roger, became an urban legend among both muggles and wizards. A flying pirate ship that swooped in, ransacked, and then was gone before you even had time to comprehend what happened. Some say that James Hook was the inspiration to the villain of Peter Pan. The Ministry, of course, was very angry at the publicity of James Hook and his piracy. But, as Peter Pan grew in popularity, the legend became a part of the story, and the Ministry didn't have to start erasing memories, though they did start trying to catch this infamous sky pirate. But James was a cunning man. He traveled the world in his flying ship, terrorizing numberous nations, but then always escaping capture. 



James, eventually had a son, Olav. He didn't necessarily know about Olav's existence immediately, as Olav was the offspring of a one night stand in Norway. But when he did, he returned to the country to claim his son. Olav was raised by pirates, learning the ways of the craft from his legendary father. 



Eventually, James passed command of the ship to Olav, and settled in the Norwegian countryside with Olav's mother. At the ripe age of 101, James passed away peacefully in his sleep.



Olav ran the ship just as well as his father. Many years into his reign, he met a woman many years younger than him, Hilde. They married, and she gave him three beautiful children. Deciding that the Hook name had been popularized too much, the family changed their named to "Krok" shortly before the birth of Bjorn.



Bjorn was born during a storm. His mother's cries drowned out by the raging thunder and rain. Many say that the storm was welcoming it's kindred soul, Bjorn, into the world. 



Bjorn's upbringing was slightly different to his father's. He was raised both on land and in the sky. His father taught him the ways of the flying ship, while his mother taught him how to interact with normal society. When he was eleven, he received a letter from Durmstrang. His parents debated the invitation long and hard, before finally deciding to send him to Durmstrang. He needed to spend time with children his own age, and have a more professional learning than his father. 



Bjorn didn't mind Durmstrang. The harsh atmosphere reminded him of home. While he couldn't fly on the ship, he could still fly on brooms, and he took to Quidditch like a tick. He was quite good too, a strong and powerful beater. He was a force to be reckoned with when off the ground. As he neared graduation he had several professional team offers. He decided to play for a Norwegian team for a few years, but it wasn't the same. So, at the age of twenty, he quit professional quidditch and returned to his father's flying ship. 



Since then, he's been flying with his father, learning the ropes of command, and ransacking Gringott's dig sites and tombs. On Bjorn's 29th birthday, Olav turned over the mantle of captain to Bjorn, just as his father had, so that he could enjoy his retirement with his wife.[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]Bjorn's been "aware" of the news, as he follows the news closely (always got to be on your toes in case authorities are close) but it hasn't bothered him. He's ignored the news that isn't relevant to him.&nbsp;

Bjorn and his crew were in Russia when the quarantine started. Though it didn't affect them personally Bjorn was very concerned because his youngest sister, Tove was in the British Isles at the time, meaning she was stuck in the country. As the quarantine laws started to ease up, Bjorn, with some excellent fake IDs, got himself and his crew back into the Isles.[/blockquote]

[div style="font-size:10px;" align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr style="font-size:10px;"]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]name:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]Sora[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]She/her[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]age:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]28[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]Mountain[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]reference:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]I live here[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]Lots.[/blockquote][/div][/div]