[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;background-color:#B6B6B4;border:4px solid #B6B6B4;border-radius:10px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="http://orig09.deviantart.net/109a/f/2013/193/e/3/katie_mcgrath_manip_3_by_miu05-d54fn01.jpg" alt=" " style="max-width:100%;"][/div]

hello there, my name is [b]Irina Krum[/b] but you can call me [b]Rina[/b]. i'm [b]seventeen[/b]&nbsp;so that makes me a [b]sixth[/b]year at Hogwarts, where I reside in [b]Gryffindor[/b] house. You could say I'm [b] brave, daring, &amp; chivalrous [/b] but I personally think that I am [b]sarcastic, creative &amp; stubborn [/b]. People say I look a lot like [b]Katie McGrath[/b], but I don't really see it...

[div align="center"][font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][i][b]Irina Rose Krum[/b][/i][/font][/font][/div]

[b][i]nickname:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Rina, Ree (by her brother), Rin (by Daniel)[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]seventeen[/blockquote]
[b][i]date of birth:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]april 19, 2006[/blockquote]
[b][i]gender:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]female[/blockquote]
[b][i]blood status:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]pureblood[/blockquote]
[b][i]sexuality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]straight[/blockquote]
[b][i]house:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]gryffindor[/blockquote]
[b][i]occupation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]
[b][i]wand:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]maple and phoenixfeather, 8 ¾ inches, springy [/blockquote]
[b][i]playby:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Katie McGrath[/blockquote]
[b][i]appearance:[/i] [/b]
[blockquote] 5’8” willowy figure, scar on her shin from a gash she received while exploring a cave near her family home in Bulgaria [/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personality[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]likes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]history, rock climbing, hiking, chocolate, flying, watching Quidditch, blackberries, the flute, the color blue, snowy days, snow tubing, Muggle 80s rock music[/blockquote]
[b][i]dislikes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]bats, travel by Floo powder, the color brown, squash (the food), people who chew with their mouths open, deep water, the nightmares she gets from her visions[/blockquote]
[b][i]erised:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]her parents being proud of an accomplishment that don't have to do with Quidditch[/blockquote]
[b][i]amortentia:[/i][/b]
[blockquote] morning dew on grass, a fresh steaming mug of hot chocolate, smoke from a campfire [/blockquote]
[b][i]boggart:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]a gigantic bat[/blockquote]
[b][i]overall personality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]When getting to know Rina, one might initially wonder why on earth she’s a Gryffindor.  Her sense of humor is very sarcastic and dry, which people sometimes take away that she’s not a nice person. It’s really just her way of getting to know if someone can put up with her; she knows Viktor Krum is her father and is used to people treating her differently because of it.  Once she feels she can trust a person, she is warm and funny and fiercely loyal. 
 
Like a true Gryffindor, she loves taking charge, using her creative streak to plan out trips to Hogsmeade as well as weekend entertainment.  Usually she is amenable to change, however if she really wants something to go the way she planned, her incredibly stubborn side will rear its’ head.  She’ll dig in her heels and not relent until the other side has conceded (which is probably a good idea)

A side to Rina that is so incredibly rare that so far only her family has seen is her scared &nbsp;vulnerable side. &nbsp;Growing up the daughter of two Quidditch players is difficult and she constantly feels the pressure to do well in that world (regardless of what her father told her), when she'd be perfectly content to just watch and cheer on the team from the stands. &nbsp;She does a very good job at not letting the stress get to the surface, but once in awhile it cracks through and causes her to doubt every choice she's ever made. &nbsp;Usually a good cry and a talk with her brother makes the doubt go away, but she has the nagging worry that one day it might not go away so easily. &nbsp;So she continues to push herself so that she doesn't have to feel that way.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personal history[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]mother:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Elena Eldridge Krum, 39, former Quidditch player, currently working full-time in the British Department of Magical Games and Sports[/blockquote]
[b][i]father:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Viktor Krum, 47, retired Quidditch player, famous for competing in the 1994-95 Triwizard Cup for Durmstrang[/blockquote]
[b][i]siblings:[/i][/b]
[blockquote] Nikolai Cedric Krum, brother, 18, Gryffindor alum, Appleby Arrows Seeker
Ripley Nikolena Krum, 16, Hufflepuff
Tatiana Viktronovia Krum, 15, Hufflepuff[/blockquote]


[b][i]pets:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]eagle owl named Arthur[/blockquote]
[b][i]history:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Irina is the second of four children born to Viktor and Elena Krum, esteemed Quidditch players for their home countries of Bulgaria &amp; Germany (respectively).  Her birth occured on a very stormy April night in their mountainside home of Vrasta after almost three days of labor for Elena (and plenty of curiosity from her elder brother). &nbsp;They were very happy with a little girl joining their family; Viktor even took the year off to help his young wife raise them so she did not have to depend on other family for assistance. &nbsp;That year turned into four as two more children, both girls, followed Irina and Viktor missed the Quidditch World Cup for the first time in his career - Bulgaria lost in the first round.

 From a very young age, Irina lived and breathed &nbsp;Quidditch. &nbsp;Viktor had purchases toy broomsticks for her and her siblings just days after each of their first steps, and she learned to fly as she learned to walk as well. &nbsp;Elena was a Chaser for the Vrasta Vultures and had been called up to the Bulgarian National team the year she met Viktor. &nbsp;Their on and off pitch chemistry had been the talk of that years World Cup, and they had married soon after. &nbsp;Elena sometimes missed being on the Quidditch Pitch, and tried to instill her love of the sport into the children. &nbsp;While her elder &nbsp;brother struggled to fly but delighted in learning, Irina was the opposite. &nbsp;She was much more interested in climbing trees and exploring the mountains near their home. &nbsp;Her father would usually be the one to join her in her explorations; while he loved Quidditch with all his heart, he recognized his daughter held other interests and wanted to encourage her to be herself. &nbsp;One of these trips when Irina was 8, they discovered a small cave with a waterfall inside. &nbsp;Going in deeper, Irina was startled by a swarm of bats and fell down a small cliff in the cave, breaking her leg and scraping several layers of skin off her right shin in the process. &nbsp;Viktor was able to quickly magic her out and get her healed, but it left a scar on her shin and a lifelong fear of bats, as well as sticking to hiking and later rock climbing instead.

When Irinas brother turned eleven, Elena was offered a huge career move - a position with the British Ministry's Department of Magical Games &amp; Sports specifically working with the arrangements of the Quidditch World Cups. &nbsp;Taking the job would mean leaving their home country of Bulgaria and moving to England - an idea the Krums had been toying with for a few years. &nbsp;With Viktor's popularity in the United Kingdom, he could easily request a transfer to a British team, and they did not want their children attending Durmstrang. &nbsp;With those factors in mind, they moved their family of six to Thirsk in Northern England and Viktor got a transfer to the Appleby Arrows. &nbsp;Irina quickly grew to love her new town, and made friends with some of the local girls in the village before going off to Hogwarts the following year.

Upon her arrival, Irina was Sorted into Gryffindor like her brother. &nbsp;While she had been intrigued by the thought of being in a different house than her brother, she was secretly relieved - having an ally when she was homesick became incredibly helpful her first year. &nbsp;Her parents wrote to them weekly, with Elena throwing out hints that Irina should try out for the Gryffindor Quidditch team. &nbsp;Every year, Irina would throw out different excuses - she was sick the day of tryouts, she was beat out by other more talented players, and last year she had too much homework to get through. &nbsp;At this point, Irina knew she should tell her mother that she simply hadn't tried out because she didn't want to. &nbsp;As a sixth year, Irina has found her groove in her studies, finding a strange love of History of Magic and Potions. &nbsp;She has a good group of friends and maintains good relationships with her siblings, making sure they eat dinner together every Friday evening in the Great Hall. &nbsp;The one thing Irina has yet to experience however, is a real romantic relationship. &nbsp;It's possible that her sarcastic nature scares people off, but she always feels it has to do with her parentage. &nbsp;Maybe this year will be the year things change, and someone takes the leap.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]alias[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]name:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Lisa[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]26[/blockquote]
[b][i]time zone:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]eastern standard time[/blockquote]
[b][i]reference:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]proboards support![/blockquote]
[b][i]other characters:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]none yet[/blockquote][/div][/div]
