[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://78.media.tumblr.com/de2cafc579d0a9ce1dcded03974e8de2/tumblr_pdepb4JFfp1sju127o1_500.gif" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]

hello there, my name is [b]iliana maria krum[/b]&nbsp;but you can call me [b]ana[/b]. i'm a&nbsp;[b]Hufflepuff&nbsp;[/b]and [b]17&nbsp;[/b]so that makes me a [b]seventh year&nbsp;[/b]at [b]Hogwarts[/b]. You could say I'm [b]patient, dedicated and loyal[/b]&nbsp;but I personally think that I am [b]easy going, light hearted and kind[/b]. People say I look a lot like [b]maia mitchell[/b], but I don't really see it...

[div align="center"][font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][i][b]iliana maria krum[/b][/i][/font][/font][/div]

[b][i]pronunciation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]EE-li-ah-na&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b][i]nickname:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]strictly ana nowadays. though as a baby mimi, only her siblings and parents would call her that now.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]17[/blockquote]
[b][i]date of birth:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]march 3rd 2007[/blockquote]
[b][i]gender &amp; pronouns:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[b][i]blood status:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]pureblood[/blockquote]
[b][i]sexuality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]bisexual&nbsp;

[/blockquote]
[b][i]schooling:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Hufflepuff[/blockquote][b][i]occupation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]ana's dream is to be a muggle football player. while she's relatively passionate about quidditch, that's a given, if she does anything at all it'd be to play for Chelsea F.C one day.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b][i]wand:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]hornbeam, 10¼", unicorn tail hair, swishy[/blockquote]
[b][i]playby:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]maia mitchell[/blockquote]
[b][i]appearance:[/i] [/b]
[blockquote]ana looks much like her playby. though, she's a short 5'3", she doesn't let that stop her. with brown hair and dark brown eyes, you'll find it difficult to find her with the former down. she's of a slim, athletic build. distinguishing features are a set of pale, scarred knees from too many slide tackles, and a light callusing of her fingertips from gripping her broomstick.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personality[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]likes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote][ul type="disc"][li]football
[/li][li]quidditch[/li][li]cauliflower[/li][li]running[/li][li]being outdoors[/li][li]laughing[/li][li]meeting new people[/li][/ul]
[/blockquote]
[b][i]dislikes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote][ul type="disc"][li]following a schedule[/li][li]writing for too long[/li][li]reading too much[/li][li]being cooped up inside[/li][li]loneliness&nbsp;[/li][li]coleslaw[/li][li]milk[/li][/ul]
[/blockquote]
[b][i]erised:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]she'd love to play for a good women's football club, preferably Chelsea F.C. though she wouldn't be opposed to a broom and good quidditch team.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b][i]amortentia:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]the smell of a fresh pitch after a spring shower. clinging salty skin after swimming in the sea.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b][i]boggart:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]the worst thing that could happen to ana would be working in an office somewhere. or hurting herself to the point of never being able to run, or play football ever again.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b][i]overall personality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Ana is as impatient as she is kind. She is prone to seeing only the lighter side of life, but isn’t afraid of danger either. Call her an optimist. She’s never entered a game without thinking about winning. But, she can be a sore loser. While not afraid to shake her opponents hand, it is with the mind of a future conqueror. ‘I’ll get you next time’, she’ll think. That, you could say, makes her reckless. Be it that she’s always looking for her next adventure, she has a sporting mind about most things. There are a set of rules in life, a game to play, and a winner. She wants to win. 

However, that does not make her an unwanted friend. Ana will always think of a way to inject light in to her world, and for her friends when they feel low. She has an eye for making people smile and enough verve to make her fly high above the clouds. She doesn’t shy away from a challenge, but that’s only if she sees it first. She has been known to turn a blind eye to darkness in favour of daydreaming. To cover her ears and slack where games are not afoot. She’s still young, after all. Ana is also an incredible flirt. Known to fall back on charm wherever she can. Especially if that means gaining the upper hand on her opponents. Because that is how the world is cut in two, your allies and your opponents. She’ll race you at a moments notice, but tread carefully, she’s wicked on a broom.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personal history[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]mother:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Elena Eldridge Krum, 39, British Department of Magical Games and Sports.[/blockquote]
[b][i]father:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Viktor Krum, 47, retired Quidditch player, famous for competing in the 1994-95 Triwizard Cup for Durmstrang[/blockquote]

[b][i]siblings:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]___ krum, brother, 19, hogwarts alum
irina rose krum, sister, 18, hogwarts alum&nbsp;
raina gabriele krum, sister, 15, hufflepuff[/blockquote]
[b][i]pets:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]a northern white-face owl named boomer, whom she adores and who does not adore her back...[/blockquote]
[b][i]history:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Ana’s parent’s had always told her that she had been impatient since before she was even born. The third daughter of Viktor and Elena Krum, she had been a pleasant surprise when Elena had initially found out she was pregnant. Even more so when Ana arrived just over 4 weeks early. Kicking and screaming, they told Ana. Always a little too ready, a foot in before the water is even cool. And the Krum’s picturesque home in the Vrasta mountainside was the perfect landscape for a young Ana to thrive. That pure, mountain air, they used to joke. It made Ana maddeningly brave.

It was supposed, of course, that having two pro-Quidditch players as parents probably didn’t help the matter. Ana grew up on pitches, watching games and being fed a diet of screaming crowds and trick flips. Her mother was quick to realize that she’d found the child who shared her voracious appetite for sports, and Ana was all too willing to oblige. Before they left Bulgaria, Ana was already zooming around on her practise broom, eager to progress to a real one before she even turned 10. 

It was at 9 that Ana’s comfortable world would be shifted on its axis. When her mother, Elena, was given the opportunity to work for the Ministry in London. Ana was old enough to feel attached to her wild home. Because, where her mother had always fed her appetite for sport, it was her father that encouraged Ana to be adventurous. To question everything, and live comfortably among nature. Ana could read a compass before she could read at all. She knew how to navigate the wilderness, and enjoy doing so. Just like Irina, whom Ana always looked up to with full moon eyes.

But, Ana could not stop what was already in motion. She kicked and screamed, but nothing changed, the Krum’s moved to Thrisk, England, and Ana had to learn how to find adventure in a whole new world. She was 9, and angry, and she made enemies wherever she could. So much so that the Krum’s worried that she would never settle. Until, of course, Ana discovered the wonders of Muggle football. This diverted Ana’s attention and she quickly forgot about why she had been mad. Football was aggressive and fast paced. And while it was unfortunately land-bound, Ana enjoyed how the limitations riled the players. The complicated rules and particulars fascinated her. Viktor had found a way to please his second youngest, and he pandered to this accordingly. Even when Ana would scrap her knees slide tackling, she held off on the fast-acting salves so readily available to wizards. ‘All the others have marks on their knees’, she would say, preferring the cartoon plasters over smoothing paste. 

Ana then split her time between football and Quidditch, saddened when she had to leave the former behind to attend the esteemed Hogwart’s School of Witchcraft and Wizardry. Her brother had already gone, followed by Irina. It was Ana’s turn, but she did not shy away from it. Ana had never seen an obstacle she wasn’t prepared to overcome. She took the trip in stride, with shin guards and designer football boots.

Upon arriving at Hogwarts, the Sorting Hat deliberated for some time about where to place Ana. She had the makings of a Gryffindor, like her siblings before her, but there was something missing. A slight deviation that changed its mind last minute. [i]Hufflepuff![/i] It declared, and Ana was the first Krum separated from the pack. It threw her to begin with, frightening her, but she’d always been taught that fear was not always a bad thing. It was natural. And Hufflepuff truly was the perfect place for her, she slotted in among her peers incredibly quickly. Ana had never struggled making friends and it showed. She always had something to talk about, and the muggleborns always had the best taste in football clubs. 

At Hogwarts, Ana did well. But, only well. Academically she did not shine above the rest, but she got good enough grades to keep her family happy. Truth be told, Ana had very little interest in academia beyond the obvious. She liked hands on spells and duelling, but she had no interest in how to turn a rat in to a cup. Or, the mindless structure of potions recipes. No, Ana had always thrived while on the move. It made her good at a few classes, and only okay at the rest. But, that was fine by her. She was going to be a professional football player. That didn’t require an Outstanding in Transfiguration, lucky for her. 

And while separated from her two older siblings, Ana always remained close. The Krum’s had always been a relatively close-knit family to begin with and Ana thrived best near her sister Irina, who always knew how to reel her in when she began to wander. And when Raina arrived the year after Ana, it gave her a reason to appear somewhat responsible. She had to maintain her Elder status or risk a revolt… But, they never did share her enduring love for Quidditch. It left Ana with only one person to bubble endlessly to about sports, family friend Daniel Hoh. She lived a happy, rosy life for quite some time.

However, despite a relatively peaceful upbringing in England, the cracks were soon too obvious to hide. Ana had never been particularly interested in politics or war, but it was hard to ignore when it was right on your doorstep. First the strange death of a Ministry leader, of which Ana took very little interest in. But, when danger soon became apparent at Hogwarts, she could look nowhere but in the belly of the beast. Especially when muggleborns began turning up dead. It infuriated Ana to be told they may have only been killed for their blood. She’d never understood the meaning of purity, but that was easy to do when you had it. 

It, unfortunately, did not end there. In reality, it was only the beginning. First the students were killed, and then a whole group of students disappeared. The people responsible called themselves ‘The Purifiers’ and Ana had never been more disgusted with her own blood status. She didn’t feel pure, not when there were others using it as an excuse to kill. The danger was only more apparent when the culprit was revealed to be a fellow student. How shocked Ana had been when she heard the news, more so when it was assumed people where joining the ranks. But, it didn’t make Ana want to leave Hogwarts. It only made her want to stay more. There were good people there, she liked to think of herself as one of them. 

The Tri-wizard Tournament soon followed, and it was perhaps the only saving grace for Ana. She had always been fascinated by the event. It was just aggressive enough to keep her attention, with enough sporting to drive her nuts. All the better when the halls were filled with students from all across the globe. She had always loved a bit of healthy competition. Ana had only wished she had been of age to put her own name forward, cursing her own dumb luck to miss the boat by a mere year. 

The event proved to be the perfect distraction for Ana, and while the threat of the Purifiers endured, Ana was somewhat ignorant to its dangers. Everything seemed peachy with the comfort of the Tournament to occupy her mind. Not even when their own Headmaster was replaced, due to illness according to rumour. But, it had to end at some point, and with it that bubble of safety seemed to go with it. Popping in a way that could not be ignored. 

The bombing of the two departing carriages, containing the visitors from both Beauxbaton and Durmstrang, reverberated throughout the wizarding community. Ana knew how it would deeply effect her parents, given where they had spent their youth. It was a terrible way to end the year, and Ana would have nightmares for months to come. Plagued by the fear of these elusive enemies. But, school had to begin again at some point. She was going to be a seventh year after the summer. Only one more year of exams before she could pursue her dreams to be a professional sportswoman! 

Summer had a way of making Ana forget about the troublesome times. She could almost rest easy, but it was not without the news of Harry Potter, an infamous figure in the wizarding world, going missing. Followed shortly by the complete destruction of the esteemed American Wizarding school, Ilvermorny. It was easier to hear about this from a third perspective, but it only proved that things had not improved as Ana had hoped. They were as dark as ever. But, light shone through wherever it could. For, the other schools were quick to open their doors to the uprooted American students. Ana was told her seventh year would be filled with new faces! She latched on to that excitement and rode it all the way to her seventh year. 

Ana enters 7th year hoping to conquer Quidditch for the last time, and pass her classes. She refuses to think about what the past years events mean for her. Or her future. It is on track, as it always has been. She just has to keep her head up. 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]alias[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]name:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]chanel[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]22 now beeech.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b][i]time zone:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]GMT.[/blockquote]
[b][i]reference:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]rissy[/blockquote]
[b][i]other characters:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]oh damn... @tia    , @ondina    , @aaron    , @elijah    , @jimmie    , @nathaniel    &nbsp;[/blockquote][/div][/div]