[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://lifewithoutandy.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/IMGS0617-2.jpg" alt=" " style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]dahlia jade leloup[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]dah-lee-uh[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]n/a[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]21
august 3rd, 2004[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]female. she/her[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Half-Blood.
Werewolf. [/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]pansexual. [/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]Sycamore, Veela Hair, 9.5inches, bendy[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]mimi elashiry[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]5’4”. Looks identical to playby, tattoos and piercings included.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Beauxbatons.
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduated 2022.
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Curse Breaker Trainee[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Crypt diving, botany, being outdoors, clear skies, fog, chamomile tea, getting her way, dirt, sunshine, beaches, southern France[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Her father, being stopped from completing her work, being cold, when other aggressive people are that way towards her, people who don’t know how to take care of plants[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]To find a cure for lycanthropy. To score big on a dig. To kill her father.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]honey, morning dew, peanuts, freshly tilled dirt.[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Getting stuck in a tomb while working. Her father. The full moon.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Two-faced is a perfect description of Dahlia. She knows when to put on a smile and turn up the charm when trying to get her way, while also being able to coldly get her job done when necessary. She doesn’t necessarily dislike other people, but she certainly doesn’t trust them. Being a curse breaker really puts her in her element because she knows that the goblins are bullshitting as much as she is, and therefore knows she can trust them more than some person off of the street. Her ‘acting’ had all the professors at school thinking she was a kind, understanding girl, while her classmates knew exactly what she was like underneath. Some even went as far as to say she took after her father in those instances. And maybe she did, if just a little bit.
	
When she isn’t pretending, she can be very cold and unwelcoming. She’s an extremely angry young woman that has been dealt a bad hand in life. It’s essentially teenage angst at the next level, where action has taken over for words. Very hostile and aggressive outside of the fake ‘her’, she isn’t afraid to tell people how she really thinks and will back it up with action if she’s pushed to do so. Punching a talkative asshole at the bar after dropping her act has happened plenty of times, much to her companions’ chagrin.

The only true softness in her life is taking care of plants, since they have no stake in her internal war, and for the most part, have never done any wrong in her eyes. She tends to her plants with a level of tenderness that is absent in the other aspects of her life, and she equates it as making up for the lack of love that her mother has towards her.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Marseille, France[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Fenrir Greyback, werewolf, asshole
Farah Elmahdy – school teacher, 40, non-magique, deceased

Various half-siblings through father.
[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]n/a[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Another woman, another story about Fenrir Greyback. Like the many accounts Dahlia has heard from her various half-siblings over the last few years, hers isn’t that much different from the rest. The target this time just so happened to be a young Farah Elmahdy, a non-magical college student from Egypt that had decided to study in Paris during that unfortunate winter. Dahlia grew up hearing half-truths about what transpired, but cross-referencing with what she has learned since, it seems like her mother, like many of Fenrir’s targets, was picked up in a bar and it went from there. Nine months later, she was born and her mother permanently settled in Marseille, France. Away from family, and hopefully away from the terror of Fenrir Greyback.

Her childhood was uneventful, unlike some of her half-siblings. The small family of two was left alone, for the most part. Though Dahlia sometimes still wonders if that was a good thing or not. Her mother despised her, and it took a number of years for the girl to understand exactly why. There was zero love during her home life, and she learned how to perfect a way to hide that. Dahlia called it acting, something that she still falls back on to this day. It hides her insecurities and allows her to squirm out of situations without having to do what she really wants to do. Placating her mother was the start to all of this, and it seemed to work for the most part.

But boy was there a surprise when she turned eleven and received notification that Beauxbatons was accepting her as a student. There were always little things here and there that were unexplainable, but she had always figured that she was seeing things wrong or that she was incredibly lucky. Not wanting to deal with her anymore, Dahlia’s mother accepted the school without second guessing what magic was, and shipped her off. 

The first four years were full of things she had never imagined were possible, and it was a place to feel accepted. She didn’t feel the necessity to act fake around these kids, despite the snobbiness of some of them. In her eyes, they were all in the same boat when it came to learning about magic. Of course, all good things come to an end, especially amongst the children of Fenrir Greyback.

Upon returning home after her fourth year, a guest stopped by. Fenrir had apparently remembered his spawn in France, and had managed to track them down despite having moved from Paris. He had come to collect, you see, and despite her mother’s lack of love for her entire life, Farah refused that request. So Fenrir did what he always ended up doing. Murdered the woman and turned the child.

The months following, before school started up again, were traumatizing and horrid. Dahlia had never physically been on her own before, despite her mother’s emotional abuse making her feel that way at times. Weeks in the hospital, being tested and taught about Wolfsbane, the potion that would ease her transition to the werewolf form every full moon. How she had to be careful now that she was a monster, and how her name was now on a list, along with werewolves from all over. News spread quickly at Beauxbatons, and she was made to feel unwelcome there by the time she returned. 

They talked about Le Loup, Greyback’s nickname in France, and whispered hushed curses whenever she was around. Dahlia grew resentful almost immediately, later attributing her mother’s treatment to the way she lashed out at her classmates. Fist fights here, duels there. Plenty of detentions and warnings of expulsion followed, but she was always able to turn her ‘act’ on in time to prove that she was only defending herself. That the other students ostracized her because of her condition, and that it tore away at the scars of losing her mother over and over again. It didn’t matter that she was lying when it was essentially a half-truth to begin with. 

She decided then and there that she didn’t need anyone else, and the second she graduated from Beauxbatons and could legally change her name, she did. To Leloup. She wanted to wear their taunts at all times, to prove that she wasn’t scared of what she had become. Plus it made her former classmates nervous to be around her. And if it ended up painting a target on her back for her father? So be it. She assumes that accepting the wolf probably means running into him again eventually anyways, and she would rather be waiting and ready, than caught off again.

By this point, she had heard the stories of her father’s conquests all around, specifically in England. Deciding that her chances of starting fresh would be better in London, she traveled there and immediately managed to find a job as a curse breaker, and entering the training program. What a surprise it was when she discovered that one of her own half-siblings was in the same career path. From there, she’s learned of others, and has decided that they are her new family. 
 [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Dahlia doesn’t particularly care about what has been going on in England as of late. It’s not her country to worry about, and as long as her new half-siblings aren’t affected by anything happening, she doesn’t feel like she should be worried about it.

Hag’s Fever was sort an irritating occurrence though, the lockdown preventing her from entering the country for almost the entirety of the summer. To make up for this lost time, she took her loot from her last job (not able to return it to Gringotts), and went and hung out in her hometown of Marseille. She viewed it as a well-deserved break after years of training, and spent most of her free time on the beach pretending that she was like any other young adult her age that was free of responsibilities.

Since the lifting of the lockdown, she’s now returned to London and trying to get back into the swing of things, having lost most of her work ethic. The goblin weren’t exactly happy that she had laid around for months on end instead of reaching out to branch units to deposit the goods and get a new job. She gave them a few choice words with her opinion on that, and went about her day, finally getting paid for the first time in months.
 [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@colin  [/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]he/him [/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]26[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]est[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]Proboards Support[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@grey   @cordelia   @lance   @mina   @lily   @blaise   @cara   @nottingham   @steve   @jimbo   @harper   @renard   @madeleine   @nell   @nessa   @charlie   @mickey   @fae   @rusti  [/blockquote][/div][/div]
