[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="http://images6.fanpop.com/image/photos/38400000/Chris-Wood-chris-wood-38445413-500-282.png"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]ares edward lestrange[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]air-ees ed-wurd le-strange [/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]ares or ed. prefers to use ed.[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]22
16th october 2002[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]male, him/he[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]pureblood.[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]believed to be hetero, most likely pan tbh[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]11 inches, almond wood, unicorn hair core, unyielding and darkly coloured.[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]chris wood[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]ares is pretty much identical to his playby. the only main differences between him and his playby is that ares' stands a little taller at 6'2 and has a small scar near his left eye, that could potentially pull off as a birth mark and a few stabbing marks scattered around his body, including near his ribs, across his back and even his shoulder with the reason behind said scars being from his younger sister: andromeda. in relation to clothing, ares is usually found with dark shirts and jeans to match, he never really associates himself with bright colours. he calls them [i]harmful to the eye[/i] and definitely unattractive.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]hogwarts -- slytherin
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]graduated in 2021
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]part time bartender at hogs head, part time [s]secret[/s] thief[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]dark colours, fire whiskey, stealing, the smell of alcohol (he blames his job), reading, manipulation, fighting, not being liked (strangely enough).[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]loss of control, cowards/being viewed as a coward, andromeda in a stable state, the memory of his torture, the longbottoms (for adopting his sisters - tarnishing their lestrange name)[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]ares has no specific goal, aside from assuring his own family's wellbeing as well as his own. even though he somewhat drove one of his family members to insanity at one point & was tortured by her.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]smell of alcohol and rain.[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]being viewed as a coward, dying at the hands of his family.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote][i]mischievous, carefree, well mannered, cunning/manipulative, arrogant: an asshole.[/i]

as a child, ares was always rather...mischievous. he was always known for stealing things from both his parent's collections and even his younger siblings rooms once they entered the world. living life two years before another lestrange and eventually [i]another[/i] was introduced, ares was rather carefree and remained to be so as he grew. he refused to crumble against the pressure of setting an example for his younger siblings, believing that they should be their own person just like how ares was his own self. although his carefreeness was usually evident amongst his siblings, especially during serious moments between the lestrange children and their parents. he wasn't afraid of his mothers harsh words when she would discover the pranks he played on his younger siblings, or even afraid of his father when he soon came to realise he didn't necessarily care about blood status - even though he had been taught the importance of both politeness and the purity of blood as a young child. but one way or another, ares always found himself reeking some kind of havoc in the lestrange household. one thing that did stick with ares that he had learned from his parents was the understanding to brush aside those who only had intentions to waste the lestrange's time. 

though, after enrolling into hogwarts once the eldest lestrange received his letter at eleven years of age and after being sorted into slytherin, it was considered as one of the best things in ares' life. considering the traits that held along with the houses name seemed to reflect him rather well along link towards his families long history of slytherin's. he felt proud to continue the line just a little longer. unlike his sisters, ares' always tries to make his day better than the previous. incorporating fun one way or another was a necessity for him in order to stay literally sane. although, his version of fun usually came with harsh words and picking on other people.

ares is most definitely rather manipulative and arrogant. this is usually evident around: andromeda as his words somewhat helped drive her into a pit of insanity in their later years and students he would pick on during his schooling days - to perform tasks he wanted completed as well as means to find out information for things he wanted to know. his arrogance comes from the history of his family name and the pride he has to be a lestrange, knowing they have importance in magical history and society. and while ares is aware of the asshole he pretty much is, he enjoys it immensely, having no intention to change his ways.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]england, born and raised[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]
[ul type="circle"]
[li]morgana black lestrange - mother - deceased as of 2023[/li]
[li]rabastan lestrange - father - deceased as of 2023[/li]
[li]ariadne freya lestrange - 19, younger sister - trainee healer in the maternity ward[/li]
[li]andromeda karina lestrange - 18, younger sister - hit witch in training[/li]
[li]sarah jane oliveira - an old fling, the mother of his son[/li]
[li]callisto adriana oliveira - 23, sarah's sister, co-parenting[/li]
[li]sebastian oliveira (lestrange) - 3, born 29th may 2021, ares' son[/li]
[/ul][/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]none[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]with autumn blowing by in england two-thousand-and-two, morgana lestrange gave birth to her first child in the late hours of the sixteenth of october. born to morgana and rabastan lestrange, the new parents had the idea to give their child and future children [i]exotic[/i] names and so the first born boy was named ares in relation to the greek god of war. considering he came out kicking, the two lestrange's decided to be bold with their choices, knowing he would eventually kick up a storm. for the first two years of his life, ares' lived simply in the small cottage somewhere in england. he was taught how to be a well mannered boy, even if he was rather mischievous and filled with joy. two years into his life, his mother gave birth to another child - the first daughter: ariadne. and a year or so later, andromeda was born. growing up alongside two females wasn't particularly difficult for ares, he grew to learn his boundaries and how sensitive they were in comparison to the things he would speak of with his father. but that still didn't stop him from being a complete jerk, pulling horrid pranks and manipulating andromeda into things she simply didn't understand. it was always evident between the three children that ares and andromeda didn't really get along in comparison to his relationship with ariadne.

though, shortly after ares' turned eleven years old he received his letter from hogwarts and was swiftly enrolled into slytherin. with pride to uphold the family reputation and continue the line of slytherin, ares' was quick to make friends and even enemies. though those who usually challenged him found the short end of the stick as with his manipulation brought many people siding with him during times when fights were sure enough to break out. throughout his time in hogwarts, ares managed to achieve grades that left his parents pleased, setting an example for his younger sisters as they grew. he somewhat excelled in both wandless and non-verbal magic, which allowed him to conjure up secretive pranks/charms on his younger sisters during the breaks in between semesters. with each prank led onto a better score for each assignment in the new school term.

by ares' seventh year, he had no clear mind as to what he wanted to eventually become. he knew he wanted to remain close to his family members but had no true intention of a future career. as a result, after graduating ares found himself working part time in hogs head as a bartender and eventually earned enough to move away from the family home. but with boredom making its presence once more in his simple job, ares decided to take risks into his hands completely and the butter fingers and mischievousness worked out for him in the long run as a thief. it was something he practiced to become better at, stealing off muggles when he walked through the streets and even from witches and wizards alike. he was never really caught. though with the drama that surrounded his sister's lives, mainly ariadne's, led to the start of the lestrange family name in danger.

in 2022 both of his sisters were adopted by the longbottoms, in relation to the domestic abuse between ariadne and the lestrange's father involving a crucio curse. while he had been a jerk to his sisters for all of their life he had never psychically harmed them like his father did. from that night, ares concluded he wanted nothing to do with his father but instead express his hatred for what he had done for the rest of his life.  he still declined to be adopted alongside his younger siblings - refusing to tarnish the pride from his family's name. considering his legal age, ares thought it wasn't necessary either. and as the year continued quietly for ares, it seemed to grow increasingly worse for both ariadne and andromeda. 

by september 2023, andromeda had reached an all time low, something that ares rather enjoyed especially since he manipulated and encouraged for her to embrace the violence. during one night, andromeda had broken into his flat and decided to torture the eldest lestrange, going as far to even stab him in multiple places like his ribs and shoulders. but with his ways of manipulation and the mention of a familiar he managed to save his life. but that night, ares knew the change he saw in his sister was a change he would eventually enjoy. and his assumptions proved to be right. close to the end of 2023, andromeda returned to ares' flat a plan in mind to kill their parents for continuing to harass and threaten ariadne. while he necessarily didn't have problems with his mother aside from her harshness, his father was primarily the problem - but ares knew this was the thing that was bound to tip the scales in andy's sanity. but he went through with it anyway.

the plan was to kill them swiftly and quickly, without guilt or regrets. in the last moments, andromeda started to change her mind but being ambushed by their father, the fight had only just begun. with a spell going wrong, the entire floor came crashing down and ares did what he thought was best, took most of the blow by covering his body over andromeda and simply letting their parents die. when ares woke up, it was officially the new year of 2024, and ares was holed up in st mungos, receiving the [i]best kind of treatment[/i]. unlike his sister, who left sometime near the end of january because of therapy, ares was allowed to leave fairly early, his issues only being based around the psychical damage caused.  it didn't necessarily change anything for himself, he was fairly used to a simple hospital life and an even simpler life once he returned home. although, now technically orphaned and having the knowledge that his sister was somewhat bat shit crazy, ares decided to lay low, even disappearing to america for a few months. [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]sometime around 2020, ares met sarah oliveira at hogs head, a beautiful but a reckless woman in her entirety. the two spent the night together, a simple one night stand but one thing ares was not expecting was the discovery of the woman's pregnancy and eventually the birth of his child in 2021. at first when it was revealed sarah would be keeping his child, ares was close to shutting the world out or simply disappearing for the longest time. he wasn't ready for most things in his life and he was most definitely not ready for a child. but with his son, later named sebastian - entering the world, ares realised being a father was one thing he wanted one day - it had just come a little early. deciding to co-parent alongside sarah, things went well until sarah departed, something that ares didn't discover until months later, when sarah's sister: callisto informed him of it. because of her sudden disappearance, the true battle for custody had begun between the lestrange himself and the oliveria's, but ares' had high hopes to have joint custody in the end. 

though, in relation to the recent events, in relation to the deaths of the ministers of magic, it had a rather big impact considering he knew his sister: andromeda, worked somewhere within the ministry. it left ares rather worried for his sister and even friends he knew that worked in the ministry for their safety. although when news of the the deaths of the hogwarts students arose as well as the sudden news of the disappearance and later death of harry potter, ares found himself not too upset by it considering he had graduated years prior, thus not really knowing anyone younger aside from his siblings and harry potter just wasn't an influential figure for the lestrange, as he was to many other wizards.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]haise[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]9teen[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]gmt, best timezone[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]suzie[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]seven other nerds[/blockquote][/div][/div]