[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://i.pinimg.com/originals/b9/df/ea/b9dfea16ce9e691cf10b098099152572.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt=" "] [/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]lancelot ray linley[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]lance[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Lance. Not Lancelot at all. Tex by his bandmates, even though he keeps telling them Texas and South Carolina aren’t the same.[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]18
August 4th, 2007[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]male. he/him/his.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]half-blood.[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]heterosexual.[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]12 ¼ inches, willow wood, unicorn hair, slightly yielding.[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]luke hemmings.[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]5’9”. Lance dresses exactly the same in his free time and even has the lip ring, which is from a dare he made with his sister based on their bucketlists.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts. Hufflepuff.
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduated Class of 2025.
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Rhythm guitarist for the magical rock band, McCloud.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]BBQ, Georgie, baseball, sweet tea, the blues, the sound of cicadas, cats, playing his bass and guitar, performing live, meet and greets with fans, finally having money, after parties.[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]the orphanage, Barbara, still harbors a grudge for being forced overseas, being on his own, being tired, candy.[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Lance finally reached his goal of graduating from school and striking out on his own. His new goal is to keep playing with McCloud and help raise their ratings in the music industry. Basically he wants international stardom now that he’s gotten a taste for it.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]cooking charcoal, bbq, sulfur following fireworks, leather[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Failing as a musician and having to return to how he was as an orphan.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Lance has spent most of his life trying to be as optimistic and happy-go-lucky as possible. For everything that happened to him and Georgie after their parents initially disappeared, he tried to stay as positive as he could for both of them, although slipping up now and again. Knowing that this was the attitude needed to make it through the move across the pond, in the orphanage, and to attend Hogwarts for a year without his sister, these traits ended sticking with him. At the time, it was just the two of them, and with the things they faced, one of them had to be easy-going enough to tackle everything that was thrown their way. While Georgie stay attached to him most of the time and rarely let anyone else in, Lance did his best to make friends that would help them out where he couldn’t do things on his own.

Another key trait is that he’s a southern gentleman. Along with the positivity, he had to bring some traits of home. He learned extremely fast that being polite and knowing how to treat others the right way was the fastest way to earn trust and respect. While that seems manipulative in a sense, he knows how to separate it from getting what he wants, because just being able to be happy and not alone is all that he wants in life.

He also has an extremely high level of tolerance, along the same vein of his easy-going positivity. Since his parents reappeared in his life though, he’s become a little more cynical, but only towards them. While he’s normally extremely trusting and accepting of how others are, he’s learned to draw the line for certain circumstances. 

But these days, he’s had a bit of a switch in personality. While the good parts of him are still prevalent somewhere deep down inside him, being thrust suddenly into stardom with the band at such a young age has made him arrogant and vain. Having virtually nothing up until this point, Lance has very quickly become materialistic and is attempting to do his best at being part of the “in-crowd”, as his band leader, McCloud, calls it. Having zero figures to look up to until meeting McCloud, the lead singer’s personality and outlook on life have certainly rubbed off on Lance in all the wrong ways.

The cynicism that used to be reserved only for his parents has come more to light in the last six months, turning into a weird mix of teenage angst and rebellion. All of his actions are facilitated by the band and the industry that he is now a part of. Going from an appreciative orphan to a rock star almost overnight has not helped Lance in the slightest, and going back to the way he was before would take a lot of undoing of his new traits and habits.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]South Carolina, USA[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Mother – Barbara Linley, 40, Unkown job in the US
Father – Arthur Linley, 39, hit wizard, deceased
Sister – Georgiana Linley, 17, 7th Year Hufflepuff[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]n/a[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Growing up in South Carolina was a dream. It was its own world away from everything else that was going on, and seemed to be the epitome of perfection. Of course not all good things last, and that dream was shattered the second his younger sister, Georgie, woke him up to a house without any parents. While this was a reality with their parents’ occupations, it was the fact that they never returned that set everything into motion. Barbara and Arthur Linley were missing, and no one could find them. From here, the two siblings were shipped to the strangest of places, and what seemed like so far away from home, that they would never return to the dream-like spectacle of their home in the USA. 

Landing in an orphanage in Britain, Lance was immediately sent off to Hogwarts, where he, along with all the other 11-year olds that went that year, was sorted into Hufflepuff. For the first time in his life he had been separated from sister, and his entire first year at the magical school was spent in turmoil. Lucky for both of them, she arrived the next year and was also sorted into Hufflepuff. Reunited once again outside of the orphanage, life seemingly felt right for the next five years. Lance hated going back to the orphanage. While both of them were treated exceptionally, he knew that the reason they were never adopted was because no one wanted two kids. At the same time, that was his only saving grace, because being separated again only to see each other while at school had already been hard enough once.

The previous school year reawakened those fears once again when no-maj-born students were starting to be killed while at Hogwarts. Lance knew that he Georgie would be safe because of this, but his familial instincts had kicked into overdrive. Being in the same house was enough to make sure she was constantly okay, but it got to a point where he was terrified that things would never stop, and the next victims would be those who didn’t have any family. Namely the two of them. It was an irrational fear, but that was the intent of those committing the crimes.

Over the past summer, something he never thought would happen occurred: their parents returned. They were supposed to be missing, dead, or some combination of both. And now they were in England looking for their children. Things weren’t as easy as Barbara and Art made it out to be though. The family they wanted to protect so badly had learned to adapt without them. Abandoning them without any cause or reason had already done enough damage, why they thought returning would make everything right again was something he was still trying to grapple with. Unwilling to commit back to their parents, he’s put up blocks to their attempts to return everything to “normal”. Lance was unfortunate enough to only meet with Barbara after his father was killed in the line of duty, and by that point it still didn’t seem real to him. As far as he was concerned, his parents had both been dead for years. At the same time, there was a feeling of finality now that it was a real death.

From there, Lance entered his seventh and final year at Hogwarts. He became a Prefect for Hufflepuff and had a girlfriend, Katherine being his only saving grace for the last two semesters of school. In the fall, Barbara left him and Georgie a sum of money in their Gringotts accounts and an apartment for after graduation. While hesitant to use anything that came from her, Lance accepted that at least, because it would help ease the monetary burden of being pushed out of the orphanage and into the unknown.

Fortunately that unknown was barely seen, because during the winter break Lance decided to shoot his shot with auditions for a couple of bands. Most of them were hesitant about allowing a current student in, since it would be months before they could properly practice or tour. Only one really gave him a chance: McCloud. Named after the founder and lead singer, McCloud offered to work around the scheduling conflicts for the few months until Lance graduated, as long as he learned all of their material by the time he got out.

Overjoyed by his luck, Lance did just that, and learned everything he needed in order to join the outfit. The first few shows in early June were rough around the edges, but he has since gotten used to performing live and living the rock star life for all the good and bad that comes along with it. He still has a lot of learning and growing to do in his new role as a musician, but he has yet to let anything stop him from going where he wants, and a silly quarantine isn’t going to stop him or the band.

[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Lance, for the most part, has started to ignore anything that goes on outside of the band. During the breakout of Azkaban, he was on winter break and busy trying out for bands. A few ended up being cancelled due to safety concerns, so he was bummed out because of that. Overall though, he knew he was relatively safe at the orphanage and going back to Hogwarts for his last term wasn’t really an issue with him either.

The quarantine due to Hag’s Fever has become increasingly more annoying though now that he’s part of the band. Initially they had planned to do a European tour, ending at home in England. But with the closing of the borders, they were stuck outside until mid-June, when visas and travels were allowed to continue once again. McCloud was pissed the whole time since there weren’t many shows to do on the fly and other ones had to be postponed or cancelled. Lance looked at it as a way to get used to musician life, and he has started to feel like he really fit in with them now that they had been on the road for almost a month. He has been worried about Georgie though, since he heard that the orphanage was taking on any wayward Ilvermorny students for the summer as well. His concerns have been more about her sanity, having to deal with all the extra people there, than they are about her health.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@colin [/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]25[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]est[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]proboards support 4 years ago[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@grey  @cordelia  @mina  @lily  @cara  @nottingham  @jimbo  @steve  @blaise  @harper  @renard  @nell  @nessa  @charlie [/blockquote][/div][/div]
