[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://data.whicdn.com/images/161191009/original.gif" style="max-width:100%;" alt=""]
[/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Philip Carson Longbottom
[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]FILL-UP CAR-SON LONG-BOTT-OM[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Phil
[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]19
march 20, 2006
[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Male, he, him
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Pureblood,[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Straight[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]13 inch, alder wood, unicorn hair[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Bradley James
[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Phil looks much like his play by, fit and blonde. He does wear glasses but he only needs them for reading books or anything with rather small print. Typically he isn’t in anything more than just dark jeans and shirts. Anything that can easily hide the dirty he is normally in everyday.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts - Gryffindor
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduate
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Herbologist
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]rain, herbology, plants, flowers, grass, trees, all things green, socks, sweets, being helpful, spending time with his family and friends, drawing, art, painting (occasionally), friends, travelling, violin (playing and listening), finding new uses for plants and plant based medicines, Quidditch.[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote][/blockquote][blockquote]severe cold, allergies, sour foods or candies, snakes, things being dirty or unorganized, violence, danger, fear, people being hurt or ill, the purifiers.&nbsp; [/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Phil has always desired of haveing a large family. One that can be happy and rely on one another in times of need. He likes to picture his one day family with many children running around, either his own or children that needed a home that he had taken in. He also desires to one day cure his father of whatever illness he was stricken with that magical healers still aren’t sure about. [/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]The smell of fresh dirt and grass or almost any plant for that matter.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Phillip has always had a fear of snakes from back when he was a child and almost bitten by one while in the garden. That and the fear that his father will never be cured and always be ill.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Philip has always been a kind-hearted soul, wishing nothing more than for everyone to get long and for there to be peace in his life. Sadly that hasn’t been the case since the purifiers came onto the scene. Yet he still believes there will be better times ahead for himself and everyone around him. Phil has a naiveness about him which can be both charming and used against him. He’s always chosen to believe in the best of people and take them for their word. He can hardly lie and wishes the same would have been true about some of the people he had known. Still, he feels that no one is beyond being redeemed for their actions, all they need is to be given the chance.

While a sunny and welcoming person there is always a shyness to him when meeting new people. That and awkwardness around serious topics or when he just doesn’t feel comfortable with the discussion at hand. Once he knows the person more he is an open book, it isn’t hard to get the Longbottom’s trust and while he knows this action could easily be used against him he doesn’t let him stop or close himself off. He wants to be the person people turn to in their time of need. Not with a stern word or harsh judgment but a smile and support. Believing that is all the world really needs.

Phil has always seemed like much of a pushover, never standing up for himself too often unless he truly had to. Instead, he just ignored it. He wasn’t in any danger and he didn’t need to cause problems for himself. Honestly, the only time he had shown much of a backbone was when someone else was in need. He could deal with his issues by just letting them be but he wanted to and needed to be there for others. Just part of the Gryffindor he is even if it never seemed like he was much of one to begin with any other time.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Scotland - Birsay
[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]    Hannah Longbottom nee Abbott, 44, landlady of the leaky cauldron -Mother

Neville Longbottom, 45, former headmaster of Hogwarts -Father

Alice Longbottom, 20, hufflepuff alum
Jayden Longbottom, 17, gryffindor
Ariadne FreyaLestrange, &nbsp; 19, healer (adopted)
andromeda longbottom, 18, hit witch (adopted)[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]None at the moment, just many many plants.
[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Philip was born the second, just a year after his older sister Alice, to Neville and Hannah Longbottom. A year after him his younger brother Jayden was born. Growing up Jayden and Philip were for the most part inseparable. Certainly, there was the fact that they were just so close in age but also as Phil got older his sister, Alice and he, fought more often. Always trying to get their parent's attention, it was a competition for them it seemed. Still, the house was mostly full of laughs between the three. There was always at least one child causing trouble somewhere. From accidentally casting underage magic to just drawing on the walls and floors. All three of the kids were a hand full but Neville and Hannah were up for the challenge.

Even from a young age Phil always had an interest in plants. Yet being a kid it was just seen as playing in the dirt and making a mess. There was a young desire to know just what all these green or colorful things were. On his eleventh birthday, Phil received his Hogwarts letter but it wasn’t like his parents weren’t aware he would be going. Neville’s children were making up for the fact Neville never showed any magical abilities as a child in spades. Once at Hogwarts Phil was sorted into Gryffindor without much debate from the sorting hat. He was happy to be a Gryffindor not just because it was his father's house but he got to have a break from his sister who had been sorted into Hufflepuff last year. Phil quickly went to learning about Herbology.

Over the years at Hogwarts, his love for Herbology just grew as well as an interest in potion-making but that just came from the fact it used Herbology ingredients. It didn’t hurt that his father had been teaching Herbology as well. Phil made plenty of friends as he got older, it was easy with the type of person he was. He opened up to people quickly after some mild shyness in the beginning. Two of his best friends being Andy and Jude. Who started dating, which he should have been happy about but he had also been hiding a crush he had on Andy for some time. Unsure of just how she felt or would react, deciding it was better to not ruin their friendship.

[/blockquote][b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Phil’s Sixth year is also when the magical world started to be shaken up and not just his personal life. There had been multiple attacks on the school or the train station. Phil didn’t like the idea of the possible violence or confrontation but he eventually joined a student-run group called Phoenix rising. Much like the D.A. had been they looked to protect the school and the students. Phoenix rising and his studies in Herbology took much of his time. Still, he made time for his friends as they were always important to him. Phil should have been sad but he was rather happy hearing that Andy and Jude’s relationship didn’t last very long. He tried to not let that show as he felt horrible about that as he tried to be there for Andy, slowly the two grew even closer.

Over Christmas break, Andy and her sister came to join the Longbottom’s where he soon found out that they were going to adopt them. Which made the situation a little awkward as Andy and Phil had already kissed and were almost dating. His mother worried about them being so close and now legally half-siblings so they decided to take a break from one another which didn’t last very long. They remained together till the end of his seventh year.

The summer of his sixth year was a rush of fun and romance with Andy but there was a damper put on it toward the end as Phil as been accepted into a foreign student program with a school in Brazil which specialized in Herbology. He was both excited and sad, it was a passion in his life but his other passion, Andy, would still be going to Hogwarts. Still, they both agreed that he couldn’t pass up this chance and during his seventh year he left for Brazil. Yet he wrote to Andy and all his family non-stop.

Phil still kept up with the news in Europe, finding out that he was going to miss the tri-wizard tournament because of his transfer. He was a little sad about that but at the same time just missed his family and Andy more. Eventually, he couldn’t take the distance anymore and return to Hogwarts around time for the Yule Ball. Surprising Andy with a dance. Phil felt that now that he was back everything would be perfect but that feeling was so very wrong. First New Years came and after an urgent message from Andy. Phil and his father found her hurt, almost dead outside her old family home. Andy was rushed to St.Mungos where she spent just over a month trying to recover from what had happened that night.

Doing his best to avoid any questions or attention about what had happened to Andy he just counted the days till she was back at Hogwarts. Finally, Andy had returned and life could get back on track but the world had other plans as soon after his father was hospitalized with some illness that no one knew about or could cure. They could just help ease the symptoms. Phil retreated to the one place he felt safe and sure, the greenhouse. He hardly came out unless for other classes and didn’t even see Andy that much. As much as he loved her the things that she had done and everything that was going on in his life were getting to him. He wanted to be happy and carefree but just couldn’t help it. It also didn’t help that he kept having weird dreams about her sister Ariadne too.

Andy tried to help him the best she could by spending time with him and even teaching him the violin. Just before his Graduation life had to add yet another twist. Just after both visit schools left Hogwarts they were attacked. Almost everyone died from both beauxbatons and Durmstrang. Many new friends he had made over the last year were gone in an instant. It was a hard thing for Phil to take, he hadn't known anyone who had actually died. 

Just before graduation came up Andy and Phil finally broke up, with all that had happened it recently and between them it just felt like the right move. Maybe one day getting back together when the time was right. After school, Philip spent much of his time in his greenhouse on Longbottom hill. It was hard to take losing so many people, some he had known when both of the visiting schools had been attacked. The world was changing too fast and while he felt like he needed to do more, he didn’t know where to start.

Phil devoted much of his time to trying to help his father, he wanted nothing more than his father to be healthy again and even took less care of himself just hiding away. Rising his plants and brewing healing potions. All things the healers at St. Mungos had tried but nothing helped. Quickly his family told him about Harry having gone missing. It was another blow to both the world and to his hopes that everything would be okay eventually. If something had happened to Harry, who he and his family had been very close to, anything could happen. Phil kept so wrapped in his little world that he didn’t even hear about the damage done to the American school of Ilvermorny till his brother told him about it weeks later.

With the recent attack on Hogsmeade and the destruction of Azkaban it was obvious to even Phil that life wasn't going back to how it used to be anytime soon and being hidden away in his greenhouses at home isn’t helping anyone. Instead, resolving to get back into the world and help the people he cares so much about and new friends too. Sitting ideally by hasn't helped anyone including himself.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Other TJ
[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]He
[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]31[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]Est
[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]You guys wouldn't let me use the restroom unless I made a character first and now I can't leave.
[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@crimson1          @lockhart          @shawn          @jacob          @lars          @viktor         @jim          @simontroy         
[/blockquote][/div][/div]
