[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"] [img style="max-width:100%;" alt="GIF" src="https://66.media.tumblr.com/3746f9637499105c5a412ab8412331bd/tumblr_pu0fx9wvi71y50hrlo3_500.gif"] [/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Blair Isabella Lopez[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]BLEHR iz-uh-BEL-uh LOH-pez[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Blair (and really only Blair)[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]18
November 2, 2006[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Cisgender female; she/her pronouns[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Half-blood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Pansexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]11 inches, aspen, phoenix feather core, brittle (current/replacement wand)

9⅚ inches, mayhaw, dragon heartstring core, solid (while at Ilvermorny)[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Rizha[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Blair is 5'8" tall, with a slim build. She has fair skin and brown eyes. Although her hair is naturally brown, she has dyed it jet black since she was thirteen. (She has also taken to adding some other color to the ends of her hair, and—more often than not—that color is purple.) It is naturally straight and hangs past her shoulders.

Her ears are pierced multiple times: twice on each earlobe and one helix piercing on her left ear. She also has four tattoos, the first two being stick-and-poke tattoos that she did herself. Her first tattoo is of an eye on the inside of her left ankle, and her second is of a star on her left wrist. Her more recent tattoos were done professionally. One is of the Scorpio zodiac symbol, tattooed on her ribcage on the right side; the other is a linework piece of a violet on her right forearm. She has a few scars from falls while learning to longboard but nothing too noticeable.

Blair's fashion sense has always been what some might call "tomboyish", though it veers towards the edgier side of things. She prefers to wear things like layered tees, bomber jackets, and ripped jeans. Additionally, she usually keeps her fingernails short and painted black.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts – Hufflepuff House (September 2024 – June 2025)
Ilvermorny – Wampus House (September 2018 – June 2024)
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduate[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Apprentice tattoo artist at Mystery Ink Arts[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Muggle/No-Maj technology; drawing; vintage clothing; classic rock; Chinese food; combat boots; fire; longboarding; the feeling of tattoo needles against her skin; being in control[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Tech bros; homophobia; green apples; blood purists; people who cancel plans at the last minute; heights; too much pink; being alone; bubblegum pop; the sound of her voice when recorded[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Blair's greatest goal is to become a full tattoo artist. She also wouldn't mind being in a relationship with someone, maybe settling down back in Texas eventually.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Cigarette smoke, witch hazel, and something that she doesn't realize is actually hay[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Blair has a strong fear of heights. Even though she wouldn't admit it, she does fear ending up alone, too.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote][b]admiration[/b] - Blair most admires those who have been able to carve their own path in the world, especially those who have done it in an unconventional way. She is very much a champion of the "outsiders" in life and doesn't necessarily stick to society's ideas of what she should aspire to be.

[b]adoration[/b] - Blair probably wouldn't use the word "adoration" to describe anything that she's ever done; it would feel a little bit soft for her. Beyond the surface, however, she adores being wanted and needed by other people.

[b]aesthetic appreciation[/b] - As a trainee tattoo artist with an artist mother, Blair has spent a lot of her time around some form of art or another. She tends to gravitate to darker, macabre, or more subversive elements in her own art, which is also reflected in the styles in which she prefers to tattoo.

[b]amusement[/b] - Blair has a pretty dark sense of humor, though it's more self-deprecating than it is at the expense of others. She has a sardonic wit, and she tends to use it as a coping mechanism.

[b]anger[/b] - Blair can be more than a little hot-headed, and everything that has happened over the past year in relation to Ilvermorny—and basically every other thing in the news in Britain—has made her even angrier. She tries not to lash out directly, but it happens when she's stressed.

[b]anxiety[/b] - As much as Blair tries to hide her anxiety, she is anxious about a lot of things. For one thing, she doesn't really know what her future holds, not to mention a fear of being forever alone. In short, she has a lot going on inside her head at all times, but she'll be damned if she exposes that to just anybody else.

[b]awe[/b] - Blair is most awestruck by the idea that the world is so big and so full of things that she'll never get to experience for herself. If she could capture even a fraction of that in a bottle, she would.

[b]awkwardness[/b] - While Blair isn't awkward in a "geeky" sense, she is a teenage girl and has had her moments. She's most awkward when she's forced to let down her guard around anyone.

[b]boredom[/b] - Anything too academic has always been boring to Blair, who spends just about every free moment either doodling or on her longboard, depending on where she is.

[b]calmness[/b] - Blair is most calm when she knows that no one is angry with her and doesn't have any other obligations weighing on her shoulders. Some rock music in her headphones definitely helps.

[b]confusion[/b] - What most confuses Blair is why she isn't universally hated. She's amazed by the fact that anyone could love her, even if only for a short while. On a more mundane note, being asked to read anything aloud in class was always confusing, since she probably wasn't paying attention.

[b]contempt[/b] - Blair most feels contempt towards people who are clearly trying too hard to fit in or trying to mold her into something she isn't. Her parents are usually on that list.

[b]craving[/b] - When it comes to food, Blair isn't too picky, for the most part. She most craves savory food. In a less literal sense, she craves fulfilling relationships with other people and recognition for her artwork on its own merits.

[b]disappointment[/b] - Blair's biggest disappointment so far has been opening herself up to someone else, only to have it blow up in her face.

[b]disgust[/b] - Blair is disgusted by people who espouse blood purist ideology—right up there with homophobes, transphobes, and misogynists.

[b]empathic pain[/b] - Unfortunately, Blair is really bad at the whole "empathy" thing. She knows that she should feel more for other people, but it's hard for her to get inside anyone's head besides her own.

[b]entrancement[/b] - Blair is entranced by the things that people are capable of doing with magical tattoos, as well as the blending of magical and non-magical technologies.

[b]envy[/b] - Secretly, Blair is envious of those who have good relationships with their parents. She's also envious of the attention that others receive from people with whom she's close, especially in romantic situations.

[b]excitement[/b] - Nothing brings Blair more excitement than an adrenaline rush. Whether it's longboarding or doing something that she probably shouldn't, she enjoys living dangerously.

[b]fear[/b] - Blair fears abandonment and ending up alone. She also fears heights.

[b]guilt[/b] - Blair most typically feels guilt after she's blown up at someone and knows that she shouldn't have reacted so strongly.

[b]horror[/b] - The idea that there are actually people in the world who are so obsessed with the purity of their magical bloodlines that they would kill for it is pretty horrifying to Blair.

[b]interest[/b] - Blair is most interested in things outside of academic pursuits, especially counterculture. If she hadn't gone into tattooing, she probably would have gone into tech.

[b]joy[/b] - Being around people who accept her for who she is without condition brings Blair the most joy.

[b]nostalgia[/b] - Blair feels the most nostalgia for anything that reminds her of Ilvermorny. Even if she didn't technically graduate from Ilvermorny itself, she still considers it her alma mater.

[b]pride[/b] - Even though she knows that not everyone is accepting of it, Blair is proud of being part of the LGBTQ+ community.

[b]relief[/b] - Blair feels the most relieved when others act in ways that lets her know that they value her, rather than just saying that they do.

[b]romance[/b] - While she isn't exactly a hopeless romantic or an open flirt, Blair does enjoy romance and romantic gestures. For her, it's more about little things than making a show of a relationship, 

[b]sadness[/b] - Anger and sadness have always gone hand in hand for Blair, but she most strongly feels sadness when she hears anything about another tragic death.

[b]satisfaction[/b] - Blair feels most satisfied when she's completed a tattoo or a piece of artwork that took a lot of effort.

[b]sexual desire[/b] - Being pansexual, Blair experiences sexual attraction to people of all sexual and/or gender identities.

[b]surprise[/b] - Blair is most surprised when she realizes that her first impressions of someone weren't what she first believed them to be.

[b]sympathy[/b] - As with empathy, Blair isn't always the most sympathetic person, but she isn't devoid of emotion about other people's misfortunes. It's easier if she's not directly interacting with the other person in question or expected to provide comfort.

[b]triumph[/b] - Blair most strongly feels triumph when she has the last word in an argument. Even if she isn't right, it makes her feel that she is.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Austin, Texas, USA[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote][b]mother:[/b]
Amanda Aguirre-Lopez, 49, wizarding artist, No-Maj-born witch, divorced from John

[b]father:[/b]
John Lopez, 53, former professional Quodpot player, pure-blood wizard, divorced from Amanda

[b]ex-girlfriend:[/b]
@whiskey, 18, Magical Wildlife Rehabilitation Center apprentice veterinarian, half-blood witch

[b]extended family:[/b]
Extended Lopez family members are [i]OPEN[/i].[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]A one-night stand and a shotgun wedding later, Blair Isabella Lopez was born. Although her parents hadn't intended to end up with a child, they did the best that they could to raise their little girl. Most often, it fell to Blair's mother, Amanda, to take care of her. Her father was often busy because of his career as a Quodpot player, and Blair's most vivid memories of her father from her youngest years are of attending his Quodpot games.

At age five, Blair was enrolled in a No-Maj elementary school, giving her mother more time to focus on her artwork instead of child-rearing. Her father, however, wasn't supportive of the decision. It was different from what he had known all of his life, and it exacerbated the issues that were already present in John and Amanda's marriage.

All good things must come to an end, which also became true of their relationship by the time that Blair had reached the first grade. In the divorce, Blair's parents retained joint custody of her, and she switched houses every other week. The older she became, the more that the arrangement got to be a hassle for her. It was a challenge enough to balance being magical in the non-magical world without having to switch back and forth between homes so often, and Blair grew to resent that her parents' divorce made it harder.

Even though it meant leaving No-Maj life behind her for the most part, Blair was grateful to receive her acceptance to Ilvermorny. If she couldn't have consistency with a supposedly "No-Maj" life, then at least she could have some consistency with a fully magical one. Once at school, she was Sorted into Wampus House, and she found her niche among the "artsy" kids. She also wound up in trouble with her teachers a few too many times for doodling when she should have been focusing on her schoolwork.

School itself wasn't something that Blair took to—not in an academic sense, anyway. She wasn't concerned about her grades and preferred to focus on what interested her outside of class: art, non-magical technology, and skating. It was the sort of thing that made her teachers comment that she would have done very well in class… if only she had applied herself to the material.

As time passed, Blair realized something else about herself as she made her way through puberty. She knew that she had always been "different"—which being magical was, in a way, in itself—but began to think that she wasn't straight, either. Blair knew that she wasn't as attracted to men as she was to women, so she initially felt that identifying as bisexual was the right fit. The more that she learned about other identities, though, she then felt that "pansexual" fit her even better. She came out to her parents at fifteen, and, while neither had issues with her sexual orientation, it felt weird to be so open with them about it. Beyond the fact of her [i]being[/i] pansexual, she didn’t think that it was really any of their business whom she dated. 

Blair didn’t really date around as much as some of her peers at school. She couldn’t see herself dating anyone for the sake of dating, but she also wasn’t very concerned with the idea of waiting for someone to whom she could see herself getting married. (In her view, that had worked [i]so[/i] well for her parents…)

By the end of her sixth year at Ilvermorny, Blair was looking forward to moving on with her life. She might have had one more year of schooling, but she was almost free, free to move away from her parents—probably to New York or somewhere exciting—and use magic and earn money on her own terms. All of that came to a screeching halt, however, when Ilvermorny was vandalized shortly after the summer break began. Angry at what had happened to her school, Blair wasn't thrilled to make the move to Hogwarts, but she didn’t have much choice.

Even more so than in the past, Blair became agitated and rebellious. If Ilvermorny could be damaged so extensively just like [i]that[/i], then what was the point of planning for anything? Increasingly disillusioned with school, Blair used her art as an outlet for her emotions. She also found comfort in one of her longtime classmates, Whiskey Earp, with whom she began a relationship early on in the year. If there was anything good that had come from transferring to Hogwarts and becoming a Hufflepuff instead of a Wampus, it was being thousands of miles from her parents’ influence and having a girlfriend who adored her.

Without Blair’s realizing it, her need for control over other aspects of her life also extended to her relationship with Whiskey. In spite of her love for the other girl, Blair was also possessive of Whiskey and demanding of her time and attention. She genuinely saw a future with Whiskey and was devastated by the fact that Whiskey didn’t seem to reciprocate her feelings towards her. When Whiskey broke up with her, Blair remained in denial about the toxicity of her own behavior. Instead, she deflected it back onto her ex, who, she felt, wasn’t secure enough in their relationship.

Bitter and seeking direction, Blair submitted a portfolio of her artwork to a magical tattoo shop in London to be considered for an apprenticeship, for which she was selected. Although it wasn’t exactly how she anticipated her life to be going straight out of school, Blair began her apprenticeship in Summer 2025. A few months on, she’s interested in specializing in photorealistic tattoos and portraiture and is looking forward to what tattooing holds for her.
[/blockquote] 
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Prior to the vandalism of Ilvermorny, Blair wasn't too focused on the things that were happening elsewhere in the world. It wasn't until her classmates started bringing up all of the terrible things that had happened at Hogwarts in recent years that she began to feel as though going to the British wizarding school was a stupid idea. There were murders and near-deaths and kidnappings and a handful of explosions… and that was only in the span of a few years.

Once she and the other Ilvermorny students got to Hogwarts that September, things seemed to be alright enough. The fact that she had a girlfriend was a good distraction, but even that couldn't stop the fact that the world had other plans. The Winter Festival was excellent… until dragons nearly destroyed Hogsmeade, and the news that Azkaban had been destroyed and its prisoners escaped on the same day wasn't very reassuring.

A Boggart infestation at Hogwarts and then the outbreak of a new disease a few months later shouldn't have felt like the end of the world. Coupled with a break-up, though, they did, and Blair would have been ready to leave the country for good—if she could have left.

Right as she began to accept that she would be remaining in Britain, the British and Irish Quidditch League finals match came, though it ended in an explosion. Blair, who had planned to attend but had had a change of plans at the last minute, was devastated to learn that there had been casualties—most of them American. Maybe it made her a conspiracy theorist, but she didn't buy that it was accidental; it was too convenient an excuse.

Gradually, over the summer, she began to connect with some others on wizarding social media who felt similarly about recent events. There had to have been more to it all, and Blair was relieved that she wasn't the only one who thought so. It was all a little suspicious, and it seemed as though there were enough people who knew more than they were letting on…[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@audrey[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]She/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]22[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote] Central Time[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]Current member![/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@ezekiel, @chrissy, @monday, @clarence, @parvati, @brody, @penelope, @kaylee, @maxima, @muffet, @dasha, @samira, @felix, @priscilla, @camila, @claricia, @honey, @tamatha [/blockquote][/div][/div]
