[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://media.giphy.com/media/SUKGCjabcNjuahwWNe/giphy.gif" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Shreya Dawn MacMillan[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]Shrai-yaa[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Rey, Shrek[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]April 27th 2007, 18 yo.[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]She/Her[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Pureblood,[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote](Older) men[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]Vine and dragon heartstrong, 11", flexible[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Ananya Pandey[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]She always dresses for the situation and the benefits she hopes to gain from it. Despite this she always carries a small locket with her that has photographs of her family in it, as they are the core of her life.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts, Gryffindor[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Alumna[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Mediwitch, first responder (in training)[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Devious plans, the truth, her family, justice, healing, helping others, rebelling, deception, musicians, beards[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]cooking, cleaning, laundry, boring things, liars, guys her own age that hit on her, expectations[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]To be a strong rolemodel for younger girls.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Bleach, rugged guy smell, old parchment, rust[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Chains, darkness, fire.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Shreya prides herself on never telling lies. This doesn't by default mean she is always truthful. She's often deceptive and is very good at deceiving and misleading people to believe what she wants them to believe. She tends to act very sweet and innocent around authority figures while at the same time doing shady dealings right under their noses. She has a great deal of pride but above all she has a great deal of love for her family and often sees her deceptions mostly as a game to keep herself distracted from the mess their father got them into.&nbsp;

Underneath the exterior Shreya is a calm and confident woman, although she's very self conscious and has grown to be distrustful over time. She is fiercely independent but longs to find somebody she can fully depend on. She's very much two opposite sides rolled into one internal mess that she hides like no other from the outside world.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Knightsbridge, London, England.[/blockquote][b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Father - Ernie MacMillan
&nbsp;Mother - @parvati     
Twin Brother - @sav 

Half sibling twins:&nbsp; ____ Flint and _____ Flint by her fathers side.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Shreya was born as the second twin, only six minutes behind her brother, although he's never allowed her to forget she came in second. At a younger age she felt a certain sense of dismay at this particular fact but as she grew older, she started using it as a strength. This mostly affected her willingness to do chores and act responsibly, which she frequently suggested wasn't to be expected from her as the youngest of the family.&nbsp;

For the most part, her childhood was good. She led a relatively safe and sheltered life. She had very little to worry about and had what she considered to be a perfect family life, at the very least until she started school. Things got a little bit more complicated in her school years, although not an insane amount in the earlier years.&nbsp;

Things got messy when she found herself becoming an adult in her own eyes. Like most girls of age 14 she considered herself very mature and was totally ready to start dating, although her interest was not drawn by guys in her own year, but rather those in higher years. It was, in her eyes, a sign of her maturity as boys her own age were obviously far too immature.&nbsp;

This belief was only made stronger when the bomb at home burst and she found out her father had cheated and her parents were getting divorced. Where she was acting out before, things got much worse from there. She kept it very well hidden, but started to do illegal things around the school grounds, being ever so careful to not get caught.&nbsp;

It got harder when her mother started working at school. something Shreya resented very strongly. Not to mention finding out she had a set of twins as half siblings as well. At that point Shreya decided for herself never ever to date a guy too close to her own age. Perhaps it was due to missing her father, no matter the mistakes he'd made. Or perhaps it was more than she hoped older guys would be more responsible. The situation did cause her to mature faster than she otherwise would have.&nbsp;

As if all the family drama wasn't enough yet, Hogwarts itself was full of misery in those years. People were murdered right at school, something that shook Shreya to the very core. She was attached to people and the idea they could suddenly disappear on her was horrible. It made the idea that she'd possibly never see her mom or dad again after the divorce unbearable and she found herself more capable of forgiving, or at least in the sense that she didn't harbour much of a grudge. Add to that the excitement and stress of the triwizard tournament and the entire drama seemed complete as a recipe for death and disaster.&nbsp;

Shreya started seeking out danger, although it wasn't always a good thrill. The calm felt creepy to her, as if she was waiting for the next bad thing to happen. It was almost like a sense of escapism, trying to avoid being hit by unexpected bad news by involving herself in the creation of it. At some point she found that helping others that had gotten themselves into more trouble than they could handle was a place she enjoyed being most, rather than the being in danger part. It helped to reduce her stress levels when things were happening and being in the thick of things allowed her to feel useful, even if her strongest point was healing and not fighting. 


That was when she decided to become a mediwitch and focussed mostly on first aid and first responder focussed magic. Long term ailments didn't have the buzz of adrenaline that the discipline she chose had and it frequently left her feeling far more bored and helpless than she cared to admit. First aid it would be, and helping those stupid enough to have gotten into serious trouble.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]The explosion during the quidditch match have shaken her hard, partially because most of her family was present. She herself was on call and was one of the first responders on the scene despite being a trainee. The faces of the dead still haunt her, even though she knows there is little to nothing she could have done for them. It only makes her more fierce in her aspiration to become better as a healer so that she might not end up being unable to save people again.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Seph[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]She/Her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]27[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]GMT+1[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]See Heleen App.[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]Argentum, Heleen, Lúthien and Auguste[/blockquote][/div][/div]