[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:75%;" alt="(image here of playby)" src="https://64.media.tumblr.com/7fbe2818f4676b4583dd404d84c0238e/tumblr_nfk5pbUyie1r8uadco9_r2_540.gifv"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Levi Vera Mazer[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]Lee-Vi Ver-a May-Zer
[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Anything besides&nbsp; his original last name of Rowle.

[/blockquote][b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]Twenty-five
May 4th
[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Male - He/Him
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Half-blood, Werewolf
[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Straight[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]10.5", Black Walnut, Hippogriff Feather[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Levi Stocke
[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Levi looks much like his playby. Tall, about six foot 4 inches with a fit
 muscular appearance with several tattoos all over his body. He also has
 a large bite like scar on his upper right arm. He also has what looks 
like a set of large claw mark scars on his back. Which have been mostly 
covered with tattoos at this point. Each tattoo either has a meaning or 
was done during a high or drunk episode and he no longer remembers what 
it meant. If it had any meaning, to begin with. Levi typically has short
 to medium length hair and the same goes for his facial hair as well. 
With brown hair and blue eyes.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts till the age of 15, Gryffindor. Home schooled afterward. 
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduated home school
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Guitarist
Lyricist[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Freedom
Play guitar
Adventure
Traveling
Having fun
Drinking
All types of music
Promoting werewolf equality
Tattoos
partying
Flirting
[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Blood purists
His family
Drugs (but still wants to do them.)
Dark small locked rooms
The taste of wolfsbane
Chains
Prejudice toward Demi-humans, especially toward werewolves.[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]To become a famous musician and not allow his addictions to ruin another chance at success.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Lavender
Citrus smells
Chocolate
Alcohol[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Small dark rooms he can’t escape from.
Losing everything to drugs once again.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Levi’s life up to this point hasn’t left him without some emotional scars. On the whole, he’s a rather carefree person and just looking to party and play music. He also lacks some social graces though. Not having much room for proper communication while dealing with his parent's treatment for three years contributed. As well as the people he surrounded himself within his later teen years once free didn’t help either. Levi is impulsive and does just about whatever he feels like. Part of what got him all into his drug addiction mess, to begin with. He also just says what he feels like, there’s a slim chance he’ll try to avoid it if it’s rude or hurt someone's feelings but that’s very slim indeed.

Due to his childhood, he’s also prone to getting rather angry when met with some of the things that’ll trigger these feelings. Typically prejudice and looking down toward werewolves. To a lesser extent all Demi-humans. He also can’t stand blood purists and has been known for punch a few when given the chance when they start their rants on blood superiority. Levi also can’t stand chains of any kind, besides necklaces. That’s more out of avoidance than causing him to get angry. He does also get increasingly angry when his original last name is brought up but he doesn’t reveal to many that he was born a Rowle in the first place.

Levi does tend to drink more than he should but his alcohol limit is rather high by this point. Still, he’ll always avoid anything stronger than alcohol. Knowing his always one hit away from relapse to his addictions. Being in a band with members that do take drugs doesn’t help but he doesn’t push his lifestyle on them. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Caerphilly, Wales[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Henry Rowle -61- Father
Ramona Rowle -60- Mother
Tristan Rowle -24- Brother
Gale Rowle -22- Sister
Thorfinn Rowle -63- Uncle, former deatheater, currently locked up in prison.
[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]A Greater Sooty Owl named Tyto.[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Levi was born into the near pureblooded family of Rowle, a family that always felt they were just short of making it on the scared list of twenty-eight truly pureblooded families in Europe. His uncle Thorfinn had been a death-eater before the fall of Voldemort and his following imprisonment. All to further his family's blood status. The rest of the Rowle family continued their belief in pureblooded superior after the fall of the death-eaters. Even if they weren’t considered pureblooded themselves by the other families. They were as close as they could get and could only work toward it in future generations. Eventually, they felt the slight mixing of their bloodline with impure members would fade from history.

This belief was passed on to their children. Levi being the oldest, followed a year later by a brother and two years later by a sister. The children grew up close to one another. Part because of the familial relationship and in part because they weren’t allowed to have any friends that weren’t approved by their parents. Playdates were set with only the purest and important of children and families. It was a life of a strict structure and constant supervision. Levi didn’t know anything else and just accepted that this must have been everyone’s life even if it didn’t feel right to him. Lifelike this always felt off even at a young age, there had to be more to it than this.

At the age of eleven, Levi received his much-anticipated letter to Hogwarts. While Levi was excited his parents just drilled into him the importance of going to Hogwarts and being among the best there were at the school. He wasn’t to do anything that wouldn’t further his future career or status in life. Especially anything that would hurt or wouldn’t further the Rowle name. Levi obliged to their demands, even if he was still secretly more excited to just be going to school. Once there he was sorted into Gryffindors without too much hesitation from the sorting hat. He was met with cheers from people he had never met before. People his parents hadn’t picked out for him to interact with. He loved the applause immediately, the attention and feeling it gave him. He thought instantly that this was something to be proud of. Sadly, his first letter from his parents after being sorted was their displeasure at Levi not picking Slytherin and if they know this would have happened they would have drilled him on Slytherin house before he had left. Like he had a choice in the matter. For the first time, he truly questioned his parents, it wasn’t anything big. Just the idea that they didn’t even know how the sorting hat worked.

Slowly this new freedom given to him at Hogwarts blossomed into a full rebellion to his parent's and family's beliefs. He had new people, even friends, from all different backgrounds. Blood didn’t matter as much here it seems as his parents made it appear. What mattered was the type of person you were more than how pure your blood was. All things his parents attempted to beat out of him each Summer. Thankfully for them, his brother and sister were sorted into Slytherin. They were the perfect children his parents always wanted. Levi soon became and afterthought to his family. Something he didn’t exactly mind.

At the age of fifteen, Levi snuck out of his home to visit a friend who lived not too far away. He had done this several times but this time was going to be much different. Under the cover of night with only and the light from a joke wand and the full moon, he made his way to his friend's home. His parents didn’t exactly check up on him anymore anyway. Just thinking about how they wouldn’t miss him for a while was fine with Levi. Till he was snapped out of his thoughts by a nearby howl. From then on things were blurry for him. Levi remembered running, he remembered hitting the ground hard from something pushing or jumping on him and the taste of blood. Followed by intense pain in his right arm and the shouting of another man's voice. After that, it all went blank.

Levi awoke days later at St.Mungo’s, alone. While being alone had been fine with him at his parent's house it frightened him at this moment. He was bandaged up on his arm and back but had no idea what had happened. His memories were too much a blur to make out just what had occurred that night. The door opened what felt like hours after he had awoken and it was a nurse, surprised to see him awake so soon. She called for someone else and with that, a man entered minutes later. He explained that Levi had been attacked by a werewolf. Sadly he indeed had been bitten and would now be one himself. It was hard to come to terms with that but that man said he was also lucky to still be alive. Thankfully the werewolf capture department was already in the area. There wasn’t much time for questions, it was all information on what his life would be like now. Then just like that the man was gone, informing Levi that his parents had only requested to be informed when he was ready to be released and they would come to get him then.

Levi dreaded that part the most, he couldn’t exactly imagine just what was going to happen when he got home but he knew it wouldn’t be good. He was now a Demi-human, something his parents despised almost more than muggles. The day finally came and he was sent home, his parents picked him up without so much of a word to Levi. The trip home quiet and awkward but that would soon change once they got there. Levi was shoved right into his room, which had now been fashioned with locks and bolts, his window barred in such a way that light barely got in. Levi protested but they coldly explained that this was how monsters were supposed to live. That cold tone was worse than any shouting he had ever received. This was his life now, he wasn’t even allowed to return to school. They couldn’t allow a monster to ruin the good family name they had worked so hard on. His siblings eventually stopped talking to him as well, even regarding him as a monster. They hardly used his real name.

Begrudgingly they still had to take care of Levi, the school and ministry knew of him, he could t exactly just go missing. They decided to homeschool Levi and gave him the bare minimum needed to survive. They even refused to give him wolfsbane. Instead, he was chained up and locked in his sealed room. Which only added to the scars on his body. This was his life for three years, pain, suffering, and the same small dark room. On his eighteenth birthday, he was taken to London with a small trunk of his items. Just some clothes and his old beat-up wand. They would have taken that from him too but they didn’t even want to try and resell a monster's wand. Left on a corner they disappeared, they even brought his siblings along so they could coldly leave him behind too without a word. He changed his last name to a random one he had read in a textbook and never looked back.

Without anywhere to turn Levi quickly fell in with a bad crowd. He stole to get by, either to make money or just stole food. Eventually, he got wrapped up in drugs and alcohol and grew more violent as time went by. Thankfully he could finally get wolfsbane from the ministry. That part of his life was at least under control if everything else was spinning out of it. The only good thing that came out of his time on the streets what learning to play the guitar. He was quick to learn and only some of that was the motivation to use this skill to make money on the sidewalk. At least that’s how his desire to play the guitar started. Yet the more he played the more he found pleasure in it.

Around twenty his life both continued to spiral out of control when it came to drugs and took shape as he desired to be in a band and an actual musician. Instead of using his talents just playing for money on sidewalks. He slowly traveled around Europe using the money from his playing and the occasional stealing to get by. Eventually, Levi had a chance to join a band but just as they started to make a name for themselves his constant drug use would destroy it. He’d be kicked out and the cycle would repeat all over again. He eventually made the choice that he needed to stop doing drugs altogether if he was ever going to be a famous musician. It took a few years and some false starts but he finally felt like he could call himself clean from drugs. Yet, probably never free of the addictions they gave him.

At twenty-five, Levi is currently in another band and they are just starting to make a name for themselves. [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]
The greater events in the news didn’t have much of an effect on Levi as it did with many other people. His life as a busker was rarely interrupted by the magical world and the attacks from the purifiers. He knew of the incidents but didn’t pay them too much attention. It was hard to pay attention between the living on the streets and the drugs. After getting clean and moving on toward trying to find a new band. He slowly paid more attention to the larger world around him.

If asked the first moment he could point to that he was taking an interest in the world around him it would be the return of retired Professor McGonagal as the new headmistress of Hogwarts. Which had him question just what had happened to the last headmaster. Over time he started wishing he hadn’t begun paying attention to the magical news and events. The schools that were visiting for the Tri-Wizard tournament were both attacked. Resulting and many deaths. Followed by an attack on the American school, thankfully no one was hurt there. Life was just as chaotic off the drugs as it seemed to be on them. The year ended with a dragon attack and Azkaban blowing up for whatever reason.

The next year hadn’t been much better at least when it came to news and events in Europe. His personal life and the band was working out pretty well. Sadly the lockdown due to the break out of hag fever caused them to slow down. Some even worked on solo projects in the meantime. The head of the purifiers was supposedly killed which Levi cheered for and got drunk with a few others. One less blood purist in the world was something he would always cheer for. Sadly that good news didn’t last long as the Quidditch championship had a firework mishap that killed several people including the minister of magic. All in all this year was just a mixed bag of news and events that Levi mostly tried to ignore. He had far more important matters like his life and the band to work on. Even if he wouldn’t have minded taking out a few blood purists himself.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@tj   
[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Cool Guy
[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]...old
[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]Est (best time zone)
[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]My soul was drawn here long ago.
[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@crimson1    @lockhart    @shawn    @jacob    @jim    @viktor    @lars    @phil    @friday    @colton   
[/blockquote][/div][/div]