[div align="center"][div align="center"][div style="width:500px;background-color:#B6B6B4;border:4px solid #B6B6B4;border-radius:10px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"]
[/div][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://78.media.tumblr.com/ede7ee143b44cbacfdb6b544cf84a38c/tumblr_inline_nk2v8jYrc51skr0w7.gif" alt="" width="336" height="172"]
[/div]




Hello there, my name is [b]Daniel McKay[/b] but you can call me [b]Danny[/b]. I'm [b]Sixteen[/b] so that makes me a [b]Seventh[/b] year at Hogwarts, where I reside in [b]Gryffindor[/b] house. You could say I'm [b]brave, daring, &amp; chivalrous[/b] but I personally think that I am [b]loyal, friendly and determined[/b]. People say I look a lot like [b]Thomas Mcdonell[/b], but I don't really see it...

[div align="center"][font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][i][b]Daniel Rayne McKay[/b][/i][/font][/font][/div]

[b][i]nickname:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Danny[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Sixteen[/blockquote]
[b][i]date of birth:[/i][/b]
[blockquote] February 2nd, 2007 [/blockquote]
[b][i]gender:[/i][/b]
[blockquote] Wizard[/blockquote]
[b][i]blood status:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Half-Blood[/blockquote]
[b][i]sexuality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Straight[/blockquote]
[b][i]house:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Gryffindor[/blockquote]
[b][i]wand:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]9 1/2 Cedar with Chimera scale fragment core.[/blockquote]
[b][i]playby:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Thomas Mcdonell
[/blockquote]
[b][i]appearance:[/i] [/b]
[blockquote]Danny Stands 5'11" And while he isn't very athletic himself his body type is slightly thanks to the fact he is always moving around or doing something when he's bored. He's never cared much for putting effort into how he looks, as long as he doesn't look like a total mess he's just fine with it. He can normally be found in muggle attire rather than uniforms or wizard robes.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personality[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]likes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Muggle comic.
Muggle arcades.
All forms of magic, even if he’s terrible at certain kinds.
Dragons.
Being with friends.
Chocolate[/blockquote]
[b][i]dislikes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]
Being forced to do anything.
Uniforms.
Being bored.
Nails on a chalk board.
Loud people or just yelling for that matter.
Being alone for long periods of time.
[/blockquote]
[b][i]erised:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Lately Danny just dreams of returning back to American to be with his old friends and getting his old life back. In the mean time he hopes to become a full fledged animagus while figuring out what he wants to do with his life. [/blockquote]
[b][i]amortentia:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]The smell of all chocolate besides dark and the smell that happens just before a large thunderstorm.[/blockquote]
[b][i]boggart:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Nothingness, a fear of just a void with nothing or no one around. Just loneliness. [/blockquote]
[b][i]overall personality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]&nbsp;Danny has always tried to be in a good mood, or at the very least tried to make it seem like he is in one. A habit he learned just to make people stop worrying about him in his life. While anything about himself he can normally just brush off as not worth his time or he didn’t care to worry about. Anything that happens to a friend, or anyone else for that matter, is different and he will try to help them the best he can no matter what or just stand by their side. Danny has always tried to cheer up other people around him at least make them laugh a little. Danny is a slacker to a tee, preferring to wait to the last minute on most things and instead have a good time.

With his forced transfer to Hogwarts he still tries to seem like he's in a good mood to avoid people wondering whats wrong with him but he finds it harder to be happy about where he's at right now. He's still a good person at heart and will help anyone who needs it but he's been finding himself getting more and more irradiated with everything. While he lacks friends he's begun killing time with becoming more and more mischievous in his pranks and rule breaking. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personal history[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]mother:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Nancy McKay, deceased at the age of 28 during childbirth [/blockquote]
[b][i]father:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Argyle McKay, Ministry official, 48 [/blockquote]
[b][i]siblings:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]None[/blockquote]
[b][i]pets:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Rodney a great gray owl that used to be the families but now just belongs to Danny.[/blockquote]
[b][i]history:[/i][/b]
[blockquote] Danny's life had been rough from the beginning. Danny lost his mother shortly after his birth due to complications, while the healers did the best they could she just couldn't be saved and his father was never the same. Argyle had always been focused on his work but now with the passing of his wife and the reason she was gone now living at his home he used every chance to avoid Danny. Danny was left to be raised but nannies or even house elves when no nanny was around. This was just the life he grew up used to and he didn't know any better as he got older. He just assumed all families were like this rarely seeing their parent.

Once he was eleven Danny got his letter for Ilvermorny the American magic school and Danny was over joyed while at least his father was happy. Still his father wasn't happy for his sons joy he was just relieved he didn't have to raise a non-magical child. He knew a non-magical child would have been more of a chore than just letting him get shipped off to school for most of the year. Danny didn't realize that and just happily went to school and had the best time of his life so far. Still it didn't take him long to realize from his new friends and what he heard about their families how different his was. They had fathers and even mothers that cared, it took him till his fourth year to figure out why and just why his birth wasn't something to be celebrated.

If life had been perfect he would have just finished school with his friends and moved on with his life. Danny was just fine avoiding his father, not being a family but two strangers who lived under the same roof. That all changed during the beginning of the summer of his Fifth year. Danny came home to the house filled with packed boxes and he was more confused than ever. Danny learned his father had gotten a job with the British Ministry of magic due to whatever events were happening over there. His father probably explained that to him but he wasn't listening. in just a few minutes his father had attempted to rip every bit of joy out of his life and Danny wasn't having it. They yelled, Danny threw multiple things at his father. even going as far as to cast spells at him, nothing serious but he was still a minor using magic out of school.

The fighting was finally over with a few more words. First from Danny yelling that his father didn't even want him and to live with here. Followed by his father agreeing with him but saying that he couldn't because he promised his mother to watch over him. With that Danny now found himself moved to London unable to stay in American if his father forced him to move thanks to being a minor. Before the move Danny did receive warnings for the use of magic while being a minor from the American magical government, they were just that, warnings. His father on the other hand saw fit to lock up his wand till he went back to school, he also made sure to remind him that it would be like this next summer and till he was an adult and could move out. This way he wouldn't be able to shame him by getting another warning, this time from the Ministry of magic.

Danny used every chance he got to express how much he wanted to go home, even while he was being transferred to Hogwarts and sorted into Gryffindor. Something he learned other students would have been proud of all he just felt like was going home, truly home. He has now been keeping to himself since he knows no one here and has felt like an outsider in both this land and school and while he's calmed down on being so angry he still isn't happy about where he's at.

Danny had tried to ignore the things that had been happening in Europe the best he could, seeing it as not his problem. Still he found some similarity with things he dealt with back home and started to pay attention because of it. People everywhere just caring far to much about blood purity but even the extremes that Danny heard about worried him. Between the kidnappings, attacks at the school and even the murders. If his father had really promised to keep him safe Danny thought he was doing a terrible job of it. While Danny tell himself this isn't his problem he would be more than willing to help anyone in need and stop these attacks. Not just because he himself was a Half-Blood but because he personally can't stand the violence for something he feels is so unimportant in the world.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]alias[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]name:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]My names Timothy but everyone calls me TJ.[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]29[/blockquote]
[b][i]time zone:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Eastern time zone.[/blockquote]
[b][i]reference:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]From one of the sites that rank HP forums. Sorry I forget which.[/blockquote]
[b][i]other characters:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]No one, I'm new here. Hi![/blockquote][/div][/div]
[/div][/quote][/quote]