[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" alt="(image here of playby)" src="https://66.media.tumblr.com/b03f0d7509f0274c565d7a6db7952fb9/defc2196fe77f05b-96/s1280x1920/74c919a9cde5527847c1e18af7d2bd5f9ea770d8.jpg"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Nixie Athena McKraken[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]Nik-see Ah-thee-na Mc-crack-en[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Nyx for close friends and family[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]23
13 June[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]female, she/her[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]muggleborn[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Demi-sexual.[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]13.2”, Sycamore, Mermaid Scales[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]ebba zingmark[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Nixie is a natural redhead with the stereotypical fair complection who stands at 5’3,  making her the shortest member of her family. She does wear glasses from time to time, though she isn’t blind have to use them all the time.  She will normally wear her glasses when she isn’t out on an adventure, usually when she is doing some mandatory paperwork..[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts/Gryffindor
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduate
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Curse Breaker[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]sweets, adventure, traveling, flying, sleeping in when at home, quidditch, her family, being able to go where she wants when she wants[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]staying in one place, sunburns, the cold, reports, being betrayed.[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]find the treasure of a lifetime, to make a romantic connection with a kindred spirit.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]fresh air, ocean breeze, someone with brains[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Being caged
Not being able to work[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Nixie likes to expect the best in people she doesn’t know, while simultaneously preparing for them to let her down. Once she gets to know someone, she opens up a lot easier. Nixie is close to her family, and she wants nothing but the best for them, though, she refuses to be seen as their week little sister.  Nixie is stubborn, and she can't stand leaving something unresolved. She is almost addicted to the adrenaline of going through a cursed tomb to find treasure. To her, going on assignment is simply a chance to solve a complex, cursed, puzzle.  It also helps that Nixie is naturally quick on her feet. Having four extremely close and active older brothers kept Nixie on her toes. Thanks to that, she got into the habit of being quick on her feet. 

Nixie is not one to like working with others, though she can if she has to, but she prefers to work alone.  She doesn’t like to rely on others, especially when in stressful situations.  It is easier to work with others, if she is close friends, and fully understands the way they do things. For her family, and close personal friends, Nixie will do anything to protect and help them out.  She would never betray any of them.  But on the other hand, If she dislikes someone, she is more likely to lash out at them, and once the trust is lost, it’s hard to get it back. Nixie does have some fire in her, if she feels angry, whether it is from a personal offence, or from a  friend being hurt, she is quite likely to explode.  This is preferably at the cause of the anger, but if not necessarily.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Castlebar, Ireland[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Father: Eoin Mckraken 59, Bar owner
Mother: Zoe McKraken 56, author
Brother: Connor McKraken 31, photographer
Sister-in law: Nelly 27, Magazine editor
Nephew: Fallon 1
Brother: Ronan 28, Archeologist 
Brother: Rory 28, Pilot
Brother: Arlen 26, Farmer 
[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]None[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Nixie was an unexpected addition to the McKraken family.  After four boys, Eoin and Zoe had decided that their family was complete, that was until Nixie came along.  She was a perfect sweet little girl. Growing up with all older brothers, Nixie learned to be tough and to fight back. She grew up outside and in the dirt, she was often the messiest one to return home during the day. As she grew older, like all her brothers before her, she started primary school. Strange things started to happen, especially to a small boy who constantly picked on her.  He did eventually stop, because of her brothers scaring him off, which lead Nixie to believe that all the strange things happening to him had been the work of her protective brothers.  This was the thought all the way up until a day shortly after her eleventh birthday.  A man wearing a strangely uncoordinated outfit came to speak to her and her parents.  What he explained to them was so unbelievable, she was sure that her brothers were pulling some elaborate prank.  But the more the man spoke, the more she started to believe, or rather, hoped that it was true. A month later, the same man met her and her parents in London at some pub that her parents never knew existed. The man then took her to the most magical experience of her life.

Nixie started attending Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry and really took to her classes.  By her third year, she made her house’s quidditch team, as their new seeker. Soon after that, flying really became a release for her. She studied hard and got the grades to prove it.  She wanted to learn everything she possibly could, finally feeling like she could excel in something that her brothers couldn’t. The only thing she didn’t like about her new found talents, was that she couldn’t show her family once she went home. She would tell them everything, though, she was certain that her brothers didn’t believe her. She did well on her O.W.L.S and chose the career path of a Curse Breaker from the start. The idea of adventure and finding treasure alured her, but her excellent grades also helped. She was good, and she was going to go for it.

After her last year at Hogwarts, her parents thought she would be continuing her education at some magical university, but she started working for a wizarding bank in London, though she seemed to be spending most of her time in Egypt.  It was a long time until Nixie told family that she worked for Goblins. It wasn’t an issue for her, she knew that they are a great race, and should be shown respect. On the other hand, her brothers found it hard to absorb that their sister worked for short, monstrous creatures.  She didn’t feel like it would be possible to make them understand. Though the mocking didn’t last long, when she reminded her older siblings that she could use magic, and they couldn’t.  Working for Gringots for the past few years, Nixie has developed a professional relationship with the goblins, and those who she interacts with.  Though she enjoys her time traveling the world, collecting cursed objects. [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Over the last few years, there has been quite a lot of crap happening around London. This is one reason why Nixie has his happy to be working in Egypt.  Happy that her family doesn’t have much to do with the magical world, when she has heard about explosions, or anything else bad happening that her family could have been close to, they were her first contact.  Once she heard about dragons getting out during a festival, that was too much. It is common knowledge that Dragons are dangerous. If you didn’t want them out and terrorizing a local village, don't put them close to the local village.  She understands that there has to be more to the story, but it was bound to happen at some point. Then, having the breakout from Azkaban happen definitely put Nixie on edge, but being a Curse Breaker, she usually finds that she has more pressing matters to deal with, while at work..[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Sophi[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]um...[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]Mountain standard[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]Co Admin Sora[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]Cassandra Moreau, Dmitri Krovopuskov, Lucas King[/blockquote][/div][/div]
