[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://64.media.tumblr.com/dd7a862e7cc22183eddbe5685318d466/d944bab98ed40704-0d/s1280x1920/2de0370cd01dc70fccdd158c5dfb93a8a8693fb2.jpg" alt=""][/div]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]Donatella Celeste McLaggen[/font][/div][hr]

[b]pronunciation:[/b]

[blockquote]don-ah-tel-ah sel-est Mc-Lag-gen[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Ella, Celeste, stage name Virgo[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]21
August 26, 2004[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Female
She/Her[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote] half-blood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]bisexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]11’ 5/16 Hornbeam, Dragon Heartstring[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Ray Mattos[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Ella stands at 5’4, and as such comes in as the shortest in her family. As a young girl, she started on a rebellious streak, getting her first tattoos, and piercings (including her tongue) during the summer before her 6th year, and some before her 7th year. She has added more piercings in her ears, and various tattoos all over. Shortly after joining the circus, she got rid of her tongue piercing, and got it split instead. She also dyes her naturally brown hair blonde, she also often has a tanned appearance, due to the time she spends in the sun.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts/Ravenclaw
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduated 2022
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]May 2022 - November 2022: Keeper for the Holyhead Harpies
November 2022-present: Ariel performer for Wizarding circus[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Heights
Traveling
Dancing
Quidditch
Performing (she did join the circus)
Sleeping under the stars
Going sightseeing
Yoga
Morning runs
Amature photography
Pastries, cakes, and pies, all baked goods really
Aerial hoop and silks (this is her main act at the circus)
Trapeze (secondary act)
Tightrope (tertiary act)[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Outsiders poking around the circus backstage
falling/being dropped
Being called Donatella
Being “grounded” (not being able to perform/practice)
Her father bringing up that she ruined a perfectly good quidditch career
Messing up in front of an audience
[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Hearing her father say that he is proud of her (but she doesn’t hang around to be disappointed)
Visit and take photos around the world[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Tattoos, motorcycles, muscles, peanut butter, tiger lilies, rain[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Drowning
Getting so injured that she can't perform again[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Ella isn't an extremely sociable person. She is comfortable with those in the circus troupe, and old friends, but she's not good with talking to strangers. Theres a reason she is a performer, she can do what she rehearsed, as high up as they will let her, but talking to a stranger for a long time just doesn't happen. When unsure, or nervous, she tends to stammer or stutter. Ella prefers to take action. If something needs doing, she'd rather move forward and solve the problem. As a member of the circus, she has a number of responsibilities, first of all as a performer. Her main act is on the Ariel silks or hoop, but she also does work and has skills in other ariel acts. She is talented on a broom, and knows some self defence, and a few stage fighting basics. Because of her work, and years of conditioning, she is extremely flexible and fairly strong, she also has a good sense of ballance. She can get bosys if she is helping to train someone to perform, but it's mostly for their own safety. 

The most relaxing place for Ella is somewhere high up. She also enjoys to bake, finding that the activity helps calm her, especially when she is stressed. Visiting her family tends to get her nervous. While she has kept up a cordial correspondence with most of her family, the idea of confronting her father face to face is something that she would just prefer to avoid - she hasn't seen the man since she joined the circus. She enjoys animals and loves to learn new things about them. When all else fails, her favorite thing to do is to put in her headphones and just drown out all other sounds and run, dance, or practice.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Godric’s Hollow, England[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]cormac mclaggen – father, 46, Senior Quidditch Reporter, former professional keeper
mandy brocklehurst – mother, 45, phlebotomist at St. Mungo’s

michelangelo mcLaggen - older brother, 23, Ballycastle Bats Keeper
____ ____ MCLAGGEN G/6th[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Phoenix - Rebel[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Quidditch had always been the highest priority to Cormac McLaggen. He proved that with his oldest child, Mickey. More or less forcing the young boy to be better than his old man was. Only a few years after the oldest son was born, Ella came. But this pregnancy was rough for both the unborn child and mother. Both pulled through, but being premature, too small, and plenty fragile, little Ella was required to stay at St Mungos. While Cormac kept his focus on his child prodigy in the making, Ella was growing and getting stronger. She first came home when she was four years old, a healthy young girl. She was a little behind, and now that she was home, she got more attention from her father. She loved it, at first. Watching her big brother flying around, getting all the attention, Ella soon took to a broom and tried to join in on the training. Oftentimes she wasn't allowed, but as she proved herself, she was able to get more of her fathers attention as he worked towards training her.

As she grew up, Ella learned about muggle gymnastics and begged to be signed up. She kicked, screamed, and cried until she got her way. And soon enough, maybe just to quiet her and get her out of the house, she was allowed to go. She loved it, and progressed quickly. She started to develop her own sense of self. When she turned eleven, she went off to Hogwarts. Expecting to get sorted into Gryffindor house, like her father and brother before her, she closed her eyes as the large tattered hat was set on her head. After some time, the enchanted item spoke a loud "Ravenclaw." The small girl jumped into her lessons, and made a few close friends. 

Like her brother, Ella tried out for her house's Quidditch team. She did it mostly for her father's attention, but she also knew that she was good at it. Being small and fast on a broom, she made it as a Seeker during her third year,  playing games were fun, the best ones were ones she played against her brother's team. Not because she was competitive, but because she could play with him. During her fourth year, she started to mess around more with her broom and some gymnastics that she knew. Seeing this, the team captain subbed her in as Keeper when their starter was injured during a game. The reserve seeker jumped at the opportunity. She really took to keeping, learning that she didn't always have to sit on her broom to block the quaffle. But now she couldn't fly past her brother when they played against each other. 

As Ella grew, she started to develop more of a sense of self, she started to do more things that she wanted to do, but she knew that her parents wouldn't approve, getting her two ear piercings, her tongue pierced and her first tattoo before her sixth year at school. She was careful to hide her tattoos and tongue piercing as best she could, getting another tattoo the summer before her seventh year at school.

During her seventh year, the girl felt pressure to get noticed by a recruiter. Her brother had joined a team and was making a name for himself by then, and following in his steps was the only logical path for her. She enjoyed the game, after all. After graduation, she started her training with the all female team the Holyhead Harpies, and got along with many of the players. But in November of 2022, the team had their first away game. Ella was so excited, and expected to come to watch her play. He didn't. She was eighteen years old now, and had finally let go. She didn't need his attention, though she still wanted it. While they were away, the team was treated to a behind the scenes of the magical circus. Ella was entranced. She no longer wanted to be where she was. As the team moved on, heading to rest up for their big game, Ella asked if she could try out. If she didn't make it, no hard feelings. But after showing what she knew, she was accepted into the circus. Not wanting to leave the team without her, she played that game, and left the team the very same night.

Performing in the circus has been a dream come true for Ella. Those in the troupe have become close to her, many feeling like more of a family than her own. During their travels, a phoenix started to hang around them, she soon learned that it had bonded with her. She wasn't sure how, or why, but it has become one of her closest friends and companions.
 [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Ella doesn’t really care about what’s happening. When she hears about bad things, she really hopes that everyone is alright. But now, she is living the dream, she spent far too many years trying to make her father proud, and get his attention, now she’s all about making herself happy, whatever that looks like.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Sophi[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote] she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]old...[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]Mountain[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]I live here >.<[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]See for yourself [a href="https://alohomorax0.proboards.com/thread/9784/sophis-insanity-version-2"]here[/a].[/blockquote][/div][/div]
