[div align="center"][font color="red"]CONTENT WARNING: Language, Violence, Drugs, Addiction, Abuse[/font]
[div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://i.giphy.com/media/MehsLncNeXqc1rSPW2/giphy.gif"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]augusto bartholomew gaston mulciber[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]ow-goose-toe | bar-th(all)-oh-myew | gah-stawn | mull-sih-burr[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote][i]IN PUBLIC[/i]
Gus, Mr. Gus, Uncle Gus

[i]IN THE SHADOWS[/i]
Ezra the Merciless[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]49 years old
27th of september 1977[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]cis man, he|him[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]"Pureblood"

Seven generations ago Simon Walker disavowed his halfblood family, changed his name to Simon Mulciber, passed himself off as a pureblood, and began purifying his bloodline through advantageous marriages for his children. No living Mulciber can trace their family back further than seven generations. It is believed by the modern Mulcibers that a tragic fire (staged by Simon himself) at one of the family estates wiped out the family birth records/death certificates, etc. from before Simon Mulciber the First.[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]pansexual, prefers tall athletic partners[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]14 1/4 in, blackthorn, white river monster spine
His first wand went missing during the Battle of Hogwarts and he's had at least fifteen since then. Despite switching wands as often as he changes socks the blackthorn and white river monster spine wand is the only one in his collection that he's had for over twenty years. It is his most reliable one and the one he uses for magical research.[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote][i]PUBLIC FACE:[/i] Laz Alonso
[i]IN THE SHADOWS:[/i] Rome Flynn[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Gus is extremely tall at 6 foot 3 and he is average build, but on the slimmer side. He has a warm brown skin tone the color of pale hazelnut wood and dark brown eyes. His salt and pepper hair is kept low, shaved almost at a buzz cut level. He has a kind face and smiles often (Laz Alonso). 

Unlike his face claim, he has tattoos. They run from his fingers to the back of his shoulders. The focal point of the tattoos are two identical roses on the back of his hands. On top of the roses in large curving script are the words: "RESPECT &amp; AUTHORITY" on his right hand and "FREEDOM &amp; SOVEREIGN" on his left. The vines coming out of the roses wrap around his ring fingers on both hands and in the other direction they have larger vines that go up his arms and meet between his shoulder blades on his back at the base of his neck. When he has something professional or family-friendly to attend he wears gloves and long sleeves.

He tells people the tattoos are merely a memento of his youth and he doesn't think he has to have them removed to be a respectable pillar of the community.

[i]IN THE SHADOWS: [/i] The ink in the tattoos is made from a stone powder containing occlumency-like properties. He learned early that the only way he can maintain his double life is if no one knows what he's thinking. Rather than wear talismans or learn occlumency he has a crushed up talisman which amplifies his ability to block out thoughts embedded into his skin. Their magical properties make them shine and glitter.

The tattoos were applied using powerful dark magic and one of the consequences of them is a generational curse. He's not sure what the curse does, exactly, and has warned all of his children to be on the look out for it when he's gone.

When he feels he has a black market meeting important enough to warrant his presence he sends one of his three representatives who speak on his ("Ezra's") behalf and joins them disguised as a muscle man. This disguise involves a potion which allows him to appear similar, but not identical to the way he did in his twenties (Rome Flynn). It also masks his identifying tattoos.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling &amp; status[/b]
[blockquote][i]IN PUBLIC[/i]
[b]1983 - 1988[/b]: home schooled by expensive tutors between the ages of 6 and 11
[b]sep 1989 - jun 1996[/b]: hogwarts school of witchcraft and wizardry, slytherin house
[b]1995 - 1996[/b]: prefect, slytherin house. senior most member of the inquisitorial squad
[b]1995 - 1998[/b]: (part) owner: hephaestus' pawn, cursebreaking &amp; antiques, knockturn alley
[b]2000 - 2004[/b]: university of edinburgh, bachelor of electronics and electrical engineering
[b]2000 - present day[/b]: philanthropist. founder and owner: hephaestus art group. The hephaestus art group owns antique shops, auction houses, jewelry stores, art galleries, estate management firms, and more. In the muggle world the hephaestus group funds archeological digs, transports artifacts, lends pieces to museums, funds arts programs and scholarships for schools, among other things. In the magical world the hephaestus group is committed to promoting the welfare of those disparaged by magical society: muggleborns, part-creatures, werewolves, vampires, etc.
[b]2004 - 2005[/b]: university of dundee, master of science in biomedical engineering
[b]2012 - 2016[/b]: castelobruxo research greenhouses, distinguished wizard of herbology
[b]2016 - present day[/b]: healing potioneering research and development at connor academy guild of healers hospital, edinburgh scotland
[b]2022 - present day[/b]: substitute professor of potions at the connor academy for magic, scotland

[i]IN THE SHADOWS[/i]
[b]2000 - 2005[/b]: cursed object developer, artifact smuggler, dark artifact distributor
[b]2005 - present day[/b]: Commission Cursed Object Creation, Dark Artifacts Smuggler
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote][i]IN PUBLIC: [/i]businessman (known for his team of cursebreakers and his work with the arts), philanthropist, researcher, welfare advocate for those magical society often shuns (werewolves, muggleborns, etc.)
[i]IN THE SHADOWS: [/i]magical weapons inventor and smuggler, poison developer[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]+ Good Food
+ Cooking
+ Fine Wine
+ Fast Cars
+ Shopping
+ Drugs
+ Cigars
+ Sculptures
+ Rugby
+ Violence[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]+ Disrespect
+ Dirt and Germs
+ Wrinkles (physical or on clothing)
+ Wasting money
+ Cheap cologne
+ Mediocrity
+ Surprises
+ Social gatherings
+ Being unprepared
+ Being unproductive[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote][i]IN PUBLIC[/i]Augusto is polite, he's charming, he knows how to take a hint, and he's endearing. When his children were young it was common to see him being a hands on father and supporting them in all their pursuits. He does various charity work, loves to cook, and has a loud contagious laugh. To strangers he's a charismatic philanthropist who selflessly devotes himself to his work. To his family he's the rock they can lean on and their fearless protector who will jump in the way of any curse to protect them. He can be a bit of a hot head, but he apologizes when he loses his temper and has a knack for using his words to smooth things over if he offends someone.

[i]IN THE SHADOWS[/i] Augusto is a very bold and daring person. In his youth he was loud and attention-seeking, but as he's grown older his brash impulses have been redirected towards his pursuits and personal growth. Instead of fighting someone when he's angry he will come up with creative ways to exact his revenge. Which could be because of something major or even something as small as a perceived slight against him. Augusto is nothing if not paranoid, but and upbringing involving years of being interviewed and harassed by Death Eaters and Aurors alike has cause that paranoia. He's ruthless and will cut down anyone in the way of his goals or his money.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]From: Edinburgh, Scotland[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]
[b]Joette Carline Mulciber[/b], wife. Investment banker. Certified genius. Looks like an actual supermodel. Winery heiress.
[b]Simon Ashley Mulciber III[/b], son. Hogwarts alumn. Hufflepuff. Auror. [i]IN THE SHADOWS:[/i] Corrupt law enforcement who keeps tabs for his father. Assisted his youngest two siblings in re-locating his youngest sister and it is the only secret he has ever kept from Gus.
[b]Jacob Wyatt Mulciber[/b], son. Hogwarts alumn. Slytherin. Twin to Lucas. Unspeakable.
[b]Lucas Archer Mulciber[/b], son. Hogwarts alumn. Slytherin. Twin to Jacob. Hit wizard.
[b]Ysoria Rachelle Mulciber[/b], daughter. Twin to Yaineris. Castelobruxo alumn. Ysoria is not Joette's child, but she does not know this. She was raised as if she were a fraternal twin to Yaineris.
[b]Yaineris Camille Mulciber[/b], daughter. Twin to Ysoria. Castelobruxo alumn.
[b]Evadne Lucille Mulciber[/b], daughter. Connor Academy alumn. Escort. [i]IN THE SHADOWS:[/i] Evie is Gus' top assassin and uses her job to get close to high profile targets.
[b]Eilis Marin Mulciber[/b], daughter. Hogwarts alumn. Hufflepuff. Novelist.
[b]Ethan Alvaro Mulciber[/b], son. Connor Academy alumn. Mixed martial magic master. Magical Wand Forces, Brooms &amp; Flight Division. Senior Levitation Wizard. [i]IN THE SHADOWS:[/i] Assisted his younger sister in faking her death
[b]Eulalie Darlene Mulciber[/b], daughter. Hogwarts alumn. Gryffindor. (deceased) [i]IN THE SHADOWS:[/i] Successfully faked her own death to hide from Augusto. Living in the Americas.

[b]Ezra Mulciber[/b], father. [i]IN PUBLIC: [/i] One of Voldemort's most important death eaters in the second war. The effectiveness of the imperius campaign can be attributed almost entirely to Ezra. He was on the run after Voldemort's first fall and re-surfaced after Voldemort's return. He was captured at the Battle of Department of Mysteries, but got out in the mass breakout from Azkaban in July of 1997 just before Voldemort took over the ministry of magic. He was not re-captured at the battle of Hogwarts and has become a major player in the global magical black market. He does not get his hands dirty, remains in hiding to evade magical law enforcement, and he runs his empire through a series of associates and representatives. [i]IN THE SHADOWS: [/i]Ezra went missing three days after the Battle of Hogwarts. Augusto expanded the family business in the black market in his absence. Augusto did eventually track him down ten years after the Battle, killed him, and assumed his identity in the black market to help put more distance between what he does in the shadows and his public image.
[b]Abigail Mulciber[/b], grandmother. (deceased) Former potions mistress at the Connor Academy for Magic. Injured protecting the school's muggleborn students from snatchers. Member of the Scottish (Muggle) Parliament. Was married to a Death Eater against her will and constantly did her best to circumvent his plans. [i]IN THE SHADOWS: [/i]Her expertise was in poisons and she practiced on muggles, muggleborns, blood traitors, and anyone else she deemed beneath her. Assisted in orchestrating the attack at the Connor Academy in which she was injured.
[b]Morgan Mulciber[/b], grandfather. (deceased) One of the earliest Death Eaters and a companion to Tom Riddle from his school days.

[b]Whitney Mulciber[/b], mother. (deceased) Castelobruxo alumn. Socialite who rarely spoke to Augusto. She lived in her wing of the estate and as a child he could go three or four months at a time without ever bumping into his mother.
[b]Shivona Mulciber[/b], grandmother. (deceased) Hogwarts alumn. Gryffindor. Herbology researcher who moved to Cuba with her husband when Gus was two.
[b]Maceo Frederick[/b], grandfather. (deceased) Castelobruxo alumn. Magical botanist.
[b]Elian Frederick[/b], uncle. [i]IN PUBLIC: [/i] Elian lives in Cuba and Gus never sees him. [i]IN THE SHADOWS:[/i] Elian is Gus' smuggling contact for the South American region. They are regularly in touch.

[i]IN THE SHADOWS[/i], lovers and associates
[b]Mrs. E.M. Fallows[/b], former lover. 12 years older than Augusto and mother of his twin sons Jacob and Lucas. She's a sadistic dominatrix who only recently retired from her job as a hit witch.
[b]Mrs. Moibeal Blair[/b], lover. The woman Augusto would have married if his marriage had been his own choice rather than arranged by his family. Her husband is unaware of her affair with Augusto. They've been eyeing one another since they were teenagers and though they are very close their relationship has been that of an old married couple for a long time. He does not consider their relationship exciting anymore. She is the mother of his daughter Ysoria.
[b]Mr. Nico Darkwater[/b], lover. The love of Augusto's life. The two of them have been together since Augusto was in his early twenties. He has a healthy friendship with Augusto's wife.

If you deal with "Ezra" in the black market you will 9/10 be meeting with one of his lesser pawns. If you are deserving of enough respect for a face to face meeting you will be met with one of these three people who represent his interests and are the only ones authorized to speak on his behalf. He will be disguised as their muscle. They are the top tier of his criminal web and he sees them each as equals rather than underlings.
[b]Lewis MacCowan[/b], representative. Cursebreaker.
[b]Devereaux Molyneux[/b], representative. Patriarch of the Molyneux family, heir to and current head of the Molyneux wineries. [i]DEEPER IN THE SHADOWS:[/i] Devereaux is cunning, ambitious, and overall a good person. He regularly double-crosses Gus by assisting those he finds undesirable (muggles, werewolves, vampires, etc.) and helped his children fake his youngest daughter's death. He has enough support and influence through his own means to protect himself if he's found out.
[b]Carys Astor[/b], representative. Cursebreaker. Bat animagus.[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]3 Alaskan Huskies
2 Blue Russian cats
4 Owls (varying breeds for sending post)
His company owns an aviary with a sub-unit for magical birds[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]
Born in Cirencester, Cotswolds in England's West Countryside. His great-great-grandparents came into an absurd amount of money and all of their descendants have been born with platinum spoons in their mouths ever since. He was raised in one of their large estates by the staff. His mother never wanted him and only became pregnant because his father was desperate for an heir to continue the Mulciber name. His father went on the run when he was four and his mother lived in her own wing of the estate so he was basically an orphan.

During his childhood his father would come home every year or other year to torture him and explain that the family's enemies would do much worse if they got his hands on him. He meant to "toughen up" the boy, but all he did was sew the seeds of hate for him. Hogwarts was a welcome reprieve from his homelife, though by his fourth year his issues at home began manifesting as drinking and sex with older students.

The following year his father's mother began arranging meetings with potential brides (not trusting him to pick a respectable pureblood woman). The year after that Cedric Diggory was murdered and Ezra felt safe enough with the return of Voldemort to return home for good. The leash on Augusto was tightened and by his graduation he was everything they wanted him to be. The drinking increased and his wife, facing similar pressure from her own family, introduced him to all sorts of muggle and magical drugs. He quickly became fond of cocaine.

He was married the year Voldemort's return was made public and his first child was born two months before the Battle of Hogwarts. The Death Eaters and magical media praised the child as the leader of the generation that would be raised in the new era. Using alcohol and drugs to make his life bearable Gus was like a zombie. Working in a pawn shop owned by his father and their associates he took some joy in using his free time at the shop to invent curses and modify existing dark magic to be more potent.

After Voldemort's fall his parents fled to escape persecution for their war crimes and he never saw his mother again. He only saw his father when he tracked him down nearly ten years later and killed him himself. In that time he had gone to multiple universities and research programs (both muggle and magical). He had developed a public image as a philanthropist and champion for the rights of muggles, muggleborns, and other types often looked down upon by magical society.

He has perfected the art of living his double life. He won't flinch when hugging a group of werewolf rights activists and never seems out of place in his muggle neighborhood. He even makes muggle press often for his charity work, philanthropic efforts, and generous contributions to arts programs.

And he will also smuggle anything for the right price. As for his cursework, it's twisted, disturbing, sadistic, and powerful magic. He spent all of his twenties and thirties perfecting his dark magic and many of his curses [i]are[/i] unbreakable. He designs custom curses for high commissions. He is also willing to track down or steal artifacts if you know how to contact him. He's also a collector of dark and disturbing magical objects.

When the mysterious murders started Gus' son Ethan was a seventh year and his youngest daughter Eulalie was only 14. He used his connections to put feelers out in the underworld and ensured protection for his children specifically. In public he made lots of speeches about unifying the community since he had been a pillar in the wizarding community for over twenty years. He condemned the groups behind the murders in public and did his best to support them in private.

He and his family were at King's Cross Station the day of the attack even though he had been warned something (though no one knew quite what) was going to go down. It was beneficial to be caught in the crosshairs and helped him look more believable when he spoke out against the Purifiers in public. He also used his connections to be adversarial to the group Kraken who he believed were too rogue to be allowed to operate. He feels that magical people have been hunted and forced into hiding by muggles for centuries and should not be turning on one another.

As a result he finds both Kraken and Chimera's Claw to be despicable organizations who shed blood senselessly. Despite his sadism he draws a line when it comes to attacks that could harm purebloods. He also doesn't view muggleborns and halfbloods as negatively. While he would still disown any of his children for having the audacity to breed with a muggle he considers it a charity to help muggleborns and halfbloods purify their line. Without knowing it, he's become quite a bit like Simon Mulciber the First in that regard.

He would rather see a group like Chimera's Claw attack the magical government in the states than a magical school. He thinks violence for the sake of making a point is childish. Though he often partakes in violence for research (his cursework) and pleasure (again: his cursework).

When the Dragon attack happened on Hogsmeade he had his daughter home for the holidays. While he didn't know [i]what[/i] was going to happen he did once again through his connections, have some advanced notice that something was going down. So he planned a family Christmas trip that involved the family being out of the country entirely at the time. Since then he has been assisting escapees from Azkaban go into hiding.

He has also offered the ministry of magic the service of his team of cursebreakers to assist in repairing the damage done to Azkaban since they have a reputation of being very talented cursebreakers and he has a reputation of being a helpful and trustworthy community leader. What his cursebreakers are really doing is studying Azkaban Island to figure out what makes the dark magic there so powerful so that it can be harnessed, replicated, and weaponized.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]allie[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]any | she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]28[/blockquote]
[/div][/div]