[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt=" " style="max-width:100%;" src="https://wwd.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/img_5752.jpg"] [/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]eleanor gwendolen ollivander[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]elle-uh-nor.[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]nell, nellie.[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]26
september 17th, 1999.[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote] female. she/her/hers.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]half-blood.[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]straight.[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]11 inches, silver lime wood, unicorn hair, firm.[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]diana silvers[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]5’7”. everything else is the same as playby. she wears glasses (more like magnifying glasses) when detailing and inlaying wands with their cores. these are typically hanging from her neck. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]hogwarts – slytherin.
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]graduated in 2018.
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]owner of the queen's wands and wordworks[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]swimming, collecting seashells, quilting, watching the sun set, using her hands, spicy foods, fireworks, being outdoors, the summer.[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]being called eleanor, talkative customers, impoliteness, bright lights being shown in her eyes, gambling, pickles, frogs (even chocolate frogs).[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]to eventually own her own wand shop.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]freshly cut wood, shoe polish, sulfur from fireworks.[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]her older sister and having to work under her for the rest of her life.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Outgoing and exuberant about working, Nell can come across as a little too aggressive at times with customers. She is very business oriented, but also believes in moving quickly and efficiently. Meaning don’t dawdle when she’s helping you. Time is money, and more money means a successful business. She likes manning the shop on her own, mostly to earn experience in the industry and earn a name for herself (other than the family name), but finds that she is often overlooked and her sister or father are asked for instead. While this irks her to no end, she understands that it is their business and she is simply the apprentice.

Nell takes more joy in her craftsmanship than she does in her customer service though. She is very craft oriented and hands on, always fiddling with something outside of work. Placing a unique spin into each wand, whether it’s the grain of wood used or the design etched into the handle, her goal is allow all of her customers to have something of their own. Her philosophy, both in wandmaking and her other projects, is to create pieces of art that will make their owners enjoy them to their fullest. And that she also has fun making.

While in school, Nell was known as the straight-laced, analytical girl that probably fit better into Ravenclaw than she ever did in Slytherin. Her own personal ambitions surpassed those of a grander scale, meaning that once she had graduated and began her apprenticeship, she felt right at home. But that isn’t going to stop her from taking the next step, which is to eventually have her own shop that can compete against the family one, where her flair and new take on wandmaking would hopefully be just as popular (or at least that’s the hope).

Nell also has a weakness to helping those that desperately need it, an attribute she gained after watching her older brother, Frankie, get pushed to the side because he was a squib. She isn’t beyond doing slightly underhanded things in order to produce the results she wants to see but she never wants to harm people. As long as the issue at hand is fixable while preserving face, she will try her best to fix it.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]godric’s hollow, england[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]garth ollivander - father, 62, retired wandmaker, half-blood.

clara ollivander – mother, 58, homemaker, muggleborn.

veronica ollivander – sister, 34, wandmaker &amp; current owner of ollivander’s, half-blood.

galen francis “frankie” ollivander – brother, 29, squib.

___ ollivander – brother, 20, half-blood.

gideon ollivander – niece/nephew (older sister’s child), 14, current 4th year student, half-blood.

garrick ollivander – great-grandfather, 116, retired wandmaker, half-blood.
 [/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]n/a.[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]The third of the four children born to Clara and Garth Ollivander, there was probably the hope that she would be the true male heir they were looking for. This wasn’t something she would find out until much later, even long after her younger brother was born. Her childhood was happily spent learning about the magical properties of wands, their cores, and the processes used when creating them. Outside of the family business, Nell quickly became the crafty one, in both arts and crafts and causing mischief around the house and in the store. When she first discovered how wands ‘chose’ their witch or wizard, she took it upon herself to try and see how many of the wands would pick her. There wasn’t any reason behind it aside from satiating her curiosity, but the pile of boxes that fell on top of her when she tried to go for the higher shelves taught her a very fine lesson: to not stick her nose into business that wasn’t hers. Actually that was her parents and older sister who said that (of which the latter was manning the front counter when it occurred), and she was only to enter the shop while closely supervised. Boredom soon caught hold of the young Ollivander and she turned to quilting and other hands on activities to pass the time.

Growing up, she didn’t really understand that Frankie was incapable of using magic, only ever catching sneers from their older sister or off comments from their mother about how disappointing it was that he wasn’t like the rest of the family. Nell liked to think that made her brother special in his own right, something she has continued to try and express to him as they’ve gotten older. Trying to hand him a wand (in the hopes that he would suddenly acquire magic) was off limits, and she was often reprimanded for sneaking the wands on the lower shelves out of the shop and into her brother’s bedroom where she would try to convince him that one of them would work for him eventually. 

Having inside knowledge on the family’s store meant she was quite the obnoxious first year when the time came, sometimes pointing out to other students that she knew exactly what properties their wands would exhibit over the years and how that would define them as a witch or wizard. Many times Nell was told to shut-up because she wouldn’t stop talking about wands, especially in class. Her obsession would follow her home each summer, where she would sit in and watch her father and sister create the magical pieces of wood from nothing. 

School itself wasn’t difficult for her, with her friends often wondering why she was a Slytherin and not a Ravenclaw. Studying for classes was second nature to her after spending her formidable years learning about wandmaking. And thus the seven years flew by with little to no problems for Nell. To say she had an average schooling at Hogwarts was an understatement. Nothing weird happened and soon she was out into the working world and beginning her apprenticeship under her father and sister. Looking back on it now, Nell is a little disappointed in herself for not being more outgoing and being too straight-laced with her school work. Living a little wouldn’t have killed her.

Starting as an apprentice wandmaker was a much more daunting task than she had realized. It was all fun and games when she watched as a child or whittled away the summers in the workshop doing whatever she pleased. Now it was for an actual career and was way more serious than she had anticipated it to be. A game it was not, and the delicate process of creating a wand on top of learning the ropes of running the shop really pushed her to her limits several times and Nell decided that she couldn’t work under her sister forever. While they had always gotten along, being in the family business when it was always ruled by an older sibling was not the life she wanted to have. She resigned herself to the fact that work and family needed to be as separate as possible, and once she had the chance she would be striking out on her own as a wandmaker. 

There was also the realization that the Ollivander name wasn’t as infamous as it once was. Somewhere in the last few decades, with the quick exchange of ownership from her great-grandfather all the way down to her sister, competitors started to sprout up all around them. The family was resolute in continuing the tradition of only utilizing three wand cores, something Nell found to be absolutely stupid if they wanted to keep up with their competition. Name alone meant nothing when there were other wandmakers getting ahead in the game. Her sister didn’t understand, obviously, only furthering the rift between the two of them. For Nell, the days of unicorn hair, phoenix feathers, and dragon heartstrings were long gone.

Now seven years into her apprenticeship, Nell hasn’t made much headway in the “business”, as her sister puts it. She’s allowed to create the Ollivander branded wands, per her destiny, as well as collect their sacred materials from vendors. And that’s pretty much it. Her daily duties consist of tending the shop and lazily leaning on the glass counter, wondering if the rest of her life will be this way. She feels unappreciated in her craft and is constantly shot down when asked about advancing onto a full-time wandmaker position at the shop, her sister refusing to give her an answer for why that is. Outside of work though, she has begun to make a little noise selling her own style of wands to those interested in something experimental and different than a normal wandmaker would have the time to do. Special cores, woods, and designs – whatever she can get her hands on that seems out of the ordinary and would definitely give her sister a conniption. So far her sister doesn’t know, and Nell would prefer to keep it that way as long as possible.
 [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Disturbed. That’s the only word that comes to Nell’s mind whenever she reads the newspaper, flashing headlines indicating another person has died or gone missing. She is repulsed that there are witches and wizards in the world potentially using her family’s creations to harm others. Obviously she understands that there is no way to prevent that, her own great-grandfather always teaching the lesson of giving Voldemort and countless other dark wizards their wands, and how they abused the tools they were given. 

The silver lining in it is that she only has to worry about one family member still being in school, her sister’s child. Her hope that no other families will have to go on without their children, or children without parents, should the Ministry or other magical locations be attacked as well. Nell knows that her job as a wandmaker and seller is to provide people with the protection they need, though she even she feels hopeless when events like the tournament or the disappearance of Harry Potter happen. Ignoring it and continuing to do her job doesn’t seem enough, but she also knows she isn’t in the position or has the abilities to take anything into her own hands. Maybe sitting passively to the side is a better place to be in the end anyways.
 [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Colin[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]24[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]EST[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]I live here [/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]Grey, Cordelia, Lance, Mina, Lily, Cara, Finn, Jimbo, Steve, Blaise, Harper, Renard, Madeleine[/blockquote][/div][/div]
