[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" alt="(image here of playby)" src="https://i.pinimg.com/originals/26/d1/88/26d1881280736e53df83fc8841b9717d.gif"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Luka Johnathan Prewett
[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]Luu-kah[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Johnny, Luck, Prumie
[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]Februari 9th, 1993
[font size="2"][i][b]33[/b][/i][/font]
[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Male, he/him
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Pureblood
(animal affinity, wolf)
[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Bisexual, slight preference for Men
[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]Vine and Dragon Heartstring, Rigid
[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Tom Hiddleston
[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Luka usually looks rather well maintained, although a small beard or stubble are anything but uncommon on his face. He most often dresses in robes that show off his professional side and looks a lot more put together than his behaviour might sigguest. He prefers darker colours most of the time and can be seen sporting expensive rings and watches when the occasion allows.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling &amp; status[/b]
[blockquote]Homeschool graduate
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Head Healer, St Mungo's magical bugs and diseases. (first year)

Before that:
Healer magical bugs and diseases (11 years)
Trainnee magical bugs and diseases, shortened version (6 months)
Mediwizard (6 months)
Mediwizard trainnee (2yrs)
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]His brother
His mother
Muggle school and technology
Being right
Himself
Reading
Learning
Winning/being better than others
Snakes
Frogs
Crocodiles
Cold toned colours
Sneaking into muggle medicine lectures
Fountain pens
The scent of disinfectant
Curing people
People that so happen to be werewolves
Alcohol
A good party
Antibiotics
Praise and adoration
Being a figure of authority
Money
Motorcycles
Freshly washed suits
Coffee
[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]His brother
His father
Himself
People in general
Being humbled or humiliated
Coming in second best
Bunnies
Terminal diseases
People that treat being different as a sickness
Treating werewolf bites
The concept of family
Pesticides
Sheep
Having to listen to other people
(Authority) figures that are not him and dare to challenge his expertise
Stains, anywhere.
Hammers and doing housework
The colour red
[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Luka is a bit of a problematic person. He's arrogant, rude and displays multiple traits that lead plenty of people to believe he is a somewhat deluded narcicist. They're probably at least a little bit right, as Luka tends to think highly of himself and not without reason. He's determined and would very easily do a lot of immoral things to get his way. He's highly intelligent and very invested in his job and career. He's not an easy person to be around and cannot under any circumstances be seen as particularly loyal.

Luka has a very conflicted view of himself and the world. He feels that people don't appreciate him as much as they should and is not sure if he is supposed to hate himself for what he (the child of the evil deatheaters) is or appreciate his differences (him not being a blood purist). He opts for the positive most of the time but struggles due to his father not being a purist but still failing to see just how much better Luka is than Trey.

Due to his at best strained family situation Luka has a very strong tendency to act out towards people that remind him of his parents or siblings too much. He's practically morally bankrupt in the eyes of others but his extreme degree in skill earned him his position in life. He's extremely good at what he does, no matter how challenging it can be to be around him.

Make no mistake, despite his flaws Luka is NOT a psychopath or sociopath. He has empathy and most certainly can empathise with people, especially if they resemble him or remind him of himself in any way. He just believes he's better than almost everybody walking the earth and spends little of his precioius time and patience on coddling the idiots of the world and displaying his empathy for them. He is simply too important for such time consuming feats in his own opinion. He can be what others see as uncharacteristically kind, but that usually holds a factor of stroking his own ego or having sympathy for the person that so strongly reminded him of himself.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Godrics Hallow
[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]O____ Prewett, adopted father, high end ministry official
F____ Prewett, adopted mother, Shop owner, specialises in illusions and enchanted items.
Heidi Prewett, older sister, criminal.
Trey Prewett, older brother, model, hit wizard, golden child.

L___ Travers, biological father, death eater, deceased.
L___ Travers, biological mother, unknown.

____&nbsp; _____, ward, age 9, squib.
[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Frog named Thor
[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Luka was born to a death eater couple, but the problem was that they got defeated and little Luka ended up without parents to care for him. They were sentenced to life in Azkaban and that is all that Luka really knows about his biological parents. He was adopted into the Prewett family at a time of turmoil. Baby Trey was about five years old at this time and had grown to be the apple of his fathers eye. Naturally Heidi didn't like this as she'd always been the pride and glory of their parents before. She took it badly enough that shortly after graduation, she disappeared to a life of crime. The age differences were rather significant since the couple started kids young and didn't start a second child until their first had entered hogwarts. The empty home had echoes of her laughter, or whatnot. 

Yet pity and a desire to riase the young boy better than his parents had been led his adoptive father to bring little Luka home to be raised alongside Trey. The boys had a small age difference but were in constant competition with one another for the attention and approval of their father. A competition that Trey often won, leading to a growing sense of resentment from Luka. He acted out and clung to their mother nearly helplessly for the love and attention that he so desperately needed. She assured him that he was worthy and taught him to use the many gadgets and toys she created. He used them to further taunt her brother and hopefully win the approval of his father.

It never came and out in the world, Luka found himself befriending another youngster from a wizard family that also seemed to fail to live up to the set expectations. They were around the same age and both carried resentment towards their respective families. It was a good friendship.

As the two grew older, Trey disappeared to Hogwarts and Luka found it had to be his moment. His father worked more than ever now that his golden boy was no longer at home. Age 11 appraoched and Luka knew that going off to school he'd end up compared to his brother as much as before, as his sibling was doing well in school and had many friends. He'd never live up to the expectations that Trey had set for the family so Luka forged an elaborate plan to stay home. He used his mothers devices, picking them apart and tinkering with them to create his own little machine. He used it to create an harmless illness, or rather the symptoms. It was mostly benign symptoms. A fever here, a rash there and while it's more than possible that his mother saw through the illusion that he created around his mysterious illness she humoured him and kept him homeschooled, understanding his need to not always be compared to his brother, as her husband constantly compared the two brothers and set them up for competition.

Seeing how his parents treated all the healers with great respect and admiration brought the idea to mind that maybe he could finally earn the love and approval of his father if he too could gain a job like that. He barely listened as the advice to keep him homeschooled hit and sealed his plan firmly. He discovered upon coming home that his local friend would not be going to Hogwarts either, as he was a squib. Luka and the other boy got a stronger bond and joined in cursing the world for their misfortunes together.

Years passed and his mother taught him everything he knew and by some miracle he scored higher grades than his brother, barely. This led him to believe that his brother was a somewhat foolish oaf, even though the man was clever enough in other ways. Yet his own behaviour was only good around the house, as he and his friend caused problems and often were drinking when they were around the village together.

After getting the needed grades, Luka decided to become a healer to at long last meet the approval of his father. He went to training, often using his free time to join his friend in his muggle classes where he strove to become a doctor. Luka himself at first became a mediwizard, presuming it was a good thing to be out in the field where needed. He was wrong as he kept running into a lot of aurors and other people that so keenly reminded him of his brother and father. While healing people brought him satisfaction, he hated dealing with the pompous pricks that ran the show, so he decided to switch specialisations. 

Several years later, approval still pending, his parents finally came clean and told him that he'd been adopted. At twenty five years of age it was a big blow to Luka and since he had been raised and easily believed in equity and had no purist views the idea that his parents were everything he was taught to dispise shook him to his very foundations. Respect was his birthright and if his father would not yield it, he would claim it for himself. 

With a far less cheery onset the man now focussed on excelling in his job, laughing when his own father came into his department one day. Magical bugs and diseases had been his next choice and well, his father left alive with the scorn of Luka. The great man, just as pathetic as all the others it seemed. He worked harder and proved himself easily, using the knowledge from both his mother and the free time he'd spent in muggle medicine to improve the quality of the ward he worked at significantly. He got promoted to head wizard, in part due to his skill and while unmentioned, also because his bedside manner was hardly positive. 

Throughout the years, especially after discovering his true heritage, Luka found himself as somewhat of a social chameleon. When facing purists he smoothly and easily preached the same purity he condamned in the face of their opposition. The most remarkable moment was when he was faced with parents that demanded him to cure their son since the poor lad was a squib. He smiled a disgusted smile as he suggested they simply give him up to an orphanage and save them both the embarressment of the taint on their family name. He suggested they get a coffee and leave, never to return. 

He never quite expected the parents to take his sardonic reply to heart and he spent the rest of the day caring for the child and teaching him things he knew about muggle medicine. He gave the kid his contact information and still keeps in touch with the boy and his life in a loving muggle family. If there boy would not be a squib, Luka would be there for him. If he was, Luka assured him it was better to grow up somewhere that parents would see one as more than a constant disappointment rather than see the truly glory and potential they held. Naturally this was in part due to his own arrogance and belief of grandure that his adoptive rather refused to acknowledge. 

He got the job of head healer when the current head healer retired. His exceptional knowledge of human anatomy combined with his innovative thinking due to his very brief time as a mediwizard showed a quick witted and knowledgable young man more than capable of weighing the risks in more difficult cases. While it was common for the head healer to have ever so slightly more than eleven years of experience they found that the lacking two or three years at most would not change the asset his skills would bring to the job. 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Seph[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her 
[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]I'm a 90's bish.
[/blockquote]
[/div][/div]