[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://64.media.tumblr.com/1497c16f9eed9e011c3920e39a168913/tumblr_or933xKSQQ1qbmp7lo4_500.gif" alt="" style="max-width:100%;"]
[/div][div align="center"][font size="5"]gabrielle eleanor shacklebolt[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]gab-ree-elle[/blockquote][b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]&nbsp;[strike]Gabby [/strike](actually, don't call her this, she's refused to respond to it since Abigail died), Elle[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]21-years-old
1 September 2004[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Female
she/her[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Pureblood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]lesbian[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]9", blackthorn, dragon heartstring[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Logan Browning[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Height: 5'5
Gabrielle looks just like her playby aside from a few tattoos scattered across her body (though nothing excessive). She has quite a few scars as well, all recent (as in the past 2 years recent). She also ha a nose ring.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts - Gryffindor[/blockquote][b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduate[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Bounty Hunter
Information Broker
Former: Hit witch-in-training Summer 2023-Summer 2024[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Being busy
traveling
Dueling
Alcohol
Smoking
Exploring new areas
high stress situation
Heights[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Elaine Dupree (She holds a looooooooooooot of resentment.)
The Purifiers
People mentioning her father and sister's deaths.
sweets
Order of the Phoenix (love/hate relationship. It's complicated. But she feels they failed her family
Watching Quidditch (enjoys playing it though)
Wasting time[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]To see the end of the Purifiers, and finally make them pay for their crimes.
To make someone pay (since Elaine can't, cause Gabrielle doesn't know she's alive) pay for Abby and her father's deaths.
To have her family all back together and whole.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Cigarette smoke, whiskey, pine.[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote][strike]That Elaine Dupree will never pay for her crimes.[/strike] This fear has partially come true, as she doesn't know Elaine is alive
That her father's legacy will only be remembered for being the Minister that failed when the Puriifers first appeared.

[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Gabrielle is a thrill seeker. She chases one high to the next and thrives in high stress and high risk situations. She is able to keep a calm head in any situation, but loves the feel of her heart racing. She is a daredevil in that sense, and warnings don't stop her from doing something, if anything it encourages her to do it even more. Though that doesn't make her reckless. She doesn't rush in blindly just for the thrill. She is always calculating the risks, and doing what she can for her own safety. (Example, she'll sky dive, but she'll actually follow safety protocols).&nbsp;

Gabrielle someone that's been scarred a great many times, and she's never quite healed from it. Those that know her from school will see through this mask quite easily, and see how resentful and angry she is about the deaths in her family.

And vengeful. Dear&nbsp; god, is she vengeful. Her anger drove her away from the Ministry because she felt like they'd never get the job done. She has little trust in authority at this point, and fully believes that if she wants something done right, she has to do it herself. She doesn't trust others to support her, as they've already failed her family so many times before. Nor does she particularly want people's help or support. She's also quite guarded when it comes to certain... attachments. As she feels her sister's death could have been avoided had Theodorus Nott never entered their lives. In fact, she's come to resent love because of this.

Though if she's not putting on a fake smile, Gabrielle is not a very nice person. She can come across very rude and arrogant, and very sarcastic. She's the type of person that&nbsp; doesn't feel a need to pretend to be nice or pleasant if she doesn't want to. She isn't intentionally mean though where she wants to hurt others, she just refuses to be sugar coat things, or fake niceties.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Wales.[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Kingsley Shacklebolt - Father. Deceased
Hestia Shacklebolt (nee Jones) - Mother.&nbsp;
____ Shacklebolt - Eldest sibling, graduated 2019
Abigail Shacklebolt - twin sister. Deceased[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]None[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Growing up the daughter of the Minister wasn't easy. The youngest of the Shacklebolts (though only youngest by a few minutes), Gabrielle had a lot to prove from a very young age. Thankfully, she had two very loving parents, and two wonderful siblings. Despite the pressures of her father's work, her childhood was a very happy time. In particular it helped that she had her sister, Abigail. They were only a few minutes apart, and thus inseparable, as many twins are. Her childhood wasn't very exciting though, thankfully. Her father tried not to bring his work home with him. WHile she knew he was the Minister she only really ever saw him as "dad".

Eventually she and he sister were old enough to attend Hogwarts and both were placed in Gryffindor house. Quite fitting, considering their personalities. Abby was always the head strong one, but Gabrielle always had a quite bravery to her. She was a fearless child who would accept any challenge you presented her with. Most of her Hogwarts years were quite uneventful. She would play for the Gryffindor quidditch team when she got older, and was also an active member, and even went on to take a leadership role in the Dueling club. She excelled in Dueling and Defense Against the Dark arts. Quite easily her best subjects.&nbsp;
[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]That is, until her seventh year. That horrible summer night. Her father had left for work that morning like every other morning, and that night Aurors were knocking on their door. Dead. Murdered. Gabrielle can still remember her mother's sobs. There were no leads yet, but they were promised that his death was being investigated. They'd catch whoever did this, and bring them to justice. Despite the horrible anguish, Gabrielle believed them. She'd been told her whole life to trust the Ministry. They'd failed her father tonight, but they'd fix it. They'd make it right.

Then, the first muggle born student was killed. Her sister and James Potter formed Phoenix Rising, and Gabrielle immediately joined the cause. Of course, the adults would get to the bottom of this, right? But that didn't mean they couldn't help! Then another murder.... And Ethan was almost killed... With each event, Gabrielle felt that unwavering trust begin to shake. Why wasn't the Ministry doing anything? Why was this still happening? She'd always been told to trust them!

The night of April 1 2023 was the most terrifying of Gabrielle's life. She was one of the students kidnapped during the attack. At the time, she didn't understand why, but afterwards she came to realize that it was due to Abigail and Theodorus' involvement. She believes that the Purifiers had meant to kidnap Abigail and grabbed her by mistake. Thankfully, she and the other students were rescued. Though she decided then and there to never be that helpless again.

After graduation she started Hitwitch training. At the same time, she was also brought into the folds of Order of the Phoenix. She was told, and led to believe, that the Ministry was doing everything they could. And that sometimes they just needed help.&nbsp; That the Ministry wasn't failing her, and that she could help them. And she truly believed this, especially when Desirae was tracked down and killed. She felt like her trust was finally starting to pay off. Until that faith was shattered.

Abigail was killed. Elaine had killed her and that Nott boy Abigail had been so infatuated with. He'd been a Purifier, something that made her blood boil. Her sister, her beautiful and strong twin sister, was gone. Taken from her by the Purifiers. Just like her father had been taken a year and a half earlier.&nbsp; Gabrielle would never believe those false promises of justice again.

Gabrielle quit her job at the Ministry without notice and packed a bag. She left with only a duffle bag and a note to her mother and older sibling saying that she was going to travel. She needed to find a new purpose in life. When she was in Australia, she was taken under the wing of a magical bounty hunter, who taught her everything they knew. She was a quick study. From her extensive dueling training at school and her year of Hit Witch training.&nbsp;

She apprenticed under this bounty hunter, until she finally felt ready to work on her own, roughly a year. Then she set off on her own to make her own path as a bounty hunter. She continued to travel the world in her work.&nbsp;

Gabrielle was in Brazil when news arrived of a magical island appearing in Europe.&nbsp; She knew there were still quite a few escaped Azkaban prisoners, with some hefty bounties, as well. So, she's finally decided it's time to come home...[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Sora[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]29[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]Mountain[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]I live here[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]To many... I have a problem.[/blockquote][/div][/div]