[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt=" " src="http://i.imgur.com/yCyOZr8.png" style="max-width:100%;"] [/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]grey xavier slater[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]gray. like the color.[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]none.[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]19
October 23rd, 2005[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]male. he/him/his.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]half-blood.[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]straight. [/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]10 inches, bamboo, thunderbird tail feather.[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]roo panes.[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote] Grey stands at a little under six feet tall, hoping that one day he'll break the six foot barrier. With an average athletic build, he prefers to wear more casual clothes on his off days, and keeps his school robes as relaxed as possible. He loves wearing the tie the most, which is odd because he refuses to wear them anywhere else. On weekends he's commonly seen with a light jacket on if he's outside, and enjoys wearing ski jackets in the winter. Having an affinity for the cold though, it's commonplace to see Grey walking across the grounds without a jacket on in the middle of winter.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]hogwarts. gryffindor.
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]graduate.
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]intern at the daily prophet.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]snow, writing, rainy days, watching quidditch, pancakes, staying up late at night.[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]sleeping, being forced to write articles he’s not invested in, pretentiousness, his parents, being someone he isn’t.[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]to be successful in his own field of work and for something he enjoys doing, and to be noticed for that (specifically by his parents).[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]the wet ground after a rainstorm, smoke, pine.[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]being pigeonholed into a lifestyle that he doesn’t want.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]A general rule of thumb when it comes to dealing with Grey Slater is to not approach him in the middle of the night while he’s working on a stack of papers. While in school this was almost a nightly occurrence, leading many to believe that the exhausted and irritable state he was in was how he normally was. He isn’t necessarily a grouch, by any degree, but very invested in his work, which is sure to carry over in his new career at the Daily Prophet.

He can come across as boring and dull when presented with situations he doesn’t really care about or take more effort than he is willing to put into them. The only interests he really has involve Quidditch and writing news articles. When working, he comes out of his shell a little bit, knowing that he has to more effort into it, so as to make a better impression. This is contrary to how he was in school, here he could care less about getting high marks on exams or raving reviews from professors. As an average Hogwarts student, his time and effort was always placed in the school newspaper, leading more often to those long nights than school work ever did.

He hates being compared to his older sister, Claire, who excelled in school before going into law enforcement, and his younger sister, Addi, who (in his opinion) is living up to their parents’ expectations expertly, as an outstanding student and Head Girl. Their constant nagging to follow in Claire’s footsteps had him entering the Auror training program post-graduation, which, while a great regiment, was not his cup of tea. His lower energy output and lack of ‘effort’ caught up to him in the end and had him looking for a new job within six months. Going against his parents’ wishes and following through with what he wanted to do took time, but he finally feels he’s in the right position in life.

Getting past his internal problems though, he can be an extremely observant (mostly due to always trying to find a journalistic hook out in the wild) and loyal friend. Trying to do what he sees is in the best interests of both others and himself, Grey strives to help out as much as possible when asked. Sometimes this becomes a hindrance because he feels like he absolutely cannot turn someone down if they need his help, mainly because he pushed a lot of his classmates away at school. Striving to be the best person as possible, Grey tries to stay on top of everything as best as he can, trying to make his somewhat dull and boring life as interesting as possible.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]london, england.[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]shela slater - mother, 48, works at gringotts, muggleborn.
tim slater – 50, works in the department of international magical cooperation in the international magical office of law (he’s a magical lawyer), half-blood.
claire slater – sister, 20-22, works in magical law enforcement (auror, hitwitch, or obliviator), former gryffindor, half-blood.
addilyn slater – 17, 7th year slytherin, head girl, half-blood.
[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]n/a[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Grey was born on a quiet day at the end of October, and joined the Slater family as the second child. While not a huge difference in age, the two siblings constantly got into fights when they were infants, both vying for attention. There was no love between the two, and it was sometimes difficult to tell if they really were siblings. Fortunately, only two years later another child was born, Addilyn. Growing up as the middle child, Grey would soon find out who his parents favorites were: the intelligent and extremely talented Claire, and Addi, the younger, bubbly (and sometimes critically-thinking) social butterfly. The lack of effort his parents put towards raising him made it painfully obvious as he grew older. Always conscious of this, he thought acting out in the form of letting his grades slip was his best way of gaining their attention. And it worked, for a short time.

Like every other child from a wizarding family, Grey received his letter of acceptance to Hogwarts following his eleventh birthday. It was finally time for him to escape his parents and start doing things on his own, hoping that he could prove to them that he was just as important as his sisters. For the first two years at school he struggled immensely, refusing Claire's help with his studies, and widening the gap between him and his parents. Entering his third year, he decided to change things around and began studying as much as possible. Hating reading with a passion, Grey's attitude soon changed and he was reading any book he could get his hands on. He thoroughly enjoyed books that focused on the mysteries of Hogwarts, and he started exploring the halls as much as he could in his free time. Over the holiday break his third year, the Slater family lost their grandfather. He had been getting on in years, and had been in extremely poor health. Loving his grandfather as a young child, Grey took the loss hard. Returning to Hogwarts after the holidays, he locked himself away socially. Completing school work seemed pointless when everyone was going to die eventually anyways. Doing the bare minimum to keep his parents happy was how he ended up going forward.

Going through his fourth and fifth years at Hogwarts changed who Grey was as a person. With Claire focusing on her last couple of years in school, the pressure of being compared to his older sister made him feel more comfortable when it came to reaching out to other students to make friends. He finally felt accepted and started to shed the edgy preteen attitude that he had worn for the last few years. He still wasn't on the best of terms with his parents but knew that letting them get their way with him was easier than always fighting against it. He managed to find a balance in all of it somehow, by joining the school newspaper in his fourth year, and quickly rising to the position of editor-in-chief for his sixth and seventh years. Being allowed to do what he wanted while still pleasing his parents was nice for once.

Sixth year brought with it the deaths of muggleborns and a rising fear at Hogwarts. Grey chose unwisely and decided to do what he did best: write in his newspaper. He liked to think that it was his own coping mechanism to what was happening around him, while others probably saw it as exploitative. A good journalist reported the news though, and kids dying was news. 

Seventh year welcomed happier news with the arrival of the Triwizard Tournament. He did enter his name into the Goblet of Fire, though figured his lack of drive to actually participate in it was probably what kept his from being selected. Regardless, he turned to his position at the school paper in order to conduct interviews with the champions and write reports on the tasks that they had to go through. All eyes were on Hogwarts and he helmed the school paper. In his mind, it was a good chance to get noticed as a journalist, even though his parents had already convinced him that he was going to enter the auror training program. 
[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduating soon after the explosions that killed the Durmstrang and Beauxbatons students, Grey felt like he needed to be with the Aurors, even if that wasn’t where he wanted to be in the long run. Someone needed to be held accountable for the atrocities that were caused, and being in the position to help out with catching them felt right to him. Ultimately though, his morale dropped as training progressed and the search for Harry Potter looked more and more futile. They didn’t need someone like him, whose heart wasn’t in it, and he didn’t think he could commit to the ultimate sacrifice if the time ever called for it. To him, fighting the good fight meant going back to what he was better at, writing articles for a newspaper. So he left the Auror program to intern at the Daily Prophet, in the hope that something he wrote would help inform the public about what was going on in their world.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]colin.[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]24[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]est[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]proboards suppoer[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@cordelia  @lance  @mina  @lily  @cara  @nottingham  @jimbo  @steve  @blaise  @harper  @renard  @madeleine [/blockquote][/div][/div]