[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt=" " src="https://secure.static.tumblr.com/8dfd642ee3ada7194c9f78a327251eaa/9unhocm/jGRnrvsbe/tumblr_static_tumblr_static_filename_640.png" style="max-width:100%;"] [/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]cordelia regan smith[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]core-dell-ee-uh[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]cordie or cord.[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]17
June 16th, 2007[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]female. she/her/hers.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]half-blood.[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]straight.[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]8 inches, holly, unicorn hair, bendy.[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]freya mavor.[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Exactly the same as playby, except she is 5’5” instead of 5’10”. Her hair is a frizzy mess a lot times, getting in her eyes and always being pushed out of the way.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]hogwarts. hufflepuff.
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]7th year.
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]n/a.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]llamas (she has a stuffed animal named Mr. Floofles), photography, cameras, charms, calm classical music, autumn, tea, being alone, origami, muggle mystery and horror books and films.[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]confrontation, being called on in class, she is allergic to peanut butter, when she stutters, large groups, having her photographs criticized.[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]to have her photographs in a museum, magazine, or lookbook. to be a healer like her mother.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]new book smell, fallen leaves, butterscotch.[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Fears.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote] Cordelia is extremely quiet and reserved, especially towards people she doesn’t know. Since she isn’t exactly the most outgoing person, so there are more people than not that she’s comfortable around, let alone talks to. Being this way, she’s found solace in her photography work as well as other art forms. The ability to express her feelings and emotions through art and photos has been really beneficial in having others understand her and help her make connections. She’s spent the majority of her years in the art club, hoping that the small community that surrounds it would help her get over her fear of social communication and help her advance her artistic abilities.

On that same note, the people she’s met within the art club have shown her that being a little more outgoing wouldn’t hurt at all, so she’s started to make strides towards doing that. A new person approaching her would more than likely elicit either silence or an awkward response, Cordelia still unsure on how to communicate properly with others on the spot. Given time, she’ll eventually learn how to get words out, amidst stuttering and nerves. She also gets extremely embarrassed from her stuttering, a problem she’s dealt with her entire life, so being made fun of for that will completely shut her down, even around friends and close acquaintances. 

One of her major flaws is the inability to see when someone is trying to take advantage of her. Because of her problems with interacting with others, false friendships have happened more than once and she falls for it every time. For the most part, Cordelia prefers to be by herself to focus on her work, but actually longs for some kind of close friend to help her figure out why people do the things they do. Outside of her social problems, Cordelia loves to use her imagination in her art, and bonding with others over that skill is what she strives for. Where she lacks in talking to others, she makes up with what she sees in her mind and puts onto a canvas or snaps through her camera. She hopes that others will see and enjoy her art as much as she does. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]scotland.[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]eleanor smith (née branstone) – mother, 42, healer at st. mungo’s, half-blood, divorced.

zacharias smith – father, 43, retired professional Quidditch player for the ballycastle bats, pureblood, divorced.

delilah smith – half-sister (from her father), 16, 6th year hufflepuff (horned serpent), half-veela.
[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]pyro – orange tabby cat[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote] To understand Cordelia, one must first understand her parents; Zacharias and Eleanor Smith. Both former Hufflepuffs that attended Hogwarts during the Second Wizarding War, the Smiths opted to remain as far away as possible from the fighting as possible. Upon graduating, Zacharias went on to play professional Quidditch for a small team, where he remained a number of years before retiring due to taking too many bludgers to the face. Having been sent to St. Mungo’s numerous times during his career, he became a common face in the hospital and was watched from a distance by one of his former housemates; Eleanor Branstone. Eleanor was now a healer at the hospital, and the two soon rekindled their friendship. After a few years of Zacharias being sent back and forth to the hospital, as well as sometimes showing up unexpected to see Eleanor despite not having injuries, he finally proposed and they were married. Fast forward a few more years and Cordelia was born.

Home life was pretty normal for Cordelia. She had a typical magical upbringing, learning about Quidditch through her father and developing a love for the little charms her mother showed her. The one problem growing up though was that she was an only child, and her father didn’t really like her interacting with other children in the magical community for some reason. Due to this, her abilities to become a normal social child never developed correctly, and her parents quickly realized upon her entering school that there were issues. Her first year at Hogwarts was terrible, not knowing how to talk or interact with her peers left Cordelia lonely, despite being sorted into Hufflepuff, the house known for the more social of witches and wizards. When she did manage to get something out, it came in either mumbles or stutters, which she was relentlessly bullied over by other first years.

Over the next few years, she started to become more and more reserved, retreating towards a new found talent in the arts. Her parents noticed this between her second and third years at Hogwarts and got her a camera, now one of many in her collection, so that she would hopefully be able to express herself through means other than talking. In her fourth year, she learned about the art club and decided to give it a shot, since she was positive in her ability to fit in there. Finding that the club was a safe location to show who she truly was, things started to get easier. The other club members were understanding of her anxieties, and gave her the space she needed to create art comfortably, adding in tips on how to improve here and there. 

Enter fifth year. From the start, things were different. The problems with the students being killed and then kidnapped made Cordelia terrified that the few friends she had made would be hurt. Her photographs and art took a sinister turn, showing her worries, vastly different from the innocent looking projects she had been to make before all of this happened. Things went on and she was reassured by her parents that it was an isolated incident that wouldn’t repeat itself again. They had survived the last war, so she knew she could trust what they said. Media sources didn’t help though, contradicting what dear mum and dad had told her, so she started to close up again, hoping that she wouldn’t be targeted for whatever reason. In between fifth and sixth year, Cordelia spent a lot of time at home, refusing to go out and do things, still afraid of the dangerous people that everyone was aware of now. Going back to Hogwarts for her sixth year was a struggle, but her parents once again convinced her that it was the safest place to be if something happened. She didn’t understand how that could be, especially after the murders that had taken place the previous year, but she went regardless, hoping to focus on the art club and her studies more. While the announcement at the beginning of the year about the Triwizard Tournament was a shock to most, Cordelia didn’t really think much about it. She wasn’t old enough to enter it, and the influx of students from the other two schools made her feel like avoiding them was impossible. It was the Triwizard Tournament after all, so just experiencing something that her parents had as well was a treat.

Fall 2024
Following a [a href="http://alohomorax0.proboards.com/post/70078"]SCATHING ARTICLE BY RITA SKEETER[/a], Cordelia's mother immediately filed for a divorce from her husband, leaving the Hufflepuff unsure of where things were going moving forward. With her parents now living in separate homes and her father's legacy as a Quidditch player tarnished, the latter half of the fall semester has put Cordelia into a mental state she has never experienced before. The addition of her supposed half-sister doesn't help at all either...
 [/blockquote]
[blockquote][b]site events reaction:[/b]The summer between her sixth and seventh year at school brought on a few challenges that Cordelia wasn’t sure she was ready to face, come the beginning of the fall term. There was talk by her parents (prior to her father’s secret leaking out) about maybe holding off on sending her back to school for her final year, at least until those responsible for the explosions were apprehended. Her parents reasoning was that they didn’t want to put her through what they had experienced during their final years at Hogwarts. Despite her normal meekness and inability to speak up for herself, Cordelia pushed them to let her go, even going as far as showing them that she was more capable with her magic than she was with everything else in her life. She really didn’t have an opinion about the addition of the Ilvermorny students, aside from the fact that there would be more people to deal with. She lost the chance to reach out to Lily when the news broke that her father had gone missing, only seeing her again on the train ride to school. With a lot of new bodies occupying Hogwarts, Cordelia is worried something else could happen, considering that the foreign students from the previous year weren’t exempt and before that, neither were the Hogwarts students.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]colin.[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]24.[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]est.[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]proboards support.[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@grey     @lance     @mina     @lily     @cara     @nottingham     @jimbo     @steve     @blaise     @harper     @renard     @madeleine    [/blockquote][/div][/div]