[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;background-color:#B6B6B4;border:4px solid #B6B6B4;border-radius:10px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="http://25.media.tumblr.com/7324969db3a8ba17bc6d46cf1fd56a18/tumblr_mf1a4lXNb31rywljgo1_500.gif" alt=" " style="max-width:100%;"][/div]

hello there, my name is [b]Ophelia Teller[/b] but you can call me [b]Fee[/b]. i'm [b]24[/b] so that makes me an [b]alumnus&nbsp;[/b]of Hogwarts, where I reside in [b]Hufflepuff[/b] house. You could say I'm [b]hard working, patient, &amp; loyal[/b]&nbsp;but I personally think that I am [b]quirky, klutzy &amp; bubbly[/b]. People say I look a lot like [b]Emilia Clarke[/b], but I don't really see it...

[div align="center"][font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][i][b]ophelia mae teller[/b][/i][/font][/font][/div]

[b][i]nickname:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Fee mostly, Lia by her brother[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]24[/blockquote]
[b][i]date of birth:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]29 april, 1999[/blockquote]
[b][i]gender:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]witch[/blockquote]
[b][i]blood status:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]half-blood[/blockquote]
[b][i]sexuality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]pansexual[/blockquote]
[b][i]house:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]hufflepuff[/blockquote]
[b][i]occupation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]welcome witch at St. Mungo's, also helps out as a volunteer seamstress on her days off at Madam Malkins [/blockquote]
[b][i]wand:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]vine and dragon heartstring, 9 1/4 inches[/blockquote][b][i]playby:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Emilia Clarke[/blockquote][b][i]appearance:[/i] [/b]
[blockquote]Ophelia stands at a short but sweet 5'2' and looks immensely like Emilia Clarke, except for that one time when s he was sixteen and she dyed her hair platinum blonde as a dare from her brother. &nbsp;He still teases her about it. &nbsp;She also has a small heart outline tattoo on her left wrist for her mother, who passed away from breast cancer.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personality[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]likes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]bright colors, fashion, the medical world, laughing, bubbles, summer thunderstorms, dancing even if she looks like an idiot, going with the natural flow of things[/blockquote][b][i]dislikes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]cancer, turnips, the color grey, rap music, blood, death &amp; destruction, wasps (she's allergic to the venom in the sting)[/blockquote]
[b][i]erised:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]her mother alive again and her family happy together[/blockquote]
[b][i]amortentia:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]that smell just after a rainstorm, lilacs, and honey[/blockquote]
[b][i]boggart:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]her mother covered in blood[/blockquote]
[b][i]overall personality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Ophelia is a quirky, bubbly ball of energy that is always smiling and laughing, even when she needs to be serious. &nbsp; She's always early, and figures out the little things that will brighten a persons' day, whether it be baking her famous (she likes to think they're famous anyway) sugar cookies, or bringing in a bouquet flowers to a patient - she always puts others first. &nbsp;She loves her job, though it doesn't pay all that much, and is perfectly content with her life as it is, much to the chagrin of her father and brother. &nbsp;Her mother though, was the one who taught her to embrace life and always do what made her happy. &nbsp;It was those words, and the help of some of her friends, that gave Ophelia a newfound confidence; she's not afraid anymore of acting on a natural feeling to her, and does not feel badly after acting on it either. &nbsp;She lets things go very easily; she's very easy-come easy-go, unless she feels the issue at hand is quite serious. &nbsp;It is very VERY difficult to make Fee angry, but on the blue moon occasion that someone does, they better run - her brother nicknamed angry Fee 'The Dragon' for a reason.

There was a time though that Fee was not one of the happiest balls of sunshine on Earth, and that was when her mother got sick. &nbsp;It was so sudden, and it was almost as if a light went out in Fee for awhile. &nbsp;She withdrew from friends, stopped sewing up new and ridiculous pieces of clothing and really just stopped being who she was. &nbsp;While she got out of this depressive funk eventually, every year on the anniversary of her mothers' death, she morphs into a shy and quiet girl who doesn't talk as much. &nbsp; &nbsp;The people she works with are used to it now, and usually keep their distance out of respect.[/blockquote]
[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personal history[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]mother:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Lydia Wilson-Teller, Muggle, deceased (died of breast cancer at age 57)[/blockquote][b][i]father:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Caius Abraham Teller, Wizard, 70, former Unspeakable &amp; Slytherin, now sits on the Wizengamot&nbsp;[/blockquote][b][i]siblings:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Octavian Teller, 32, former Slytherin, Ministry Official[/blockquote]
[b][i]pets:[/i][/b]
[blockquote][a href="http://animalonline.info/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/turkish-van-cat-nxop90qb.jpg"]Pam the Turkish Van[/a]
[/blockquote][b][i]history:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Caius Teller had it all going for him - he had friends, power and money, and was Head Boy of Hogwarts during the 1970-71 school year. &nbsp;He had an job as an Unspeakable in the Department of Mysteries through his cousins' friend Augustus Rookwood. &nbsp;He had heard of Lord Voldemorts' gaining power, and with Rookwood as his mentor, it would have been very easy for Caius to join the Death Eaters, if it had not been for Lydia. &nbsp;Lydia was a Muggle, beautiful and free-spirited, she entranced Caius from their first chance meeting while he was on a job about two years into his career. &nbsp;She worked in a second-hand bookstore and always wore a flower in her long dark hair. &nbsp;Caius realized two things: that he was madly in love with this woman, and that she would never be accepted into his circle. &nbsp;So their relationship was kept secret; Caius opened up a second vault at Gringotts and would store his earnings there, knowing that his parents would cut him off the moment they found out about Lydia. &nbsp;It was immensely stressful for Caius, leading this double life, but every time he was with Lydia, everything seemed worth it. &nbsp;He told her how he was a wizard and the world he was part of early on in their relationship, but to his surprise, she took it in stride, saying she always thought there was 'something magical' about him. &nbsp;He was able to shake Rookwood off by telling him his parents would prefer for him to stay on his chosen career path, avoiding joining the Death Eaters. &nbsp;This paid off in 1981 when Voldemort was defeated. &nbsp;Caius was never suspected of any wrongdoings (as he had should not have been), and with Rookwood soon behind bars, he was finally able to do what he wanted to do for nearly a decade - marry the woman of his dreams. &nbsp;As expected, his family had cut him off financially, but he had built up a small fortune of his own through saving and living simply with Lydia, and they were still able to live comfortably.

Lydia and Caius had wanted children since the early days of their relationship, but with the Wizarding World in turmoil and Caius not being able to tell his parents about her, they decided to wait until they could marry to have children. &nbsp;Octavian Teller came into the world in 1991. &nbsp;They had wanted to give him a sibling; most of Lydia's family was dead or living in far off places, and Caius' family didn't speak to them, but Lydia struggled to conceive again. &nbsp;They had given up hope of ever having a second child, when at age 42 she discovered she was pregnant a second time! &nbsp;She gave birth to Ophelia Lee Teller on a rainy day in April at home, much to the delight of her older brother and father. &nbsp;Ophelia's childhood was a happy one; she was a mummy's girl from Day One, and could cheer her father up even after a long day at the Department of Mysteries with her bubbly smile and giggle. &nbsp;Octavian went off to Hogwarts when she was just three years old, and was Sorted into Slytherin like his father. &nbsp;Ophelia would spend days roaming around the meadows by their little cottage near Guildford with her mother, feeding and tending to the baby animals, or just picking wildflowers for their kitchen table. &nbsp;By night her father would read to her from different magic books; The Beetle &amp; The Bard was a fixture on her little shelf. &nbsp;When she was 7, she made the flowers in a vase on the table float in midair, showing that she was indeed a witch. &nbsp;Her parents were excited, though Lydia knew that meant her baby would go off to Hogwarts when she was 11, making it bittersweet.

Ophelia arrived at Hogwarts in 2010, a year after her brother had graduated. &nbsp;He came to see her off on the Express with her parents, even though he had just received an internship with the Minister himself. &nbsp;Upon arrival, Ophelia was Sorted into Hufflepuff house over Slytherin. &nbsp;Her father and brother were surprised, but Lydia, who had read Hogwarts: &nbsp;A History while she had been dating Caius, wasn't surprised. &nbsp;She told her husband that if she had been a witch, she most certainly would have been Sorted into Hufflepuff, and he begrudgingly agreed with her. &nbsp;Ophelia was not nearly as ambitious as her older brother had been - Prefect, Head Boy, Beater on the Slytherin Quidditch team - but found a love for Herbology and Care of Magical Creatures. &nbsp;She was quite abysmal at Transfiguration, and found that some of the subject material in Defense Against the Dark Arts frightened her. &nbsp;She discovered a love of sewing and fashion early on; her mother had always sewn her fun and bright outfits, and she was happy to mend her friends' robes, which would snag on anything from tree branches to other peoples' feet. &nbsp;She knew she was not destined to follow in either her brother or fathers' footsteps at the Ministry, but she felt perfectly content to go wherever her heart ended up taking her.

Ophelia's fourth year at Hogwarts was the most difficult she had to endure; just a week before returning to school, her mother Lydia was diagnosed with Stage IV breast cancer, and was given mere months to live. &nbsp;Caius was beside himself; he tried to bring in Healers from St. Mungos' to cure her, but Lydia would not hear of it. &nbsp;Her own mother had died from the disease years previously, and she felt that if she did not let nature take its' course, there would be repercussions. &nbsp; Ophelia found herself distracted at school; her grades low and her social life dwindling. &nbsp;Finally, her Head of House called her into their office, and she explained her situation. &nbsp;She was given permission to be at home with her mother on her final days - she would be given time and opportunity to make up her work after she had proper time to mourn. &nbsp;The cancer worked faster than anyone could have imagined, and Lydia Teller drew her last breath at 10am on October 31st, Halloween. &nbsp;The family was devastated; Ophelia didn't even want to return to school - she just wanted to sit by her mothers grave in the meadow near their cottage, where she had instructed them to bury her - and grieve. &nbsp;Her brother finally convinced her to go back to school, promising her that their mother would not have wanted her to sit around and be sad all the time. &nbsp;Their mother had been full of light like her, he said, and she wouldn't want that light to go out. &nbsp;Ophelia returned to school, and threw herself into her studies; she was still quiet and reserved, and barely spoke to anyone. &nbsp;It took until the end of Summer term for her to really feel like her old self, even though she still felt like there was a part of her missing. &nbsp;She fixed this at the suggestion of her brother - with her fathers' permission, she got a tattoo of the outline of a heart on her left wrist; every time she looked at it she would remember her mother would always be with her. &nbsp;Her mother's death also left Ophelia an interest in Wizarding medicine; her father was insistent that Healers could have cured her, but she was not as convinced. &nbsp;Researching wizarding medical marvels would become somewhat of an obsessive hobby for her, though she knew she could never master all the subjects needed to become a Healer.

Once Ophelia graduated, her father and brother tried to persuade her to join the Ministry. &nbsp;At this point, Caius had retired from the Department of Mysteries and had joined Wizengamot, and told her he had plenty of pull should she want to choose a career path. &nbsp;Ophelia declined, and instead applied for a job as a receptionist at St. Mungos'. &nbsp;When her father asked why not apply for a Trainee Healer, she told him that her poor grades in Transfiguration &amp; Potions had made her ineligible - besides, she didn't like blood. &nbsp;This way, she could still be in the Healing world, but not actually have to be a Healer. &nbsp;Her family didn't really understand, but let her do her own thing, as it was what Lydia would have wanted. &nbsp;To her credit, Ophelia did rise up from mere receptionist to Welcome Witch in a few short years, and while she doesn't make a lot of money, she loves going to her job every day and does feel like she is making a difference. &nbsp;She was one of the first to hear of the kidnappings at Hogwarts, and helped the Healers in making sure those injured in the rescue were brought to the right place so they could receive proper treatment. &nbsp;She also was there the day a group attacked Kings Cross, injuring both Muggles and some wizards in the process. &nbsp;She was very grateful that the students were unharmed, but saw how much work the Mediwizards and Healers were exhausting themselves with, and for the first time wished she had acquired the grades needed to study Healing...[/blockquote]
[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]alias[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]name:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Lisa[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]27[/blockquote][b][i]time zone:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]EST[/blockquote][b][i]reference:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]dragons[/blockquote][b][i]other characters:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]@irinarose       ,&nbsp;@hermionejean       ,&nbsp;@susanvictoria       ,&nbsp;@calliope       ,&nbsp;@finn       ,&nbsp;@louis       
[/blockquote][/div][/div]