[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt=" " style="max-width:100%;" src="https://www.bellazon.com/main/uploads/monthly_2019_04/829B1F84-DE55-4157-952E-75199D43120F.jpeg.45317f94f986bb94d1a98f7c274054e7.jpeg"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]nova hypatia vector[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]no-vuh[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]none[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]22
October 23, 2003 – Mole Day[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]female. she/her/hers[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]half-blood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]pansexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]8 ¾ , apple, unicorn hair, rigid[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]neve caffrey[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]5’6”. Same as playby.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling &amp; status[/b]
[blockquote]Graduated 2022. Ravenclaw.[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Baker at The Pi Pâtisserie [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]baking, sweets, perfection, working, summer storms, late nights, the stars, relaxing, smoking[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]food going to waste, a messy kitchen, rude customers, her father (thank Merlin he’s dead), her current ‘step-mother’, relationship commitment[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Nova is all about working and keeping herself busy. In school, she kept this up by taking as many classes as possible, feeling like the better off she was in school, the less likely she was going to be outright abandoned by her father (though that writing was on the wall as he went through another two wives before she even entered Hogwarts). The introduction of her five younger siblings told her that she was never going to be the most important of his children, and her attachment issues started when she was young. By distracting herself with baking under her aunt’s watchful eye and school work, she avoided a lot of the issues that came along with Octavian Sr. and his idea of what family meant. The only permanence in her life were the things that she did herself, and not what went on around her.

Because of these commitment issues that her father had, or didn’t depending on who you asked, she was bookish in school, overloading herself with classwork and only making friends with some of her classmates in Ravenclaw. She found that the more technical of classes at Hogwarts, namely Arithmancy and Potions, were fairly easy, as her family tended to specialize when it came to exacts and numbers.

As an adult and with her father now dead, she has started to work on the problems that she grew up. She still actively dislikes her most recent step-mother, mostly because she’s barely older than her older brother, and has never viewed her as a motherly figure. Nova is relatively cold towards the woman and has no problem showing that in public if need be. With her half-siblings, she has discovered over the years that none of them are really at fault for being born into the family the way they were. They were all unfortunate results of their father’s follies, and she can’t continue to blame them as she had done when she was younger.

When it comes to her bakery, she has done her best to keep it up to the standards that her aunt held it to. Perfecting her pastries and baked goods to an exact and being as warm as possible to customers was his mantra, and she’s been doing her absolute most since she graduated from Hogwarts and took over a few years earlier. The only thing she dislikes the most is the mess she creates every morning when prepping the day’s goods and that left by customers at the end of the day, but as long as she’s respected in her own shop, she’s fine with pretty much anything these days. Being relaxed in her own space makes her comfortable, where she previously wasn’t unless at her aunt’s home.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]London, England[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Octavian Vector – father, 53, con-artist, deceased (2021)
Elora Caldwell – mother, 30, employee at the bakery, “missing”/deceased (2006)

Septima Vector – grandmother, former Arithmancy professor, deceased
John Smith – grandfather, baker/former shop owner, deceased
Decima Vector – aunt/“adoptive mother”, 58 (twin to Octavian Sr.), owner of The Pi Pâtisserie

@octavian  – half-brother, 30, current Arithmancy professor
Ada Vector – half-sister, 16-17, current 6th year
René Vector – half-sister, 16-17, current 6th year
Isaac Vector – half-brother, 14-15, current 4th year
Alan Vector – half-brother, 14-15, current 4th year
Leonhard Vector – half-brother, 14-15, current 4th year
[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Mars – Havana Brown Cat[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Where to begin? The Vector family history in the last three decades was a complicated mess, only exasperated by Octavian Sr.’s drive towards young women and their coffers. A fact that took the second of the Vector children, Nova, much too long to realize. Ignorance was bliss, and very well hidden by her father’s twin sister, Decima, who was consistently burdened with her brother’s discarded follies. She would never see it that way and certainly never treated her nieces and nephews with disdain, but there had to have been a point where she simply gave up and accepted her role as guardian to them. Things maybe would have been under control if the elder Vector family members were still alive, but alas they were not. Octavian Sr. and Decima were the children of Septima Vector, a long time professor of Arithmancy at Hogwarts, and John Smith, the original owner of the bakery still being run by his daughter. 

As second born, Nova didn’t fully understand what life she had entered into until it was her turn to be turned over to her aunt. She has zero memories of her mother, Elora, left with only a few photographs and keepsakes. Her aunt has explained over the years that she didn’t even know her brother had remarried and had a second child until he showed up with Archie at the bakery, leaving him in her care. From there, there wasn’t much until she was left with her aunt while her parents went on a muggle cruise, her mother never to return. According to her father, she must have slipped off the deck in the night, none the wiser until it was far too late. Muggle authorities ruled it an accident, and that’s how her father reported it when he came home. At three years old, Nova didn’t understand it at all, and there was probably a point where she drove her aunt crazy asking where her mother was.

Her father basically disappeared after that. Not physically, but was definitely absent in the sense that he only rolled by when it was convenient for him to do so. Archie was in school so that left her with her aunt. She was distracted with learning how to bake and cook, something of a nifty trick that the Smith side of the family had picked up and sometimes passed down. Like her aunt and grandfather before her, Nova seemingly acquired this ‘ability’ as well. It wasn’t anything spectacular, but it was a goal to work towards as she grew up.

In 2009, there was suddenly a new mother. At six years old, she didn’t understand what that meant. All of her time was still spent living with her aunt, and there really wasn’t space for her with the new introduction of twin younger sisters. Nothing changed with her father, who was seemingly only interested in his new wife and children, which hurt Nova because she watched it hurt her older brother. The two of them were officially adopted by Decima Vector at this point, which only put on paper what had already been going on for years.

Just as quickly as the new step-mother arrived, she disappeared and was replaced by another, even younger woman. Looking back on it, Nova has realized exactly how pathetic her father was. The new one, Harmony, was the worst. She was barely older than Archie from the way her brother spoke of her, and Nova mimicked his views on the situation. They were unfortunately blessed with three more brothers, triplets, and she finally had enough understanding to really grasp how weird that was. Five younger siblings in the span of two years wasn’t exactly something she liked, and it only kept her father away from his already brief and scattered visits. There were enough times where she was brought around and looked after by Harmony, which she absolutely hated, because the woman tried to act like her mother. It was more like being babysat and playing house, in which she hated both even at eight.

Harmony remained though, which was a constant that Nova absolutely disliked whenever she wasn’t at school. It was her only reprieve, mostly because her step-mother was nosy enough to bug Decima at the bakery when she was bored and tired of looking after five toddlers. 

School was unbelievably welcome. While she couldn’t bake anything because the house elves did everything, she was finally able to do what she wanted to. It was here that she felt like she needed to excel at her studies, in the hopes that her father would look her way once or twice because of a good grade. Sorted into Ravenclaw, Nova spent so much time in the books that she almost forgot to make friends during her seven years at Hogwarts. She wasn’t anywhere close to being the best in her year, nor even in Ravenclaw, but that didn’t matter by the time she was ready to graduate. Decima had decided that the best path forward was to really work on the family ability, and one day, have Nova take over the bakery. She was overjoyed, so much that she didn’t even care that she had to spend a couple of years at Hogwarts watching over her youngest siblings.

She was old enough to understand by then that none of them were at fault for what their father had put them through. Harmony was equally a thorn in all of their sides, but she was easy enough to ignore most days. That was, until 2021 when an owl arrived at school. It said that there had been an accident, nothing new to her there, and that her father had died. She felt more for her younger siblings, who didn’t really understand what that meant yet, than she did over the death of Octavian Sr. There had been so little contact over the last few years that it she felt like she could finally breathe. She didn’t have to push herself to get noticed, and while that left her a little lost at first, there was already a plan in place for her future with her aunt and the bakery.

Her last year at Hogwarts was a relief. All she had to do was dodge Harmony’s annoying letters and help out her younger siblings, and then she was free from it all. Archie ended up teaching Arithmancy during her seventh year, which also happened to be one of the NEWT level classes she had already been signed up for. It made everything easier with all of her siblings there, and the release of graduation was even better, knowing that the younger ones would still have him around if they needed help.

Immediately after graduating, she went home and started working under Decima. Perfecting her inherited ability was easy enough, as it was something that she had been working on since she was little. Putting it into practice and dealing with customers the whole time though? That took some effort. She was used to being in the shop but it was different when she was working for herself. Years of watching her aunt at work certainly helped though, and it didn’t take long for her to start running most of the everyday tasks in her aunt’s stead.

The upheaval of the world around her didn’t go unnoticed. Nova liked to tell herself, as students died at Hogwarts and visiting schools were killed as they left the Triwizard Tournament that it would eventually end, just like her father’s reign did. It was a horrible way to cope with the uncertainty, but she was used to taking a deep breath and trucking on as if nothing had happened. Her ability to help those around her came in the form of baking, and that was what she continued to do as people were injured at the Quidditch Finals and the country was blanketed by Hag’s Fever. Whatever came next would most likely be met with the same attitude, at least until it affected her directly.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@colin     [/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]he/him [/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]26[/blockquote]
[/div][/div]