[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://data.whicdn.com/images/313089508/original.gif"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Samira Ali Warsame[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]/sæˈmiːrə ɑːli wɔ:sɔm'eɪ/[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Samira goes by "Sami" or "Sam" almost exclusively.[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]17
March 4, 2007[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Cisgender female; she/her pronouns[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Half-blood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Bisexual and monogamous, with a preference for women[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]9 inches, red oak, dragon heartstring core, pliant[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Alisha Boe[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Sami is 5'5" in height, with a slim build. Of mixed Somali and White British ethnicity, Sami has brown skin, although she is noticeably fairer than some of her Somali relatives. She has wavy dark brown hair and dark brown eyes, and her hair reaches not far past her shoulders. Sami has no significant scarring, though her ears are both pierced once on their lobes and she has marks from where she had tried to pierce a second set of lobe piercings. While Sami has no tattoos, either, she's considered them.

On most days, Sami can be found in her Hogwarts uniform, typically with a few infractions. It's not uncommon, for example, to see her shirt unbuttoned lower than it should be and/or her Gryffindor tie slightly looser at her collar. When not in uniform, she prefers to wear Muggle clothing and follow their fashion trends, especially since she lives in an area that has a considerable Muggle population. She enjoys playing around with makeup when she gets the chance, as well, and is also talented at Somali-style henna art.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts; Gryffindor[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Seventh-year[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Summer nights, jelly slugs, candlelight, [s]firewhisky[/s] butterbeer, reading about people's bizarre conspiracy theories, nail polish, Charms, sambuus, spontaneous adventures, henna art[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Heavy coats, soggy cereal, letting people down, body odor, Herbology, wearing her hair up, gore, the process of coming out, bleak winter days, early mornings[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Sami's greatest desire is to find love and to explore the world with that person by her side.

In the short term, though, she's not really sure what to do with her life once she's finished school.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Frankincense, firewhisky, and white chocolate[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Sami fears that she'll never find another relationship like her first love and that she will end up dying alone.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]
[b]energetic:[/b]

While she hasn't been formally diagnosed as having ADHD, her primary school teachers suggested that it was a possibility. Sami has always been on the hyperactive side, whether running around as a child or just fidgeting with whatever she happens to have on hand, she's a very kinesthetic learner and is usually doing [i]something[/i], though she's never been hugely into sports. 

[b]impulsive:[/b] 

Similarly, Sami can be impulsive, maybe more so than she would care to admit. Especially when she was younger, she did a lot of things because she thought that they would make her look cool, like drinking alcohol and smoking. She's fortunately avoided any major consequences for her actions, detentions notwithstanding. Now that she's older, rather than looking to the "cool kids", Samira is more likely the one to be doing the peer-pressuring of those younger than she is.

[b]rebellious:[/b]

Having been at Hogwarts for years, Sami knows what she can and can't get away with doing, and she still occasionally tests her limits. She's used to getting in trouble, so it doesn't really bother her, though she'll try to talk her way out of it. She sneaks in alcohol and other contraband for parties when she can, though the former is easier for her to get than it once was, being seventeen.

[b]fiery:[/b]

Maybe it's a Gryffindor thing, but Sami is a spitfire. Things can get heated with her pretty quickly, especially if it's a confrontation with someone whom she doesn't like. Along with her impulsive nature, she tends to throw her whole self into things, especially when she's genuinely attracted to someone.

[b]flirty:[/b]

Particularly when under the influence of alcohol, Samira can be a flirt. She's very touchy and affectionate when she's had enough firewhisky, and it's not uncommon for her to try to go even further with others.

[b]tenacious:[/b]

Sami is determined, and maybe too much so. Once she decides to do something, she's not easily swayed. That doesn't mean that she thinks things through as much as she should, though, because she certainly doesn't.

[b]insecure:[/b]

Contrary to her image and behavior at school, Sami is closeted to her family, with the exception of her slightly older cousin, Yasmiin. Because most of her family (on her father's side, anyway) is made up of relatively conservative Muslims, she's terrified of what their reaction would be to her being bisexual.

[b]secretive:[/b]

Because she doesn't feel that she can be herself around her family, Samira is similarly guarded about her home life while at school. She's never had any of her school friends home to visit, and she tries to keep her "two lives" (as she sees them) as separate as she can.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Tower Hamlets, London, England[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]
(Note that some of the names here are following Somali naming conventions.)

[b]mother:[/b]
Nicola Pugh Warsame, 40, Pupillus Domum social worker, half-blood witch

[b]father:[/b]
Ali Warsame, 41, Accidental Magic Reversal Squad member, half-blood wizard

[b]younger brother:[/b]
Aaden Warsame, 9, primary school student, half-blood wizard

[b]paternal grandmother:[/b]
Saado Hassan Barkhad, 63, retired secretary and former homemaker, half-blood witch

[b]paternal grandfather:[/b]
Warsame Abadir Abadir, 1956-1991, half-blood wizard (presumed pure-blood), former employee of Somalia's magical government, deceased 

[b]paternal aunt:[/b]
Nasteho Warsame, 44, occupation open, half-blood witch, resides in Minneapolis, Minnesota, USA

[b]paternal cousin:[/b]
Yasmiin Warsame, 19, WADA student, half-blood witch, from Minneapolis, Minnesota, USA[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Samira's history begins with the arrival of her father and his family to Britain from Somalia in 1992. After his father—an employee of Somalia's magical government—was killed in a Muggle-related conflict, Samira's grandmother, widowed, sought resettlement for herself and her children abroad, which was granted to them by the Ministry of Magic in Britain. The family arrived in East London, where they settled into their new lives. Unable to speak fluent English at the time, Samira's grandmother took a job with a local Somali-run business in order to earn a living.

Samira's aunt, Nasteho, was educated at Hogwarts upon their arrival, although she was placed in the first year, rather than the second, because of the differences in schooling between her small school in Somalia and Hogwarts.

After some time spent in the local Muggle primary school, Samira's father, Ali, began school at Hogwarts in 1994. He was Sorted into Hufflepuff, where he experienced the Triwizard Tournament in his first year. Of course, the possibility that Lord Voldemort had returned to terrorize the magical world put a not-insignificant damper on things as he continued his education, as did Umbridge, Albus Dumbledore's death, and the Carrows' control over the school.

Although Ali considered leaving Hogwarts at the end of the 1998-1999 year once he had sat his OWLs, his mother urged him to remain in school to make something of himself. He did, and it was the following year that he met Nicola Pugh, a fellow Hufflepuff student a few years younger than he was. While they only reconnected once Nicola had left school, they fell in love with one another and began to date. Not long after that came marriage, which was followed by the birth of their daughter, Samira.

Raised in a multicultural and multiracial family, Samira's upbringing was difficult to categorize into neat little boxes—not that she really cared to. While her mother was blonde, fair-skinned, and blue-eyed, Samira was never too bothered by it. Most of her friends in primary school weren't white, either, though it was frustrating when well-meaning people who looked like her mother would assume that she had been adopted if the two of them were out and about without her father there.

Still, she grew up closer to her father's side of the family than her mother's, mostly because she lived with her parents and grandmother, from whom she learned how to make Somali dishes and how to create body art using henna paste.

It was never kept from Samira, either, that she was a witch, and she looked forward to the day when she would be able to go to Hogwarts. Her parents didn't talk much about what the wizarding school had been like for them, not wanting their daughter to be afraid of what had become a peaceful place or for her to try to repress her abilities.

As with most magical children, Samira had her share of problems with accidental magic before she had gone off to Hogwarts to learn how to control it. Luckily, she was a talkative and imaginative little girl, anyway, so her teachers sometimes assumed that she was exaggerating things for attention. At home, though, her parents and grandmother were pleased—even if she did once decapitate her baby brother's toy rabbit.

Eventually, Samira got her Hogwarts letter, and she was thrilled. She headed off to school, where she chose to go by "Sami", and was Sorted into Gryffindor from the moment that the Sorting Hat touched the top of her head. Hogwarts was the greatest place that she had ever been, and she immediately dove into life at the school. She was quick to make friends with some of her fellow students and go on adventures around the castle and grounds with them—even if it meant getting into a little bit of trouble.

By the end of her first year, Sami had also made friends with some of the students in the years above her. Among them was a Slytherin girl named Nefertiti Bulstrode, whom Sami was keen on impressing. Nefertiti was in the year above her own, but she was a Metamorphmagus and already a Beater for the Slytherin Quidditch team, which made her extraordinarily cool.

Sure, there had been a few little embellishments that she had added to her own background to make herself seem equally exciting to be around, but Sami was happy to have found a friend like Nefe. She had had friends before, of course, but she thought that the Slytherin was even [I]best[/I] friend material.

As time passed, Sami realized that maybe her feelings towards the older girl weren't just friendly. Maybe there was something more than friendship there, though she wondered if it was all just in her head. How was she supposed to know if she liked girls for real, and what if Nefe didn't? She didn't want to ruin their friendship because of that!

Reluctantly, in her fourth year, Sami confessed her feelings for Nefe, and she was even more surprised to find that those feelings were reciprocal. Afraid that rumors would start about them, Sami tried to keep things on the down-low for a while before she and Nefe made their relationship official. While she wasn't very close to all of Nefe's friends, she was sure that things would work out. She had a [I] girlfriend[/I], and she got more and more comfortable with saying that—to everyone except her cousin, Yasmiin, whom she told a short time later.

Their relationship continued, as strong as ever, until around the start of Nefe's seventh year and Sami's sixth. Things began to slow down, and Sami could sense that something wasn't "there" between them anymore. If there was someone else, then she wished that her girlfriend would have been honest with her. Samira's fears that Nefe was cheating on her led them to break up, and the Gryffindor spent the remainder of the year doing everything possible to avoid her ex.

As her sixth year came to an abrupt end, Sami was ready to move on—or, at least, that was what she tried to tell herself. With her cousin, Yasmiin, arriving at WADA and the news about Ilvermorny, she hoped that the American influx would provide her with enough of a distraction to make it through her last year of school.[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Not unlike that of the previous generation, Samira's time at Hogwarts has been full of all sorts of strange happenings, especially. For her, the deaths of politicians were one thing, considering that there was probably all sorts of insider information happening behind the scenes to which the general public wouldn't be privy. (That was basically how politics, especially at its upper levels, worked, wasn't it?)

It became concerning when Muggle-borns began getting killed right and left, but, again, it wasn't exactly the first time that someone had had problems with Muggle-borns. Whoever it was would get caught, naturally, and get thrown into Azkaban for life—and the rest of the world could move on with theirs.

When Elaine revealed herself as the murderer and the kidnappings happened, Sami had operated under the assumption that—now knowing who was responsible for the terror at Hogwarts—the Ministry would go and catch her.

As time went by and [I]that[/I] still didn't happen, Sami grew concerned. The one thing that kept her mind at ease was that everyone knew who Elaine was and what she had done. By confessing to the killings, she had effectively put a target on her back. That probably hadn't been her greatest move, in Sami's opinion, though any concern that Elaine might have been on her way back to finish what she had started seemed invalid by the end of the Triwizard Tournament.

The explosions of the Durmstrang ship and Beauxbatons carriage had been devastating, but a different group—and not Elaine—claimed responsibility for that one. Just as everyone, Samira included, was trying to make sense of it, they learned of yet another complication: Ilvermorny had been vandalized, and many of its students would be coming to Hogwarts.

Samira wasn't too sure how that one would go, especially so soon after foreign students had already been killed so suddenly and horrendously, but she had reason to remain positive. Her cousin, Yasmiin, had gone to Ilvermorny, too, so at least she could fill her in on what there was to know.

In the meantime, there was also another hiccup. Harry Potter—easily the most famous wizard alive, if not in all of recent memory—was missing and then presumed dead, followed into the autumn by a string of what were possibly serial killings committed against wizards and Muggles alike. The seeming randomness of the latest deaths has Samira on edge more than she'd like to admit, mainly because she's been able to find explanations for everything else to put her mind at ease.

Now, she's just trying to get through her last few months of school, even if she has no idea what's awaiting her on the other side.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@audrey    [/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]21[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]US/Canada Central/Eastern[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]I've been here![/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@maxima, @parvati, @oona, @honey, @kaylee, @ezekiel, @clarence, @priscilla, @tamatha[/blockquote][/div][/div]