[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;background-color:rgb(182, 182, 180);border:4px solid rgb(182, 182, 180);border-radius:10px;font-family:georgia;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][span style="font-size:10px;"][div align="center"][img src="http://38.media.tumblr.com/43c93520c3ef660eef2465c73731df9b/tumblr_nes1c46Skc1rc8qr9o2_500.gif" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]hello there, my name is [b]victoire weasley[/b] but you can call me [b]Vic[/b].[/span][span style="font-size:10px;"]&nbsp;i'm [/span][b style="font-size:10px;"]22[/b][span style="font-size:10px;"] so that makes me a [/span][b style="font-size:10px;"]alumni[/b][span style="font-size:10px;"]&nbsp;year at Hogwarts, where I reside in [b]Slytherin[/b][/span][span style="font-size:10px;"]&nbsp;house. You could say I'm [b]ambitious, cunning &amp; resourceful[/b][/span][span style="font-size:10px;"]&nbsp;but I personally think that I am [b]intelligent, stubborn and loving[/b][/span][span style="font-size:10px;"]. People say I look a lot like [/span][b style="font-size:10px;"]emma stone[/b][span style="font-size:10px;"], but I don't really see it...[/span]

[div style="font-size:10px;" align="center"][font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][i][b]&nbsp;victoire apolline weasley[/b][/i][/font][/font][/div]
[b style="font-size:10px;"][i]nickname:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]Vic[/blockquote][b style="font-size:10px;"][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]Twenty two[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"][i]date of birth:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]May 2nd,2001 [/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"][i]gender:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]witch[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"][i]blood status:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]halfblood, 1/8 veela[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"][i]sexuality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]demisexual[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"][i]house:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]slytherin[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"][i]occupation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]unemployed[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"][i]wand:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]11” rosewood, with a Veela hair core, donated by her Grandmother Apolline, just like her mothers wand except a little longer. It's sort of a family tradition.[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"][i]playby:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]emma stone[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"][i]appearance:[/i] [/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]Vic is fairly tall at 5'8". She has light blonde hair from her veela side.&nbsp;She has a lot of business clothes because she used to work in the Ministry, but when she is off duty, as she is now, she wears comfortable t shirts, joggers, and cute but sporty and casual clothing.[/blockquote][div style="font-size:10px;" align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman" style="font-size:10px;"][font size="6"][b][i]personality[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b style="font-size:10px;"][i]likes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"] politics,&nbsp;family, friends, respect, supporting others, fighting back, making decisions, strong career moves, France.[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"][i]dislikes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]being seen as only a pretty face, people not taking her seriously,&nbsp;losing important positions and relationships, Elaine and her cronies, having to step down.
 [/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"][i]erised:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]since achieving her life goal of becoming the minister for magic,&nbsp;Vic really doesn't have a new big goal set yet. For now, her desire is just to finish getting better and get back in the fight. [/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"][i]amortentia:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]roses, popcorn, rain, wine [/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"][i]boggart:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]her friends and family being mad when they find out where she's been, losing teddy, royal or Odette, not being useful to the cause anymore.
 [/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"][i]overall personality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]Vic is a strong, independent woman, with ambition that could take her to the moon if she wanted to go there. She achieved her lifelong goal of becoming the minister for magic, which goes to show just how ambitious she is. She is so career driven, that she ended her 2 year long relationship with Teddy during her 7th year so she could focus on her studies and then her career afterwards. They have since gotten back together, but her career as the minister did take a toll on the relationship in many ways, considering how much focus she was put on being the best minister she could be.

Even though she's ambitious, resourceful and career obsessed, Vic has a lot of love to give, and just has trouble showing it sometimes. She is madly in love with Teddy, aggressively protective of her family, and would die for her best friends. She knows she hasn't been the best friend considering she's been working so hard and leaving people behind, but she loves them no matter what.

Over the past year Vic has learned a lot about her priorities. She's become more invested in things of an emotional nature. She still isn't the best at showing her feelings out right, but she is learning. She has always been so set on not letting anyone see her as just a pretty face, that she has often treated people with business tone and harshness to combat her veela charm.

Vic is incredibly stubborn, and has a really hard time doing things in any way other than her own. As the minister for magic she learned she had to work with a lot of department heads, which she liked, but it was hard when they had different opinions from her own. She's also incredibly stubborn in the fact that she hasn't told anyone but Teddy and her healers that she has been sick for the past four months and that is why she stepped down from the minister position. She has been stubborn in that regard because she refuses to make any of their lives harder by giving them something to worry about when it comes to her.

If there is one thing Vic hates, it's having nothing to work towards. And at this point in time, she doesn't have any plans for her career because it was put on hold so suddenly. She didn't even know if she was going to make it through the last four months, let alone what to do afterwards. Now that her health is finally on the upkeep she is struggling with what to do next. She's becoming easily frustrated and agitated, being a little more snappy than her usual self, and not thinking as hard before she speaks. She'll get back to her normal well thought-out, well put together self eventually, she hopes.[/blockquote][div align="center" style="font-size:10px;"]________________________________________________________[/div][font style="font-size:10px;" face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personal history[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b style="font-size:10px;"][i]mother:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]Fleur Weasley, 45, ¼ Veela, Witch[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"][i]father:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]William Weasley, 52, curse-breaker for Gringotts Bank[/blockquote]
[b style="font-size:10px;"][i]siblings:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]Dominique, 17
Louis, 16[/blockquote][b style="font-size:10px;"][i]pets:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]A little wiener dog named Walter[/blockquote][b style="font-size:10px;"][i]history:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]Victoire has lived a charmed life with a big family and everyone knowing her name since the day she was born. Her mother was famous for competing in the Tri Wizard tournament and her father was an important piece in fighting the war against Voldemort. She was also Harry Potters niece, which warranted even more attention. She was the oldest of the Weasley clan cousins, and the press has been reporting on the major events of her life since day one. Victoire grew to be used to it, but didn't particularly seek it out. From a young age, though, she figured that if people were watching her she may as well use that for positive change.

She quickly grew to love politics and learned the ins and outs of social cues. Her mother was a big part of that. Fluer was a loving mother and an aggressively supportive wife, and she cared for her family fiercely. Still, she did expect them to act their best in front of important people.

Victoire wasn’t at all surprised when she was sorted into Slytherin house. Her father, the curse breaker, taught her early on that being resourceful and ambitious were two of the most important things in life, and she took that to heart. Many gasped at the sound of the name Weasley being in the same sentence as the house Slytherin. She was the first of this Weasley generation, and therefore broke the trail of Gryffindors.

School was an important time for Vic, and she found herself getting more and more involved in school politics, her education and her dreams for the future. She worked hard to be top of her class, and was Prefect and Head Girl while she was there. It was early on when she decided she wanted to be part of the Ministry, though she wanted to be both an auror and on the more political side of things. 

She dated Teddy Lupin for two years before breaking it off in her seventh. She felt like she was losing focus of her goals and ambitions, and that's why she ended things. 

She spent a lot of her time comparing the two and decided, a little after graduation, that she would continue in the Aurour-In-Training program and use what she learned to get in with the Ministers office. She served as an Auror for a year and a half before she finally felt ready to take on the application for Junior Assistant to the Minister. 

She was in that position under Minsiter Cain. Then he was killed in December of 2022, and for a little while no one was officially minister. However, in the desperate times Vic was elected. She was the minister for magic. She held the position for a year, just when it seemed things couldn't get any worse. Elaine revealed herself at the attacks on April first, 2023, and Victoire had several missing teenagers on her hands. The aurors and order sent in a rescue team, and all but one made it out alive. Then there was an attack on Kings Cross, where Royal was injured and an auror died. 

She was against allowing the tri wizard tournament to commence, but she was out voted. She attended the first task, but not the second or the Yule ball. She decided to spend time with Teddy instead. However, that's when she started to get sick.

It was subtle at first, but then careened into chaos quickly. She had to step down without warning, Hermione Granger taking her place. She disappeared, Teddy by her side, being treated privately and not telling anyone what was wrong. If they asked, she just said she was overwhelmed and wanted to focus on her relationship. Two things that weren't common for Victoire Weasley. 

She is finally starting to feel better, and is working toward being honest about what's been going on... And trying to find a new future.[/blockquote][div style="font-size:10px;" align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font style="font-size:10px;" face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]alias[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b style="font-size:10px;"][i]name:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"] Suzie[/blockquote][b style="font-size:10px;"][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]26[/blockquote][b style="font-size:10px;"][i]time zone:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]est[/blockquote][b style="font-size:10px;"][i]reference:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]been here many moons[/blockquote][b style="font-size:10px;"][i]other characters:[/i][/b]
[blockquote style="font-size:10px;"]River Lydia Andy Ethan Dominic Adonia Karen Callisto [/blockquote][/div][/div]