[div align="center"][b]TW/CW:[/b] drugs, depression and various other states of minds [/div]
[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://www.gotceleb.com/wp-content/uploads/photos/zendaya-photoshoot/in-manhattan-bridge/Zendaya:-Photoshoot-in-Manhattan-Bridge--06.jpg"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]prudence "rue" oria weiss[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]proo-duns oh-ree-ah [a href="https://www.pronouncenames.com/weiss"]v-ay-s[/a][/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]rue and only rue.[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]21
26th december 2003[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]female/gender neutral, she/her, they/them, leaning more towards non-binary/gender-fludity, but still confused. (switches between pronouns)[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]pureblood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]bisexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]the wand is made of plum wood and has a core of pegasus feather, 10 inches long and is swishy
[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]zendaya[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]pretty much identical to playby, 5"10 in height, slim physique, prefers to wear comfortable casual clothes, or fun party-like over formal wear. sports a few ear piercings, and a small nose ring. hair is usually messy and wavy, or can be found sported with a hat. makeup can either be dramatic or minimal, but rue is never seen without a scatter of glitter somewhere on their face. sometimes can be seen with glasses, depending on the day.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]ilvermorny: wampus [1st-6th]
hogwarts: slytherin [7th][/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]graduated, 2022.
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote][b]previously[/b]: potioneer apprentice & part time night teller at ripam de sanguinem
[b]currently[/b]: dark potioneer & black market merchant[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]potions, dark arts, being referred to as they/them/their over she, muggle movies, how fascinated their parents were with muggle society (before father's death), siblings, alcohol/drugs/potions/contraband that make them feel good, smoking, non-verbal magic, wandless magic, travelling, staying up all night, expressing ones self through appearance[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]isolation, how quiet the family home felt after their dad died, her current relationship with her mother, the thought of her siblings falling into a similar life like hers, small spaces, bright lights[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]even though she fears herself and the life she lives, a part of rue wishes to become the best dark potioneer ever. being the best meaning she finds ease in selling to members of the purifiers and/or to silly minors who stick their noses inn the wrong places. another part of her wishes she'd get clean. [/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]rain, coffee, cinnamon[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]herself, living a life of addiction for life, her sister becoming like her, her friends/sister/family discovering what she does (working with some purifiers, selling to minors), death above all / death caused by the things that's killing her.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote][i]cunning/crafty/sly, understanding, sensitive, thoughtful, stubborn, witty, discreet[/i]

when rue was a child, she was entirely different to how she was now. she was full of joy and energy, enjoyed the lighter things in life and didn't think of all the restrictions that she was faced with. as she grew, like any ordinary person, rue began to change. she refused to listen if she was called by her full name: prudence and she enjoyed the rebellious side of things. while she had a growing interest in potions and creating them, rue only took the interest seriously after her father died. it was then when her personality took a dip for the worse as rue grew to become more [i]crafty[/i] and [i]sly[/i]. selling illegal 'dark' potions wasn't easy in hogwarts, but through rue's words and actions of manipulation, -- as well as help from mina -- she managed to make her way through. because of it, it also proved how [i]discreet[/i] the weiss girl was about things, always planning things with care and plotting out routes of action if she were ever caught.

above this, rue is also [i]stubborn[/i] and [i]witty[/i], as she's always unwilling to change her mind on things, depending on the context as a whole. her wit comes from her late-father, who always found humour or dry humour just from the top of his head. the weiss can also be described as [i]thoughtful[/i] and [i]understanding[/i], mainly towards her friends instead of clientele. rue tends to be the listening ear and advice giver for her friend's dilemma's, especially for mina -- after meeting her in their seventh year together. but above all, rue is incredibly [i]sensitive[/i]. she hates the person she has become, which has impacted many of her relationships, including the one with her mother -- after losing her father but she knows she has nothing else, nothing that doesn't make her feel like a burden.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]new orleans, usa[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote][b]mother[/b]: ____ weiss (née bennett), 46, head healer of spell damage at st mungos
[b]father[/b]: oskar elias weiss, deceased after rue's 17th birthday

siblings:
[b]sister[/b]: W___ O___ weiss, 17-20 (could also potentially be a twin?)
[b]brother[/b]: O____ weiss, 15-17, open hogwarts house[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]thorn, eagle owl[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]winter of 2003 had been a miraculous time for the weiss family, to rue's mothers sheer memory of it anyway. by christmas day, rue's mother had fallen into labour and in the early hours of the twenty-sixth, prudence oria weiss, first born of the weiss family screamed her way into the world. born into a mixed family of african american and german, rue grew up following two cultures in the home. her father, an auror from germany would recite stories of his time as a young scholar in durmstrang and how germany and europe used to be, while her mother, a head healer in the small hospital for wizards in new orleans, would speak of the new orleans culture and how different holidays or different events would bring all the folks, regardless of blood purity together by the bayou. for a few years, rue grew up as a happy pureblood, learning how the wizarding society differed themselves from the no-maj side of things. when her younger siblings were born -- two years between them -- she saw the responsibility it took to be an older sister, and remained thoughtful around them, taking their needs into consideration as well as her own like any ordinary sister.

by eleven, rue had been accepted into american's own wizarding school: ilvermorny and on her first evening there, when her name was called for the weiss to step upon the symbol of the Gordian Knot, the roar of the [b]wampus[/b] invited her in. for her first few years, rue struggled to find her place in the wizarding school. she didn't know what she liked the most or even liked the least. she was an average student all around and had a small handful of friends that she fit in with. but by her fifth year, rue finally found her place, the thing that gave her euphoria even outside of term time and that was potions. she enjoyed the difficulty of it as a whole, how perfect each measurement of an ingredient needed to be in order to create the perfect potion. sure, she had made plenty in classes in all of her years in ilvermorny, but rue remembered the moment she made her first potion without a professor's supervision. it was the draught of peace, and at first the weiss believed she had failed, until the sight of silvery vapour was enough to confirm her success.

from fifth year onwards, rue made it her goal to prove to her parents becoming a potioneer was a possible life-time job. and with rue's age growing, so did her skill. by her sixth year, she was the best in her classes (ones vital for her ultimate goal anyway) and nothing could take that away from her. until...tragedy struck. it was shortly after the start of rue's sixth year when it happened, her father who was an auror had been severely injured during a mission. at first, he had been placed in intensive care before the drawn conclusion was he would be bed ridden for six months or so. there was hope he would recover quickly and so, the weiss family didn't worry. until he simply got worse. his health was declining and each member of the family knew rue's father would die soon. it didn't add up though, with the spells and potions, heaps of medication he was put under but yet, his health wasn't getting better. 

during the winter break was when rue grew worse. she couldn't stand seeing her father in the state he was in but once he was dosed with his daily amounts of potions...he felt bliss. for a short period of time anyway. and as curious as any sixth year could be, rue wanted to forget the pain she felt daily whenever she saw her father. so an hour or so after the elder man had fallen asleep, rue took his potion. a few drops on her tongue was all she needed but even her mother wasn't aware rue had taken it that night. shortly after rue's seventeenth birthday, oskar elias weiss died and it hit the family like a ton of bricks. it was abrupt, concluded it happened over night in his sleep and immediately the family began to mourn. christmas was ultimately ruined. out of everything he had wished for, rue's father wanted to be buried back home in germany, considering he hadn't been home in...seventeen years. it was this course of action that stirred up the move. at first, all the weiss children refused, and even some of the elder members of the family that lived nearby refused to allow it, but rue's mother was ruthless. she wanted to do what her deceased husband wanted.

by february, rue as well as her siblings had settled into a small home nearby her father's old village. her love for potions had increased as well as her craving needs for them also. she didn't want to admit she was slowly following the life of an addict, especially as she didn't understand herself. until september 2021, rue mourned with her family, distracting herself with the odd drop or two of a calming potion, hidden discreetly from her mother and siblings. while settling into europe and by september of the same year, rue felt ready enough to return to school, except this time it was completely and utterly different from ilvermorny. durmstrang didn't seem right enough for rue to attend so instead the choice of hogwarts was all she had. she enrolled privately, where she was housed into [b]slytherin[/b], just because a strange hat placed her there. the same way the weiss felt in her early years of ilvermorny, rue felt out of place, a kid who knew a lot about potions and such, how to brew them, ingest them and breathe out pure euphoria from them...but didn't have many friends to express it to. until she met someone. a certain someone.

mina oliveira hadn't always been a fan favourite. hell, professors only allowed her to graduate simply because they wanted to get rid of her. she was failing in her third year...and her fifth year and after receiving warnings from both years, by the sixth, the professors had given up. when rue met mina however, it was as if things fit into place, like they had been friends for years even if it were only a few short terms. rue was smart about what she wanted, and what she wanted to achieve. and so did mina. so when the oliveria caught the weiss selling her first editions on her own twist on the classic potion: pepperup, to a few minors, they kept things secret and worked hand in hand. rue brewed the upper, which she eventually compared to the muggle drug 'speed' and the two of them tested together. rue knew it was stupid, trialing her own product, but when a pain hurt like no other, the weiss would choose the option of feeling numb over everything. 

by graduation, rue was sure she had sold her upper and even testers of new...darker potions to almost every elite kid in seventh year. everyone was responsible with their own weight and if caught, actions were ensured it wouldn't trail back to her. well. mina made sure of that anyway, threats weren't entirely rue's strong point. unlike many other seventh years, rue had no aspiration to fight for a top quality job or internship, except the one thing she worked hard to prove to her parents as a younger student. an apprenticeship as a potioneer under a small firm was enough to guarantee her mother's happiness. though, rue had compromised with the firm to begin her apprenticeship whenever she planned to return from her trip back home to america, in her home town of new orleans, which begun in the early summer of 2022. rue stuck by mina's side, the two knowing nothing other than drinking, partying and an excessive amount of no-maj drugs and potions on rue's behalf right up until rue decided it was time for her to head back to europe, to finally start the apprenticeship.

shortly after her secret recruitment under the purifiers and sudden increase of progress under the apprenticeship, which was meant to take months of development, harsh gossip got out that led to the weiss girl to drop it after a few short months and take up the dark side of potions. she enjoyed brewing potions like the next person, but instead enjoyed weaving in the small delights that muggles enjoyed -- the same delights she had managed to steal off the clueless souls back in new orleans -- with the advancement of magic. her first creation, the twist on pepperup had been modified once more, dozens of practice spells and different ingredients ensuring the success to create a potion with a psychedelic effect to it. it was one of the first of rue's many creations. 

creating potions for herself or even the purifiers had been rue's hobby as of recent, along with selling such contraband items at the black market. it was how she was able to make a scrape of a living and live in a nice apartment after all. since her father's death, her relationship with her mother and siblings declined. she rarely saw them now, considering she had moved fairly far from them, and her siblings still attended hogwarts. matters only grew worse with each moment she spent by her mother's side, especially during holidays. the elder weiss speculated rue was an addict, and while it was something rue refused to own up to, deep down, rue agreed. [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]while rue felt sympathy for the lives lost in the student attacks, they were rather strangely interested in the power the attackers held. by then they had graduated hogwarts, spent what felt like the longest time in america by mina's side and their apprenticeship career in potioneering had started off on a good foot by early 2023. the following attacks, as cruel as they were, were enough for the weiss to seek out the purifiers, wanting the power of the purifiers for their own protection. as well as to gain different skills from other potioneers. 

it was odd when they was first recruited, only having sold small quantities of potion uppers to minors back in hogwarts and never seemingly doing bad things aside from that...and their own intake of their product. but with new-given power, advancements in previous skills, new accomplices and accesses to resources -- gossip had gotten out in rue's apprenticeship firm, many speaking of how they were interested in the dark arts of potioneering and had experimented with prohibited potions. it only reminded rue of their past when they simply wanted to make extra pocket change and have reasons to test their own product...rue couldn't stand in the face of failure or the truth and dropped their apprenticeship, taking a liking into dark potioneering.

ilvermorny's destruction only brought more uncertainty and sadnesss for rue, and while they didn't graduate from the wizarding school, it still held a close spot in their heart. though, the day of the dragon attacks proved how much rue had changed in the past few months, considering they participated behind the scenes, providing potions and contraband for the purifiers for the ultimate infiltration. and from the headlines alone, it seemed things went to plan.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]haise. ofc.[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]!!!! they/them !!!![/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]can i be twenty now[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]gmt[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]trapped[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]dana, edrik, zen, sari, jiyu, yvonne, bryelle, ares, flora, veronica, miles, calliope[/blockquote][/div][/div]