[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://github.com/sarcasticmoth/proboards-templates/blob/main/pics/cade/File_137.gif?raw=true" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]cade owen woodward[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]k-ay-duh  | oh-when | wuh-ud-wurd[/blockquote][b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote][b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]30
August 2, 1995[/blockquote][b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]He
he/him/his[/blockquote][div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Half-Blood[/blockquote][b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Straight[/blockquote][b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]Black Walnut, Unicorn Hair, 13 inches, firm[/blockquote][b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Henry Cavill[/blockquote][b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Cade looks much like his playby, he stands at 6’1” and has dark hair that is naturally curly. Often it is kept short and groomed but at times he has been known to grow it out and the curls become more apparent. He also typically sports some stubble but has also been seen with a full beard or even clean-shaven. He dresses very casually but if he has to “dress-up” then he is meticulous about it.&nbsp;[/blockquote][div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts - Ravenclaw[/blockquote][b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduated[/blockquote][b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]2013 - 2015: The Daily Prophet Intern
2015 - 2022: The Daily Prophet Reporter
2022 - 2024: Junior Assistant Editor of the Daily Prophet
2024 - present: Senior Assistant Editor of the Daily Prophet[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Reading
Writing
Socializing
A Challenge
Mai Tai’s
Cooking
Wine
Traveling
Gossip
[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Lies
Coffee
Someone wasting his time
Bullies
People that are late
Picky eaters&nbsp;[/blockquote][b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]To write an award-winning story, to have a family, to help his sister[/blockquote][b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]chicken soup, cherry blossom, peaches[/blockquote][b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Failure, not being able to help someone when he was able to[/blockquote][b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]There is a fine line one can walk regarding lawful or neutral good behavior and intent. The law and rules are there to guide people in the “right” direction and to also support good behavior and actions but also discourage anything else. However, the interpretation of said rules is still up to the individual. In contrast, an effort can be well-meaning and have a good result even if a law was bent or broken. Cade is a well-meaning person, truly in his heart, he wants good things for people that deserve it, and if there is something he can do to encourage that, he will do so. His ideas were instilled in him young as his mother formally was a Report for the Daily Prophet. And even though she focused on Magical Sports, it didn’t stop her from ensuring her son knew that writing pieces for the public was a big responsibility. It was something that must be taken seriously. It was a big responsibility since it was public-facing. These were ideas that stuck with him and drove who he would become when he was older. But that brought up another thing when he’s investigating and writing, he has his network of contacts and individuals who he knows would know something, but he protects them. 

When the sorting hat was placed on Cade’s head, it was torn between Ravenclaw and Gryffindor. His sister had both been Gryffindors, and they were both headstrong people. Cade honestly pitied whoever got in his oldest’s sister’s way because she had the drive and energy of an oncoming freight train. While his middle sister was more headstrong in a chaotic way. Cade wondered where he fell in that spectrum. He knew he wanted to do something good in the world. He’d already gotten knocked over on the train for standing up for another first-year against an older student, but he’d felt it was worth it. That sounded like a Gryffindor, but at the same time, it wasn’t. Cade was a loyal person, but not the blanket loyalty for [i]all[/i] good that one might see or have heard of from famous Wizards and Witches. Still, he focused more on the [i]ideas[/i] brought to him. The idea that a student is picked on because of their name or background or (as he found later) were werewolves or some kind of marginalized people was ridiculous to him. The Sorting Hat yelled Ravenclaw. 

Cade never struggled to find his inner confidence or voice. He gets along with almost anybody and enjoys socializing with people. He is very personable and pleasant to be around. However, natural self-confidence and charisma tend to attract people in general but he was very comfortable. While Law Enforcement wasn’t a goal, it didn’t mean he didn’t want to see justice where it could be brought. But aside from being a people-person, he is also a patience one. He knows when to wait and when to go, but his issue is just stopping himself at a point. When he began his reporting career, he had a problem with letting go of threads that weren’t worth the time and chasing every lead because he had a goal, and he could see it and needed to get there. His sister calls him a workaholic, and that isn’t that far off the mark. He does socialize but would instead be working and chasing down whatever path the leads bring him toward and finishing his story. This has brought him to various parts of the world. He enjoys the adventure of traveling. All this experience and exposure have only added to his ability to observe people and even read them a bit. He notices when someone’s face changes and shoving down some emotion they are trying to hide. 

But of course, with all the positive traits come the negative ones. Cade is a workaholic who has trouble letting go of something that he needs to. There is always something driving him to keep pushing because he might get it. His Editor has had to get in his way several times because he couldn’t let go of a story. After all, that lack of closure never sat well with Cade. When he loses his composure, he tends to get ahead of himself in the sense that he likes to be right and feels that he knows what he is talking about when he is talking about it. His older sister finds him overbearing at times, and Cade sees it as she doesn’t want to see the light and see the right way to do something. It’s not a matter of control but more a matter of “listen to me because I know what I’m talking about,” or at least he thinks he does on some issues. And then you have the curse of every reporter. He likes to know what is going on, and whatever he can hear, he will listen to or sometimes go out of his way to find out. 

[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Surrey, England[/blockquote][b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Cecilia Woodward, Mother: Former Daily Prophet Quidditch Reporter - Retired
Owen Woodward, Father: Former Potioneer - Retired
Elena Woodward, 31 - Older Sister
Catherine Woodward, 35 -Older Sister[/blockquote][b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Snowy Owl named Momus[/blockquote][b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Cade was born when the Wizard World was entering a frightening state, and it remained that way until he was about three years old. At that point, everything started to feel safe again for his family (according to what his father recalls), and life went forward. He was born as the third and last child of Cecilia and Owen Woodward. His mother had been a Quidditch Reporter for the Daily Prophet and his father, a local Potioneer. His childhood was relatively normal. Both his parents had attended Hogwarts and had been witnesses to the actions and events at the time. His mother would have moved to reporting the news had it not been for her young family. When Cade was six, his oldest sister received her letter go attend Hogwarts and Cade was eager to go, but he still had to wait. His next older sister received her letter and the following year was Cade. 

It was interesting to see how differently he and all his siblings were at school. His oldest sister had top grades and was a perfect and eventually Head Girl. In contrast, his other sister was happy to do the minimum—much to his parents’ chagrin. But they saw the oldest and wondered where her drive was. Cade had his own purpose, he’d already stood up on the train for a boy that was being picked on—another first year and gotten himself pushed down, but he’d gotten right back up. In the end, it hadn’t stopped much but just the bullying for the moment, but he called it a win. At that age, he wasn’t yet that tall to be getting into such situations. When he got into his second year, he was able to try out and successfully join the Ravenclaw Quidditch team. It was such a thrill to him, and he enjoyed the athleticism of it and the inclusion of being on a team. Finding friends had never been the hard part. However, he tended to spend more time writing snippets and articles for the student paper than doing his Transfiguration homework, but he liked to keep busy. 

The later years went about the same. He played Quidditch and had a growth spurt when he was about sixteen, which helped his lone venture of standing up for the little guy. All the while, though, he also tried to keep track of his sister and what she was doing. More often than not, he was dragging some seventh-year boy smaller than him into a hallway to have a “discussion” with him, but then Elena would be angry with him. He couldn’t help it. It was his family, and he wanted her to do well and be happy, but he wasn’t one to let things go, so he didn’t stop. She graduated, but over that summer before his seventh year, she left home after an argument with their parents and seemed to fall off the face of the earth. It saddened him, and he felt frustrated he couldn’t do anything while still at school. His mother tried to look for her using her Newspaper contacts though her ability was limited when she retired right as Cade had graduated. When he reached his fifth year, he also gained new responsibility—he was made a prefect, and he felt accomplished. However, it was probably something so small in the span of things. 

Cade finished with decent grades, though his abilities for Transfiguration and Potions were sorely lacking. Over the summer, he began an internship at The Daily Prophet. It was a bumpy start. Since his mother had worked there previously, there were always whispers of nepotism and the like. Suddenly he knew he’d done right by siding with the marginalized groups at Hogwarts, such as the students that were werewolves or poorly treated because they had a specific family name. This was a taste of that. But he pushed through, he wasn’t one to let that bring him down, and if anything, it created a need to be a bit intense about things. And when he finished his internship and was hired full time, the smaller stories were small enough to chase down every lead and have detailed and complete reports. Still, he wanted the glory that also came with that. There wasn’t much recognition in writing dull stories about “new shop in Diagon Alley” and writing a small quip for it. Or just writing obituaries for the next hundred and fifty-year-old wizard that passed away. Those times frustrated him, but he was also helping his sister, who had reappeared, get back on her feet. Hence, the downtime wasn’t totally wasted. 

His work became his life, and if it wasn’t for his more extroverted personality, he might have suffered for it, but really he didn’t mind it all that much. But for a few years, it was just that, small stories. Stories about a Magical musical artist going on tour or announcing a new album, a young man arrested, made the paper because their parent was some famous Auror or someone who worked in international relations. Basically, for a few years, the largest piece he had written was an opinion piece on “The Validity of the letter ‘T’ in Horizont Alley,” which he had strong feelings about, but it wasn’t big news. Then finally, in 2017, he caught a break. It was supposed to have been a small story, and it had been based on something his father had mentioned off-hand to him. By that point, his father had retired but still had some connections in the industry and said how one of the (now closed) potions shops didn’t seem to have much business but always seemed to be standing. Typically potions shops were bustling places. Whether one needed a calming draught, wolfsbane, or something more complicated—everybody visited them. Always. To have a shop that didn’t seem to be doing [i]anything[/i] was a strange look. 

Cade didn’t bring it to the attention of his editor yet and instead visited the place. Since he’d grown up seeing his father work, he was more or less familiar with what he might see in a shop or at least things a Potioneer might have, and it was….lacking. With some digging and talking to some people, Cade had at least 1 seedy connection to get information from. He discovered it was actually a front for a smuggling operation. Now that he had some more details, maybe not so much [i]evidence[/i], he could bring it to his editor, who approved that he take the story. Cade dug into this story, the operation wasn’t big, but the items dealt with were the issue. The magical world has many things that are considered illegal. Most of them relate to Dragons, and that’s precisely what this was. He also went to some Law Enforcement officials, but they hadn’t taken what he had seriously since he didn’t have a lot at that time to give them and that frustrated him. He knew what he was talking about, but they wouldn’t listen. In the end, though, he was able to write his piece on The Potions’ Shop and illegal smuggling of illegal Dragon Goods, and then Law Enforcement paid attention. Cade felt as if he was on top of the world, and then the stories he was assigned began to increase in terms of seriousness and public attention. 

The years passed, and the world still changed. Still, he even wrote his stories and enjoyed traveling to do so if it was an international topic until he was promoted to Junior Assistant Editor of the Paper. It meant he was less in the field, which he had mixed feelings on. But it gave him a new responsibility and experience he enjoyed immensely. In a way it was like what he'd experienced after interning and then a few years of small and inconsequential stories but he was learning about being the Editor through doing this grunt work. And then, the last promotion. To Senior Editor, he was thrilled.&nbsp;However, his only struggle right now is to accept his role and the newfound responsibility while still letting his reporters write. One would say he micromanages, but he just likes this done right the first time. 

[/blockquote][b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]When things started to shift in the Wizard, World Cade kept an eye out. When Shacklebolt had been found dead, he tried to help with that story, but it didn’t get very far. They were there to report the facts and the news, but it was all in Law Enforcement’s hands and out of reach for them.  And then students began to be found dead at Hogwarts, his alma mater. It was an issue that hit closer to home due to that, but again facts were scarce, and it didn’t matter where Cade stuck his nose or asked his contacts, but there wasn’t a thread to follow. The one that really shocked him was after following the Triwizard Tournament closely since the world was watching. Then it ended, but the explosion killed so many students, including one of the Champions. It had saddened him, but there was also little to report on that. The part that frustrated Cade was that. There wasn’t much he could do, but he still holds on to those incidents and stories because, in his mind, they aren’t resolved. The same with the Quidditch Final and the terrible accident killed Hermione Granger and then the Azkaban incident and the dragon in the village. These events don’t feel concluded to Cade, and now as an Editor, he has a chance to look more into it, but the leads are cold, and the threads just aren’t there. Perhaps it’s only his need for closure getting in the way of him letting it go. The latest, however, which he plans to be personally involved in, is the appearance of this new mysterious island….[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@thevanessa[/blockquote][b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her&nbsp;[/blockquote][b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]rude[/blockquote][b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]GMT-8[/blockquote][b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]the wyrdness touched me[/blockquote][b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@vanessa   , @anastasia   , @layla   , @leonardo   [/blockquote][/div][/div]