
[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" alt="GIF" src="https://64.media.tumblr.com/4846182e1fc902f8eba99bed8f1b8c10/7911a69739b2bbb8-2b/s500x750/dbad737408280860b1f513b7d4d0ba373eb0cdb6.gif"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Yara Leila El Fayed[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]YAH-rah LAY-luh EL FY-ed
[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote] Unless you're family, just call her Yara.[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]19
January 2, 2007[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Cisgender female; she/her pronouns[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Muggle[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Heterosexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Tua El-Fawwal[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Standing at 5'4" with a slim build, Yara has olive skin, brown eyes, and long black hair that is nearly always covered by a hijab for religious reasons. She wears glasses (currently a pair of wire-rimmed frames) or contacts. Her earlobes are pierced once on each lobe, while her nose is pierced on her left nostril. She has a small mole on her nose towards its center and a slightly larger mole above her lip on the right side.

Overall, Yara dresses very fashionably and enjoys styling her outfits (including her hijabs) in a multitude of ways, though everything that she wears is modest. She is relatively feminine and generally wears at least some makeup on a daily basis but generally doesn't bother with high heels or the like.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]BEng Computing – Imperial College London (2025 – )
Muggle primary and secondary schooling (2011 – 2025)[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]First-year undergraduate student[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Full-time student[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Computers and technology as a whole; K-pop and K-dramas; hibiscus tea; the magical world, though she isn't really a part of it; homemade Egyptian food; traveling; spending time with her sister; buying way too many scarves; living in London; art, but she isn't very good at it[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Islamophobia; having to answer questions about her beliefs constantly; when she can't tell if something is halal or not; being unable to see without her glasses or contacts; computer glitches; staying up late; her parents' strictness, though she does love them; how often it rains in England; being away from her younger siblings; dogs[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Yara hopes to graduate with a first in her undergraduate degree and hopefully continue to postgraduate study. Apart from that, she'd love to see a K-pop concert in person.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Honey, mint, and cinnamon[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Aside from fearing for her sister's safety in the magical world, Yara fears that she will end up swept up in the goings-on in the magical world herself. She also fears academic failure, and she's not a fan of dogs.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote][b]studious[/b]

Yara is very intelligent and has devoted a good portion of her life to her academics. She is driven and determined to excel in her life and in her eventual career, and she enjoys spending her time engaged in scholarship. Since she's pursuing a degree in Computing, Yara's studies do take up a lot of her time, but she genuinely enjoys diving into complex topics.


[b]creative[/b]

Though she doesn't really have an artistic streak, Yara is a creative thinker. She isn't afraid to approach problems from different perspectives until she finds one that works, and she's happy to try her hand at things even if she doesn't necessarily know what the outcome will be.


[b]realistic[/b]

Yara is very much a realist, keeping herself firmly grounded and not letting her expectations get too high. It keeps her from avoiding disappointment later on down the road, and it makes life easier in the long run. It's not uncommon for her to serve as the "voice of reason" to other people, and she isn't one to allow herself to get too carried away.


[b]religious[/b]

A Sunni Muslim, Yara adheres closely to the religious beliefs with which she was raised. She wears hijab, for instance, and follows Islamic dietary laws. While some might view her as being conservative in her beliefs, she maintains an open mind towards Islam and feels that her own beliefs are compatible with the way in which she lives her life. While she isn't a witch herself, she doesn't feel that there is an inherent incompatibility between Islam and magic, provided that that magic isn't Dark.


[b]honest[/b]

Yara is a very honest person. While she isn't the type to come right out and say something harsh without warning, she will answer someone truthfully if asked for her opinion. She's a little less reserved about providing her unsolicited opinion when it comes to her siblings, but she is conscientious enough that she wouldn't dare say or do anything out of true malice.


[b]oblivious[/b]

Though Yara doesn't realize it, there's plenty about the magical world that she doesn't know. Things at Hogwarts haven't always been sunshine and rainbows, and her view of the magical world has been colored by how her older sister, Yasmin, has written about it and talked about it over the years. Yara thinks that she's "in the know" about the other world that her sister has been a part of for so many years, but it would be a crushing blow if she were to find out how dark and terrifying life can be as a witch or wizard.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Cairo, Egypt, originally; now living in London, England[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote][b]mother:[/b]

Hafiza El Fayed, 47, housewife and artist, Muggle woman


[b]father:[/b]

Jafari El Fayed, 59, businessman, Muggle man


[b]sisters:[/b]

Yasmin El Fayed, 20, bartender and artist, Muggle-born witch

Yrene El Fayed, 10, student, Muggle, twin to Yahia


[B]brother:[/b]

Yahia El Fayed, 10, student, Muggle, twin to Yrene


[b]paternal grandfather:[/b]

Kaliph El Fayed, 89, Muggle man


[b]paternal grandmother:[/b]

Aisha El Fayed, 81, Muggle woman[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Yara El Fayed was born and raised in Cairo, Egypt, younger than her older sister Yasmin by just a year. Their life was an upper-class one but relatively normal, on the whole. There was certainly nothing to suggest that the El Fayed family was markedly different from any other in any way, and they didn't think of themselves as such. Yara was the ideal child, the kind any parent would hope to have: She was obedient to her parents, got along with her sister, and generally didn't have many issues at all in her life. In a word, she was privileged without being spoiled, and she knew from a very early age that there was no need for her to be loud or unruly.

While her sister gravitated towards more artistic endeavors, Yara was less interested in painting and drawing than in building things and taking them apart. Art class gave her something to do outside of school, though, and she didn't dislike it; she simply didn't take to it as naturally as her sister did. Instead, with money at her parents' disposal, she was eventually signed up for all manner of STEM classes and camps and absolutely adored them. Even in her regular schooling, she was very good at anything to do with mathematics and science, and she loved getting to do even more.

As she and her sister grew older, though, Yasmin received one opportunity that stood out above all else: She was a witch, and she was being asked to attend a school for magic called Uagadou. While Yara worried for her sister because of everything that she had heard about jinn and shayatin, she was relieved that Yasmin didn't seem to be possessed or dangerous. She didn't know what she would have done if that were the case, but even their parents' concern was that Yasmin would receive the best magical education available to her. Instead of Uagadou, Yasmin was sent all the way to a school in Scotland called Hogwarts.

Yara didn't want Yasmin to be alone at boarding school, but she knew that she had to accept that she wouldn't get to see her quite so often. At around the same time, their younger siblings were born, so Yara knew that she wouldn't want to leave them without an older sibling to help guide them.

Receiving confirmation—with the absence of any communications from any magical schools—that she wasn't magical like her sister was difficult to handle at first. Yara even briefly considered going to boarding school in the United Kingdom to be closer to her older sister. The downside to that, however, was that it would make it even harder to conceal the real reason why Yasmin had been shipped off so far away from home in the first place.

As she learned more about what Hogwarts was like for Yasmin through her letters home, Yara thought that it sounded fantastic. She was oblivious to the more dangerous goings-on, but not being separated from her older sister by such a distance seemed like a good solution. It was then that Yara decided that she would go to the United Kingdom for university, no matter what, and she made it her mission from that point forward.

While Yasmin spent her time at Hogwarts, Yara spent her time studying. Even during family and school holidays, she could usually be found with a book in hand or her laptop on her lap—not that Yasmin couldn't persuade her to put down her academic work for a little while. As much as it stung to miss out on so much time with her sister, Yara was able to develop her own interests and realize that she wanted to continue to study computers beyond the little circuits and robots she'd put together in camps as a kid.

Finally receiving an offer from Imperial College London for a Bachelor's of Engineering in Computing was how Yara thought it must have felt for Yasmin to find out that she was a witch so many years before. It was even better that she would get to live in London, like Yasmin was, and that they would get to spend more time together than they had since they were children. Yara accepted the offer from Imperial without a second thought and happily moved to London to join her sister in September 2025.

Now, midway through the first year of her bachelor's degree, Yara knows that she made the right decision, and she can't wait to see what the future holds.
[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Yara's knowledge of what has happened in the magical world is extremely limited, but she doesn't realize that Yasmin has been keeping her in the dark about it as much as she has. While she knows that there are Dark wizards and witches out there who do murder people, for example, she thinks that it's no different from the dangers present in the Muggle world and doesn't realize the full extent of what the Dark Arts are capable of doing.

She also knows a little bit about the limitations of magic in relation to technology and the fact that that has been improved upon since Yasmin was in school, although she doesn't fully understand how the government in the magical world works or the tensions behind such issues. (Why anyone wouldn't want the ability to use a phone or the internet is beyond her…)

At the same time, she has no problems with the magical world—or what she knows of it—and is disappointed that she cannot interact with it as fully as her sister can.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@audrey  [/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]She/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]23[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]US Central Time[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]Current member![/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@sarah, @scorpius, @ezekiel, @chrissy, @monday, @clarence, @parvati, @brody, @oliwia, @penelope, @kaylee, @maxima, @wormwood, @muffet, @dasha, @samira, @felix, @priscilla, @blair, @camila, @claricia, @honey, @tamatha, @emmanuelle, @xiulan[/blockquote][/div][/div]
