[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt="" style="max-width:100%;" src="https://media.giphy.com/media/rwGunOYje9Jp6/giphy.gif"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]vasilia abigail fortescue[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]va- seel- e - ah ah-bee-gal four-tess-queue[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Vas, lia, silli[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]20
June 1[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]female. She/her[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]squib - comes from a halfblooded family[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]demisexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]none - she can't use one.[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Hattie Watson[/blockquote][b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]5'6 height.

Vasilia is almost a stereotypical red hair. Fair skinned, plagued by far too many freckles and hazel eyes. She has a [i]lot[/i] of tattoos,&nbsp; and is constantly getting more. She has some very severe burns on her arms from a fire, but the tattoos help hide the burns.

She has a very casual style, basically she likes to be in on the action so she prefers clothing that lets her 'roll of her sleeves' and get in on the action, if you will. Basically clothes that she can get dirty and not really care about.[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Muggle grade school and secondary school.[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]graduated muggle secondary school
currently attending a 4 year culinary school (she's in year 2)[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Ice Cream Artisan at Fortescue's Icecream parlour
(technically also a culinary school student, but not really a 'job'.)[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Um... ICE CREAM
puzzles
music
partying
dancing under the stars
ice skating
summer days
cooking
experimenting with cuisine&nbsp;

[/blockquote][b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]winter
uniforms
silence
when ice cream melts and gets everything sticky.
When people make fun of her family's ice cream parlour.
People that "can't survive" without magic.[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Vasilia wants to be a world famous chef, and to someday open her own restaurant (she hasn't quite decided what kind of restaurant though.)[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]cinnamon sticks, home made sugar cookies, apple cider, vanilla, salted caramel, buttered rum, pine...&nbsp; she has a t hing for strong smells.[/blockquote][b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]her family losing/selling the business. (this fear is growing since her parents are older in years and no longer able to do as much as they could before.)
fire - explained in depth in her history but she's had a fear ever since she got severely burned.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Vasilia is fun, loving, sweet and charismatic. A social butterfly, she can hold a conversation with just about anyone and anything. Years of working in her family's shop have taught her how to read people exceptionally well, and how to handle them. You know those people that could talk someone off a ledge? She's that type of person. She just knows what to say, and how to say it. When you meet her she treats you like an old friend, and makes everyone feel welcome.&nbsp;

Vasilia has a creative and curious mind. She loves to try new things, though especially with food. She's always experimenting with recipes, and trying to create something new and exciting. She's a serious foodie. So when you are around her, expect to be well fed.&nbsp;

Vasilia has her faults though, being such a people person she wants to make everyone happy. So... She doesn't really know how to say no. She is always taking on more, and more, sometimes far to much then she should. At the same time, she is also quite independent so she doesn't ask for help easily. She doesn't want to worry those around her, or let them see her struggle. So, she'll carry the weight of the world and smile the whole time.

She is a very clumsy person though. Her hand-eye coordination is definitely lacking. She's the sort of person that can and will cut herself while cooking, will drop things on the floor, and trip on thin air. But hey, she's a good sport about it! In fact, her clumsiness is a quirk she's quite fond of, as odd as that sounds!&nbsp;

Vasilia loves life. Despite being a squib in a magical family she holds no resentment or jealousy (anymore) for her lack of magical abilities. She's come to terms with who she is. She loves herself, and loves to have a good time. She's the girl that will frolic in a field, make a flower wreath, make up her own constellations when star gazing, and has to dance when music comes on.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]London, England (you could even say Diagon Alley from how much time she's spent there!)[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Abigail Fortescue, 58-years-old, mother (cares for husband full-time)
Florean Fortescue jr, 62-years-old, father (terminally ill)

____ ____ Fortescue, 24-years-old, brother
____ ____ Fortescue, 7th year student, brother
[/blockquote]
[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]a calico cat named Sugar.[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Vasilia was the little girl her parents always wanted.&nbsp;Her parents decided to start their family later in life than most. It wasn't necessarily by choice though, the couple had had a difficult time conceiving. When their first born son was born it was a wonderful blessing after years and years of trying. Vasilia's birth though was unplanned, as her parent shad come to believe their little boy was the only miracle they'd have. This second miracle came out kicking and screaming, announcing her presence to the world. Even as an infant she was a vocal, but happy girl. She was the sort of infant and toddler that made noise purely for the enjoyment of making noise. Only a few short years later and a third blessing joined the family, another boy.

Vasilia had a happy childhood, as one might image when your family owned and ran an ice cream shop. She always felt like she was living in a fairy tale. She loved to try all the flavors and help her parents and their employees create the ice cream. When she was still a child, there was a kitchen fire at the family home while she and her mother were cooking. While the fire was quickly contained, Vasilia's arms were burned extensively.

There was also something quite off about Vasilia. She never seemed to show any sign of magic. Both her brother's were displaying signs, but not her. Vasilia's parents had growing suspicions that she might be a squib, but those suspicions weren't confirmed until she turned 11... and no letter arrived.

While many families would be devastated by the news of a Squib (The Ollivander's just down the road from the ice cream shop had had just such an event several years earlier) the Fortescue's took this information in stride. It didn't change who Vasilia was. And while Vasilia, as a preteen and teenager felt a hint of jealousy for her two brothers she also had a strong support system. Each summer when her brother's would be home for the summer they would tell her all the wonderful things they'd learned at Hogwarts and she would tell them everything she learned at the muggle schools. Being able to attend school in the same area as her family's shop also gave her the opportunity to spend almost every afternoon at the shop, working with her parents and the employees.

It was during these teenage years that Vasilia learned to love cuisine, and decided that she would someday become a chef. While ice cream was a favorite she didn't want to limit herself to just one thing. After finishing secondary school she took some time to work in her family's shop full time, before enrolling in culinary school.&nbsp;

Between her formal culinary training and her informal training from her parents, Vasilia has become quite the chef, and has even convinced her parents to let her be one of the ice cream artisans, responsible for the creation of the shop's ice cream.&nbsp;

In recent years though, as her parents have gotten older, more and more of the shop's weight is falling on her. Her father, due to decline health has been forced to step away from the shop entirely.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Vasilia is a generally very optimistic and 'hopeful' person. So while the murders, kidnappings, and the prison break were very concern Vasilia is also not exactly concerned for her own safety. What she knows about in regards to the 'news' is what she's forced to know by patrons of the ice cream parlour and her family.&nbsp;

Though, the Prison breakout has caused a bit more of ruckus in her life, particularly pesky Aurors demanding to search the shop over and over again for any fugitives. In her mind, these criminals pose little threat to the shop because... Why bother with an ice cream parlour? If you wanted to rob someone, there were plenty of other shops down the road that made better targets.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Sora[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]27[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]Mountain![/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]I'm a stalker.[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@sarah           and @ambrosia          [/blockquote][/div][/div]