[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://64.media.tumblr.com/a9ce889bb7966f213cdb89eef797cf32/7cc289a46d91ba3d-5e/s1280x1920/edbb924bbc540461abb93acdc1d39def10a90ae8.jpg" alt="" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Emrys Mordrain Holopainen[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]emm-riss mor-dr-ay-ne hoh-low-pi-nen)[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Goes by Mordrain on hos solo albums
Any other nicknames are up to others.[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]20 - turned into a vampire at 18
December 13, 2005[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]male
he/him[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]half-blood, full vampire[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote] pansexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]Wand - 14 ⅝” ebony, dragon heartstring
Guitar - hornbeam, vampire fang[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Diego barrueco[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Emrys, like all vampires, has pale skin and red eyes. He finds himself smiling more often, if only just to show off his prominent and sharp canines. While he is thin, he has retained a muscular physique. Wears plain clothes, or anything picked out by a professional stylist. If he goes outside during the day, he always is sure to wear dark sunglasses. If he must be out on a sunier day, he is sure to wear a hood, with as much skin covered, keeping his head low for minimum sun exposure. He does have a number of tattoos, mostly on his arms.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts - Slytherin
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduated 2024
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Musician
Bandmate - drummer
Consultant musician[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Blood - preferably from the source, but will use the blood bank when needed
Music
Singing
making/writing music
Flirting
groupies
drawing
alcohol
Smoking long with not so legal substences
making music (is skilled in a number of instruments) - Piano, guitar, bass, drumbs, violin,
writing music
blood lollypops
cake
sweets - the more decadent, the better
listening to music - all kinds
Traveling
Performing in front of an audience
Flying around as a bat
Being famous[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]all kinds of sports
strict rules
people who are uptight
judgemental people
freeloaders
people using him because he's famous
the great outdoors
garlic
Silver
Direct sunlight
People who are clingy
posers[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Already living his dream. As long as he can keep living his dream, he’s happy.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Blood
Groupies
Chocolate
Alcohol[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Commitment
Career ending by :Hands breaking, Losing his voice, or Going deaf[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Emrys cares deeply for his family and for his pets. Past that, he has one or two close friends, with no intimate relations, he isn’t one to get too attached to anyone. Genuinely close relationships don't come easy to him. He opens up enough to make temporary connections, but not enough for anything lasting. Emrys doesn’t like to be tied down to any one thing. He is in a band, but also consults and does his own solo work. He has his own place, but rarely invites others over. The longest monogamous relationship he had, in his adult life, was between three and four days to become a vampire. If someone that he’s currently spending this time with, claims that he is their boyfriend, that’s their choice, but he’s guaranteed to have at least two other intimate relations going at the same time. If he found himself without the company of someone, and longing for it, he will usually start in the corner, or in an area where he has a good look at the “stock” that he is picking from. At that point, he would pick out likely partners for the evening and watch them, before making his move - much like a predator picking out its prey.

Emrys finds himself in the company of many people - lovers, fans, groupies, bandmates - while this is true, he is careful not to risk changing anyone into a vampire. He is mindful to not feed from the same person two nights in a row. Turning someone into a vampire, created an unwanted connection to them.  He does feed on his romantic partners, if they consent to it. Because of this, he has had much practice creating the blood-replenishing potions, and/or always has the created potions on hand. Emrys loves to get attention, on stage or one on one. When spending time with someone, he will amuse himself with light conversation, but if he hears something he doesn’t like, get’s board, or loses interest, he considers himself done. 

Emrys loves to live in the moment. He doesn’t like to dwell too much in the past, what’s done is done. He also doesn’t care too much to think about the future, he’s living his dream now, why not enjoy it. Because of this he prefers to say what’s on his mind, without any filter. Oftentimes, many of his comments can come out crass or inappropriate. He would normally classify himself as a passovist. Preferring to back off or let up, but he will defend himself if push comes to shove.

His one true passion in life is music. He plays a number of instruments, composes, writes and consults for others and his own personal work. If he comes across a problem that he can't simply solve, Emrys can think better by playing music, or starting to compose. He always carries around small muggle bills and wizard coins to give to those on the street. He won't give when others are watching, and he is much more generous to those who are playing music. Because of his parents, he knows Finnish, Dutch, and English, he is fluent in all.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Father from Finland
Mother from Netherlands
Born in the Netherlands
Mother, stepfather and kids  moved to England at age 10[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Radford Holopainen - Father, 48, wizard born, famous rock musician 
Luna (nee Visser) Edwards - Mother, 40, muggle born witch who is an expert in arthurian myths/lore (in both the magical and muggle world)
Oliver Edwareds - Step-father, 43, professor of ancient literature at Oxford

Paternal half sibling - 21
Paternal half sibling - 15
Maternal half sibling - 16
Maternal half sibling - 14
Maternal half sibling - 12
Maternal half sibling - 11

A number of connections in the music industry

Ex-girlfriend(s) from 4th-7th year (before the Yule Ball)
Number of flings/romantic encounters/one night stands/lovers[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]short hair orange tabby cat - ector
russian blue cat - serina
burmese python - fluffy
thestral - grim[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Radford Holopainen was the greatest rock and roll musician to come out of Finland. Luna Visser was hooked. She saw him in concert and fell deeply in love with him. She started to follow his tour around, attending every concert she could. Soon, she was noticed. Radford invited her to a private encounter and he seemed to like the girl too. Their romance was unconventional, but he invited her to follow him for the end of his tour. She gladly dropped everything to travel with her love. When the tour ended, the two moved in together. Not long after that, Luna discovered that she was pregnant.

Luna Visser was obsessed with Aurthurian legends and myths. She desired to name her child accordingly. But rock legend Radford wasn’t so sure. The two had many disagreements regarding the name of their child. Finally agreeing on the name Emrys Mordrain. The next set of arguments landed on whose last name the child would have. The couple had been living together, but they both knew that it wasn’t going to last forever. Because his first and middle names were both ultimately chosen by Luna, she conceded to let the boy have his father’s surname.

For the first couple of years of his life, Emrys had a rock and roll father, and a studious mother. He fisted piano keys and strummed guitars, loving the pure sound that they made. But as expected, the two started to drift apart. Radford wanted to travel, and meet more people, while Luna wanted to dive deeper into her studies. Around the time that Emrys turned four, Luna met Oliver. They connected on a much more intellectual level.  The two had a short courtship followed by quick marriage. As he grew up, he took to playing music, reminding his mother about his father. The family moved to England when the boy was ten, for Oliver’s new job. Splitting time with his father, and his mother’s family the boy had the chance to observe both lifestyles. 

Because Emrys lived primarily with his mother, he was invited to attend Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry. He flourished at school, making many friends. During fourth year at school, Emrys got a girlfriend. His mother had encouraged him over the years to follow her example, find someone to care for and be faithful to them. So he worked hard, and spent all his freetime with this girl, but he still felt his mind and eyes shifting. 

After that, he started to find ways to spend time with anyone who interested him. Whether or not they were his current girlfriend or not. At first, he started to feel guilty, but the guilt quickly dissipated. He started to learn now to admire others while his girlfriend wasn’t looking. The summer after his sixth year, he spent time with his father, and started to write and arrange music for his foreseeable career.

Emrys’ seventh year brought new perspectives, new students and new opportunities. He met and got along with a number of forine students. He found ways to enjoy his time and learn more about them and their culture. Emrys even convinced some of them to show him their temporary dwellings. His antics didn’t go unnoticed by his girlfriend, who dramatically broke up with him in front of the entire school. This didn’t deter some students. He was able to take a girl to the Yule Ball, even spend some time with a few other students - off alone where no one else would see them.

Graduation brought sweet freedom. Emrys’ went straight from the Hogwarts express to a friend he had met the previous summer. The two had an arrangement, and he was ready for their agreement to start. About three nights later, he left, now being a vampire. From there, he started his new life. Still striving to have a good relationship with his family, he could now make the rules about how he lived. After that, Emrys started to record his own songs, and also joined a band as their drummer. [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]In all honesty, Emrys thinks that while current events like the firework malfunction, and the quarantine sucks, nothing really seemed to directly affect him. The Quarantine did keep him and his band in the area, but that wasn’t the worst thing.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Sophi[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her [/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]Um...[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]Mountain[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]I live here[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@dmitri , @nixie , @thursday , @torrian , @fiona , @jasper , @orion  [/blockquote][/div][/div]
