[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://66.media.tumblr.com/01ce8ee25c22bdb42f0f8a0f942d1a98/tumblr_prwvlnO1um1qab1z1o2_500.gif" alt="GIF" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Muffet Martha Hubbard[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]MUFF-it MAR-thuh HUHB-erd[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Muffy[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]34
October 16, 1990[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Cisgender female; she/her pronouns[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Squib of Scourer descent[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Heterosexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]How dare you![/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Phoebe Waller-Bridge[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Muffy is relatively tall, at 5’10”, and has a thin build. She is very fair-skinned, with short dark brown hair and dark brown eyes. She has a crooked nose, which—aside from genetics—was once broken when she was a child, as well as a dark splotch of a birthmark on the left-hand side of her forehead. She tries to cover up the mark with her hair as often as she can, as her mother would tell her in her childhood that it was surely a witch’s mark.

Muffy dresses conservatively, usually wearing long sleeves and long skirts or trousers. Her style is generally feminine, although she prefers bolder colors such as navy and red to pastels. What she wears is most definitely worn for comfort and not to keep up with the latest trends, and most of her garments are relatively plain.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Homeschooled
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduate[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]New Salem Philanthropic Society member[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Freedom (her own, at least); proselytizing and pamphleteering; baking; her family; moral superiority; the United States of America; pseudoscience; genealogy; children; dogs[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Witchcraft; the Devil; mainstream media; obscenity; divination; those who don't believe magic to be a threat; cats (as they might be a witch's familiar); public education; symbols she can't identify; drugs and alcohol[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Muffy's greatest desire is to continue the legacy of her ancestors in the extermination of witchcraft and wizardry.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Pamphlets, cinnamon apples, and vanilla bean[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Muffy most fears that witchcraft will continue to damage the fabric of society, and that witches and wizards will oppress non-magical people. Second to that, she fears that one of her relatives will turn out to be a witch or wizard.
[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote][b]vengeful[/b]
Viewing witches, wizards, and the other magical creatures of the world as the source of its problems (and particularly [i]her[/i] problems), Muffy has spent her entire life learning to hate magic. She is hellbent on finding tangible proof of the existence of magic and exposing witches and wizards to the non-magical world. 

[b]neo-Luddite[/b]
With the exception of the tools that she uses as a Scourer, Muffy is very anti-technology. She feels that phones, apps, and screen time are only progressively rotting children's brains. She's fine with electricity and cars and all of that [i]"normal"[/i] stuff, but anything too progressive is [i]dangerous[/i], don't you know?

[b]fearful[/b]
Most of Muffy's utter ridiculousness is rooted in her deep-seated fear of witchcraft. She genuinely believes that she and others like her are the persecuted ones, at risk because of the existence of witches and wizards.

[b]hypocritical[/b]
A lot of Muffy's beliefs and behaviors are pretty contradictory, mostly because she has bought into a weird and almost cult-like organization. At the heart of it, of course, is that witches and wizards are very bad, while innocent people like her are only trying to do good. Her moral code has a tendency to change based on whatever vices or societal issues can be blamed on witches and wizards, and, hey, [i]she's[/i] obviously not the problem. It's easier to shift the blame to somebody else than to admit that maybe she's got it backwards.

[b]prejudiced[/b]
For Muffy, witches, wizards, and anyone who might be associated with their demonic ways are the problem, even if they're otherwise great people. She has no real basis for that view, except that it's what has been drilled into her head her entire life, passed down to her parents by their ancestors.

[b]loyal [s]or brainwashed[/s][/b]
Muffy is a devoted member of the New Salem Philanthropic Society and its mission, gladly volunteering herself for anything and everything she can to make their message known. She views the organization as central to the very core of her being, and second to that is her family. Looking beyond that teensy "out to get wizardkind" aspect, she's a great aunt and sister and can make an excellent casserole.

[b]proud[/b]
Muffy is proud of a lot of things, especially when it comes to keeping old traditions. She's proud to be a Hubbard and a hardworking American from the Midwest, and she's especially proud of her sisters' children for continuing the family legacy.

[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Posey County, Indiana, USA[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote][b]mother:[/b]
Martha Richter Hubbard, 67, New Salem Philanthropic Society member/housewife, Squib of Scourer descent


[b]father:[/b]
John Joseph Hubbard, 70, New Salem Philanthropic Society member, Squib of Scourer descent


[b]sisters:[/b]

Constance "Connie" _____ (née Hubbard), 41, New Salem Philanthropic Society member, Squib of Scourer descent

Josephine _____ (née Hubbard), 37, New Salem Philanthropic Society member, Squib of Scourer descent

Abigail _____ (née Hubbard), 30, New Salem Philanthropic Society member, Squib of Scourer descent

 Elizabeth "Buffy" _____ (née Hubbard), 28, New Salem Philanthropic Society member, Squib of Scourer descent


[b]nephews:[/b]

Jeremiah _____, 23, New Salem Philanthropic Society member, Squib of Scourer descent, son of Constance

Nathaniel _____, 21, New Salem Philanthropic Society member, Squib of Scourer descent, son of Constance


[b]nieces:[/b]

Grace _____, 18, New Salem Philanthropic Society member, Squib of Scourer descent, daughter of Constance

Faith _____, 16, New Salem Philanthropic Society member, Squib of Scourer descent, daughter of Josephine[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Muffet Martha “Muffy” Hubbard was born on a farm in an unincorporated area of Posey County, Indiana, to two parents of Scourer descent who were already established members of the New Salem Philanthropic Society by the time of her birth. Before her were two sisters, Constance “Connie” and Josephine, although Muffy would not stay the family’s youngest child for long. Long before her two younger sisters, Elizabeth “Buffy” and Abigail Hubbard, made Muffy the family’s middle child, their mother had already noticed something peculiar about the little girl: She had a dark and misshapen birthmark, almost like an inkblot, on the left-hand side of her forehead.

As a child, Muffy was constantly reminded of the birthmark and forced into submission because of it. Her mother always threatened her that it was a sign of a curse that a witch must have cast on her, forcing her to behave lest she would become a witch, too. It kept Muffy unfailingly obedient to her mother—and petrified of witchcraft and all things magical. She, like her sisters, heard the stories their parents told them, as casually as other parents would tell their children bedtime stories. Tales of witch-hunting and long-dead ancestors filled the Hubbard girls’ imaginations and fueled their hatred for the “other”. They wanted to be like those from centuries before, who had fought with all of their might to protect the world from such evil forces.

Over time, as Muffy and her sisters aged, they became gradually more involved with the New Salem Philanthropic Society. Educated at home to keep them safe from outside influences, the girls cherished the time that they got to spend with the other children their age who were connected to the society through their own parents. They were increasingly entrusted with the knowledge of their family heirlooms and the properties bestowed upon them, and they, too, swore their allegiance to the society and its aims.

Once she and her sisters were young adults, Muffy loved nothing more than spreading the New Salem Philanthropic Society’s message, carrying her tools with her when she and the rest of her family would travel around the country. Sometimes, they came away successful—or at least with some hope that they were on the verge of a breakthrough—and other times not so much, but the Hubbards kept at it, growing their “outreach” network to as many other like-minded families and individuals as they could.

Spurred by others’ accounts of their encounters with witchcraft, Muffy’s sisters began to marry and establish families from within the Second Salemer organization, paranoid that they might otherwise fraternize with those capable of true and dangerous magic. Massachusetts naturally became a popular travel destination for the Hubbards, although they craved something more fulfilling than revisiting the sites of the infamous witch trials and hitting dead ends. Perhaps, they and some others decided amongst themselves, they were looking in the wrong places. Perhaps they needed to spread their beliefs as Second Salemers beyond the United States…

And thus, under the guise of an extended vacation in Europe, the Hubbards followed some of their peers and traveled to London, England. While the city certainly wasn’t as Muffy expected it, she was amazed to discover that some of her tools were picking up on traces of magic more strongly than they had before. There was clear, obvious magic in the United Kingdom, and she became more determined than ever that she and her family would find it.
[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Given that she is a Second Salemer from the United States, much of the goings-on in magical Britain haven't had much relevance to Muffy's life. While she's certain that she has uncovered wizards and witches for herself in America, she has had nothing to substantiate her claims beyond the New Salem Philanthropic Society. From the stories that she has heard over her lifetime, Muffy knows that there are bound to be centuries of wizards and witches still residing in Europe, too, and she is eager to have traveled to the United Kingdom to see what she and her family members are able to uncover on their supposed "vacation". Maybe, finally, she'll get some real proof of her own.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@audrey  [/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]She/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]21[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]US/Canada Central/Eastern[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]Current member![/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@chrissy, @samira, @clarence, @parvati, @brody, @ezekiel, @penelope, @kaylee, @maxima, @oona, @priscilla, @camila, @honey, @tamatha  [/blockquote][/div][/div]