[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt="(image here of playby)" style="max-width:100%;" src="https://thumbs.gfycat.com/BleakCleverFalcon-size_restricted.gif"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Xantha Jane Willowmoore 
[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]zan-tha[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]X, Xan, Xanthy, Xyxy
[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]19 yo
First of April, 2006
[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]She/Her[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Muggle[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Bisexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Dove Cameron
[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Xantha is a typical pretty and cute looking girl. Her appearance is with her in terms that she can look innocent without putting in much effort. She uses this to her advantage and usually goes for pastels in her clothes. 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Muggle Schooled, dropped out of art school. 
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduated high school, dropped out of art school.
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Dancer. 
Painter.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Dancing, painting, snow, whiskey, camp fires, fireworks, colour, light, her mom and little brother.
[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Her father, her family other than her mother and little sister, people disappearing, cheaters. 
[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]To become a famous artist. But really a dancer.
[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[/div][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][blockquote]Paint disolver, deodorant, chalk, silk. 
[/blockquote][b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Heights, breaking bones, never being able to dance or paint again. 
[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Xantha is a girl of reason. She's sceptical about supernatural things. There's no such things as ghosts and try to convince her that anything such as magic is real. There's always a logical explanation and if there isn't, we just haven't found it yet. She's quick to find reasons things make sense and slow to accept any flaws in her logic. She's down to earth and practical on that point. 

Xantha has drive and passion, especially when it comes to her crafts. She loves dancing more than anything but loves combining it with painting for what she considers to be works of art and passion. She often paints in unconventional ways and far more as an outlet for her anxiety, anger and other negative emotions than because she has ambitions to sell her art.

Rules were not made for Xantha and she doesn't follow them often. While she's not keen on doing anything highly damaging she has a fair amount of spray cans she takes all over London. She squats in abandoned buildings, the older and more ruined, the better. She steals, but only to feed herself. She loves being on markets but doesn't steal to sell. If she takes something it's for the sake of consumption or otherwise staying alive. 

She's also adventurous and loves living on the edge. Despite being terrified of heights she'll get to the roof of a skyscraper to sleep there for sake of the view. She doesn't believe much in limits and refuses to set them for herself. Any place is her stage, once she sets her mind to it. 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]London, UK.
[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Mother: Jane Willowmoore nee Bridges - Care facility, sick.
Father: Xenon Willowmoore - Father, police officer in Wales somewhere.
Younger sister: Xena (Jr) Willowmoore - 4th year hogwarts.

Uncle: Radon Willowmoore - Ministry employee.

Desmond O'Neill (ex boyfriend), unknown.
Henry O'Neill (ex boyfriend), unknown. 
[/blockquote]
[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Kneazle named Spot. (she thinks he's just an ugly weird cat)
[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Xantha was born and raised in London by her mother and father. Her father was close to his brother and always told little Xantha how he'd been special and gone to boarding school in Scotland. When she was young, Xantha was impressed. Her uncle had been very talented, obviously. As she got older she was sceptic since it never got mentioned what his special talents were and he was never around anyway. He probably had some sort of problem going on that led him to boarding school.

Yet this early talk of her very impressive Uncle had made little Xantha determined to also get to a special school. She worked hard when she found her passion in dancing and she was good. She progressed and found herself dancing better than any in her class. Hard work and hours upon hours of practise certainly got her places. 

Her first boyfriend came at the age of fourteen. A boy in her class, Desmond. They had seemed happy and Xantha thought she had everything figured out, until she caught Desmond sneaking around with another girl. She was heartbroken but her father comforted her and everything was okay again.

When Xantha was fifteen her neighbours died in mysterious circumstances and their very ugly cat Spot decided to come live with Xantha. He loved the family and protected their house. All was well. Strange people stopped by, but were often persuaded to leave by her father. Everything was clearly okay. 

Six weeks later she caught her father sleeping with another woman. She doesn't remember anything other than that and is glad the visual is not burned in her minds eye. Her father and mother fought and her dad left. He never came back or let anything slip. Spot had been a little strange around her father though, very aggressive. Spot was a very clever cat that had clearly noticed something was off.

It was a difficult time but Xantha struggled through it. She grew up and lived with her mother and little brother for two splendid years before her mother got diagnosed with an illness. She would no longer be able to take care of her and Xenon (Jr) and so they wrote their father. Xena was allowed to come live with him and his new wife in Wales. Since Xantha was already off age (except she was 17 and not actually of age yet) she was to find her own way. Xantha was furious as this meant her father couldn't even get her birth year right after being gone for a mere two years! 

She left home with nothing but a backpack and ambition, assuring her mother she'd found a place. Mostly couch surfing with friends while she got her finances in order. In reality she started squatting and buying spray cans to decorate London when not doing auditions in hopes of one day making it big and getting a lead in a dance production. 
[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]She's completely obvious about everything going on. She did hear there's a royal ball but naturally she wasn't invited. 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Seph[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]She/Her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]not sure
[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]Cryptoids[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]A ghost told me.[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]So many babes.
[/blockquote][/div][/div]