[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;background-color:#B6B6B4;border:4px solid #B6B6B4;border-radius:10px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt="" src="https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/236x/dc/79/25/dc7925ad5b483d0ccfd83606841f0e2e--ingrid-nilsen-beauty-crush.jpg" style="max-width:100%;"]
[/div]

hello there, my name is [b]Rosalie&nbsp;Williams[/b]&nbsp;but you can call me[b] Rosie[/b]. i'm [b]18[/b]&nbsp;so that makes me a [b]7th[/b]&nbsp;year at Hogwarts, where I reside in [b]hufflepuff[/b]&nbsp;house. You could say I'm [b]hard working, patient, &amp; loyal&nbsp;[/b]but I personally think that I am [b]bubbly, curious &amp; creative[/b]. People say I look a lot like [b]Ingrid Nilsen[/b], but I don't really see it...

[div align="center"][font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][i][b]Rosalie Jue Williams[/b][/i][/font][/font][/div]

[b][i]nickname:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Rosie[/blockquote][b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]18[/blockquote]
[b][i]date of birth:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]12th October 2005[/blockquote][b][i]gender:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]witch[/blockquote]
[b][i]blood status:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]half-blood[/blockquote]
[b][i]sexuality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]straight[/blockquote]
[b][i]house:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Hufflepuff[/blockquote]
[b][i]occupation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]student[/blockquote]
[b][i]wand:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]12 1/8th inches, rosewood, unicorn hair core[/blockquote]
[b][i]playby:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Ingrid Nilsen[/blockquote]
[b][i]appearance:[/i] [/b]
[blockquote]Rosie stands at roughly 5 feet and 5 inches. She is fairly lean and meek looking with slightly pail skin. She spots dark brown hair that falls in loose curls and waves and is medium/long in length, falling just past her shoulder-blades when left natural; however, she is a fan of changing her hair when she's bored and has always played with [i]temporary[/i] changing colors and styles using magic that she has yet to mastered. Rosalie has brown eyes that she got from her mother, and, she blames her father for her paler complexion.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personality[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]likes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Coffee
Chocolate: actually anything remotely sweet&nbsp;
Writing
Rain/storms/snow/colder weather
Animals 
Wandering, exploring, travel
Cooking/Baking
Sports[/blockquote]
[b][i]dislikes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Tea
Eggs: the texture freaked her out
Snobs
Defense against the Dark Arts class: it intimidates her and she thinks she's awful at it despite her pulling average marks.
The color green: she finds it very repulsive and isn't sure why. Not natural green, she likes trees, just the artificial, bright, slime color.

[/blockquote][b][i]erised:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Rosie would love to be a professional writer and has considered either writing novels about the wizarding world as Muggle Fiction/Fantasy books. Or, on the completely other side, she would also like to go into sports journalism due to her fathers love of sports and because she used to watch muggle games with her father all of the time and loves the excitement that comes along with them. She also would always follow Quidditch with her mother and loved it also. Her goal is to be a success possibly in both worlds, Muggle and Magical and make her parents proud.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b][i]amortentia:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Rain: the smell, the feel, the sensation, everything.
Coffee
Bodies of water: the dirt and salt and sand mixed with water has always been a calming scent for her.

[/blockquote][b][i]boggart:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Confrontation: especially with someone she knows well, or, someone whom she knows doesn't like her or has a temper.
Being lost/not knowing how to get home: while she is keen on travel, she is one to stick to the trail.
Spiders: which makes living in an old, stone castle fairly hard. However, maybe that is why she likes the cold weather so much, because it makes the spiders disappear for a while.&nbsp;

[/blockquote]
[b][i]overall personality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Rosie is a very sweet girl. She is bubbly and fun and loves to adventure so long as she knows the way back to where they started. She isn't the best student and has unique taste in subjects, with Care of Magical Creatures and Divination being her favorites, and Defense against the Dark Arts and History of Magic being her least favorites.&nbsp;

She loves to write, it's always been a hobby of hers. She keeps a journal and writes in it almost everyday about whatever crosses her mind. She has considered writing books for muggles as fiction books, but she has also been considering sports journalism as of late. Either way, she would like to have a profession that she can use versatility in both worlds. As a half-blood with a muggle father, Rosie is very open minded about muggles and spent the first 10 years of her life as a muggle.&nbsp;

On any given day, Rosie could be found in a coffee shop, especially if there was snow outside. She would be nestled near a window with her pen in one hand and her mug in the other, just breathing in the scent of the roasted beans mixed with caramel while she marveled at the pure beauty outside and let her mind think the deepest thoughts that a 17 year old Hufflepuff could ponder.&nbsp;

Rosie is a loyal friend. She likes to think of herself as a shoulder for anyone to cry on and a safe person for anyone to talk to, however, with recent events around the castle, she's become a little more closed off. the thought that she had been going to school with a murder and that it wasn't only one student, but could be who-knows-how-many scared her, as she was sure it did everyone. With her background with muggles, and as the daughter of a muggle, Rosie was very afraid and hated walking the halls alone. She was not one who was stingy with her emotions, but she still hated letting people see her cry or cower or jump in fright and felt the safety in numbers.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personal history[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]mother:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Cho Williams (Chang), 45, Professional Quidditch Commentator, Pure-blood, Married.[/blockquote][b][i]father:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Stuart Williams, 44, Lawyer, Muggle, Married.[/blockquote]
[b][i]siblings:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]N/A. Rosie is an only child[/blockquote]
[b][i]pets:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Orange cat named Goldie that her family has had since Rosie was 10.[/blockquote]
[b][i]history:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Rosie was born in Dublin Ireland. Her parents had fallen in love in Dublin a few years after her mother returned from Hogwarts and a few years before she was born. Her father was finishing up his last term at Law school when they met and, despite his non-existent magical abilities, Cho Chang fell in love with him. They had only had one child, and that was Rosie. Rosalie was named in part for her father's mother, who's name was also Rosalie, the woman had died before Rosie ever got to meet her. Her middle name came from her mother. Jue, in Chinese meant joy. Rosie had been an easy pregnancy and an easy baby and her mother found the name fitting.&nbsp;

Rosie grew up as an only child in a cozy Irish cottage in a residential neighborhood of Dublin. She was brought up the muggle way, however, she did often see her mother using magic. Magic was never something that was kept from her, but, because her father couldn't use magic. her first signs of magic came at the age of 7, when, on a particularly rainy day, while she was forced to sit inside the stuffy classroom in her grammar school, the windows all flew open. Rosie was delighted to feel the cold air and to be able to smell the rain, the other kids shouted and the poor teacher rushed to get them all closed. Rosie told her mom all about the phenomenon on the way home from school and her mother explained to her that it probably wasn't due to the wind.&nbsp;

Rosie received her Hogwarts letter at the age of 11 and actually turned 12 during her first year at Hogwarts, since her birthday fell in the awkward month of October. Rosie was sorted into Hufflepuff house due to her friendly nature. She never liked school as a child because she hated being stuck inside for hours, and, whenever possible she always sat by a window. Hogwarts was no exception, however the subjects did interest her more and she was glad to have classes outside. She found herself very good at Herbology and for her first 2 years it was her favorite class. Once she entered into her third year and began taking electives, she fell in love with Care of Magical Creatures and also Divination; and, while she was sure she didn't really have the Seers Eye, the subject intrigued her to no end. Despite her love of sports and her mothers Quidditch ability, Rosie never tried out for her house team. She was more of a spectator than a player and felt just fine with that. She never missed a match, however, no matter what houses were playing because she loved the adrenaline and excitement that came along with them.

As Rosie aged at Hogwarts, she made a decent amount of good friends and a even larger amount of fair friends. She really liked to think of herself as someone that anyone could go to if they needed anything. She loved to be helpful and loved to listen. She wasn't sure how confident she was in giving advice, but she would if asked. Mostly, she liked to make people happy and didn't want anyone to be upset with her, which sometimes lead her into unfortunate situations because she was too afraid to say no. The only detention she ever got was for helping a fellow student sneak food out of the kitchens long after hours because they had missed dinner. The two of them got caught by a prefect on their way out.&nbsp;

Over the past year, however, Rosie had felt a shift within herself after learning of the events. She was lucky enough to have been left alone, at least so far. She was the daughter of a muggle though, and even though she took pride in who she was, it was heartbreaking and terrifying to learn that there were fellow students at her school, walking her halls, maybe even sitting next to her in class, who thought was a disgrace and maybe deserved to be murdered like the ones before her. And while the newly appointed headmaster and Minister for Magic gave her hope, as her mother had nothing but nice things to say about either of them, she couldn't help but shake the weight of the dread that she had going into her 7th year. The thought of leaving the school out of fear had entered her mind, however, that wasn't the type of person that she was. Rosie was a giver, and she knew that if she took that way out, she would be leaving countless others behind, others who could need her help. She was a bit protective in that way. It was the kidnappings that really unsettled her, Rosalie had heard of the stories from the victims and it terrified her to her every bone. Now, she was a 7th year. She had come back to school only to discover that on top of all the terror around around her, the school would be hosting the Tri-Wizard Tournament. Rosie had not submitted her name, and she still couldn't help but remember all of the stories that her mother had told her about the tournament that happened while she was in school, how a boy very close to her had died. Rosie couldn't help but think, with the murders already, why make students fight for their lives any harder? However, she could see a good side to it also. it was bringing together schools in a time of despair and there was safety in numbers. It was also giving the student something to talk about, something good and fun tot think about and look forward to. It was a little ray of sunshine, a glimpse of hope.&nbsp;[/blockquote][div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]alias[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]name:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Ali[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]21[/blockquote]
[b][i]time zone:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Pacific[/blockquote]
[b][i]reference:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Just some good, old fashioned Google-ing (all my normal RP sites are inactive and I wanted to be active so I went searching)[/blockquote]
[b][i]other characters:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]N/A this is my first[/blockquote][/div][/div]