
[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://ilarge.lisimg.com/image/16781567/1080full-vanja-jagnic.jpg" alt=" "][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]fae iona cloudbreaker[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]fay[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]n/a[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]25
January 23rd, 2000[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]female. she/her/hers.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Pureblood. Druid. [/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Straight.[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]All of her magical conduits come from the same willow tree:
11 ¾ inches, willow, griffin feather, springy.
Merlin's Staff (current holder, post-October 1st, 2025)
Instrument: Celtic harp[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Vanja Jagnic[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]5’6”. Fae is a metamorphmagus, so while she can freely change how she looks, she only uses her ability to change her hair. Her natural hair is straw blonde, but she opts to have more vibrant pinks, yellows, blues, and purples so that she is different from the majority of her peers. Her typical clothing consists of flowy dresses, though when working with animals she’ll have more work appropriate garb. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Homeschool.
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduated.
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]High Druid.
Previously: Visitor Guide[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]music, flying, griffins, the quiet of early mornings, meteor showers, full moons, willow trees, sleeping in hammocks, meeting visitors of Hy-Brasil[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]the stress of heading the council and responsibility of Hy-Brasil at times, magic mushrooms, large gatherings (outside of required functions), being treated like a child by the council, injured animals, wilting flowers, the chill of winter[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]To govern the people of Hy-Brasil effectively so that they can all continue maintain the lives they have built. To reach better footing with the Ministry so that there is more give than take from druids. She still desires to raise and take care of griffins despite being locked in as High Druid for the remainder of her life.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]freshly tilled earth, ocean breeze, honey[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Failing as the High Druid. Any number of things could lead to this, and her fears only grow with each new Minister of Magic and the things going on in the world outside of the island. Her own personal fear is losing herself to her role.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Fae is a soft-spoken and ethereal individual outside of her role as High Druid. She maintains her own personal peace by removing herself from her work whenever she can, so that she still has some semblance of a life that isn’t focused solely on her position in the government. While her core personality is still the same now as it was prior to the ancestor’s choosing her, she has had to forego her desire to continue her relaxed and lackadaisical lifestyle that she enjoyed greatly. Her greatest enjoyment has always come from discussing music and griffins, and any outsiders that were privy to her visitor tours while she was still working there would probably say that she talked the most about how the best music was like a light breeze playing over the wings of a buzzing bumblebee.

In her role as High Druid though, she has proven to be an unwavering rock. She refuses to allow the Ministry to take more than they already have and has certainly drawn a few naysayers from the mainland over the last five years. Finding a middle ground, or even a way to discuss with them, has been difficult with the frequent changes of power lately, and that has caused her to be more callous about propositions to talk. Taking care of Hy-Brasil stresses her enough to the point where she wishes the Ministry would get their act together so that she can stop acting as the antagonist in all of their correspondences. The last thing she wants to do is lose the faith of her people, because she believes that they all deserve to live how they want.

As a metamorphmagus, she is not immune to her powers slipping out when certain emotions take over. Her hair will turn a deep scarlet red when she’s angry, or a periwinkle blue when happy. She isn’t one to outright bite people’s heads off when angered, but there are limits to her patience. Fae is willing to give people any number of chances to prove themselves good and worth her time, probably far more often than she should as High Druid. Her leniency bleeds into allowing more visitors over the last few years, who she is always overjoyed to meet if given the chance.

At the end of the day, Fae would have preferred to live her life as it had been, and she isn’t shy to say that. Circumstances aside, she’s unbelievably proud of what she has accomplished so far and had to deal with since being chosen five years earlier. Being High Druid has certainly forced her to break out of her shell more than she probably ever would have otherwise.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Hy-Brasil[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Cian Cloudbreaker – father, 55, owner of Cloudbreaker Farms
Étaín Cloudbreaker – mother, 55, owner of Cloudbreaker Farms

 [/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Storm, a speckled Griffin (not really a pet, more so her best animal friend)[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Born during the month of January, Fae Cloudbreaker would have normally been considered an unlucky individual, had it not been for the events that would transpire twenty years later. The Cloudbreaker family had historically run a farming operation on Hy-Brasil, set atop hills far higher than where the other druids lived, and this could be dated back for generations. Her parents were no different, inheriting the family business and continuing their ancestral role as farmers, living closer to the clouds and their griffin neighbors they had long shared neighborly pleasantries with. 

Aside from being unlucky enough to be born during January, it was quickly apparent that Fae had inherited a family ability (and an almost forgotten one by that): she was a metamorphmagus. She was an easy child to understand because she quite literally showed her emotions with various shades and hues oh hair color. Growing up on the farm meant learning about how to work hard from a young age, and respecting the land around them. One could argue maybe even more so than the average druid. Being one with nature was one thing, but Fae always enjoyed working with it more, and how treating the crops and animals they raised right rewarded the family. In that matter, it only seemed fair that magic was to be treated the same way.

In school and around her peers her age, Fae was the quiet one that sat in the back. An observer, she liked practicing what they were taught over messing around with the other kids. Her closest friend couldn’t even attend school after all - the speckled griffin, who she affectionately named Storm, that lived in the pastures near Cloudbreaker Farm. She got along much better with the animals around her home than the other children, and had no qualms with refusing to play with them if her griffin friend couldn’t join. Despite the harmonious bonds between druids and animals, there was still the fact that the giant griffin, albeit young one, was not the best creature to be jumping through the woods with a pack of children. So Fae typically went off to play with Storm instead of the other kids, and that continued on well into her teenage years and young adulthood. She preferred the peace and quiet that was home, fully content with interacting just with her parents and Storm.

That was, until she turned fifteen and was sent off to Hogsmeade and Hogwarts for the first for exams. Having never left Hy-Brasil, the world outside was a suffocating and overstimulated experience. And she enjoyed it way more than she ever thought she would. Of course, that posed a lot of problems, because she didn’t want to leave home once she was done with school. Hy-Brasil was still going to be a wealth of comfort and safety, and she really didn’t understand how everything on the outside worked. To get a better idea of it, she decided to start volunteering as a visitor guide at the port. By the time she had “graduated” from school (with two more visits to Hogwarts under her belt now), she decided that staying on the island was better than nothing, but she could still get the thrill of talking to new people by being a full time tour guide for any visitors coming to the island. To her, that was the best of both worlds and satiated her hunger for knowing what was going on outside.

When the High Druid died in 2020, the whole island began preparations for who the new selection would be. Fae had never particularly thought of herself as an exceptional druid or witch, and certainly didn’t live an interesting life whenever there weren’t visitors on the island. But the golden snidget landed on her, and she was thrust into the position. The first year was tumultuous; the council had long been maintained by the same members, and they seemed (to her) to be disgruntled that a twenty-year old without much experience in their government had been chosen as the successor. But there was nothing to be done, and resigned to her fate, Fae dove in head first, learning of all the things she was now responsible until the day she died.

By 2022, she had begun to feel more confident in the role. There had been pushes by the Ministry following her coronation as the new High Druid to try and get certain aspects of Hy-Brasil integrated with their British counterparts, but she continued to hold out on to what had already been agreed upon between her predecessor and Minister Kingsley. The way of life that she had grown up enjoying had been because of that, and she wanted to keep it that way for as long as possible. 

And then the Minister was murdered. His own successor only lasted six months, following the same fate. Fae barely had a chance to start formalities with the man, before a much younger woman stepped into the role. The Ministers themselves were never an issue, but the council had warned her of the other politicians hidden underneath the Minister. The branches of government that wanted to place regulations on their creatures or how they practiced their magic. Kingsley had been pushy, but he was just being a politician. Under Victoire Weasley and her successor, Hermione Granger, Hy-Brasil and Fae felt like they had to continuously remind the Ministry of what their exact purpose and way of life was, constantly battling against long standing rules surrounding their education or the trace.
[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]With news of Minister Granger’s death, Fae wasn’t even sure how to react. Their relationship had been professional, and for once it sort of seemed like there were agreements they could have reached that may have benefited Hy-Brasil long term. But that was impossible to know, because apparently their people had elected a former athlete as the new Minister, and Fae wasn’t sure how that could really work out (and she realized how hypocritical that was, because she was chosen by a bird landing on her shoulder). During the later summer months, following the Minister’s death, Fae started to put together paperwork and a plan with her Ministry liaison to introduce to the new Minister once he took office. She was disappointed that it was going to be like going back to square one again, for the fifth time three years.

Hy-Brasil probably would have remained the same as it had been, if not for the barrier surrounding the island suddenly disappearing at the start of October 2025. She knew that the barrier of protection was created and maintained by Merlin’s staff, placed there by the man himself, and that she was one of only a few that knew the true location of the staff. With the barrier gone, and amidst the ensuing panic, she whisked away to the cave where it was located, finding the staff removed from its normal position, and laying upon the ground. There hadn’t been any training on what to do should this happen and the way of producing the barrier had surely been lost ages ago, so she brought the staff back with her to present to the council, hoping they would help her decide on the next step to take.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@colin  [/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]he/him [/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]25[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]est[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]idk[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@grey  @cordelia  @mina  @lily  @cara  @nottingham  @jimbo  @steve  @blaise  @harper  @renard  @nell  @nessa  @charlie  @lance  @madeleine  @mickey [/blockquote][/div][/div]
