[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://64.media.tumblr.com/e0623cb227c721e977975a21e10e26ef/tumblr_ollfjlO6LN1u4gmt6o1_500.gifv" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Jean DuPont[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]john du-pon[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]jay, jeanie, jj - whatever you like to be honest[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]19
January 8th, 2006[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]he/him - male[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]half-blood
half druid[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]pansexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]12 1/2", aspen wood, veela hair.[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]ezra miller[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]much like his playby, Jean is very tall at 6'1", with long, angular limbs and a pale complexion. He has a very strong jawline and shaggy black hair which he either grooms to perfection or lets fall wildly - depending on his erratic moods. He has a few tattoos on his person, a half moon on his shoulder and the phrase '[insert name here]' printed on the inside of his wrist in brackets. He can often be seen in eccentric, unmatched clothes he has stolen or thrifted from second-hand muggle stores.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Beauxbaton[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]graduated 2024[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]odd jobs. boudicca grace housekeeper when on isle.&nbsp;
con artist/grifter
will also help find belongings if possible - for cash.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]telling stories
travelling
finding things
drinking
smoking
making ava laugh
big cities&nbsp;
secrets

[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]being stuck in one place
enclosed spaces
religious zealots&nbsp;
boredom&nbsp;
anybody talking sh*t about ava&nbsp;
having no money&nbsp;
sobriety
being serious/emotional
loneliness&nbsp;

[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]when jean looks in to the future he's in a high rise flat with lots of windows, with a closet full of expensive clothes and a dark room for his sister to stay in. the house is never empty and the fridge is always full. he is the centre of attention.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]a crisp, fresh cologne or musky perfume. sun baked towels and the rolling salt of an ocean wave.&nbsp;[/blockquote][b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]jean cannot bear to feel insignificant or alone. to be truly known and still not enough haunts him. he also fears the harsh press of loneliness and losing his sister ava - that the allaway's might stop him from seeing her altogether.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Jean is a child that learned to tell stories instead of truths. Changing his name and his personality to suit whatever situation he is in. He is a social chameleon who can't quite figure out which colour to turn. He fears the dull, drag of monotony and so avoids it at all costs. Having grown up struggling to be seen and heard, he is often the loudest voice in a room. His stories twice as theatrical, his recounts a little off colour. Jean is also very self-driven, having learned that the only person who will fight his corner is himself. Ava is perhaps his biggest accomplishment. His dedication to her is Jean's most selfless act, though it is based on entirely selfish reasoning. He cannot bear to be alone and will do whatever it takes to avoid it. Even sticking around in Hy-Brasil-Boring. Or sleeping with strangers on the mainland.&nbsp;

At his core, Jean is deeply lonely. He craves acceptance and adoration. Having grown up without a family of his own, he desires the support, though is deeply afraid of allowing himself to be remotely vulnerable. The only person who has ever seen the 'real' Jean is his little sister Ava. And that is simply because she wouldn't trust any other fabricated version of him. He is a performer at heart, with a full bellied laugh and a charming personality. Falling from self deprecation and vanity as quickly as the tides change. He has expensive taste and a desire for excess. Jean wants to live and live well, even at his own detriment. Say what you will, a night out with Jean DuPont is not a night one is quick to forget.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Conteville, France. Saint Conteville's Insititute for Boys - orphanage.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]biological father: Fenrir Greyback
biological mother: Eira Allaway, died at 25

Mari Allaway, grandmother, 50
Cadogan Allaway, grandfather, 52

Siblings:
Avalbane Wolfsired , younger sister [full blood - aware]

Half-Siblings:
Rhys Greyback [paternal - unaware]
Jamie Greyback [paternal - unaware]
Dahlia LeLoup [paternal - unaware]
Maxima Greyback [paternal - unaware]

[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]non[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]On the quaint French border commune of Conteville Jean Dupont was born, and quickly deposited at the nearest orphanage. His mother was a Druid girl from a prestigious family on the elusive, private Island of Hy-Brasil. Eira Allaway had no intention of getting pregnant when she encountered Fenrir Greyback on the bracing borders of France. She had left the overbearing shackles of her home to experience life, but that had not included an unwanted child. It was a time she did not look back on fondly, knowing that a child would not be welcomed by her family. That its blood would bring shame upon the Allaway name. She could not bear it and so her pregnancy was completed in secret. Jean was left in the pews of a muggle church with a note pinned to his blanket and nothing more. 

The catholic nuns took the child to the sponsored orphanage of Saint Conteville’s Institute for Boys. Where the nameless infant was given a placeholder name and registered under the local council. Try as they might, they found no trace of his mother as she had long since fled for home. Jean DuPont was the boy with no family, no claim and no name. The catholic nuns were harsh, but mostly fair. Had it not been for Jean’s rebellious spirit and hyperactive personality, he might have gotten along fairly well. Alas, he was often victim to the stinging bite of a switch and had recited so many Hail Mary’s that he felt on personal terms with the ancient woman. They said he must have come from ‘bad blood’. That he was too quick to lie and rely on escapism where faith would do him better. Jean simply did not like the life dealt to him and so made a habit of creating others. Telling strangers fake names and tragic stories just for the fun of it. Eventually, lying became second nature to Jean. 

As Jean grew, his penchant for magic made itself well known. As a boy, he began displaying erratic bursts of magic that left furniture floating and plates flying. Jean had no understanding for it as he had been raised non-magique. Unfortunately, the nuns thought him possessed and sent him away to be exorcised at the High Church in the city. Had it not been for the intervention of a Beauxbaton alum, Jean might have died. His abilities cast in shadow, and shame. The wizard sent Jean to a fostering family of non-magique’s with experience in dealing with magical children. Jean was overjoyed, thinking himself something of a superhero. In actuality, he was somewhat mediocre. Years behind his fellow witches and wizards, though he was still invited to attend the Beauxbaton Academy of Magic when he came of age. 

Jean could not believe his luck. The Academy was breathtakingly beautiful. Finally, he was living in a place that reflected his desire for beauty and excess. He was not confined to the drab, humble attitude of Catholic nuns. At Beauxbaton he could be free, though perhaps he took this a little too literally. Jean did not have an academic mind, but a thrill for dramatics. An odd, often solitary boy who could be seen talking to himself or dragging his peers in to conversations without thought or reason. He was a good friend for the moment, but his odd bursts of energy and flaky, absent-mindedness bought him few friends. He was often made fun of as Jean was quick to tell tall tales. Every person who asked him where he had come from would receive a different, more fantastical answer. Jean had never been ashamed of being an orphan until he was around so many people with families. It was a hard lesson to learn, but he coped in his own odd way. 

Though he did not excel in classes or written examinations, Jean was very good at practical magic. He was also good at finding things. An ability rooted deep in his marrow; Jean felt tethered to the things he wanted to find. It was not an instantaneous ability, but one that grew with him. As a child, it did not matter where the nuns hid his precious, donated toys, Jean would always find them eventually. By ‘chance’ or ‘cheek’. As a teenager, Jean began to realise that he felt rooted to the people and the things he desired. When the river diving team hid his clothes after practise, Jean simply wandered across the grounds in his swimwear and found them dumped in a rose bush. When a young first year became lost in the maze of greenery, it was Jean who found her huddled under a craggy rock crying. Soon enough, Jean realised this was not a typical thing to be able to do. He begun testing his theory. Daring students to hide his precious belongings and betting them gold that he could find them for himself. He always won, even when a boy swallowed his rose pin in an effort to thwart him. 

Jean graduated Beauxbaton with few honours. Not a single sole attended the ceremony for him but he pretended he did not care. He had his stories, and when asked told of all the mad, fantastic places that kept his loved ones from him and his celebrations. However, without Beauxbaton to give him house and home, Jean had no idea what to do with himself. He was suddenly so very lonely. Without a steady job to keep him in place, Jean began to consider using his innate ability in a way he had never considered before. Perhaps, should he want it so very badly, he could find his mother. The family he boasted and lied of having could truly be out there. He need only to want it enough. It took time and focus Jean had never had before. His ability had only been flexed for menial, silly little things that got him gold and laughter. Finding a person so dear to him was more difficult, and yet when he felt that pull he’d never been more sure in his life. 

Jean’s ability led him towards the strange, magical island of Hy-Brasil. Where lore only stretched to the bordering isles where wizards and witches said very little. The only thing that allowed him to enter was his blood. Any who guided him on his way told him to turn back, that there was nothing for a boy like Jean there without a passport. Jean lamented that he was supposed to be there, that his blood led him there. He was utterly convinced his mother lived there and when he set foot on the island, fighting tooth and nail to get there, he knew it was true. Something clicked in him, though he was not met with the welcome he thought would find him. All they knew was that he had druid blood, luckily that was enough to gain him entry. This was the only thing that saved him upon first contact. 

Meanwhile, Jean had a singular focus. He told anybody who would listen, and could understand, that he was looking for his mother. He’d been surrendered to a church in France in 2006, very soon after his birth. Nobody willing copped to the child, but Jean knew he was in the right place. That tether leading him to the commune of the Allaway’s. A gruff, stoic family who had no living children. Just a single grandchild, the shy colourless preteen. When Jean seen her for the first time, he knew. This was the child that had brought him to Hy-Brasil. It was a hard lesson to learn, that his birth mother was dead and her existing family had no idea that Jean existed. Reluctantly, they agreed he must be her child as Eira had been in France at the time and Jean was half-druid. Ava was his sister. He did not grieve for his mother long, as he’d never really had her in the first place. Jean simply rejoiced at the fact that he had a family at all. Though they were not as equally pleased to have him. 

From that moment on, Jean created a tentative bond with his birth family. He was a nuisance, of course. Without an understanding of their strict customs or language. Ava had been so sheltered; they spoke only of the terrible influence he would provide. Jean didn’t care, they couldn’t send him away without good reason. Plus, he was blood. He had Eira’s eyes and pale complexion. And sometimes, when he smiled, he looked just like her. Ava was something else entirely, a creature that fascinated Jean. Her timid nature offered a challenge he was determined to overcome. It took over a month for Ava not to run when she seen him coming. Eventually, through stubborn perseverance, the two developed a strange bond. Jean told Ava ‘la vie il faut la vivre’. It was half a year spent forging a bridge between worlds and languages. Jean considered it a worthy quest. They could not have been more at odds, and yet something cemented them together. Be it blood or bond. 
 [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Upon discovering his family, Jean spent most of his time after graduation on Hy-Brasil. It left him fairly detached from the wizarding world and the events taking place there. Had he been more aware, though, it is likely Jean would not have been very moved. His fleeting attentions and waning self-centeredness meant he rarely seen beyond his and his own. Hag’s Fever meant Quarantining on the isle and staying with the Allaway’s, which suited him just fine. Though it did become slightly oppressive as time passed. Jean had never been very good at staying rooted, preferring to feel free from the shackles of responsibility. It also meant he could not attempt to smuggle goods and gifts on to the isle for Ava. It was quite irritating, all in all. 

When the barriers fell, Jean felt a thrilling excitement. Finally, he might be able to convince Ava to travel to the mainland with him. To see the world with his family, had it not been for her strict guardians, Jean would have smuggled her out a long time ago. Jean travels between Hy-Brasil and the United Kingdom quite regularly. For work opportunities, entertainment and a little bit of freedom. But, with Ava exposed to a little more of the world, it’s quite possible they will find far more than they bargained for. 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]chanel[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]24[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]GMT[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]rissy[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]whose to know![/blockquote][/div][/div]