[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt="" style="max-width:100%;" src="https://64.media.tumblr.com/a7d24293113e6b91014e417d5af22177/425e67a1b2993718-68/s540x810/b43f85bda945cde5696102a79379e51e2f2dfd8a.gif"]
[/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]eeva kilpela[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]ee-vah[/blockquote][b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Vee, Veve, Eve[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]26
July 2, 1999[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]pureblood druid[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Pansexual
Demiromantic[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]Wand: 11 1/4 inches, dogwood, unicorn hair
Staff: cedar, unicorn hair
Instrument: ocarina, unicorn hair[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Katrina Lilwall[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Height: 5'7
Red hair, covered in freckles. She's a stereotypical red head with warm brown eyes. Her ears are pierced several times, her nose has been pierced twice, and her belly button pierced. Eeva is very fit and strong, clearly someone that works out and takes good care of her body.

She has a pretty edge dressing style most of the time. She likes heavy make up, dark colors, crop tops, tank tops, and combat boots.

[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]home schooling[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduate[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Performer (she ran away to the circus)[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Performing (She IS a circus performer after all!)
Dancing
Singing
The cold
camping
Star gazing

[/blockquote][b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Dark wizards (And definitely a few in particular...)
Being in one place to long
big cities (unless it's for a performance)
People prying into her personal business after she's s
Going "home" (she doesn't hate home, just the painful reminders)
Holidays[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]To finally get justice (revenge) for her family against the dark wizards that killed them.
To visit every country in the world.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Dew, pine trees, wild flowers[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]That events will repeat themselves (someone is killed and she can't protect them).
Small/dark places.
[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]
Eeva comes across as a very aloof, carefree person. Someone to follows the wind, changing direction without rhyme or reason. She's the sort of person that isn't nailed down easily. She's nomadic by nature, and would rather spend her night under the stars then in a cramped apartment.&nbsp; She's very spontaneous, and often changes her mind with little warning. She also isn't the sort to share her reasoning, nor does she usually have any besides she "felt like it". This behavior makes her wildly unpredictable, though thankfully the behavior is harmless. This behavior has also made her quite independent and "self reliant", as she rarely expects others to follow her whims.&nbsp;

Eeva is a very environmentally conscious and nature loving individual due to her upbringing and her heritage. She's the sort of person that always recycles and will always choose the better for the environment option.&nbsp; She's also a very health conscious person (as her profession depends on it), and is very careful about what she eats.

When conversing and with other people her "head in the cloud" personality comes across quite strong. Her attention with flick in and out of the conversation, and she's quick to change the subject if a topic comes to mind. She's an incredibly difficult person to have a serious conversation with. Though this is very much intentional. Those that know her history know that her strongest defense mechanism is to just avoid serious conversations in general. She isn't one to really get angry, or upset, or overly passionate in a conversation, instead just staying an almost neutral "aloof".

Boiling beneath the surface though is a deeply hurt person. She's very guarded, and her aloofness is a way to protect herself. She doesn't have many deep relationships because of this, and doesn't open up to strangers about the traumas of her past. Nor will she discuss them with people that know about it.&nbsp;

Eeva hasn't coped with her childhood loss well. Instead, she's let it fester. So despite her outward personality she is someone that desperately wants justice (though, it's more like revenge). She wants those that hurt her family and community all those years ago to suffer, and pay for what they did. She whole heartedly believes in "an eye for an eye", and has come to care little for the rules and laws that condemn such ideology. She believes that while mercy, friendship and happiness are things every good person deserves, anyone that isn't "good" doesn't deserve it. You reap what you sow, and laws that protect you are void once you commit crimes against humanity. She wholeheartedly believes that the dark wizards that attacked her home and killed her family should be hunted down, tortured so they finally know how the druids and sami felt, and then killed. In a nutshell, a very twisted "I'll treat you the way you treat me" mentality.&nbsp;

[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Finnish Lapland (Stuorraguovssahasat)[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Loviisa Kilpela (nee&nbsp;Pöllönen), mother, deceased. Was a guardian
Luukas Kilpela, father, deceased. Was a Guardian.
Reko Kilepla, brother, deceased. Was a Guardian-in-training

Taikalainen family - cousins[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]None (may buy a magical creature pet later)[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Eeva was born and raised in the Finnish Druid/Sami community of&nbsp;Stuorraguovssahasat. HEr family was quite small, with just an older brother five years older. But they were happy. Her father's family had a heritage of being "protectors" of the community, guardians. A calling both her parents chose and loved. Reko, as he got older, even followed in their path. Eeva was the odd one out, the carefree, free spirited child. She was the sort to go dance on her own, and pick flowers, and all around just enjoy life. Her attention never stayed on anything too long. The only thing she really stuck with was her love for music, dance, and performing. She participated in everything she could, learning many traditional songs and dances at a very young age. This remained one of her only passions growing up. Despite her clear disinterest in the family "calling", her parents were happy. They taught her everything they could, but also let her pursue her passion whenever she was free.

When Eeva was fifteen however, her entire life turned upside down. While outsiders were visiting the small community, dark wizards attacked. Her parents, and brother, of course, were there to try and fight them off. That was their duty as guardians. Only... They didn't come home that night. All three were among the dead. While the dark wizards were arrested it didn't change the fact that they'd orphaned the druid girl. While she had other family in the community it wasn't the same. Her parents and brother were gone. THat was the day that a darkness entered her heart. An anger that couldn't be extinguished.&nbsp;

When she turned 17, Eeva ran away. Unable to bear the constant reminders of her lost family. She packed a bag and never looked back. She joined up with a magical circus in Oulu and started to perform. With more professional training she excelled. While the world outside the community she grew up in was a strange and terrifying place it gave her the relief she needed. Something that didn't remind her of her family.&nbsp;

The circus was the sort that traveled, and she with it. She learned many different acts and performances. The circus in particular loved her druid blood, as it made her a natural for working with the many creatures, especially when something happened. Her most common and popular acts involved singing, as she could call on her druidic and sami background, and performing with the magical creatures. They would never hurt her intentionally, which made her an ideal choice to be in charge of them.&nbsp;

With the circus she was able to see the world. For years they traveled across the continents. A life that Eeva came to love. The freedom of not being stuck in one place for long. Of course, it also meant taht she had few meaningful relationships with non circus members, but it was a sacrifice she was willing to make.&nbsp;

After the fall of Azkaban though, that anger she'd been carrying for years came to a boil. She didn't know if the wizards that had killed her family escaped, but the idea that people as horrible as them were on the loose... Well, she had ten years of unresolved anger. But alas, the circus was in South America at the time and there was little she could do. After the quarantine ended, however, the circus coordinators announced they'd be heading back to Europe. Specifically the UK...[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]While most the events have had little effect on Eeva, the Azkaban breakout deeply disturbed her. She was already harboring quite a bit of resentment towards criminals due to her family's death so the break out intensified those feelings.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Sora[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]29[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]Mountain[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]I live here >.<[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]too many[/blockquote][/div][/div]