[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://64.media.tumblr.com/d7f5a90638e9f7f1d39069ae26c698d1/3beee17ed3808e06-8b/s1280x1920/fd6522e1e5ae4ad358b735724772ab5c5562c85d.jpg" alt=""][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Cashel Ri Nightwalker[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]ka-shl ree night-walker[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Everyone now knows him as Ri
Those who know him pre-banishment call him Cash[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]25
January 23rd, 2000[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]male
he/him[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Pureblood Druid - Banished[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Straight
demi-romantic[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]Wand - 16” English Oak, Phoenix
Staff - Willow, Boomslang Venom
Ocarina - Chestnut, Fooper Feather[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Stephen James[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Different from many druids, Ri has always been able to tan well, has light green eyes and naturally has dark brown hair. He normally has his hair slicked back, but occasionally lets it go wild. Ri stands at 6’1 and has a number of tattoos across his body, with the most prominent being the brand on his forearm that he received when he was banished from his home. He also has a nose piercing, and a number of ear piercings.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Druid School
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduate
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]2018-2020: Druid Guardian
Present: Pirate, thief, animal smuggler, magizoologist [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Heights
The feel of falling
Magical creatures
Nature
Making alcohol
Smoking
Getting tattooed
Drinking alcohol
Thunderstorms
Flying through clouds
playing music
sketching
flying
clear night sky
sleeping outside in a hammock
wild nature of Hy-Brasil
magic mushrooms[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Being judged because of his past
The thought about being hated by his family/friends
Being branded an banished for doing something that he knew was right
Sharing his feelings
Dark arts
large gatherings
the forced disconnect from his family, friends, past, and home
seeing an animal injured
governments (especially when the make rulings without the full story)
large gatherings
the forced disconnect from his family, friends, past, and home
seeing an animal injured
governments (especially when the make rulings without the full story)[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]To be welcomed back to his home, the Council admitted that they were wrong to banish him and that he was right to do what he did (he also knows that this will [i]never[/i] happen.
Beyond the impossible, he doesn’t know what he wants with his life anymore, while the dust has settled after his banishment, he still feels a little lost.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]The air right before a storm
ocean breeze
Alcohol
Fresh fruit off the plant[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]being grounded (never being able to fly, in any way,  again)
Vanishing from the minds of the druids he once held dear to him.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Ri’s life was turned upside down when he was banished. Everything that he thought he knew was turned upside down. From this he learned to always be sceptical, less for those he feels comfortable around, but it’s always there. He also learned from this that it is better to look out for yourself, than to try to help someone. While he will still secretly help those who truly need it. 
But he has always been more reserved. Ri isn’t one to share his thoughts or emotions with others. When he feels very comfortable around them, he tends to open up some, especially when asked. He rarely will open up to someone unprovoked. Ri is also not one to strike up a conversation with anyone. He is often found pondering, sketching, or working. Often thinking about what life would look like if he hadn’t gone to the ruins that day. But knowing that nothing will change, he progresses. Admitting it to no one, Ri does feel lost. He has made a new life for himself, but still feels drawn to his old life and home, which he can never return to.
While not showing many emotions, Ri has made good friends on the ship, and will show some emotions to them, even if they are more calculative than natural. He also has a good ear for languages, picking words and meanings up quickly. Ri is very talented at dueling, martial arts and throwing knives.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Hy-Brasil[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Father - Eoghan Nightwalker, 60, guardian
Mother - Riona (nee Wormwood) Nightwalker, 52, winemaker
Older Brother - Laird Nightwalker, would be 27 (died age 22)
Younger sibling - 21 (open)

Paternal grandfather - Tabor Nightwalker, 92, retired guardian
Paternal grandmother - Yseult Nightwalker, 86, retired priestess
Maternal grandfather - Cían Wormwood, 85, retired winemaker
Maternal grandmother - Brigid Wormwood, 83, retired winemaker
Maternal Aunt - Nuala Wormwood, 54, winemaker
Maternal uncle - Aengus Wormwood, 55, winemaker
Cousin - @wormwood 
Cousin - Medb Wormwood, 28, winemaker, pure-blood Druid witch

@fae   - Astrological twin, former flame
@bjorn   - captain[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]n/a[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]January, thought to be unlucky by the druids, if they only knew. From the day of Ri’s birth, it would seem as though his life had already been planned out. He was born the same day as a little girl, Fae Cloudbreaker, meaning that they were destined to be together. Being young and free to explore Hy-Brasil, Ri enjoyed exploring the island, playing with those his own age. During the harvest season, he and his siblings would help his mothers family gather grapes for making wine. He was happy, and when he saw an injured animal, no matter how big or small, he would nurse back to full health. His mother said that was his calling.

As he grew older, the boy started to partake in classes, and when he was fifteen, he left his island for the first time and went to Hogwarts for his OWLs. He liked what he saw, noting the differences, though he was sure that he would always stay on his island. He loved it there, it was home. Going again to Hogwarts two years later, for his final NEWT exams, he had grown a lot and decided what he would do with the rest of his life.

After returning home, and with school finished up, Ri started on the path to become a guardian just like his father. He did all that was expected of him, he started on a respectable career, and began looking for someone to be with romantically.

Early 2020, Ri had settled in as a guardian, keeping things calm on Hy-Brasil. He found himself dealing with mostly tourists, making sure they respected the rules of the island. One evening, while taking a break from his job, he spotted his older brother, Laird, wondering into some runes that everyone knew only priestesses and high druids were allowed, and they only went during certain times of the year. Silently, he followed his brother, knowing that something wasn’t right. He could hardly believe what he saw. His own brother performed dark magic. Ri had a choice, leave to get reinforcements - and risk missing the act and sounding crazy - or to act now and explain himself later. Sending a quick message using his patronus, he chose to act, banishing the wand from his brother's hand and he confronted whom he once respected and looked up to. A fight ensued, by the time the guardians arrived, Laird was dead, and Ri’s hands, bloodied in the action. Ri was taken into custody, accused of murdering his own brother. With no evidence of dark magic being performed, the young man knew that no one would believe his story. Least of all his own family. His banishment was the last ruling that the old High Druid, leading to him being branded, and shipped out, never to return. 

Being released to the world, Ri felt lost. Not having any time to feel sorry for himself, Ri jumped into looking for a job. He now needed money, something that he had never cared to possess before. Months of searching, and he was turned away at every try. He was making his way to ask a magical creature reserve, when a dangerous creature broke from its area and began to rampage. The druid boy quickly assisted, bringing the creature back, calmed and happy. After being turned down for the job, Ri walked away, defeated. His mind wandered to a place that it had gone many times since leaving his home. With a heavy sigh, he contemplated something dark and weak, but what other options were there? He had nothing, and no one now.

This was when he was approached by a stranger. After some time, and an introduction, Ri began to sail on the Jolly Roger, assisting in the less than legal transport of magical creatures, among other things.
 [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]It has been five years since his banishment, and while this is the world he now must live in, he cares little for their problems. Hearing that his astrological twin, and once good friend, and old flame became High Druid after his leaving, it has left Ri to think “what if” a lot over the years.

Hearing about the barrier going down on the island, he wants to help, but knowing that he can never set foot on his home again leaves the taste bitter sweet.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Sophi[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]Unsure (Must be 18-years-old or older)[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]MST[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]This is my home[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]See for yourself [a href="https://alohomorax0.proboards.com/thread/9784/sophis-insanity-version-2"]HERE[/a].[/blockquote][/div][/div]
