[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://64.media.tumblr.com/a7d75041941d9edb741f6c2ae8c59d8d/598a0a3af7af511b-86/s500x750/77299a7936bdfb3f96f0fa8bff92b5becc8ec798.gifv" style="max-width:100%;" alt=" "][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]tiernan brennus nightwalker[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]tear-nan br-en-us night-walk-er.[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]tye. he has others but he prefers tye and and only when it's said like tie. [/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]23 | october 13th. [/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]he/him.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]pureblood druid. [/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]bisexual. [/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]10", oak and bowtruckle skin, flexible. [/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]jacob elordi.[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]tye stands at about 6 foot even. he's got something of an average build but he's lithe from his years of being a hunter while he was living on hy-brasil. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling &amp; status[/b]
[blockquote]druid school.[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote][i]previous:[/i] hunter.
[i]current:[/i] unemployed.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]the thrill of a chase, open spaces, blue skies, the sound of waves on the shore, wine, tending a garden, watching things grow, all animals, people, thunderstorms, flying, the woods at night, tracking things.  [/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]disturbing the balance of nature, when people take too much, loosing a catch, the disconnect in his family, his brothers being gone, when his parents don't listen, being held back, not being able to do his own thing, being controlled. .[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote][b]hot headed[/b] | you'd think being hot headed and being a hunter wouldn't mix but tye made them work pretty well. while he was hunting he was able to calm himself, the quiet and focus he needed to do kept him in check. it's when he was at home and around other people that he sometimes found his temper flaring. he's not one to hold back when he doesn't feel right about a situation and if something gets his back up he's going to react. he's had a hard time since his brother was banished, fighting against the opinions of the other druids, refusing to believe what they say is true. 

[b]stubborn[/b] | he's not one to be told what to do and when to do it. from a young age he's always been his own person and hardly anyone has ever been able to convince him to do things. his older brothers were the exceptions to the rule. they could get him to do just about anything because he idolized them so much. since they've both been gone it's been hard for people to get through to him and steer him in what they think is the right direction. 

[b]out spoken[/b] | he's never been one to mince his words. he'll speak his mind because that's what he feels he was born to do. he doesn't feel the need to sugar coat the things he says because what's the point? if he didn't say what he felt he'd feel like he was letting himself down and not getting his point across. he feels that when people hide what they really feel and don't say what they really want to say it just makes situations worse, drags problems out and doesn't fix anything. 

[b]calculating[/b] | being a hunter he's had to be calculating. he's had to learn how to think ahead, how to plan for the unexpected and to have more than one plan in any situation. if he ever returned to the village empty handed he'd feel so much shame so there was the need to come up with multiple ways to bring meat back if his first plan failed. he's still learning to use this skill to his advantage in the day to day but he's learning, the skill is there he just has to hone it still. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]hy-brasil.[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]father | eoghan nightwalker | 60| guardian.
mother | riona (nee wormwood) nightwalker | 52 | winemaker.
older Brother | laird nightwalker | would be 27 | died age 22.
older brother | @cashel        | 26 | pirate/thief/smuggler.

paternal grandfather | tabor nightwalker | 92 | retired guardian.
paternal grandmother | yseult nightwalker | 86 | retired priestess.
maternal grandfather | cían wormwood | 85 | retired winemaker.
maternal grandmother | brigid wormwood | 83 | retired winemaker.
maternal Aunt | nuala wormwood | 54 | winemaker.
maternal uncle | aengus wormwood | 55 | winemaker.
cousin | @wormwood      
cousin | medb wormwood | 28 | winemaker.[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]none.[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]really there wasn't anything different about how tye grew up to anyone really. sure there were differences being a druid but the basics were the same really. he had two parents who loved him, two older brothers that he idolized and a whole host of extended family and cousins and the rest of the druids on hy-brasil that made it feel like his family was endless. he grew up following his brothers, helping tend to the vines their family grew to make their wine and learning all he could about the natural world around them. he'd long shown an affinity for being able to catch animals. he'd catch them and his brother would tend them and care for them. he never set out to hurt them, he loved animals but there was a certain thrill about being able to outsmart animals that in all reality had a stronger survival instinct than he did. 

he grew up learning the druid way of life, the magic they had and he wasn't the worst when it came to his studies but it was hard for him to just sit there and do them. his parents struggled to make him even though it was important and the only one who could talk him into sitting down long enough to do them was usually cash. cash was the brother he connected with the most even though he loved laird just as much. perhaps it was because he and cash were closer in age. his parents eventually honed onto the fact if they needed tee to do something, to ask him through his brother. 

the first time he left the mainland was when he had to attend hogwarts to do his exams and if he was honest with himself he didn't really see the appeal of the rest of the world. his life was pretty good where it was. he had his family, he enjoyed the job he was training for and the island provided them with what they needed. he was intrigued by some of the modern aspects of the world but he didn't find them interesting enough to go back to the mainland once he was done with his exams. he stayed on the island, fell into the routine of life and for a while it was good. 

then everything changed. cash murdered laird. that's all he really knows. he's never heard any other version from his parents or the powers that be on the island. he was barred from talking to cash after it happened, kept away from his brother when he was sentenced and then not allowed to see him before he was banished from the island. it was like the whole world broke in that moment and nothing felt right. both his brothers were gone. his parents were angry, bitter and they would hardly talk to him about it. all he wanted to know what had happened and the story he'd been fed about how cash had killed his brother in cold blood for no reason. as angry as he was at his brother for taking lairds life something in him refused to believe it had been for nothing. that wasn't cash. it wasn't his brother. 

things continued to spiral from there. tye found himself falling victim to his temper more and more. he got into arguments with other druids who spoke ill of his brothers, he got into fights with the ones who wouldn't back down and he found himself being punished more and more for it. the times he felt the most at peace where when he was out in the wilderness, when he was hunting because he had to focus on the task, keep himself in check because the animals could sense him, sense his anger and the energy he was putting out into the world. he tried to stay on the island. he tried to make it work but eventually he knew he couldn't. he could hardly look at his parents because they weren't telling him the truth, they could hardly look at him for the shame he was brining them with his unruliness and he knew he needed out. 

so he left. he left the only place he'd called home with nothing more than the clothes on his back and his wand. he's been trying to find his brother ever since he left the island. he knows the world is huge but he knows his brother is out there somewhere and that's enough to keep him looking. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]shadow.[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her.[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]not old enough to be your mother.[/blockquote][/div][/div]