[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/article_thumbnails/magazine/2018/05_2018/sam_heughan_magazine/650x350_sam_heughan_magazine.jpg"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]petri taikalainen[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]peh-tree[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]pete - for mainlanders who cannot fully pronounce his name[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]22, 12 May[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]he/him[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]druid[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]pansexual, polyamorous[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]willow and unicorn hair, 12 3/4 inches, supple[/blockquote]
[b]staff:[/b]
[blockquote]willow and unicorn hair[/blockquote]
[b]instrument:[/b]
[blockquote]mandolin[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Sam Heughan[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Petri is a towering 6'4, long and lean. He has sleepy, grass green eyes and a broad nose and the hint of a smile always plays at his lips. He is slightly less bulky than his playby, and has shoulder length red hair that is usually tied back. He also wears horn rimmed glasses when reading or working.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Homeschooled
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduate
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]St Mungo's Plant and Poisoning Apprentice Healer[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]potions, the smell of mixed herbs, frosty air, providing for his family, helping others, peppermints, evergreen trees, reading, nature[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]burning things, coffee (so bitter), textbooks, being away from his kommun, people who are skeptical of being healed, contrived buildings, trolls[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]To heal the world of all pain[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Peppermint, freshly fallen snow, pine[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]For Hag's Fever to have a resurgence, for his family to turn their backs on him[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Petri is, by all accounts, a good person. He believes strongly in healing the world, witch or wizard, druid or muggle. A traditionalist by Druid standards, Petri has a deep connection with nature and using natural resources. He is easy to mislead and incredibly trusting. Petri will bend over backwards to make life easier and better for other people, and is loyal to a fault. Petri finds joy in little things, such as spending time with family, making balms for dry skin and silent winter days. He is not overly fond of the world outside his kommun, though decided to spend some time at St Mungo's to increase his healing knowledge.  

With little to no technical knowledge, Petri is like other druids and does not trust muggle technology. He believes wizards got on fine for hundreds of years, so there is not much need to change things. Having a reluctance to change might make some see him as petulant or stubborn, but Petri is just comfortable with the status quo, unless it involves healing an ailment. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Lapland, Finland[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Otso Taikalainen - younger Brother, 5, druid.
Tyyne Taikalainen - younger sister, 14, druid.
@virvatuli  - younger sister, 18, druid.
@aidan  - cousin, 19, druid, apprentice at MWRC
Pertu Taikalainen - twin brother, 22, druid.
@eeva - cousin, 26, druid, circus performer
Hilla Taikalainen née Pöllönen- Mother, 48, Druid, reindeer herder.
Väinö Taikalainen - Father, 52, Druid, Elder.[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]a snowy owl called Adda[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote][From Virva's App]
Petri grew up in a small community of druids, Sami-born-wizards and other nordic wizards. It was a small group of druids that branched off from Hy-brasil when Finland came to be some hundred years ago. While initially a lot like most druids, they came to find that the country cared more for nature than most and the Sami people upheld many beliefs and traditions that were the same as those of the druids. While still highly distrustful of any non-magical people, they are slightly less hostile towards muggles. They allowed trade with the muggle Sami, as they follow the same religion and tradition as the Northern druids. They look down on those choosing to intact too kindly with even those muggles but are slowly growing less suspicious, or at least the youth is. They do feel very strongly about dark magic, possibly more so than the originals. If you are found guilty of practising dark magic you will not only be banished but you'll be stripped of all magic materials and any druid markings you might have. If the process kills you then the spirits found your deeds worthy of curses and consumed your sacred soul to return life to the lands you stole it from.

Petri and his twin brother Pertu grew up without great incident. The pair got into magical and non-magical hijinks, usually started by his twin and finished by his younger sister, Virva. Petri spent many winter and Yule celebrations with his cousins in Hy-Brasil, and grew exceedingly close with his cousin Aidan when he was old enough to speak. The pair often wandered about their lands, searching for herbs and plants with which they could make a magical paste. Petri's goal was always to make a fix-it-all salve that when swallowed or rubbed on an injury, would take away the pain. As such, Petri's youth was sheltered, but not unhappy.

Petri was always the quiet Taikalainen sibling, preferring to keep to himself unless he was with a trusted member of his druid clan. With his lack of much human interaction, he grew up to be an easily misled young man. He attended classes within his kommun, and never spoke much until spoken to. Some of the other druids found him odd, even amongst their own kind and led him into various nefarious plots. One such plot was that Petri was lured into the lair of a tribe of trolls. The young druids had told Petri that they'd found a special plant in the clearing, and he believed them without a doubt. Luckily, his twin brother came to the rescue and with the distraction of twin mandolins, Petri and his brother were able to get away unscathed.

Unfortunately, that was not the only incident where Petri put his trust in the wrong people. Years later, after completing most of his magical schooling, Petri signed up to a natural healing course offered only to serious students, and worked on a project regarding spattergroit and various natural remedies with a beautiful boy called Siiggur. He'd been struck from first meeting, and Siiggur used that to his advantage. Petri wrote their entire paper and taught Siiggur everything he knew, letting Siiggur steamroll over him and take all the credit come time for final marks. Though Petri easily forgave the beautiful boy, it was part of the reason he decided to move to the mainland (frightening! But at least Virva was there to protect him) and join St Mungo's as an apprentice healer. [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Petri was far removed from most of the magical occurrences happening in Great Britain before he relocated from his kommun in northern Finland to London tat the start of 2025. Though reluctant to assist outside of his realm of expertise, Petri was pulled from the plant ward to work on patients suffering from Hag's Fever. He would never forget those endless nights, those final breaths and the ringing in his ears of various emergency bells. Petri was also on shift when the fireworks malfunction happened, and helped to treat those patients who did not require immediate attention. Haunted still by the Hag's Fever patients, Petri turned his focus again to finding a cure all salve of sorts. When the Hy-Brasil barrier fell, it did not much affect Petri as he had been able to visit Hy-Brasil whenever he wanted. He did feel bad for the druids there who wanted to remain unknown, but he reasoned things are always found out eventually. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Ana[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]She/her.[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]27[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]GMT[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]I was dragged here[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]Felix, Astrid, Brígh[/blockquote][/div][/div]