[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://66.media.tumblr.com/9952773d4a1123cc0d6fdd6419d3aca4/tumblr_ph20kd9gZF1vgpb6so3_400.gif" alt="(image here of playby)"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Virvatuli Lahti Taikalainen[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]Vihr-vah-tuh-lee[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Virv, Vir, Lahti[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]18, June 24th[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Female. she/her[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Pureblood, Druid
[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Pansexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]None[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Jessica Luostarinen[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Virva is slender but surprisingly strong for her stature. Her eyes are an icy blue that is claimed to look almost unnatural. She often looks a little strange in her environment and favours bright colours over muted ones any day. She regularly sports hair accessories made of natural materials like flowers, bone and leather, usually all combined.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Homeschooled
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduated[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Auror trainnee at MoM UK[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Reindeer, snow, pines, her family, children, magic, nature, squirrels.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Industry, technology, dark wizards, forest fires, creaking of ice.[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Living with her family in nature surrounded by her kids and a lot of reindeer, singing songs.
Being a strong auror able to protect everybody she cares about.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Snow, petrichor, reindeer.[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Everything that she touches dying in her hands, being isolated in a cold dark place without any life around her. Dying in a blazing fire, being stuck under the ice and unable to dig her way up.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Virva is a peculiar kind of girl. She has little to no inhibitions and carries her heart and emotions on her sleeves. Despite that she'd smart enough to deceive, although she only does so when she feels it's needed to protect the ones she cares about. She appears very naive most of the time but is a lot wiser than her often erratic behaviors shows. Those that get to know the silly youth often find themselves surprised at the hidden depths of her personality and the sacred wisdom she hides that was passed down from her father.&nbsp;

Virva can be quick to anger and can be very hot headed when you rub her the wrong way. She's open and warm in all possible ways unless you give her reason not to be. She forgives easily but always remembers a wrong that has been done so that she won't trust again if she's wronged twice by the same person.&nbsp;

Virva loves children and reindeer most of all and has endless enthusiasm when interacting with both. She's far more patient around them and often volunteers to babysit both her younger brother and many of the other druid children in the community.
[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Northern Finland (Lapland)[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Otso Taikalainen - younger Brother, 5, druid.
Tyyne Taikalainen - younger sister, 14, druid.
Petri Taikalainen - older brother, 21, druid.
Pertu Taikalainen - older brother, 21, druid. 
Hilla Taikalainen née Pöllönen- Mother, 48, Druid, reindeer herder.
Väinö Taikalainen - Father, 52, Druid, Elder.

@cas    - Acquaintance, looks up to him.[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Mäki, the Moke[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Virva grew up in a small community of druids, Sami-born-wizards and other nordic wizards. It was a small group of druids that branched off from Hy-brasil when Finland came to be some hundred years ago. While initially a lot like most druids, they came to find that the country cared more for nature than most and the Sami people upheld many beliefs and traditions that were the same as those of the druids. While still highly distrustful of any non-magical people, they are slightly less hostile towards muggles. They allowed trade with the muggle Sami, as they follow the same religion and tradition as the Northern druids. They look down on those choosing to inact too kindly with even those muggles but are slowly growing less suspicious, or at least the youth is. They do feel very strongly about dark magic, possibly more so than the originals. If you are found guilty of practising dark magic you will not only be banished but you'll be stripped of all magic materials and any druid markings you might have. If the process kills you then the spirits found your deeds worthy of curses and consumed your scorced soul to return life to the lands you stole it from. 

When Virva was seven, two curse breakers showed up to the village. It was uncommon, yet not unheard of. Between the various cultures, powerful artifacts surfaced from time to time. While both the Sami and the druids were not fond of curse breakers, they accepted dealings when artefacts were tainted and cursed by dark wizards. Though the two curse breakers did not stay for long, Virva strongly took to one of the men, it certainly helped that he taught her a few magic tricks with permission from her father. She was growing into her powers at this age and already took kindness to the reindeer that her mother cared for. 

While the two men were over, a small group of dark wizards attacked and several of the villagers died. Casimir managed to save the life of young Virva, making himself her eternal hero in the process. Not that he was aware of that. After overcoming the threat, Casimir and his master soon left again, but he'd left quite an impression on young Virva. While her parents were not too happy that Virva was interested in people not too loved by their community, they were careful to first see how it developed before trying to make her understand what was wrong with hungering after artefacts that did not belong to them. Yet Virva was soon to show that her interest was far more in the idea of becoming a skilled fighter than in curse breaking, and her parents left the seed to grow. It was clearly the will of the spirits. 

In the years after the loss of their community members was the next thing to leave a large impression on Virva. While her father briefly offered her the option of studying magic at a school, he  taught Virva all she needed to know and she became a good and crafted witch by the time she ordinarily would have graduated. Having mastered plenty of the basic magic she went to Helsinki for the first time to partake in the actual NEWT level exams to get a certificate to be able to apply for a job outside her own community. Virva fully intended to see the world outside of her community, that much had been clear from a very young age. While her parents supported her, they were wary of the world outside and gave her many pieces of sage advice on her way out to explore the world. 

After due dilligence and some research Virva decided that the best course of action to become more like her childhood hero was to join a squad of highly skilled evil fighters. She didn't quite remember the details of why they had been here, but she wanted to be able to protect her people much like he once had. She found that the credentials at the British ministry were worth more than those she could get in Finland, so she sought a wizarding family to take her in as au pair. It would mean she didn't have to worry about food and lodging too much while she worked on her internship, as she referenced the traineeship she had as auror. While she plans to eventually go back in full to the druids community, she also wants to visit Hy-brasil and learn more about her druid cousins, as she mentally sees them. [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Considering the big explosions, the escaped inmates and all the other stuff that kept the UK such a busy place, Virva considered it to be very normal that their auror department had to be one of the best in the world. Still, at times she was starting to wonder if her choice hadn't been particularly stupid, as dying in the line of duty wasn't exactly one of the things she intended to do. She wanted to learn how to fight and defend others, but this wasn't quite what she'd had in mind. Maybe something just a little less chaotic? Either way, she wasn't about to quit now.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Seph[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Sher[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]28[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]GMT+1[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]-points to Heleens sheet-[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@seph   , @auguste   , @luthien   , @shreya   , @argentum   , @bobby   [/blockquote][/div][/div]