[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://64.media.tumblr.com/9012e28d3c7a72091105864bca1304c9/587fd8245ddfa748-3e/s1280x1920/5099ba29407e1ab04b634a2809828f5e7b829745.jpg" alt=" " style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Aofe Oak Willowbreath[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]ee-fa oak will-oh-br-eh-th[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Open to suggestions[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]24
22 March 2001[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Female - she/her[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Pureblood Druid[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]bisexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]Wand - 15.6, ebony, Mermaid scales
Staff - spruce, Mermaid hair
Lyre - willow, fairy wing(s)[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Renata valliulina[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Aofe stands at 5’4, and has a very slender shape. Her long orange hair is normally let to naturally curl as wit peases, though sometimes she will straighten or curl it to look nice. Her fair skin and baby blue eyes stand out against her darker hair. Aofe rarely wears makeup, but if she doesn it is usually some dark eyeliner to emphasize her eyes.  She has a number of small tattoos around her body, most hidden by wearing clothes. One of such tattoo is in line with her right shoulder, just under her collar bone that says “never say never”[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Druid School
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduated 2019
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Head Ranger[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]climbing
being out in nature
music of the forest
magic mushrooms
swimming in the ocean
taking care of magical creatures
stargazing
modern wizards sweets
herbology
making potions[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]dark arts
people beating around the bush (just come out and say it)
talking behind her back(if you have a problem with her, say it to her face)
muggle cities (though she does have to go in them occasionally)
acromantulas
Poaching or trophy hunting magical creatures 
flying muggle machines
unnatural sounds[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]At present, to get all magical creatures that fled Hy-Brasil back home safe and sound
To one day have a family of her own[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]ocean air
summer breeze
genuine smiles
feathers
electrified air around and during a thunderstorm[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Hy-Brasil being developed
dementors
losing her connection to nature and creatures[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Aofe is a free spirit. She goes where the wind takes her. She likes to take things with an air of positivity. She believes that a life well lived is a happy life. She always tries to find the good and fun in everything. Though bad things do happen there’s always balance, and good things to be found in it. The girl has a close connection with the earth and all nature, spending plenty of time in all elements she dances and climbs on the earth, while she swims and splashes in the water, and glides on the wind using the wings of her dear winged Granian. When she doesn’t know what the best step to do is, she finds a nice place where the sounds of nature are calming, she will then sit, close her eyes and let nature speak. Feeling the movement of nature helps her keep balance on the island. She loves all forms of nature, magical or not.

The girl follows her whims, and the movement of the world around her. She is usually a happy person, but her mood can turn sour when the situation dictates it. Aofe does have a mischievous streak, mostly around friends and family that she is most comfortable with. Though when she turns from her happy demeanor, best beware if you're on her radar. She can be quite a fierce protector of what she loves.

She is a hard worker, though she loves what she does, so it hardly feels like work, even if it isn’t easy. Speaking fluent Goblin and Mermish certainly help her as well. When she speaks with a magical creature, she addresses them in a language, and tone that they would best understand. She has always loved to learn, and is not afraid to ask questions. Though she hates hearing simple answers such as “no” or “fine” and vague answers such as “because I say so.” If you can't give a decent answer, best not bother. If there is a reason, she prefers all the information, so she can make her own decisions. Also, when she asks stuff how someone’s day is, she actually wants an answer, not a generic basic lie of an answer. Aofe strives to keep an open mind in situations, wishing to hear all sides before making a final decision. 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Hy-Brasil[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Caesar - paternal grandfather - 90 -  former council member
Rae - paternal grandmother - 87 - retired teacher
Efron - maternal grandfather - 91 - magical conduit maker
Kari - maternal grandmother - 76 - retired customs officer

Adair - father - 55 - visitor guide
Bambi - mother - 49 - magizoologist 

Unn - older sibling - 25
Sage - younger sibling - 21[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Phoenix - Quinn
Winged Horse: Granian - Lir[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Spring is a time for change and new growth. Aofe was born on the last day of Ostara, the Druid’s celebration of the spring equinox. Her birth brought life and excitement to her parents. The young babe was a happy girl, always laughing and smiling. Little changed as she grew. The second she could stand on her own two feet, was the second that she was off. Taking off to explore every nook and cranny before she could even talk.

The older she got, the higher she climbed, and the more she explored. As she was free to roam, she befriended many of the creatures. It wasn’t uncommon for her to bring an injured or lonely home. A young dragon with a broken wing, Niffler who seemed to have gotten the wrong thing stuck in its pouch, or even a bowtruckle who had lost its way (fully intending to help it find its home in the morning). When she was seven years old she saved a baby phoenix that fell from a tree. It wasn’t really a baby, she had noted the ash falling, it was just one that had mis-stepped when burning back down to childhood. Either way, the determined little girl took it home, like all the rest. She nursed it and helped it get back on its feet. As all the others, she had promised her parents that she would let it go when it was ready. But the creature became rather attached to her, and she named it Quinn.

The inquisitive girl loved to learn and enjoyed her lessons. She learned best when seeing and doing, rather than more traditional methods practiced off the island. Though when the time came, she did have to go to Hogwarts for her OWL and NEWT exams. Choosing to spend the months there in the forest as often as she could. Though she did find a love for their sweets.

After graduating, Aofe spent a year off the island, working at a magical reserve, learning how others off the island worked with the creatures, learning new healing methods and whatever else she could. After that time, she returned back home and became a ranger, helping the island keep an economical balance. [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]The past October when the barrier went down, it caused a lot of work for Aofe and the other rangers. She went right to work, chasing down the creatures that fled in confusion. She has assisted some in returning, but she knows there are still many out, lost and probably scared. With the events, the council created a new Advisor position, appointing Aofe. Having direct contact with the Ministry in regards to the ongoing search for bringing back all Hy-Brasil creatures.

While she does travel a great deal, she cares little about the goings on in the world outside. She knows about the newest island, but due to her Druid upbringing, wants nothing to do with it, even if her nature is more on the curious side.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Sophi[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]Unsure (Must be 18-years-old or older)[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]MST[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]This is my home[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]See for yourself [a href="https://alohomorax0.proboards.com/thread/9784/sophis-insanity-version-2"]HERE[/a].[/blockquote][/div][/div]
