[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][/div][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/originals/30/2b/30/302b30356bfbef96e9969ee2cad38b55.jpg" alt=""]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]avalbane tierneigh wolfsired[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]av-all-bain[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Just Ava, please[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]14-years-old
July &nbsp;29, 2011[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Female
she/her[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Half blood
Half Druid[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Demisexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]wand:&nbsp;9 inches, willow, unicorn hair
staff: same wood and core as wand
instrument: harp - same wood and core[/blockquote][b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]nastya zhidkova[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Height: 4'10

Ava is... unusual that is for sure. The girl was born with Oculocutaneous Albinism, which is to say that her body doesn't create melanin. So, in a nutshell... she doesn't have any pigment. Her hair is naturally white, her skin pale, and her eyes appear to be violet. It should be known that her eyes aren't violet, not really. Because her eyes lack pigment, her pupils are actually translucent, so they always have a purple/pinkish hue to them. You are literally seeing the blood vessels in her eyes.

Being albino has, unfortunately, plagued the girl with quite a few problems through her life. A lack of pigment can be far more harmful then many people realize. She has several eye problems. She is sensitive to light (bright lights can be uncomfortable and sometimes even painful). Her vision in general is poor, but it hasn't gotten too bad yet (her eyesight is slowly getting worse) so she does need to wear glasses to read anything and to see anything that is too far away. She also has Nystagmus (also common in albinism), which is irregular rapid eye movement. Basically, her eyes will sometimes begin to 'shake' very quickly back and forth. Her skin is also affected, in the sense that she is completely incapable of tanning (no pigment=no tan), but also far more receptive to sunburning because she doesn't have that layer of protection. She literally has to cake on the sunscreen if she's going to be out for more then a few minutes.



She wears a special pair of glasses (magically enchanted, of course) that help correct her vision but also protect her eyes from bright lights.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Home school (grandparents and a few... select others teach her)
"Beauxbaton" to all her fellow teenage druids (they don't know the truth)[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]equivalent of a fourth year[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]n/a[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]dusk
small spaces
being alone or with one/two people she trusts
exploring
reading anything she gets her hands on
Adventure novels
butterflies (She has quite a few books on them.)
Animals in general
Writing letters
spending time with her brother (she doesn't know about her other siblings yet)[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]new people
crowds (she classifies 3 people a crowd.)
bright days
parties
people asking too many questions
being touched unexpectedly
people looking at her
big/open spaces.
Being called her "last name"[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Ava really wants to get over her.... trouble with people. She's the sort of girl that wants to be confident, and strong, and be liked.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]the ocean, old books, pine[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Ava has severe social anxiety, and is absolutely terrified of strangers. To the point that she goes out of her way to avoid everyone that she doesn't know and would burst into tears when confronted during her younger years. Now that she's a bit older though she runs and hides.
Ava is absolutely terrified that her biological father is going to come and kill her (thanks grandparents for instilling that fear...)[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Ava, for lack of better words, is a pathetic human being. She has led an unusual life so, because of that it's had a negative impact on her personality. She has very, very poor social skills. But even that it an understatement. The girl is deathly shy, to the point that when she was a child she actually cried if you so much as looked at her. Thankfully she's outgrown that but she does get very squirmy if she catches you staring at her for more then a few seconds. For obvious reasons she is very self conscious, and she has problems with her appearance being brought up by anyone (even her own parents.). Even those that know her can sometimes struggle to get her to speak much, her verbal communication usually short sweet and to the point. She doesn't bother much with useless conversation fluff, making her quite direct. 



The girl is, to no surprise, a loner. She's always struggled with making friends but she is extremely loyal to the few she does get close to. She isn't the sort of person to have any half hearted friendships, or short lived ones. So if you managed to get on this girl's good side you'll have a friend for life. She is very sweet as well, without a mean bone in her body. She is quick to compliment others, quick to encourage, and quick to point out praiseworthy achievements of those she cares for. If there is anyone that can make you feel like you are an extraordinary human being, it's Ava. 


She's also infamous for just.... disappearing when she feels overwhelmed. The girl has an uncanny ability to find hiding places to the point where she will seek them out upon first getting familiarized with a location.
 Ava is very jumpy, and unfortunately clumsy at the same time. So you can easily startle her... and she'll likely fall on her face in the same moment.&nbsp;

Ava is a terrifyingly smart person. She absorbs information like a sponge. Though most of her knowledge is superficial in the sense that she is book smart, not street smart. She can understand how something works, in theory, but put it in front of her and she can't do it herself. Though, she doesn't share this knowledge with most people. Her grandparents, of course, know to an extent but even then they don't really know just how smart she really is. No, her past has told her to keep her mouth shut most of the time.[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Hy-Brasil[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]biological father: Fenrir Greyback
biological mother: Eira Allaway, died at 25

Mari Allaway, grandmother, 50
Cadogan Allaway, grandfather, 52

Jean Dupont , older brother (full blooded brother. She is aware of him)


Rhys Greyback, older brother (she's unaware of him)
Jamie Greyback, older sister (she's unaware of her)
Maxima Greyback, older sister (she's unaware of her)
(some others as well.)[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]none.[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Avalbane's story isn't a happy one. Her mother was a naïve druid girl brought up by two very strict and over protective parents. They didn't let her do much of anything, even by druid standards. In general, the Allaways were always known as a very secretive and withdrawn family. They chose to live as far as possible from other druids, and rarely attended festivals or ceremonies except when necessary. Their daughter, Eira, rarely got to spend time with other druid children, her parents worried that she'd be "poisoned" by non-druid ideas. In all, they were extremists.&nbsp; When Eira was 18, however, she did what many children brought up in sheltered live styles did. Took off and went a little freedom crazy. She wanted to see the world. Experience the wonders that her parents had never let her. One night she had one drink too many and woke up the next days with only memories. She knew what she'd done, of course, and the brief memories of the man. Not handsome by any standard, but he'd been there.&nbsp;

It was supposed to be a one time thing, never to come back up. Only, several months later she realized she was pregnant. She initially thought of going home to her parents but was worried what they might think. So, she started to look into adoption options, once the baby was born. She was in France when the baby boy was born, and she immediately dropped in off at an orphanage.&nbsp;

She didn't think much of the baby boy she gave up. She stabilized a bit, getting a job, an apartment. Creating a life of sorts. Several years later a familiar man reappeared in her life. The father of her first born son. To be honest, she'd liked how dangerous the man seemed the first time and so, a short affair followed. After two months though, he left. And once again, she found herself pregnant. She never even knew his real name. 

Around the time she was six months pregnant there was a story in the news of a "Greyback sighting". The name was familiar. Being a druid she obviously knew the name of the most infamous werewolf in history. As werewolves were monsters. Only... when she saw the story she realized she vaguely recognized the face and a horrible realization struck. The father of the son she gave up. The one who had to be the father of the baby she was carrying. Was Fenrir Greyback. She wanted to have an abortion then but it was too late. She was too far along. So, she returned home, to her parents. Hoping they could help sort out the mess. She didn't know her father was on the council that year though. And that when she told him she was pregnant and who the father was, he'd tell the rest of the council. An abomination, that's what the child would be. While the child wouldn't be a werewolf themselves they were still the offspring of the monster, Fenrir Greyback. But what were they to do? The decision was clear. They would exile Eira.&nbsp; The decision was reached too late though. Because Eira went into labor and gave birth to Ava. By a horrific turn of events, and mostly due to the Allaways isolation from the rest of the druid community, Eira died during childbirth before a healer could reach the home. They couldn't exile someone that was dead... But now what of the child? Again, the council met, and the decision was reached that the grandparents would raise the child. In isolation. Until she was old enough to fend for herself.&nbsp;

So, reluctantly, the grandparents raised the child. Though they did not give her their name. Instead, they gave her the name "Wolfsired" so that all would know what sort of abomination she was.&nbsp;

Her upbringing wasn't necessarily "sad", though quite difficult. She rarely saw or played with other children, as no parents would let them play with the wolf sired child. Her grandparents were never cruel but they were never loving either. They were strict and cold, and very hard on the girl. They are quick to insult, reprimand, and often hit the girl. The only love or kindness she ever knew was from a druid girl ten years her senior. Fae Cloudbreaker. Fae was always kind to her, and told her about a great many things. When Fae started working as a tour guide she even told Ava all about the strangers that visited the island and the strange outside world.&nbsp;

As Ava got older her parents were her main source of education, though it was a poor one at that. They didn't let her attend "normal" druid schooling with other children, instead choosing to tutor her themselves. THough their idea of teaching was to throw a book at her and tell her to read it. This worked surprisingly well for Ava. She just inhaled information. So they threw more books at her. Keep her busy, and out of the way.&nbsp;

When she reached eleven her grandparents, with the council's blessing, spread the rumor that she was sent to Beauxbaton. Far away. While Hogwarts would have been a better lie, there were a few druid children that attended the school, and the yearly exams for fifth and seventh years would have revealed the lie. But they didn't send her to Beauxbaton. Instead, they heightened her isolation. Forbid her from going into town, or talking to anyone else on the island except the council and her grandparents. By sheer luck, Fae had been made Head Druid a year earlier. While her isolation somewhat pleases Ava (because of how horribly shy she is), she's reaching an age where she's starting to realize just how.... lonely isolation really is.[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Ava only knows what people will tell her. Which is, not surprisingly, very little. Ava doesn't really have much contact with strangers so her news is heavily controlled. The only thing that really caused any issues was the barrier going down, because it caused a direct influence in her life. More people on the island, lots of strangers. Her anxiety has reached new heights dealing with these Ministry strangers. Her grandparents have also been a bit stricter about her comings and goings, because more people means more eyes, which means more chances of people seeing her.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Sora[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]29[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]Mountain time[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]I live here[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]Don't make me name them all >.<[/blockquote][/div][/div]