[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://66.media.tumblr.com/f6d378c5e7381b0b1bcbda1b1f0bb3db/tumblr_inline_nlw676KyTP1rifr4k.gif" style="max-width:100%;" alt=" "][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]sutton scarlette avery[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]sut-ton scar-let av-ery[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]avery.[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]23.
december 1st. [/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]pureblood.[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]bisexual.[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]cherry, veela hair, 9", rigid.[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]barbara palvin.[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]if there is one thing sutton is sure about, it's that she's beautiful. she's been blessed with good genes and a figure that most women desire, though it's not as good as it was before her daughter was born. her hair is cut long but is always tidy, either pulled up while she's at work or loose around her shoulders the rest of the time. her eyes are light and striking, as is the smile that is just below them. she keeps up with the latest fashion, well the stuff she things is tasteful and while in public she likes to wear clothes that show her figure off. behind closed doors at home she relaxes in jeans, sweaters and flats.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]hogwarts | slytherin.
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]graduate.
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]obliviator.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]her job, the high life, chaos, having control, pulling strings, looking her best, passing glances, flowers, being a mother, the elitist cause, flirting, most of her family, everything being in it's place, clean lines.[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]when people try and change her mind, mess, dull days, when people tell her to relax, bad hair days, looking dowdy, broken nails, screaming children, fluorescent lights, people who are too righteous, disloyalty, slimy feeling things. [/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]to help the purifiers change the world for the better.
to not completely screw up her child. 
to find someone who keeps her interested. [/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]ginger, clean air, lavender. .[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]small spaces.
loosing the family fortune.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote][b]vindictive[/b] | if she's wronged, she wants to make that wrong right. she's a believer in an eye for an eye and that it's to be taken literally. take something from her and she'll take something from you. she can be ruthless because she was raised to be by a father who taught her that to let people get the better of you or if someone managed to make you look weak, it needed retaliation. 

[b]possessive[/b] | what's hers is hers and if there is something she's not good at is letting go. she likes to have things, just to have them. to say that she does and sometimes to flout them in front of people, if it will get a rise or a reaction. people or objects, it's the same. taking something away from her will meet with a fierce resistance and definite revenge.  

[b]controlling[/b] | she likes to have control of situations, or she likes to be in situations where she trusts the people in control. she's a lover of chaos but only if it's controlled and she has fair knowledge of how it might work out, with a way out if need be. her job gives her the greatest rush because she has the power to control what she takes away from minds, what she leaves and whether or not something goes wrong ...

[b]selfish[/b] | she's mostly all about herself. if something doesn't benefit her there's a good chance she won't do it, or she'd have to way out the pro's and con's pretty thoroughly in her head. there are some exceptions to this rule though, the one person she'll put ahead of herself every time is her daughter. nothing matters more to her, apart from maybe the cause she was brought up to believe in.  

[b]confident[/b] | she's more than secure in who she is. she doesn't doubt herself for a second and she knows exactly what she is. she'll walk into a room without hesitation and when eyes are on her she gets a certain enjoyment out of it. sometimes it can cross into cocky but not often. cocky is tacky and if there is one thing she was raised with it was class, to portray yourself with a confident demeanour. 

[b]narrow minded[/b] | she's not open to opinions that she doesn't share. her opinions are solid and she won't be swayed from them. she's a pureblood elitist through and through, muggleblood has no place in the wizarding world, it's been tainted enough in the years that breeding with muggles has been seen as a good thing. 

[b]mother[/b] | one thing that really surprised her was how much she loved her child. she'd always been selfish but the second ashlyn was born, most of the world became about her. sutton did reserve some selfishness for herself but otherwise it's her daughter. she wants the world to be a place that ashlyn can thrive in, she wants the world to be a place that her daughter can everything she's destined. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]england.[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]atticus avery | dead | was 58 | accountant.
henriette avery | dead | died at 56 | homemaker. 

--- avery | 21 | brother.
--- avery | 18 | sister.
--- avery | 17 | sister.
--- avery | 16 | brother.

ashlyn eden avery-lestrange | 3 [/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]none.[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]sutton is the oldest daughter of a cold man and an even colder woman. their children were used to carry on their family name. to put pureblood back into the wizarding world and this was never kept a secret to the avery children. did that mean they were neglected? not in many senses. they had people to look after them, they had what they wanted and if they desired anything it was made available to them. the most important thing they had though, was each other. the love from their parents might have been missing from their lives but they loved each other. from the oldest to the youngest, as much as there were differences between her and her siblings she loved them, though she was still herself. she came first, they came second. they were lucky in one sense, there was never any differing affection for them, their parents were detached from each of them so, at least in sutton's mind there was no reason to be jealous of them. they were people she could confide in, make do her bidding while they were young enough to be swayed by her big sister influence.

she was the first of her siblings to go away to school. she'd been around other children before, the children of her parents circle but it hadn't prepared her for the platform for the train. she'd been taken and left there by one of the minders they had, her ticket tucked into the coat of her coat, her luggage sitting next to her on a trolley. it was the first time in her life that jealousy had really hit her. there were families there, beaming faces and faces that were covered in tears, kisses and hugs abound and words of affection passed between those getting on the train and those waving on the platform. she'd raised her head slightly higher, taken on that stiff upper lip she'd always been expected to have and boarded the train without anyone there to wave her off and there was no one to tell her they'd write to her. she knew it would be the same when she returned at the end of the year, there would be a stone faces nanny there to pick her up, no excitable parent and certainly no welcoming party. though she knew her siblings would be glad to see her but she'd be missing out on something to many people on the train would have. 

she did her best to push those thoughts from her mind. she had one focus as she walked through the doors of the great hall. that was the house she'd be placed into. there was only one house for her family, only one house that would please her parents somewhat and that was slytherin, the house of green and silver. the house that had been her parents house and their parents before dating all the way back to the days of salazar slytherin himself. it was the house the hat called out as it sat on her head and she felt something akin to relief as she slid off the stool and went to join her house. settling in was hard and making friends was slightly harder for her and it took the first year of school for her to form something close to a connection with some other students. 

for seven years she did the journey to and from school, though she did find herself enjoying it just a little more when all four of her siblings had joined her. she had her good subjects and her better subjects, though bad grades were something she tried to avoid. it wouldn't reflect well on her parents if she got bad grades. they'd made that well and truly clear before she'd started her schooling. she took to charms more than other forms of magic, finding them easier to master than say potions or transfiguration magic. it was why she started making plans to work for the ministry when she graduated, as an obliviator. if there was one thing she didn't want to be it was stuck like her mother, with no career and a husband who lorded over her. it was a fear of hers, one she didn't realise until the thought occurred to her, that she might get stuck in a marriage and loose everything about herself. 

she graduated without a problem, started her career in the ministry and with that freedom of being out on her own, able to forge a path that might be a little different than what her parents wanted, of course she kept it as close to her chest as she could, after all if they found out she was sleeping around with the oldest lestrange they might not be too happy. her parents were nothing if not predictable. they expected her to be husband hunting while out on her own. she didn't find a husband but she did find herself in the situation she didn't want to be in. she was nineteen and pregnant, having just started her career at the ministry it wasn't ideal. the simplest solution would be to take care of it quickly but something stopped her. she couldn't bring herself to do it. which angered her parents to no end. she was given three options, get rid of it, go somewhere else to have it or be cast out from the family and the money she was living off. she chose to leave. after all it seemed like the best option for her. she made the move to america, some might say she could have stayed closer to home but she transferred to the macusa, so she could continue her training as an obliviator until she had ashlyn. 

she felt a sense of guilt, though thinned as it was about leaving her siblings alone with her parents but she needed to do what was best for her. it's what she always did. for three years she lived in an apartment paid for by her father, worked as hard as she could at her job while still leaving time for the fun she was accustomed to and she tried to raise ashlyn as well as she could without much help from a nanny, though she did have one, there was only so much she was willing to give up for the child she loved. she kept in contact with her siblings, through letters and inviting them to the states on their holidays, not that they always came but she wanted them to know the offer was there. her world changed more than a little while she was in america. first her mother died, she'd gotten an owl from her father, the first since she'd moved, saying that she'd died of disease. there was no further explanation and if she's honest with herself she didn't care to ask for one. 

a few months after that another letter arrived, this one telling her that had father had been put into azkaban. he'd been caught, finally, smuggling restricted items into britain. again she couldn't say she was upset about it though she did worry a little about her siblings. she couldn't up and go home yet, she was still an unwed mother with a child she'd have to explain and while she didn't care what people thought she didn't know if her father had put anything into writing that would result in her being cut off if she came home. it wouldn't last though, atticus avery would escape from azkaban in the breakout, only to be killed a few weeks later by the aurors hunting them. that letter was official, coming from the ministry itself and the only feeling she felt when she read the words was relief. she could finally go home. only she was stuck in america just a little longer because before she could put everything into order for her move the borders were closed, her home country put into a quarantine that she would have to wait out. 

she did, though albeit a little impatiently, she made the journey home once it was lifted, though it was a far more tedious task than she'd have liked it to be. the process to get back almost lasted as long as the quarantine itself. once getting home she was reunited with her siblings once more and found that by some unexpected chance, miracle or practical choice on her parents part that the family fortune and estate was to be divided up amongst them. she decided it was a final act of duty to the children they'd created and possibly one to save face. after all how would it look if atticus avery had children living in anything but luxury after his death. gossip and speculation were to be avoided at all costs in life so it stood to reason they'd need to be in death too. she took some time to settle back in, starting her job at the ministry and getting ashlyn accustomed to the cold that she would always feel while living in england. now she just has the task of tying up old loose ends, which she can't deny, she's looking forward too. 

   [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]she's been out of the country for the last three years so she's only been able to keep up through papers and letters with her family. if it didn't directly involve them, hurt them in some way or affect her then she really did fail to take much notice. the break out of azkaban made her life easier in some ways because it solved a problem she wasn't sure how to fix so she's more than glad it happened. plus there was something about people who were in jail for crimes that she didn't think unjust being back out in the wizarding world that she liked. 

hags fever she took noticed of because it stopped her getting back into the uk, it annoyed her. it bothered her and she thinks they were over reacting in more ways that one because while the disease was contagious, it failed to be deadly. she's not itching to catch it though and she's glad that none of her siblings contracted, namely because she didn't want the family home to burn down.  [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]shadow.[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her.[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]27.[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]awst.[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]next question.[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@luke         , @edward         , @sunday         , @calder         , @katiya         [/blockquote][/div][/div]