[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;background-color:#B6B6B4;border:4px solid #B6B6B4;border-radius:10px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img height="246" src="http://www.moviefancentral.com/images/pictures/review39414/jim.gif?1331741359" alt="" style="max-width:100%;" width="435"]
[/div]

hello there, my name is [b]Jimothy Barnes[/b] but you can call me [b]Jim, James [/b]. I'm a [b]Adult [/b]and&nbsp;[b]34[/b] so that makes me a [b]graduate[/b]&nbsp;at [b]Hogwarts[/b].&nbsp;You could say I'm [b]brave, daring, &amp; chivalrous[/b] but I personally think that I am [b]laid back, friendly and fun.[/b]. People say I look a lot like [b]John Krasinski[/b], but I don't really see it...

[div align="center"][font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][i][b]Jimothy James Barnes[/b][/i][/font][/font][/div]

[b][i]pronunciation:[/i][/b] Jim-a-thy Jay-mz Bar-ns

[b][i]nickname:[/i][/b] Jim (preferred name), James

[b][i]age:[/i][/b] 34

[b][i]date of birth:[/i][/b] February 27th, 1990.

[b][i]gender &amp; pronouns:[/i][/b] Male, he, him.

[b][i]blood status:[/i][/b] Half-blood

[b][i]sexuality:[/i][/b] hetero

[b][i]schooling:[/i][/b] Hogwarts, Gryffindor.

[b][i]occupation:[/i][/b] Ludicrous Patents department. 

[b][i]wand:[/i][/b] 12 and a half inches , ash, dragonheart string core.

[b][i]playby:[/i][/b] John Krasinski 

[b][i]appearance:[/i] [/b] Jim looks just like his face claim, shifting between actually fixing his hair or not caring about it on a day to day bases.


[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personality[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]likes:[/i][/b] Flying, messing with his coworkers, sleeping in, his days off, listening to old music, muggle items, his family. Being around friends and certain coworkers.

[b][i]dislikes:[/i][/b] Paper Work, his job(most times), people who say guesstimate, waking up early, hot weather, people who use magic for something that could be easily done by hand and people who disrespect squibs.

[b][i]erised:[/i][/b] To never have to do paper work again or more to have a job he totally enjoys. That and to one day have a family. 

[b][i]amortentia:[/i][/b] Perfume, chocolate, Italian food, WD-40.

[b][i]boggart:[/i][/b] Spiders and being in water where he can’t see the bottom.

[b][i]overall personality:[/i][/b]

Jim has always been an outgoing person even as a child, quickly making friends and being someone many people liked to have around. While magic came as a surprise to him as child he also was quick to learn and was excited to see the magical world around him. Being brave in the face of so many things he had very little knowledge of. His friendly and laid back demeanor allowed him to get along with most people and he’d rather have it that way. Having issues and problems with other people are too much of hassle to have in a day to day life to him. 

He’s rarely annoyed by much and his only major pet peeve is when people insist on using his full first name. While he loves his parents he despises the name he was given as people have always mocked him growing up for how silly it sounds. Sadly it was the combination of both his grandfathers names and he never had the heart to change it even as an adult. The only other thing to annoy him in his life is his job and some of the coworkers he had to deal with. He has begun messing with some of them with pranks and some of the crazier patents he has to deal with.

Jim cares a lot about people and the ones he loves even if he doesn’t show it as much as he should. Willing to do anything for people he cares about. Going above and beyond if he has to or feels like he needs to, anything to make things right. He joined the order of the Phoenix later than most had but he couldn’t always just sit back at a desk and watch the world spin around him. Especially when he’s worried not just for people like him who are muggle-born but the muggles like his father. 

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personal history[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]mother:[/i][/b] Lilith Ann Barnes, 61, squib retired shop keeper.

[b][i]father:[/i][/b] Gerald D Barnes, 60, muggle mechanic.

[b][i]siblings:[/i][/b] Lilith Beatrice Barnes Jr, 30, unemployed 

[b][i]pets:[/i][/b] Black owl named Hoots

[b][i]history:[/i][/b]

Jim was born to a seemingly normal muggle family. He grew up with no knowledge of magic whatsoever and attended muggle school like any other muggle would. Eleven long years of knowing nothing of the magical world didn’t prepare both his father and himself for the owls they kept trying to break into their home one day. Yet his mother was oddly calm about them once she returned home from work. In fact she was overjoyed by the owls who wanted to rudely find their way though any window or open door they could. 

That night Jim’s mother could finally explain to both her husband and son about the world they didn’t know about, the world of magic hidden to muggles. At first his father was outraged she had hidden this from him for so many years. That was till Lilith started crying, which shut his father up immediately till he started to apologize for how he just acted. Jim’s mother went on to explain why she never told anyone about it. She was what was considered a squib, a child born to a magical family which had no magical ability. Essentially she was a muggle to the wizarding world and she had no place there. Instead she joined the muggle world  where she could belong and not be made fun off. 

Yet Jim had inherited the magical abilities she had not and she couldn’t have been happier for him if only a little jealous of the life she couldn’t have led. While both his father and Jim didn’t like that Lilith kept something like this from them it was far easier going through all this with someone who knew what was happening. It made trying to figure out where to go and what to get quicker as their first trip to Diagon Alley was almost over whelming. Magic was real this whole time and muggles as they were called just didn’t know. 

It didn’t take much for him to settle into the magical world just fine. Everything was new, amazing and just a little bit scary but Jim loved every bit of it. What magical children took for granted he was amazed by because he had never seen anything like it before. Of course the one thing that caught his eye above anything else was flying. His mother told him there was also a sport that revolved around flying and Jim just wanted to hear more. There just wasn’t enough time to get caught up on everything as the summer was over and it was time to leave for Hogwarts. Of course he was excited but he had never been away from his parents for that long he was still nervous as any kid would be.

Jim was sorted into Gryffindor and quickly made plenty of friends. He found many students just like him who had no knowledge of the magical world and didn’t feel so alone. The first year was mostly him just trying to learn as much as he could while becoming ever more obsessed with Quidditch especially the role of seeker. Jim wanted to join as soon as he could be he was no where near ready during his first year. He was still learning how to fly and while it was coming quickly he just wasn’t there yet to be on the team. With his second year Jim at least got himself on the reserve team, it wasn’t much but he couldn’t blame anyone. He was still new and they already had a seeker who was a seventh year. He did get to participate in practices. 

The years at Hogwarts went by fast and Jim dreamed of a life of being a professional Quidditch player. He graduated with top marks in most of his classes, excelling in both Charms and Potions. Still he attempted to follow his dreams which only lead him to one conclusion. He wasn’t as good as a profession player. As much as he loved Quidditch he knew he would never be good enough to make it in the professional leagues after his many tryouts. He was disappointed but it was just obvious to him. 

Lacking both a direction and feeling down Jim was convinced by a friend to get a job with the ministry. It was just supposed to be a temporary thing but months turned to years. He found himself good at his role in the ludicrous patents department even if he didn’t like that fact. It was all paper work and inspecting people’s ideas for both being original and doing what the creator said they would. At times it could be interesting maybe even fun but most times he was bored. Even for a lack of trying or caring he was still working faster than his coworkers. Inspecting the things he needed to and finishing the paper work while having enough time to kill to cause just a little havoc to his coworkers at times just to have some fun. 

Jim’s life had been boring for the most part and he’s grown used to it. The only change in the last few years it the rising threat of a group known as the purifiers. They’ve attacked Hogwarts and the student body multiple times all because of the issues on blood purity. Something Jim never understood being born essentially from a muggle family. Still he imagines this was what his mother must have felt like. People trying to push you out of the magical world just because of your blood or in her case being born with no magical powers but still part of this world. The attacks didn’t just stop at harming Hogwarts, the year of the tri-wizard tournament saw the attack on the student body of the visiting schools. Sure another terrorist group claimed responsibility but Jim didn’t believe it for a second. It was too big of a coincidence to not be related. 

Jim could just feel how on edge so many people were, just waiting for the next attack to happen. As much as he wanted this all to just blow over he couldn’t just do nothing. Nothing is all he felt like he ever did at the ministry. These people were not only a threat to him but his muggle family If left unchecked. Speaking up about his opinion to a friend led to him finding out about the order of Phoenix. Before long he was a member at the worst time. Just a month or two after joining Harry Potter had disappeared or worse was possibly dead. Jim had never met the man but he knew enough to know this was a big blow to the order. Big enough to split it apart and Jim didn’t know what to do next but sided with Finn and her faction of Ouroboros. All he really wanted was protect the people he cared about most of all.
   
 


[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]alias[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]name:[/i][/b] @tj  

[b][i]age:[/i][/b] 29 (... almost 30... god I’m old...)

[b][i]time zone:[/i][/b] EST 

[b][i]reference:[/i][/b] I found this place one day and never left.

[b][i]other characters:[/i][/b] @crimson1  (I taggged him right!), @lockhart   , @shawn   , @jacob  
[/div][/div]