[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt="(image here of playby)" src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/sarcasticmoth/proboards-templates/main/pics/asher/asher_app_header.jpg" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]asher rowan burke[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]ash-err[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Ash - [i]only[/i]&nbsp;by his sisters[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]thirty-three
01 September 1992[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]male
he/his[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]pureblood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]straight[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]12 inches, yew, werewolf hair, unyielding[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]jonathon rhys meyers[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Asher stands six feet even, though his rigid posture often gives him the appearance of being taller. Very rarely does he smile, and his most notable feature is a pair of piercing blue eyes. Typically he wears dress shirts or a blazer. Appearances are everything he was taught growing up, but despite how uptight he might appear, he has an affinity for dragon-skin leather jackets and sunglasses. His hair is often styled to appear more “casual” at times. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling &amp; status[/b]
[blockquote]Durmstrang graduate 2011[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]2011 - 2013: Intern, Department of Mysteries
2013 - 2017: Unspeakable, Experimental Charms &amp; Research
2017 - 2022: Unspeakable, Death Chamber
2022 - Present: Head of Department of Mysteries
The Ivory Room Owner - for Illegal Dueling/Gambling/Smuggling

[/blockquote][div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Brandy
Solitude
Purebloods
His family 
Charms
Dueling
The finer things in life
Perfection

[/blockquote][b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Smiling
Idiots
Mistakes
Anything muggle related
Losing

[/blockquote][b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]What is there to say about the first-born son of a notable Pureblood family? Asher was raised and told he was special and to always keep his head up high. But, it wasn’t just words to ensure that he grew up with confidence that wasn’t warranted. However, it wasn’t a problem as Asher quickly learned what appearances met and showing that unwavering confidence. Any flinch of a smile or your eyes showed your hand—he couldn’t have that. And really, it was just about achieving that exemplary level of excellence. That was Asher’s goal as a child, and as the only child until the age of just over five, he was the apple of his parents’ eye. But, they were trying for more children--which didn’t bother Asher in the slightest as he was eager to assume that role of big brother and be someone his siblings could look up to. It all felt so natural for him. 

Being the older sibling of two siblings made Asher learn patience, but he also learned that during his school years at Durmstrang. While his sisters had been homeschooled, his parents felt it was essential to have their eldest with a bit more visibility in the right social circles. And chiefly among those names that once filled the ranks of Death Eaters. So over those years, Asher still stood tall, existing in a quiet arrogance versus his sister’s more flashy confidence. But despite the extreme differences in personalities in the Burke siblings, they stand in solidarity—their loyalty to one another undeniable. Asher has already needed to display his capability to be merciless on a few unlucky souls who tried to cause his family trouble. Especially Ivy in her journey. 

Overall, to summarize Asher, the first word would be stubborn, perhaps pretentious, as not shy about it. His views on muggle-borns have changed over time and not to be friendlier, but his work in the Ministry keeps quiet. Preferring to observe and take in tidbits of information, especially on people, for use later. His mantra is that knowledge is power and where better to gain great knowledge than the Department of Mysteries, where despite just being a Department Head, not even the Minister of Magic interferes. Still, his ambition is as quiet as he is but hiding behind that fake charm and friendly greeting when he walks the halls of the Ministry. 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Cape Town, South Africa[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Caradoc Octavian Burke - 60’s, Pureblood, Retired Obliviator
Helena Travers Burke - 60’s, Pureblood, Retired Witch Weekly Writer
@ivy       - 28, Adopted Pureblood, Hogwarts Magical Theory Professor
@hazel       - 27, Hogwarts Alchemy Professor

[/blockquote][b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Owl - Apate[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Asher was the firstborn son of Caradoc Burke, a close relative of the family tree branch that helped found Borgin and Burkes in England. And he was happy as any Pureblood father would be to have a son and heir to pass on his name and legacy. However, they struggled to conceive more children, and Asher was an only child until the age of 5. This included private tutors until he was old enough to attend Durmstrang. It was clear that all the children had curious minds and no lack of ambition although it was displayed in vastly different ways. The adoption of a brother, a pureblood, of course, helped fill out the family, and Asher was happy to have a sibling to interact with despite the age difference. But then he gained a sister, Hazel, as well. Their personalities vastly differed and naturally, Isaiah and Hazel grew close due to their age. No matter, Asher focused on the goals set out for him and didn’t dwell on the lack of the same emotional connection with his younger siblings—dwelling was a distraction. 

When it came time to choose schooling, his parents opted for Durmstrang due to their expanded curriculum and connections with Pureblood society plus the political climate in South Africa made his parents cautious. His sisters, however, would be homeschooled although they were both intelligent and curious in their own right—plus Hazel would hopefully be married to an eligible pureblood heir at the right time. The only thing that bothered Asher’s parents was his questions, his natural curiosity for things that most wizards didn’t think about. This philosophical nature was discouraged, but Asher wanted to know why things were the way they were and how to make them better, how to make them absolutely perfect. So he studied and focused on standing out at Durmstrang among his peers, whether academically or when challenged to a duel. He could do it all and would happily hex anyone that doubted him or went after his family. 

But despite the discouragement toward anything muggle-related, Asher was pretty much indifferent for some time. At least until he witnessed firsthand the mistreatment of his brother, which only served to infuriate him. Not even wizard kind would stoop so low, which added to his views and cemented them further. Asher graduated from Durmstrang and decided that he could move to England and work in the Ministry of Magic—there were bound to be connections there. Also, he was intrigued by their Department of Mysteries, where he was accepted as an intern. By the time he finished his training and began working in the experimental division, his brother Isaiah had transitioned and he now told people he had two younger sisters. While happiness was hardly a priority in the society he was raised in, he noted how both his sisters stood with their heads held up high as he did and that’s all that mattered to him. Plus, he was happy to hex anyone that had an issue with his sister—magical or muggle. 

During this time, he also studied Occlumency at the recommendation of the Department head at the time, and via the same instructor, he practiced Legilimency as well. Knowledge was power, after all. One might call an Unspeakable life to be simple and dull due to its lack of “action” as one might compare this career to that of an Auror perhaps. But Asher found his own excitement. His upbringing and name gave him connections as other well-known Pureblood names were connected with certain illegal activities that caught Asher’s attention. And while his focus was to master knowledge, it didn’t mean he wasn’t a hell of a duelist, and in the underground circles where dueling itself wasn’t [i]technically[/i] illegal, but the gambling was. 

And that was his life, studying the mysteries of the world and then transferring to the study of Death itself as he remained in his secret circles. Any spare time was spent communicating with his sisters or at least trying as the age gap and personality differences became more apparent as he grew older. Plus, this dueling ring was mainly Pureblood members such as himself—but many years later, when an old friend Carrow took back control of the Club where this was hosted, Asher decided it should be open to all still secret. But very quickly, over the past few years, events in the world began to change and shift dramatically. First, the Minster of Magic was killed, and then students were found dead at Hogwarts, the magical school in the UK. But by far the most interesting thing to happen was the election of such a young Ministry Employee as Minister of Magic—but Asher kept quiet, though it was hard not to sneer at the name Weasley. 

The Tri-Wizard tournament brought his Alma Mater to Hogwarts as he thought it was very curious about his school’s champion. It was one thing that he was a half-blood but a Greyback no less. The attack on the students, however, did have an impact on him. It wasn’t that these were children or innocent lives, but it was just something he took personally. His work in the Death Chamber and the dueling on the side only made him push harder for that mastery, for those secrets yet to be revealed. Soon, however, he found his opportunity—an outlet for his beliefs that could one day be plans. Ivy told him about a group she had found and joined, the Purifiers, and how they wanted to change the world. Asher couldn’t think of a better way and joined his sisters in this, but secretly, of course. By this point, he was the Head of the Department of Mysteries, and what a scandal it would be if he was linked with such a dangerous terrorist group. 

Asher saw their effect, though he was disappointed (along with Ivy) that the Magic Dampener had been damaged so severely in that operation at Azkaban. Though by now, he was using his underground dueling club to selectively find more individuals for their cause, but carefully, of course. The risk of a Ministry raid was always there and speaking to the wrong person—though being in charge gave him the advantage of delegating, so his face was hardly seen in that fashion. And despite the common causes that push him, Ivy and Hazel forward, their personality differences are always a factor. Still, they were all perfectionists with a taste for the finer things in life and in search of a better way to mold the world. --Asher, with his knowledge gained as an Unspeakable where nothing was off-limits and in the criminal world, Ivy with her extensive knowledge and curiosity for Magical Theory and Hazel for her natural affinity for Alchemy and the transformation of the mundane to the magnificent. 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]vanessa[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]old enough to have used a payphone[/blockquote]
[/div][/div]