[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://36.media.tumblr.com/5dfb72199eec74632e14c27097106d45/tumblr_mug6z9mkKv1qfoekio1_500.jpg" alt="" style="max-width:100%;"]
[/div]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]Zephyr Andrew Davies[/font][/div][hr]

[b]pronunciation:[/b]

[blockquote]zef-er&nbsp;
day-vees[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]

[blockquote]Zee
Zephy[/blockquote]

[b]age and birthday:[/b]

[blockquote]28 1/2 years old
27th July 1997[/blockquote]

[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]

[blockquote]Male&nbsp;
He/Him[/blockquote]



[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]

[b]blood status:[/b]

[blockquote]Muggle Born[/blockquote]

[b]sexuality:[/b]

[blockquote]he has never even kissed someone he is very confused[/blockquote]

[b]wand:[/b]

[blockquote]13 ¼ inch elm, dragon heartstring
[/blockquote]

[b]playby:[/b]

[blockquote]Even Peters[/blockquote]

[b]appearance:[/b]

[blockquote]Like his Playby. Blonde hair, bleached. Naturally more sandy. Brown eyes. 177cm. Average build. More on the puny side. Meek and Mild by nature. Nil scars or distinguishing features. Wears glasses on occasion. Has a childish aura and seems younger than he is at first glance.[/blockquote]


[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]

[b]schooling &amp; status[/b]

[blockquote]Homeschooled.[/blockquote]

[b]current occupation:[/b]

[blockquote]Linguist specialist. Translator at the Ministry of Magic. Italian and German. Shuffles between departments as needed.&nbsp;[/blockquote]



[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]

[b]likes:[/b]

[blockquote]-ice cream &amp; other sweet treats
-socialising (even if he is terrible at it)
-having fun&nbsp;
-travelling&nbsp; (even if he is yet to do much of it)
-meeting new people (even if he is bad at it)
-having a laugh
-bad jokes
-flowers
-rainbows
-animals
-cartoons
-dancing (badly)
-muggle technology
[/blockquote]

[b]dislikes:[/b]

[blockquote]-being laughed at/made fun of
-mean people&nbsp;
-being forced to socialise
-over bearing personalities&nbsp;
-people taking advantage of him
-being the butt of people's jokes


[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]

[blockquote]Zeph Davies has a heart of gold, that sometimes people take advantage of. He's too sweet and wholesome for his own good sometimes. With his sheltered upbringing he can find it hard to see the bad in people until they've already walked all over him. He is a people pleaser to the core. He is gullible and goes with the flow a little too easy.&nbsp;

He is intelligent but has very little common sense. He is goofy and loves to be in the middle of the fun, even if sometimes the joke is unfortunately directed his way. He can be overly trusting when trying to make new friends. He enjoys the freedoms his new move has brought him and he is enjoying getting to know himself but his sheltered upbringing has also made him incredibly naive to an annoying level. he is keen to make lasting friendships and experiment with a more romantic relationship, but at the end of the day he is very clueless and comes across a little odd and awkward.[/blockquote]



[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]

[b]origins:[/b]

[blockquote]Rome, Italy[/blockquote]

[b]relations:[/b]

[blockquote][i]Daniel Davies.[/i] Father. Muggle. English. Diplomat to Italy from the UK. Happily Married. Wealthy. Good relationship.&nbsp;

[i]Marina Davies [/i](neé Fusco). Mother. Muggle. Equally good relationship as Daniel.&nbsp; Happily Married. Trophy Wife. Retired Model.&nbsp;

[i]Leila Davies[/i]. 35. Sister. Close relationship. Muggle. Based in Paris, France. Married. One smoll son and daughter. Niece and Nephew to Zeph.&nbsp;

[i]Nathaniel 'Nate' Davies.[/i] 32. Close relationship.&nbsp;Muggle. Based in Barcelona, Spain. One smoll son. Nephew to Zeph.&nbsp;

[i]Mrs Smith[/i]. Old Lady. Retired now. Very Close. Magical Tutor. Still in very regular contact.&nbsp;

[/blockquote]
[b]pets:[/b]

[blockquote]Small grey tabby kitten called Toby.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[b]history:[/b]

[blockquote]Zeph was brought up in a healthy happy home. He had the life of a normal child until he turned eleven. A letter from Hogwarts arrived and turned his world upside down. Even though he was living in Rome, he is half English and was on the register of births for Hogwarts. This was all quite big news because he wasn't even aware he was magic in the least. He was the first in his family and it was all relatively unknown. His parents were immediately suspicious of sending him away to school, but not against educating him magical. Through contacts from the Hogwarts representative, they were in the privileged position to provide private home schooling in both magical and on magical subjects. He completed his schooling to the highest level and even went on to even complete a University Degree in a Muggle University. Daniel Davies, forever the diplomat and cunning business man, paid for extras tutors to ensure his children spoke flawless English as well as at least two other languages. Zeph's bestowed extra languages were; German and French. His university degree was an online one, was also in linguists because he simply couldn't pick what else. Growing up in Italy he also speaks Italian fluently, and English is the language spoken at home.&nbsp;

While his siblings were going out to school and socialising, Marina kept a firm grip on Zephyr. He had some friends, but really wasn't allowed socialise much, nor did he have time between his regular schooling and magical schooling. Even in his early twenties he was more of a homebody, concentrating on his studies.&nbsp;

His emotional growth was stunted by an overbearing mother, and a father who tended to be absent and just throw money at problems to fix them. Marina often controlled who he was talking to online or the very few childhood friends he had. Zeph is Marina's golden&nbsp; boy and always had a firm control on her 'baby'. Pleasing his parents was a big part of his upbringing and he was never really able to break away from them.

Although he is nearly 29, he has not had a lot of life experiences separate from his parents. He has travelled, but not alone. He has gone to bars, but never without his parents or siblings or their pre-screened friends. After completing his first degree in linguistics. He studied for a second degree in classics and philosophy. Up until now he has been working as a 'home secretary' to his father aka sitting on his arse doing yet more study at home, and helping his father when he does briefly make an appearance at home. Mostly he just follows his mum around to her social gatherings trying to pawn him off on their daughters and such. But no, her friends know better.&nbsp;

When his old tutor Mrs. Smith got in contact to let him know there was a Ministry job going to someone with multiple languages and a linguist degree, it seemed like a perfect venture for Zeph.&nbsp;It caused some arguments; but finally he talked his parents around to letting him go for it. It was surprise he actually got it. When he told his father he'd be working for THE Ministry of Magic, it was the first time Daniel told him he was proud of him. He was excited to actually integrate with magical society as he has never had anything to do with it, or any clue what is going on with it at all, bar a few exchanges he has has with Mrs Smith over the years. These did of course [i]not [/i]include anything about the multiple random explosions that seem to have been happening.

After helping get him set up with an apartment that was, frankly much too nice&nbsp; for an entry level job, he has been living his best life and trying to navigate his new found freedom. He is keen to get to know people and will be mixing with a lot of different departments within the ministry from his broom closet office.&nbsp;

He's excited to begin his 'great big adventure' even if he is blissfully ignorant to the turmoil he is about to be dropped in.&nbsp;[/blockquote]



[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]

[b]name:[/b]

[blockquote]Dra

[/blockquote][b] pronouns:[/b]

[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]

[b]age:[/b]

[blockquote]27[/blockquote]

[/div][/div]