[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt=" " style="max-width:100%;" src="http://i179.photobucket.com/albums/w298/Mikestorm234/30a6d6d5-a6b9-4893-81e1-0529554dc3a4_zpse5f07940.jpg"][/div]

hello there, my name is [b]Matthew Johanson[/b] but you can call me [b]Matt[/b]. i'm a/an [b]Gryffindor [/b]and [b]17[/b] so that makes me a [b]7th Year[/b] at [b]Hogwarts[/b]. You could say I'm [b]brave, daring, &amp; chivalrous[/b] but I personally think that I am [b]quiet, calm, &amp; determined[/b]. People say I look a lot like [b]Daniel Radcliffe[/b], but I don't really see it...

[div align="center"][font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][i][b]Matthew Sven Johanson[/b][/i][/font][/font][/div]

[b][i]pronunciation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Mat-thew S'ven Yo-han-son[/blockquote]
[b][i]nickname:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Matt, MJ, Matty, Sveny[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b] 
[blockquote]Seventeen[/blockquote]
[b][i]date of birth:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]February 17, 2007[/blockquote]
[b][i]gender &amp; pronouns:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Male, he/him/his.[/blockquote]
[b][i]blood status:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Halfblood[/blockquote]
[b][i]sexuality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]hetero

[/blockquote]
[b][i]schooling:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts, Gryffindor. 

[/blockquote][b][i]occupation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Student working on becoming an Auror[/blockquote]
[b][i]wand:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]12 inches, oak. unicorn tail hair.[/blockquote]
[b][i]playby:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Daniel Radcliffe[/blockquote]
[b][i]appearance:[/i] [/b]
[blockquote]6'3, an athletic build, short hair[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personality[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]likes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]playing his guitar, studying, exploring, wizards' chess, wolves, being around friends[/blockquote]
[b][i]dislikes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]snakes, liars, manipulators, violence, arrogance, blood purity nonsense[/blockquote]
[b][i]erised:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]He wants to become an Auror like his father while also working towards starting a family of his own.[/blockquote]
[b][i]amortentia:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]the air after a storm, pumpkin[/blockquote]
[b][i]boggart:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Heights due to a poor experience with rollercoasters when he was seven, and failing to live up to his own standards as he tries to push himself forward from who he was in the past so that he can achieve his goals.[/blockquote]
[b][i]overall personality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Matt's changed a great deal from his fifth year. Originally a shy and reserved teen hidden within a shell, he's now more confident even if he's still on the quiet side. He's more social than he used to be, being willing to accept offers from people to hang out that he normally would've acted like he didn't hear before. He's still a little hesitant on the trusting side, but he's far more willing to give people a chance to earn his trust than before. He still is reliable and trustworthy when it comes to those that do call him friend, not hesitating to come to their aid when necessary.

Matt's primary hobbies and interests remain relatively unchanged despite his time in America. He still enjoys playing on his guitar, exploring, and playing Wizard's Chess despite not being very good at the latter. He also still enjoys spending time at the lake, usually to let his thoughts clear and relax from stressful days. He can also be seen spending time in the courtyard when he's studying or playing his guitar.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personal history[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]mother:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Marina Johanson, 40, believed Deceased[/blockquote]
[b][i]father:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Sven Johanson, 40, Auror.[/blockquote]
[b][i]siblings:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Melfina Johanson, 17, Slytherin[/blockquote]
[b][i]pets:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Jinx, a Great Horned Owl[/blockquote]
[b][i]history:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Matt was born along with his twin sister Melfina in a small wizarding community outside of Glasgow, Scotland. From an early age Matt seemed to enjoy the idea of being around magic, his expression always being one of curiosity and excitement whenever his parents were using magic. As he started talking, he would pretend to be casting the spells he heard his parents use, his face one of enjoyment as he did so. When he and Melfina turned three, his parents moved them to a slightly larger wizarding village near Edinburgh, and it was a decision which changed their lives.

When Matt &amp; Melfina were four years old, a dark wizard attacked their home while the Johanson family was there. Matt's mother was seemingly killed by the dark wizard when she went to help Matt's father who was dueling the dark wizard. The man then grabbed up Melfina while starting a fire in the house in several places, leaving Matt's dad little to no choice. Rescuing Matt and getting them both out of there, Sven then attempted to rescue Melfina, but by then the dark wizard had escaped with Melfina in hand. Also in the immediate aftermath, his mother's body was nowhere to be found. After this incident, Sven took Matt and moved to Hogsmeade in hopes that being close to the school and being away from where the incident occurred helped Matt to heal.

As Matt grew up, he went from being outgoing and friendly to reserved and walled off, not really playing like he would, be it playing with other kids or pretending to be a wizard like he did when he was younger. All the while Sven held back the desire to go hunting for Melfina and the man who kidnapped her, not wanting to abandon Matt as he grew up dealing with the pain of a deceased mother and a missing twin sister. Matt received his Hogwarts letter when he was eleven, giving his father some hope that he would then be able to bounce back. After a trip to Diagon Alley to get Matt the supplies he would need, Matt was sent off to Hogwarts, being sorted into Gryffindor.

His first three years were pretty uneventful, with Matt staying out of peoples' way rather than getting involved in things that he felt were needless or just didn't concern him. He did start to develop a strong distaste for liars, manipulators, and those who were arrogant around that time, holding it in however as he felt like he couldn't do anything about it. In his fourth year Matt did start trying to break out of his shell at times, often to mixed results and he usually ended up being given reason to retreat into his shell and stay out of people's way again. During his fifth year, his dad's search for his twin sister was finally successful, something that left Matt feeling overjoyed. That feeling soon changed when his father revealed that he and his sister were going to be placed elsewhere as he continued to hunt for their mother's killer. During that summer Matt spent time connecting with his sister, a task that quickly proved difficult as they prepared to move in temporarily with a friend of their father's. This would be something he was unsuccessful at until the end of their time away from England.

After his fifth year, Matt and Melfina were sent to the American Wizarding school of Ilvermorny, being placed in the Thunderbird house during their one year stay there. During this time Matt saw the bulk of his personality changes courtesy of the attitudes and personalities of the American students around him, something which at times frustrated him and other times amused him. The friendships he developed gave him confidence he didn't previously have, as well as helping him to learn how to trust people. As a result, he did leave with some regret, knowing the climate he was going back to in London and the United Kingdom as a whole. The vandalizing of Ilvermorny definitely made him wary, though with little he could do about it. He does write to his friends back in America, but his eyes are on the dangerous events around him especially the situation pertaining to Harry Potter.[/blockquote]
[b][i]site events reaction:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]For the most part Matt's been relatively quiet in regards to the events around him. That is not to say he's without his doubts and concerns, having been a bit relieved once he got settled in Ilvermorny that he wasn't dealing with events such as the Triwizard Tournament or the fallout of the attack on Hogwarts by Elaine Dupree. The deaths of three of his fellow students shook him a great deal, leaving him a bit more withdrawn than he already was at the time. He is supportive of the idea of Hermione Granger serving as Minister of Magic based on what he's heard of her over the years, but he is still uncertain of the future of London and the magical community as a whole.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]alias[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]name:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Aaron[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]28[/blockquote]
[b][i]time zone:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Central USA[/blockquote]
[b][i]reference:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Proboards Support/Returning Member[/blockquote]
[b][i]other characters:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote][/div][/div]