[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://i.ibb.co/bbBdyr2/download.jpg" alt=" "][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]anastasia marie karkaroff[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]ahna-staysia car-kah-roff[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Do not call her by her full first name
Ana
Anya (ONLY by cas)

[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]twenty-five
august 22, 2000[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]female, she/her[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]pureblood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]bisexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]red oak, werewolf nails, twelve-inches, unyielding[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]natalie portman[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]looks like her playby, five foot 3[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Durmstrang[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduated[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]2018-2020: magical interpol trainee
2020 - present: international crime task force

[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Running
Winning
Chess
Reading
Challenges
Dueling
The beach
Whiskey[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Being patronized
Being treated differently because she is a woman
Impulsiveness
Tardiness
failing[/blockquote][b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]To be respected and prominent, that the Karkaroff name has a positive reputation[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Sage, smell of the sea, honeycrisp apples[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Being forced out out of the ministry, being disgraced, failing her own expectations, death of her brother, following her uncle and father’s footsteps. [/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]If Ana was to stand in front of a mirror and look at herself, she would see her soft features and brown eyes, skin free of blemishes or scars--but she would also see every single harsh and negative word every spoken to her by her mother. The voice never strays far from her mind and even now continues to criticize every decision and every choice. You stare long enough into a mirror and even the most beautiful face becomes ugly. Ana was raised and pushed to try and fit a particular mold, she was a pureblood and of a famous name. Their family had status and so she would be as the daughter of a pureblood family of status should be. [i]Put in her place[/i], in the background, speak when spoken to and most importantly—obey. Unfortunately for the matriarch of the Karkaroff family, Ana was a stubborn child who preferred her brother’s old clothes to wearing dresses and preferred the company of her nannies to her own mother. Tesia hardly had any words of wisdom or encouragement for young Ana and very early began an endless cycle of verbal and emotional abuse that led to an increased need to act out and rebel which only fueled her already unstable mother. 

Ana is strong-willed, independent and stubborn but despite the air of confidence all these traits tend to represent she still finds a need for validation as her own insecurities are often increased by the idea that had been planted in her brain so young that she wasn’t doing it right, she could do better, she was bringing shame onto her family, she wasn’t meeting expectations. Still, she pushed through and despite all that her willful nature allowed her to be successful and adopt a personality that accepted challenges very easily, Ana likes to win and she likes to show people that she [i]can[/i] do it and  to continue to remind them that she won. The years of constant verbal and emotional abuse created a tough skin and she is not one to be rattled easily and it takes some time for her temper to appear if one has the patience to do so, and on that note she doesn’t startle easily as well. The only prevalent male figures in her life were her three older brothers who helped toughen her up as much as her own mother did and teach her that the world did not owe you anything and you had to take it yourself. 

One can say she is cold-hearted, she is willing to duel any man that questions her ability due to her gender and show them that she is not to be taken lightly. The idea of a central family unit was also instilled in her but she found as she got older she was only ever able to stand the company of her eldest brother and in that there is an almost unbreakable loyalty but she also offers this loyalties to those very close to her and those who manage to behind those walls. She doesn’t trust people by nature, though often she finds them not meeting her expectations and would rather not bother with them anyway. Another point of insecurity for her is her sexuality, she has known since she was in school that she was bisexual but she didn’t dare tell her mother or family and the fact that Cas knows is a bit of an accident, but it did not affect their relationship and she doesn’t quite hide it either. Sometimes she wondered if she chose the company of women as an act of rebellion but not that she’s ever quite let anyone of any gender that close to her heart. 

Acts of rebellion were common in her younger years and her school days, for example her mother telling her that her hair was too long and that it was time to cut it and so she did, but she also died it pink. There is a little bit of the flair for the dramatic in her nature, if only so people will know what she has done and they can see for their own eyes. She finds great pleasure in dueling especially with patronizing men who think that because she is a woman of a smaller stature she will be easily beaten, but she doesn’t have a problem knocking them down and walking over to stand over them as they lay on their backs and gently place a high heel on their chest and ask them if they concede and then consider helping them up. She looks to be the best at what she does and that is more for herself than for the praise it brings. 

Her relationship with her family is tenuous at best, she gets along well with her oldest brother Cas but even that took many years to build as they can be found often bickering instead of exchanging pleasant words as one might expect siblings to do. 

 [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Prague, Czech Republic[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Oskar Karkaroff, 63, former Death Eater, former Azkaban inmate
Tesia Karkaroff, 60, mother, recluse
Igor Karkaroff, former Death Eater, deceased
Casimir Karkaroff, 30, oldest brother
Aleksander Karkaroff, 28, older brother
Damian Karkaroff, 27, older brother
Leo Karkaroff, 10, beloved family dog
[/blockquote][b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Snowy Owl - Kira[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]The end of summer 2000 brought the newest addition to the Karkaroff family which already had three boys, the oldest being five and the youngest two. Oskar Karkaroff was not present for the birth as he wasn’t interested in a baby girl as he was ensuring that his boys even at their young ages were at the standard he wanted for his family, for his name. However, things changed rather quickly for the prominent pureblood family as Ana’s father was arrested, tried and sentenced to Azkaban all before she was the age of three--she doesn’t remember him since he was sent off as such a young age and rarely even saw her mother up until she was a little bit older. The only figures she had in her life were nannies responsible with her daily needs and her older brothers who despite being so young were forced to be men. While the young girl would try to escape her dresses and clunky clothing in order to play outside with her brothers they had no issue pushing her into the mud to toughen her up since that was all they knew of the world themselves. 

Ana’s mother was always an extreme authoritative figure in her life and unlike her brothers who might have shared the brunt of their father’s wrath in shared amounts Ana was the only target for her angry and emotionally unstable mother. Women in their society were expected to act like all the other women like cookie cutter ladies and Tesia used all her will and strength to fit the young girl into that mold. Ana wasn’t all that interested, however, she preferred to roughhouse with her brothers and climb trees and run until her lungs felt like they were on fire. But she couldn’t do that in a dress or sitting sipping tea so slowly you expected it to last you a lifetime. With every new rule and every new restriction Ana pushed back, but her mother pushed back [i]harder[/i]. The wild-eyed woman would scream and berate Ana until tears streamed down her face in anger and shame and even when Ana would briefly become the robotic cookie cutter lady--she was always doing something wrong. But, there were no scars--no proof. Nothing to indicate how Ana’s life really was at home because it was all words and manipulation and gaslighting. 

[i]’Why can’t you do this right? Why can’t you be like the other daughters? I give you EVERYTHING and this is what I get in return.’[/i] Never a compliment, something was always wrong. Ana kept her mouth shut and pushed through it. Even if she didn’t want to wear the dresses and learn all the “proper” manners she pushed through it and despite what her mother told her she got complimented--but never the one she wanted. When Ana was still young one by one her brothers started going off to school and she would see them over the holidays and over the summer but the older they got the less and less they wanted to do with her. She would ask about her father and nobody would talk about him or speak his name though as she watched their situation begin to spiral she understood that their family’s place in society was dwindling and her mother was holding onto threads of what they had before. It was her obsession, her mind seemed stuck in the past and she took out her anger and all these outbursts were directed at the young girl. Ana was never a very angry child, she wasn’t prone to outbursts or to be provoked and that was the advantage of three older brothers who didn’t hesitate to push you around and a mother who did nothing but try to get you to react so it could be your fault. But one day, she did react. Ana yelled back and was met by a slap across the face that almost left her dizzy. [i]’You WILL obey, there will be none of that insolence in this house and this family.”[/i] 

Ana remembered shaking with fury and rage as angry tears streamed down her cheeks and she swore she would never feel so humiliated in her life. Never. Nobody would ever make her feel like that again. When Ana reached the age where other children were to begin their tutelage at Durmstrang, the school that her family had always attended and her brothers currently did there was pushback from Tesia on whether her precious daughter should be sent away when she just need a few years before she could be married off to the heir of a well-off pureblooded family but her oldest brother would not hear of it. And Ana was grateful but nervous though her demeanor never showed it. By the time she arrived at school the staff and other students had been dealing with her three older brothers for some time and she found there was a mixed response. Some heirs of prominent families pestered her endlessly while others would avoid being in the same room as her. The Karkaroff name didn’t have the power it once held prior to the end of the last Wizarding War though they all knew the name from the former Headmaster, her uncle. 

However while she was first at the school she had [i]all[/i] her brothers there though by the time Cas graduated she wouldn’t see him for quite some time as he went in search of treasure instead. There was a sense of abandonment in Ana, but it didn’t last long--she’d learned to fend for herself against her mother for all these years so how was this any different. Though her other older brothers were either walking around with arrogance only afforded to them by their blood status while the other focused on his studies and hardly said a word. Ana did fairly well in her studies, as it was something to focus on that mentally stimulated her unlike all the things she had been brought up to learn by her mother. Though having to go home for the holidays and the summer time was not something she was given the option of not doing especially as over the years every time she went home the manor looked more worn, more unkempt and less and less familiar faces that had been there since she was born were present. It bothered Ana as they had been kind and good people, bringing her small bits to eat when her mother would deprive her because she was “too fat” and helping wipe away those angry tears. By the time Ana was seventeen she was a far cry from that small girl that was happy to get to go to school and escape her mother’s wrath. She pushed back more and more against the expectations as she had her own of herself, though no matter what she did her mother had nothing but sharp and painful words for her. Ana hated her. She doted on Damian though and attempted to have Ana do the same though this is where she adamantly refused to do anything with the pratt. 

School was full of other children from all walks of life, she befriended some, fought with others and others fought with her. Her name tended to bring mixed results and after a couple of years of tolerating their behavior she began to defend herself. With her small stature physical violence wasn’t all that effective depending on the attacker but she did have a knack for hexes and jinxes and those became a primary source of defense. The tendency for others to be around a corner as walked to her next class made her quick on her feet though her brothers tended to do a good job of that and she very quickly found they wouldn’t be so quick to defend her in any way, lest they get their hands dirty fighting her battles. Dueling became her favorite club and activity by far during these years and she focused in her classes that aided that, even whatever Dark Arts that were taught. With every new victory whether it be a small or large one there was this sense, this feeling that she thrived on. Well, who wouldn’t? And she sought that out, what new challenge was there that could give her that feeling again. And she thought about what kind of career she could pursue after her studies were complete. She didn’t have an interest in marrying into some family only to be around to produce heirs and children and continue the “blood purity” scheme. 

She wanted just as much as Cas to prove her place in the world. Yes, she was a woman but she could do whatever was asked of her and whatever challenge came her way and she continued to practice dueling as well as honing other skills after she left Durmstrang. There had been a hesitation to go home, to see her mother and her brothers but she did more out of a sense of duty than any familial love and found her mother in an interesting state. This woman who had spent all these years trying to break her down into conformity was a shell of who she had been and Ana couldn’t even muster up a feeling for her, not even pity. Family occasions were not common and if they did occur were dull and dreaded. Ana was interested in bigger things, so she followed her oldest brother’s lead and went somewhere where despite her name being known she would be given a chance, she hoped. At eighteen she began training with Magical Interpol, she wasn’t ever sure if her nationality or her name helped her get into a the International Criminal Police Force though some were quick to point out the irony of her career choice considering her father’s current status as an Azkaban inmate, but it only fueled her determination to not only succeed but in such away that would render any doubters hopefully speechless. 

Ana finished her training and around the same time her brother relocated to the UK as well and they were able to reconnect. It took time but Ana found that if there was one person she could trust it was her oldest brother, and he even began to guide her in Occlumency to help protect herself further in this world. After some time she was eventually talked into helping behind the scenes though she was hesitant at first with her Ministry job that she was doing well with but Cas convinced her that with her Occlumency she would be able to survive just fine and also help a greater cause in the world. The loyalty ultimately to her brother won over as well as her own goal of earning respect for herself and her name in whatever way possible and she began to help Ouroboros along with her brother. Her life thus far has been very work focused and she has dated since her school days whether it was a fling or even mildly serious but she doesn’t have the time or patience for more serious emotional attachments especially with a man who is just going to patronize her, in the meantime she always has her wand nearby to duel as her skills have improved to a great level since she was a teenager with Cas being the only one willing to practice with her. 

 [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Ana sides with her brother and Ouroboros and is able to use her Ministry work to help the cause, she doesn’t see quite the evil in Heliopath but does not like the impulsivity of it,  and her upbringing in “blood purity” and those causes always left a bad taste in her mouth and her eventual dislike of the Purifiers. Recent events such as the prison break out and the terrorist attacks have left her rather busy with work especially with rounding up the escaped inmates. She’s found new allies in the Ministry, in her faction and with the Americans as well but she tends to stay guarded despite smiling. Her father’s escape did not affect her much as it did her brothers, but she still knows it's not a good thing. Still she pushes herself to be more involved for two reasons, the first for her goal of respect from being successful and two so she can gain more knowledge and insight on the situation. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]vanessa[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]>.> not thirty[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]PST[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]I got off on the wrong bus stop[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@vanessa  [/blockquote][/div][/div]