[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;background-color:#B6B6B4;border:4px solid #B6B6B4;border-radius:10px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="http://24.media.tumblr.com/f895f4096d964d2be7d1f9309ff1e711/tumblr_mvbp9hfJsV1qzl9k5o1_500.gif" alt="" style="max-width:100%;"]
[/div]

Hello there, my name is [b]Gilderoy Lockhart Jr&nbsp;[/b] but you can call me [b]amazing, handsome or just great[/b]. I'm [b]17[/b] so that makes me a [b]Sixth[/b] year at Hogwarts, where I reside in [b]Ravenclaw[/b] house. You could say I'm [b] intelligent, knowledgeable, &amp; witty[/b] but I personally think that I am [b]Self-centered, Determined and all around cool guy[/b]. People say I look a lot like [b]Austin butler[/b], but I don't really see it...

[div align="center"][font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][i][b]Gilderoy Leroy Lockhart Jr [/b][/i][/font][/font][/div]

[b][i]nickname: [/i][/b] Roy, Locky
[b][i]age:[/i][/b] 17
[b][i]date of birth:[/i][/b] March 31, 2007
[b][i]gender:[/i][/b] Wizard
[b][i]blood status:[/i][/b] Half-blood
[b][i]sexuality:[/i][/b] Straight 
[b][i]house:[/i][/b] Ravenclaw
[b][i]occupation:[/i][/b] 
[b][i]wand:[/i][/b] 9", cherry, dragon heat-string.
[b][i]playby:[/i][/b] Austin Butler
[b][i]appearance:[/i] [/b]

Gilderoy stands six foot tall and takes incredible pride to always look his best any chance he gets. He normally ends up being the one taking the longest in the bathroom insuring he looks as amazing as everyone else should think he is.

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personality[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]likes:[/i][/b] 
Attention, people talking about him, learning new ways to impress people, looking good, proving others wrong, women, dueling, music and being the hero.

[b][i]dislikes:[/i][/b]
Being ignored, people lying about him or his father, not being around when something important happens, allowing others to take the spotlight from him and failing at anything.

[b][i]erised:[/i][/b]
To one day be as great as his father was, at least according to all the stories his mother has told of him. 
[b][i]amortentia:[/i][/b] 
Flowers, the smell of old books, and the cologne he normally wears.
[b][i]boggart:[/i][/b] 
Losing his memory like his father had and ending up like him, washed up and forgotten by most of the wizarding world.
[b][i]overall personality:[/i][/b]

Gilderoy is much like his father when it comes to personality. He is self centered and truly seems the most passionate when it's something that involves him. He's near obsessed with the idea that everyone should know about him and the great things he will one day do with his life. Gilderoy is also fixated on making sure he looks the best he can at any possible time both physical and in the way he acts around others. 

Unbeknownst to him that's where the similarities end. He's actually willing to work hard and practice to be the best, even if he hides the fact he has to practice to make himself look better to others. He genuinely wants to help people, he wants to be the hero he thinks he was meant to be from birth. He was raised by his mother to believe that he'd need to work hard to be the great man that his father once was but it was already in his blood. Gilderoy just needed to put in the effort. Unaware that his father never did anything besides cheat his way to fame. 

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personal history[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]mother:[/i][/b] Gladys Gudgeon, 56, works at TerrorTours in Diagonal alley
[b][i]father:[/i][/b] Gilderoy Lockhart Sr, 60, ex-author. (Lost his memories.)
[b][i]siblings:[/i][/b] none.
[b][i]pets:[/i][/b] a black cat named maxis
[b][i]history:[/i][/b]

Gilderoy is the son of the once great man he gets his name from and an almost bordering on obsessed fan who fell in love with him through his books and stories. All of which were events that were stolen from the people that had actually done such brave feats. His father lost his memories during his term as Defense against the dark arts professor. How it happened was still much of a mystery but many believe it was related to the events happening at the school that year. Even Though he lost his memories it was never revealed how much of a fraud he was. His fans still believed him a hero and he was allowed to live a quiet life signing autographs and being forgetting over time to the world. All but to one fan whose obsession never let up, that woman was Gladys Gudgeon. 

It took almost two decades till his father had recovered enough to be allowed to leave but he had no where to go and didn't remember anything from his past still. Gladys of course swooped in and took him in, if she did it out of compassion or the hopes a love would form no one was sure but if that was her plan it worked. The two got married two years later and had a son that Gladys insisted on naming after Gilderoy. His father just happily agreed, after losing his memories he was now a rather happy and carefree man. 

Gilderoy grew up in a happy home, with his mother constantly telling stories of the adventures of his father. While his father would just nod and agree that it must be true because it's in a book with his picture on it. Still his father was very forgetful, a side affect to the damage of whatever erased his mind many years ago. Gilderoy came to accept it but it didn't hurt any less when the man would forgot his birthday, how old he was, and the rare bad day that he forgot he had a son all together till he was reminded about it. Gilderoy didn't hate his father, he came to respect the man and look up to him after all the stories his mother told him. It lit a fire in the young man to one day be as great as the man in these books while to never suffer the same fate of losing his memories like his father had. 

For all his mothers bragging about how one day Gilderoy would be as great as his father she would remind him that he would have to work hard. Not many knew how much of a fraud his father was which was probably was saved Gilderoy from ending up just as corrupt and entitled as his father. He didn't expect the world to just accept him as a great man, he would have to work for that title just like he believed his father had.

Once he was accepted into Hogwarts Gilderoy was sorted into Ravenclaw. Something his mother and him took with great pride in while his father just said good for him. It was the type praise that he was used to from the man who didn't know much better anymore or remember it was his old school house as well. His first few years were rough, Gilderoy knew he would have to work hard but still he didn't expect to be as average as the next student right from the get go. Still he practiced each night in secret on anything he hadn't done perfectly, till it wasn't a problem anymore. The stories he planned to write and have written about him were of a hero that could do anything, he was going to work as hard as he could to be that hero. 

As the years went by things did get easier, not to the point were he didn't have to keep working hard but he eventually found his groove. Gilderoy found the confidence he needed in those years in both his growing abilities and his physical appearance. He's aware many didn't care for how he acted but he considered those people just jealous of the greatness that was to come from him. 

In the last year there had been many attacks on both the Ministry and Hogwarts by a group obsessed with blood purity. Something Gilderoy was both worried for the people around him and saw as an opportunity to prove himself if it ever presented it's self. Yet each time there was an attack he either wasn't there or could do nothing to help. Even more than the urge to be in the spot light he disliked the feeling of being helpless, it wasn't a feeling for a hero such as himself. The same feeling happened when the Tri-wizard tournament started and his name hadn't been called. Still he didn't dwell on it, deciding that it was the tournaments lose that he hadn't been picked, not his.
 

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]alias[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]name:[/i][/b] TJ
[blockquote]
[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b] 29
[blockquote]
[/blockquote]
[b][i]time zone:[/i][/b] est 
[blockquote]
[/blockquote]
[b][i]reference:[/i][/b] I've been here.
[blockquote]
[/blockquote]
[b][i]other characters:[/i][/b] @crimson1        , @shawn        
[blockquote]
[/blockquote][/div][/div]