[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt=" " style="max-width:100%;" src="https://66.media.tumblr.com/a211f691450941a0d61ed94144ce6835/tumblr_inline_nzr7lg83Q91rifr4k_500.gif"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]edward remus lupin[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]ed-ward ree-mus loo-pin.[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]ted or teddy.[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]April 3, 1998 | 25.[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]male | he/him.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]half-blood.[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]bisexual. [/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]10 inches, pear, unicorn hair, rigid.[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]taron egerton.[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]teddy stands at just under 6 foot, close enough that he argues the point. he can change his appearance at will most of the time but he chooses not to unless he has to. he's got naturally brown hair and his eyes are green. he has a few freckles on his left cheek and one of his eyebrows is slightly smaller than the other. he tends to keep his hair cropped short though not that short it looks like fuzz. his clothes are usually casual unless it's a fancy occasion and he wears a deep green cloak while he's working or at the ministry.  [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]hogwarts | hufflepuff.
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]graduate.
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]hit wizard.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]his job, spending time with his family, telling stories, changing his face to fool people. a roaring fire, firewhiskey, hearing stories about his parents, seeing his grandmother smile, family dinners, seeing his extended family, going to new places and old time muggle movies.[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]firewhiskey, apples, hearing bad things about his family, when jobs don't go right, arguments with no end, feeling weak, the feeling of falling over, people who dislike muggleborns, getting berated when he breaks rules, music without meaning and cooking.[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]to be the kind of father he was robbed of having. 
to understand how other people think.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]musk, fresh air, smoke and liquorice.[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]leaving his children without a father. 
his teeth falling out at once. [/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote][b]fair[/b] | teddy is a hufflepuff through and through. he doesn't judge people on who they are, only by what they've done. he's also able to see the circumstances that lead people to do things and he tries not to let anyone else and their judgements cloud his own. 

[b]loyal[/b] | ever loyal to a fault, teddy will defend the people he loves till his last breath. the people that earn his loyalty are the people that he calls family. having little family has made teddy feel the need to create his own and the ones he chose are his to defend. he'll stick up for just about anyone he thinks needs to be stuck up for and he's always giving a helping hand to the little guy. it does have it's drawbacks though, his loyalty will sometimes get him into trouble if he isn't careful, because the people he's loyal to have his trust and he's been known to trust those people blindly and often without question. 

[b]modest[/b] | he is what he is and that's that. he doesn't talk up how good he is at things because he knows there will always be people better than him. he doesn't like people that think too much of themselves and he doesn't have the time to sit there and listen to people gloat about how good they are at something. 

[b]perfectionist[/b] | he likes to do things right and he can take a fair amount of time doing so. he's very much of the mind, do something the first time and do it right, rather than do something quickly and risk needing to go back to it. 

[b]slightly eccentric[/b] | he has slightly unorthodox methods but most of the time he gets the job done. he's been known to approach the people he's hunting while looking like them, he'll have conversations with himself regularly while he's mulling over situations and he has no problem filling his work drawers with items that he finds while out on jobs. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]somerton, uk.[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]andromeda tonks | grandmother | 78.

remus lupin | father | deceased.
nymphadora lupin | mother | deceased.

harry potter | godfather | 'deceased'.

weasley and potter families.
black family.[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]a black lab named astras. [/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]teddy lupin was born to two people who loved each other and loved him a great deal. they just had to try and change the world before they really got to know him. orphaned as a baby, teddy grew up under the love and care of his grandmother, andromeda. he grew up on stories of his wild haired mother, his strong father and the moral of their story was always that they tried to make the world a better place. it was clear just after his birth that teddy took after his mother in one giant way, his hair turned a bright yellow. he had another important person who was a part of his life from day one and that was harry potter and with harry came the weasley clan. he might have been an orphan but teddy was never lacking in family. he was surrounded by them. 

there was really nothing out of the ordinary for him growing up, well at least he never thought so. he had to learn to control his ability but his grandmother having had experience helping his mother, helped him through it so he could walk down the street and not have his hair change colour or his face change completely. when he turned eleven, he like others before him got his letter and he boarded the train that would take him through the next seven years of his life. he was happy to be sorted into hufflepuff, it was the same house as his mother and being in it made him feel a little closer to her somehow. he quickly fell in with a group of friends and went through the years with them. he started dating victoire weasley in his sixth year of hogwarts and at the time he was naive enough to think that was it, they'd be together forever. he was chosen as head boy in his seventh year and to this day it's still the accomplishment he treasures the most. 

he started the training to become a hit wizard as soon as he left hogwarts, having graduated with grades just good enough to get into the program. he'd always wanted to follow in the footsteps of his mother, and in his later years his godfather. he'd wanted to help keep the world a better place, so he could keep the it as safe as possible for his family and future family like his parents had for him. he knew his grandmother worried for him and he didn't blame her, she'd lost most of her family already at the hands of dark wizards but to teddy, being able to stop someone from ruining someone's life or the world they lived in was important. with that, his future seemed set. or so he thought. it was that year that vic ended things with him, the loss of the relationship shook him a little more than a young love should have but he couldn't help but feel like there was a part of his life missing, something that was supposed to be there. he threw himself into his training and a few years later he'd become a fully fledged hit wizard. it was a bitter sweet moment because his parents weren't there to share it with him but he knew they'd be proud of him. 

the next while was a mess of feelings, work and hard times. he fell back into step with victoire, the now minister for magic and he couldn't have been prouder of her. though it wasn't all smooth sailing. there was drama, fear and the worry that the world was going downhill fast. things started happening. vic became sick and he left with her, took time off from his job and he went with her while she got well because there wasn't anyone more important than her to him at the time. it took some time but after a short while he was back in his job, vic was doing better and things, at least on some level seemed like they were on the up but they weren't. worse things were yet to come and they would make teddy yearn for the days of small jobs and simple stresses. 

 [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]while there has been a lot of things happen in the wizarding world there is one thing that eclipses all else for teddy. the disappearance of his godfather, harry potter. the news of losing the man who'd been his father figure shattered him. teddy threw himself into finding him. it fractured his relationship with victoire, their focus on finding harry rather than on each other and they didn't survive it, both agreeing to go their separate ways because it was easier than dealing with their loss together. turning to firewhiskey to help himself deal with the goings on of the world around him teddy started to feel himself spiralling into a hole without a life rope. the two people he could rely on were gone, his grandmother had gone through too much for him to burden her with his problems so for the first time in his life teddy felt alone. 

teddy is one of the wizarding worlds first line of defence when it comes to dark wizards. the demise and falling of azkaban has stretched the ministry to it's limits and it's been all hands on deck and go go go for the people working in them. the need to find these dark wizards is great because with them free, the world could easily fall into chaos, the wizarding world and the muggle world alike. teddy was burning the candle at both ends for what felt like eternity, working with the ministry by day and trying to find any lead he could on harry's disappearance by night. he didn't let himself believe that he was dead, because there was no way he could let the thought of him being alive so easily, that would be giving up. though there has been some small relief in the stress of recent events when harry revealed himself to be alive, at least to the select few he deemed needed to know. now it's just hunting for the dark wizards that are in hiding that's got teddy running around in circles, that and the bottle of firewhiskey he craves at the end of each day.   [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]shadow.[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her.[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]26.[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]awst.[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]ad on another site. [/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@luke                [/blockquote][/div][/div]