[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://64.media.tumblr.com/07cd2f708bfeb2b1a98b40176a76ac22/064e936d999ee1b9-ff/s500x750/2b10612bd5539fa36a0a536aff9d3c456bf7f272.gif" style="max-width:100%;" alt="GIF"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Scorpius Hyperion Malfoy[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]SKOR-pee-us High-PEER-ee-uhn MAL-foy[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Scor, Scorp[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]20
November 4, 2005[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Cisgender male; he/him pronouns[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Pure-blood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Bisexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]10 ⅐ inches, reed, unicorn hair core, pliant[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Willem De Schryver[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Standing at 5'10", Scorpius is neither extraordinarily short nor extraordinarily tall, and he has a thin build without much muscle. He has fair skin, sandy blonde hair which he has lightened to a platinum color, and grey eyes, giving him an appearance not dissimilar to that of his father, Draco. Scorpius has neither tattoos nor piercings, though he has a scar around his right ankle from where he Splinched his foot during an Apparition lesson in his sixth year of school.

In terms of fashion, Scorpius owns and wears both wizarding and non-magical attire, depending on the occasion. For the most part, he tries to strike a balance between the two, though his preference is for relatively casual Muggle attire—jeans and tees and the like, mostly in darker colors or neutrals. Regardless, he is generally neatly dressed.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts – Slytherin House[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduate (2024)[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Magical Artefacts Development and Testing Office Employee (Spring 2025 –)

Department of Magical Law Enforcement Intern (Summer 2024 – Spring 2025)
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Books; peacocks; magical history; Muggle technology; having close relationships with other people, including platonic love; darkness; staying up late; snowfall; people-watching; sweets[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Blood purist ideology, though he finds it difficult to divorce himself completely of that part of his lineage; Dark magic; hot weather; waking up early; people who can't see others as multifaceted beings; toxic masculinity; the smell of smoke, especially pipe tobacco; confrontation; when lots of conversations are going on at once; spicy foods[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Scorpius wants to make something of himself and do enough good so that his legacy might outweigh that of many of his corrupt (or downright evil) family members before him.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Warm sugar, vanilla, and yellowing paper[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Scorpius's greatest fear is being wrongfully imprisoned or never managing to rectify his family's wrongdoings. He also has recurring nightmares about the sweets trolley from the Hogwarts Express.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote][b]intelligent[/b]
Scorpius is very intelligent; some might even say "geeky", which he wears as a badge of honor. In school, he was always very academically gifted, though his favorite subject was Muggle Studies, which eventually led to his current position. He loves learning, on the whole, and tinkering with Muggle objects to make them work around magic is just part of that.

[b]determined[/b]
When it comes to his outlook on life and his goals, Scorpius is very motivated. He doesn't want to be associated with his family's soiled legacy, and he's constantly working to make sure that that doesn't happen. He puts a lot of effort into enchanting Muggle technology—feeling that it will make life much easier for everyone eventually—and is always trying to improve upon it… and himself. 

[b]loyal[/b]
Even though some of his family members and others might consider him [i]dis[/i]loyal for not remaining true to the very traditional views that they feel he should hold, Scorpius is loyal to a select few people with whom he is close. He doesn't have the widest circle of friends, but he values human connection. If Scorpius trusts someone, he'll have their back.

[b]open-minded[/b]
Scorpius is open-minded, having moved far beyond the narrow worldview espoused by many British pure-bloods. He doesn't jump to conclusions about people or situations easily, especially because he knows what it's like to be the subject of snap judgments.

[b]introverted[/b]
One thing that Scorpius most definitely isn't is an extrovert. Unfortunately, given his family's history, this made him seem horribly pretentious as a child, which was something that he never really knew how to counteract. He isn't always forthcoming about how he's feeling, either, especially if it would lead to his looking emasculated in certain company. This sometimes puts him in a bind, since he can get caught between the expectations that others have of how he should act and his own instincts.

[b]gentle[/b]
Scorpius is a gentle person. While some people might be shocked by that, he's never been nor wanted to be "tough" or cause anyone suffering. Ideally, he would live his life without hurting anyone at all, though he knows that that's not a realistic goal. The closest he can (reasonably) come is by avoiding the Dark Arts, which he's more than happy to do.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Malfoy Manor, Wiltshire, England[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote][b]mother:[/b]
Astoria Malfoy (née Greengrass), ~44, occupation open, pure-blood witch

[b]father:[/b]
Draco Malfoy, 45, occupation open, pure-blood wizard

[b]paternal grandfather:[/b]
Lucius Malfoy, ~72, former Death Eater, pure-blood wizard

[b]paternal grandmother:[/b]
Narcissa Malfoy (née Black), ~70, former Death Eater, pure-blood witch

[b]maternal aunt:[/b]
Daphne Zabini (née Greengrass), ~46, actress, pure-blood witch

[b]maternal uncle (by marriage):[/b]
@blaise, 45, Professor of DADA/Head of Slytherin House at Hogwarts, pure-blood wizard

[b]maternal first cousins:[/b]
_____ Zabini, 19, occupation open, pure-blood
_____ Zabini, 18, occupation open, pure-blood

[b]extended family members include:[/b]
House of Black, Greengrass and Malfoy families, among others[/blockquote]
[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Scorpius Malfoy was born to Draco and Astoria Malfoy in November of 2005. It was long enough after the end of the Second Wizarding War that life had begun to settle for Draco and Astoria, whose families' pure blood and tendencies towards the Dark Arts had left them relative outcasts in the reformed magical society that developed following the defeat of Lord Voldemort. In a world that had been rebuilt following decades of brewing conflict, it was difficult for Draco and Astoria to find their footing. Left embittered by their pasts and too proud to make amends properly with the likes of the former Dumbledore's Army, the Malfoys raised their only son in a relatively isolated environment.

As a result, Scorpius grew up quiet and relatively reserved. He loved his parents, though the world of most of his childhood was no larger than the grounds of Malfoy Manor, for the most part. His parents wanted to shield him from rejection, but that also came at a price. Although merely quiet and inquisitive, most of the other children Scorpius encountered seemed to think that he was haughty. It wasn't that he didn't want to make friends and explore the world; he did, but the closest thing that he got was a library of books.

When he arrived at Hogwarts and was Sorted into Slytherin at age eleven, Scorpius quickly found that his family's reputation—as Dark or as traitors to their kind, depending on who one asked—followed him. He didn't think of himself as a bad person, though he knew that his paternal grandparents, especially, had done some bad things in their lives. He loved them, and he didn't want to distance himself from them, but he knew immediately that he wanted to carve his own path at Hogwarts.

Scorpius, as his father before him, did well in school, but he kept his head down and didn't seek out praise—especially when Muggle Studies was his stand-out subject. He wanted his actions to speak for themselves, instead of having people assume that he had gotten what he had because his family had wealth and (admittedly dwindling) power. He found it difficult to make or keep friends for very long, but he appreciated the friends that he did have, especially as times began to get dark again.

As Scorpius probably should have expected from what he knew of his parents' time in school at Hogwarts, nothing good could last forever. Around his sixth year was when life began to change. Murders began to happen left and right, followed by the kidnapping of the pure-blood students in the year above him. It was uncomfortable, especially when others assumed that he would be inclined to take a similar path.

But that was the last thing that Scorpius wanted to do. Instead, he decided that he would work for the Ministry to keep anything else from happening—at least to the best of his ability. His final year of school, which included the Triwizard Tournament, was unusual but not frightening… until the explosions of the Durmstrang Ship and Beauxbatons Carriage killed many of the two foreign delegations that had been at Hogwarts all that year.

Although shaken, Scorpius kept his head up and began an internship with the Department of Magical Law Enforcement at the Ministry. The arrival of many of Ilvermorny's students to Hogwarts once he had left also brought new changes for the Ministry, including a new focus on developing Muggle technologies to work in densely magical environments in ways that hadn't been previously permitted.

From there, Scorpius joined the new Magical Artefacts Development and Testing Office, eager to put his interest in Muggle Studies to good use—and hopefully for the greater good of the magical world as a whole. (Though his parents weren't thrilled with the idea, Scorpius did his best to get them on board.)

With the fall of Azkaban and the deaths of Hermione Granger and others at the Quidditch finals still fresh from earlier in the year, Scorpius is mostly concerned about what will happen to the magical world as he knows it. He just wants to be a force for positive change, though, no matter what.[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Having been in his later years at Hogwarts as everything began to go down with Elaine Dupree, Scorpius is well aware of the dangers that she and others like her pose to the magical world. He always did his best to distance himself from the more elitist sections of pure-blood society, though it was difficult. His family's own history further complicated matters, and Scorpius was glad to leave Hogwarts, if only to avoid the gossip from his peers.

The technological revolution that came to magical Britain and Ireland in late 2024 was perhaps the greatest thing ever to happen, in Scorpius's mind. He couldn't wait to get his hands on everything that he could and find out how it would work with magic like never before.

2025 was ushered in with even worse news, however. Not only had dragons descended upon Hogsmeade, but Azkaban had fallen, and its prisoners had escaped. From that point, Scorpius was at a loss for what to think. Just as things were improving—or so he thought—they were reminded that nothing had really changed.

Then, as summer was on the horizon, Hag's Fever came to mess everything up again. While Scorpius himself caught the disease, it was only a minor case, and most of the issues related to the outbreak and the travel restrictions didn't affect him as much as many others.

The explosion at the Quidditch finals and the mass casualties felt eerily similar to Scorpius to what had happened as the foreign students were leaving Hogwarts in his seventh year. Although he wasn't at the match, the death of Minister for Magic Hermione Granger—who had done so much to improve magical and Muggle relations, in spite of his father's dislike of her—hit him harder than he wanted to admit.

Now, although still trying to wrap his head around every little thing that has happened, Scorpius is focused on doing his work and contributing to magical society in a positive way.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@audrey  [/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]She/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]23[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]US Central Time[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]Current member![/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@ezekiel, @chrissy, @monday, @clarence, @parvati, @brody, @penelope, @kaylee, @maxima, @muffet, @dasha, @samira, @felix, @priscilla, @blair, @camila, @claricia, @honey, @tamatha, @wormwood, @emmanuelle[/blockquote][/div][/div]