[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt="" src="https://66.media.tumblr.com/e7221d4b99c81f5fe03d040980a1757a/tumblr_pamf9kadjT1u0vpvmo2_500.gifv" style="max-width:100%;"][/div][div align="center"]
[/div][div align="center"][font size="5"]Colton Nash McCoy
[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]Coal-ton N-ash Mc-Coy
[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Colt or Nash
[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]Twenty eight
January 3rd, 1997
[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Male, He, him
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Half-blood

[/blockquote][b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Pansexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]10 and a half inches, Ash, Jackalope Antler[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]James Marsden
[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Colton is a man who is very much stuck in the past. Both the past as in the western stories of Sheriffs, cowboys, Indians, and bandits. As well as the past of his own life. He prefers to dress much as he would back at the McCoy ranch which was similar enough to what he pictured the old west was that liked it even more. To someone who had never seen him, it would look much like a cowboy just walked out of an old west book or movie. 

Still, that isn't always an option or at times he's fine with being in casual everyday close that the normal city folk might wear. Even then he still keeps the cowboy hat. At this point, it's just an extension of who he is.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote] Ilvermorny - Wampus

[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Ilvermorny Graduate
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]MACUSA Auror captain of the Foreign aid Department for the Ministry of Magic (sheriff)[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Country music and most music in general.
Horses, both the magical and No-maj kind. As well as most animals.
His family, for the most part.
Working with his hands.
Dueling.
Horse riding.
Bringing the bad guys in.
[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Being still for too long.
Stuck indoors for too long.
Disrespectful or rude people.
People who hurt others or animals.
Peanuts.
Clowns.
His parents insisting he just come back to the ranch.[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]To continue to rise the ranks of MACUSA and become the chief Auror back in America. Not just in the foreign aid department in Europe. After that he wouldn’t mind starting a family.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Fresh dirt, fresh air and lavender.
[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]While Colt enjoys horse riding, both the flying and non-flying kind of horses. When he was young he fell off and broke his arm. He had long since gotten over the crippling fear of riding but it’s always in the back of his mind while riding. Worried he might fall off again and break his arm or something else.

Colt hates clowns, it started with one particular rodeo clown and now includes all clowns in general. The make-up and laugh, just everything about them Colt finds upsetting. 
[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Colton is very much the down-home country boy he comes off as. He’s very respectful to people until they prove they don’t deserve it. He also can’t stand when someone is rude or disrespectful to someone else, especially women. Manners were figuratively and sometimes literally beaten into him. To never curse in front of a woman, always hold the door for others and help whenever he could. It’s just part of who he is at that this point, second nature. He’s always had a soft spot for women, children and the elderly.

While Colton is technically the law being not just a member of the MACUSA Aurors but the captain of the foreign aid department in the Ministry. He can understand how too many laws can get in the way of a job getting done. He’s not one to turn a blind eye to someone abusing their power but finding that gray area and getting the job done for the betterment of innocent people he can easily allow. They are there to fight the bad guys after all as he sees it.

He’s also a very driven person, you can’t just rise the ranks of Auror to be a captain without having a passion and determination to do so. Colton has never been one to ask for things, rather enjoying proving himself and working for it. Once he sets his mind on something he gives it his all till the task is complete. This also leads to him having a very competitive nature in just about anything. He can’t stand to lose anything from sports to something related to work. 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]The McCoy ranch near Grand Junction, Colorado[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Father, Alexander D McCoy - 60, Owner of the McCoy Ranch
mother, Delaney McCoy - 57, Co-Owner of the McCoy Ranch

Brother, Dallas Ray McCoy - 33 Ranch hand, magical horse jokey, next in line to own the Ranch.

____ ____ MCCOY T/H/4th
____ ____ MCCOY P/R/2nd
[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]None at the moment.
[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote][/blockquote]
[blockquote]Colton was born into a family of proud ranchers for all kinds of magical breeds of horses. Even some non-magical kinds. They bred them both for selling and for competition in the many magical horse type competitions that became popular in the west of America. Living as a McCoy was hard work. While other kids got to play and have fun Colton couldn’t remember a time he didn’t have some responsibility related to the ranch and horses. It was a family affair and each member had to take a part in it. His parents, his older brother and his two younger siblings. That’s not even counting the many farmhands they had which were also either cousins or aunts and uncles. Colton couldn’t so much as turn a corner without running into a family member it felt like.

It was easy to embrace the ranch life in the dusty desert ranch near Grand Junction. The ranch was well hidden from the No-maj world. It either was invisible or to the No-maj’s with slight magical resistance it appeared like a mirage would in a desert. Growing up Colton was so wrapped up in the stories of the no-maj old west, cowboys, Indians, bandits, and sheriffs. He claimed he would one day be a magical sheriff but was told that wasn’t a thing. The closest thing to that would be an Auror. So that’s what Colton set his sights on. His parents humored his dreams while thinking he would just spend his life on the ranch. Tending to the family business.

Colton received his letter to Ilvermorny which wasn’t unexpected, it had been some time since a no-maj was born in the McCoy family even with them being of mixed blood. That and Colton had already shown several magical outbursts growing up. Once there he was sorted into Wampus just like his older brother. It seemed like the perfect fit for him. Colton spent the next seven pretty uneventful years working as hard as he could in school and when not in school working on the family ranch. Graduating with high marks in several subjects.

Once he graduated from school and back home he was put right back to work on the Ranch. His family was glad to have another full-time family member to assist the Ranch. Yet that wouldn’t last very long. Only a month out of school and Colton had already been applying for jobs with MACUSA in the law enforcement department, which he was quickly accepted as an Auror in training. His parents were outraged, it was the family's duty to take care of the ranch and homestead. Not to just up and runoff, ignoring their duties.

For some time, this caused a major rift between him and his family. He still loved his family and the ranch but that just wasn’t his life, it was his parents and the family members that wanted it. His older brother was much more the rancher they wanted than he could ever be. He didn’t speak to his parents for many years after that, not for a lack of trying but they took a long time to get over his decision. To this day still not respecting his career choice, waiting for this whole Auror business to get out of his system.[/blockquote]

[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Being an Auror at the time of a number of the events that happen in Europe he kept an ear out for any information. It wasn’t his department but it was important to stay on top of any situation that might cross over to America. He also had his problems to deal with as well. There were growing rumors of a magical supremacist movement going on and Colton along with several aurors were tasked with tracking down any details on the matter. It seemed Europe and America had a few of the same issues but Europe’s supremacist movement, the purifiers was far more active than the rumors MACUSA had so far on the group known as Chimaera’s claw.

Just when Colton was thankful all they had were small incidents and rumors the supremacist, taking offense to comments made by the headmaster of Ilvermorny attacked the school. Damaging it to the point it was no longer safe for students for sometime. Hogwarts, the magical school in Europe had offered to take the America students in and MACUSA accepted. They didn’t have many other alternatives. Colton continued his work, bringing in a number of the Witches and Wizards that attacked Ilvermorny. The Chimaera’s claw was back to mostly being just rumors around the time the woman know as Elaine Dupree was declared dead by the ministry of magic.

Things seemed to have calmed down on both fronts, til there was an accident at the Quidditch tournament in Europe. Shortly before the that chief MACUSA Auror for the foreign aid department in the ministry retired. Colton was asked to step in with the recent developments. Colton asked what was fuss was since it was just a tragic accident but higher up members in MACUSA believed there was more to it. Possibly even a resurgence of the purifiers. Which would only give the Chimaera’s claw more reason to take bold actions again. Colton stepped up and was stationed in Europe and with the ministry in just a few short days. Here to help the European people with the type of America justice that could just save the day.
[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Other TJ
[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]he/him 
[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]32
[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]Est
[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]Someone offered me candy and next thing I knew I was here.
[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]Some peeps.
[/blockquote][/div][/div]
