[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt=" " style="max-width:100%;" src="https://i.ibb.co/SVY4F24/Log-in.png"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]leonardo adrian medina almeda[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]lee-oh-nahr-do | ah-dree-ahn | meh-dee-nah | ahll-meh-dah
[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Leo

Chiquitín - only by his mom, grandma and sister
[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]28
August 28, 1997[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]He
he/him/his[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]muggle-born[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]straight[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]Pine, Mermaid Scale,&nbsp;9 ¾ inches, bendy[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Rami Malek[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Much like his playby, standing at 5'10"&nbsp;

[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Ilvermorny - Horned Serpent[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduated[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]2015 - 2017: Curse Breaker
2017 - 2025: Ministry: HR - "Background Checks &amp; Investigations"
2025 - present: Ministry, IT
2019 - present: Black Market Merchant
 - Admin on The Elysian Fields , hidden (very small) online black market network for goods and information
Hacker - alias er3bus (for the muggle and magical world)[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Quiet
Computers
Writing Code
Reading
Fixing things 
Puzzles
Drugs (occasionally)
Star Trek
The Beach
Studying Transfiguration spells

[/blockquote][b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]People that talk too much
Liars
Hypocrites
His family 
Being interrupted
Loud noises

[/blockquote][b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]To be confident and well-liked, that his choices are not wrong and not questioned[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]vanilla, saffron, rosemary[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Being arrested, being seen as an abject failure, not being able to get out of a situation[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Leo is what you would expect and what has been said about someone working with computers and it works with his job at the Ministry. He is on the shyer side and really finds himself feeling very awkward in most situations. From a young age his family and culture had made decisions on who and what he was supposed to be, however, finding out he was the only magical child in a no-maj (and Catholic) family spawned its own set of problems. The pressure increased after that and he was forced to lie to keep up appearances. What will the family think? How is that supposed to make us look? Don’t you ever think about your family? Since he was a boy these questions were always in the air--verbally and with the look his parents tended to give him when they were in public. The awkwardness is just a result of that, wondering what people will think of what he is doing and why. It didn’t help that he has a twin sister who seems to do [i]everything[/i] right.

However, when he got older he started to push back--frustrated at what he had to deal with. Leo started to lie and disobey. And you know what? It felt [i]good[/i]. The rush of that freedom, of doing what he wanted versus what other people told him to do. That was addicting and when he started down that path he even felt confident as well. Growing up with a no-maj family introduced him to things that were not common in the Magical world, at least not fully. Things such as technology and from a young age Leo excelled with computers and preferred to hide behind a monitor than face a crowd. It also helped him feel free of the rules, of the expectations and the pressures that had always hung over his head. 

He wouldn’t go so far as to call himself a rogue element, but in a way he is. There are still internal guidelines he follows. The imposition of morals and rules that do not align with himself strikes against who he feels he really is, now that he is older he won’t allow anyone to tell him  what to do or what to be anymore. His loyalties lie to himself, and occasionally a select few other people but for the most part he doesn’t tend to align himself with anything. Maybe it was the strictness of his upbringing, the lack of freedom and the suppression of who he was in favor of who he was expected to be. You see, his culture doesn’t allow for a ton of individualism, it goes against the hierarchy. Leo sees the hierarchy in many things in his life and he exists within one in the Ministry but only because it is useful to him. 

Working in the Magical community in the ever growing online presence he has the edge with his knowledge and knows how to take advantage of it. He can be focused when he is in his element and confident. But on the outside people will just see the shy, kind of awkward guy from IT who is happy to help with the simplest IT question or problem without a fuss but as soon as he leaves the office and goes home and turns on his laptop he is who he feels he was meant to be. A neutral party only helping people expedite their needs, legal and illegal but of course that is who he is per his online alias and not his real name. 

[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Ceuta, Spain (off the coast of Morocco)[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Leonardo Adrian Medina Garcia, 48, Father - Lawyer
Adela Maria Garcia Zárate, 47, Mother
Leya, 28, Twin Sister - used to be best friends but she sided with the family 
Maria, 26, Younger Sister
Teresa, 24, Younger Sister
Alejandra, 22, Younger Sister
Angela, 20, Younger Sister - only sibling he still talks to occasionally
Gabriel, 18, Younger Brother

[/blockquote][b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]None[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Leo is the eldest of his siblings and older than his twin sister by a few minutes. In total there are seven of them and Leo was expected to be a role model and act like some kind of heir for his father. His father, Leo Sr., was a respected Doctor in their town while his mother stayed home with the kids. From a young age it was drilled into him basic things such as manners, how to dress, how to look and how to act. The questions of what will people think? What will the family think? How is that going to make us going to look? That will make your father look bad. They always hung over his head and while his sister thrived in that environment it only caused Leo to retreat back into his shell even further. It wasn’t who he was and he sensed his mother might have known that but she would never speak out against his father on his behalf, it wasn’t her place to. 

It became apparent when he was older, just after his brother (the youngest) was born that he was bound for a life that that was completely against those expectations. There in that small Spanish town off the coast of Morocco came a letter and and later a Wizard to very carefully and calmly explain to Leo’s very Catholic parents that he was actually a Wizard. Magic existed, it was secret but this was his path now. Leo was elated but the sense of excitement was also filled with a profound sense of disappointment. First, he and his twin sister would be separated for school. Despite their very different personalities they were the best of friends at that age and she did her best to try and help him so he wasn’t in so much trouble with their father all the time. Second, how were his parents supposed to explain this away to the rest of the family and all their friends? That last part he didn’t much care about but they were relentless in letting him know the trouble they were causing him. 

So, then the story was created. Leo, being the computer whiz kid that he was, was going to attend a boarding school in the United States while his sister went to school in mainland Spain. But really while he had the choice to attend the wizarding school in France which was geographically much closer his father wanted him as far away from his mind as possible without completely abandoning him (since that wouldn't be very Christian of him, and what would the family think?).&nbsp; Though Leo didn't mind, it also would give him a chance to work on his English and the less he had to deal with his father the better.&nbsp;So, Leo turned eleven and he knew that their parents had favored his brother Gabriel ever since he was born but now more than ever it was evident--at least from his father. He began his first year at Ilvermorny, was sorted into Horned Serpent and he was a bit overwhelmed at first but despite remaining mostly shy and awkward he did okay, there was a huge learning curve not only being an entirely different country but also learning about the magical world. His family status as ‘no-maj’ got him some looks but he kept his head low and focused on studying and the few friends that were able to look past it. Still, he was expected home on Christmas and during the summer. Finding the irony in sitting through Christmas mass despite him being a Wizard. While his magical knowledge increased, so did his technical knowledge and what he could do with it, especially when he was home during the summer. 

There was a sense of control he’d never had before. And while his father doted on his brother and mostly left him alone with the occasional comment or two he focused on that and also pushed back whenever Leo Sr. did decide to pay attention to his first born and try to get him to change his path. “You won’t even do it for the family?” he would ask and Leo would feel the pressure in his chest again. He loved his siblings more than anything but he felt like his soul was being snuffed out at the time. So, he kept rebelling and going against them and for the first time in a long time he felt free. Still, he couldn’t completely let it go. And when he finished school he chose a career that despite its incredible risk might garner him some praise if his face and name were in the Prophet or some other Magical paper. 

In a way Curse Breaking was like hacking, without the computer of course. There was puzzle in front of him and walls and locks that weren’t intended to be breached. Treasure that they weren’t supposed to be able to reach, protections put in place much like a firewall and the traps were like software responding and reacting to an intrusion. It was rough for Leo, as much as he didn’t mind the dirt and the sand he never seemed to end up on the glorious jobs, though his training was a full two years as was standard. He missed sitting at a desk but there was no glory in that. Then it happened, just at the end of his training. He and his trainer entered a tomb, it looked all routine--and then it wasn’t. Leo doesn’t quite remember what happened, he remembered hearing a lot of walls moving and stone crumbling and then he woke up in St. Mungo’s. 

It wasn’t a serious enough injury to take him out of the field but he had enough by that point. It wasn’t worth whatever glory he was going to get out of it and since he’d voluntarily stopped talking to his family after he graduated school and attended his sisters graduation, only his youngest sister seemed to check on him. There really wasn’t a way for them to know what had happened to him so he had reached out to his sister, though it didn’t change much in terms of family. It was odd, losing that sense of family for him when it was so ingrained but it was for the best if he wasn’t just going to be some kind of puppet. 

Leo left Curse Breaking despite having technically completed his training but his opportunities were a bit limited more because of his unassuming personality and he wanted something relatively low pressure. He had the skill set to possibly join the Ministry in Improper Use of Magic or similar departments or even the grades to be an Auror on paper. Still he was more interested in information, it was the hacker mindset from his life in the no-maj world so he opted to work for Human Resources in Background Checks. It was like what he did on the web but in this world it was more paper with the help of magic. It was a good way to build a network also without trying too hard. In his downtime however he focused on the no-maj web, it was where he'd come from after all.&nbsp;

A few years into his role he was the unassuming guy in a hoodie that worked in HR, just a cog in the big giant machine he didn't ultimately care for but it was something to do. But he reconnected with an old friend, someone who had helped train him when he was a Curse Breaker and despite the obvious illegality of the activities and how it contrasted drastically with his Ministry work, he slowly went into that world. It started small but grew over the years until something wonderful happened. A shining open door opened in 2025 that would bring the magical world up to speed on technology and Leo could hardly believe the announcement. His favorite part of the no-maj world was coming to this world. New departments were added at the Ministry and he immediately joined IT and with his knowledge he was a shoe-in for the role. Training wizards older than some of his school textbooks wasn't his favorite part, but now the Magical world was on the web and he felt powerful with his personal skillset.&nbsp;

One of the events he had watched carefully in the no-maj world was the battle between the Dark Web and various agencies around the world. The Silk Road was a site that used a tor (untraceable) network and what began as minor selling in bitcoin expanded to a huge black market for goods and information. Eventually it was taken down but there was always the buzz on the dark web for the reinstatement, though nobody was really brave enough to do it. If Leo didn't have his life in the magical community he might have gone in that direction, but it seemed such a small part of his life now. However, now that magical technology was becoming a thing he saw an opportunity as did many others. Other wizards and witches who he only knew by their online aliases but they were like him, born "normal" only to find out they weren't and they bonded over the opportunities for this in the sense of the laws on trades and tariffs he found ridiculous or the cost for small merchants to transport goods. Or goods that for whatever reason were illegal to trade and buy. 

It didn’t make sense to him, and he knew the same limitations excited in the no-maj world as did in the Magical world. So, he used his own skills and connections to help. The project being so knew isn't a large one by any means, but large enough for those seeking to find it. Connections are still being made and Leo's insight into his time with Background Checks helps him find the people the Ministry rejected but would possibly be in this field. The main challenge of course is convincing some of the old timers who still prefer to handle their business via Owls and letters that there was a better way to do their business and a safer one.&nbsp;With that in mind they chose the name ‘The Elysian Fields’ since really you had to be invited in. Though Leo was sticking to a theme matching his own online alias "erebus", meaning darkness but a child of chaos. 

These days Leo can be found walking through Diagon Alley and Knockturn Alley and that other Alley to visit his usual shops and help people he has befriended over the past eight years, and over this past year the people that have reached out for technical help. People tend to find his shy nature endearing and relatively harmless, so people don’t think too much at him or look at him twice when he passes through Knockturn Alley. 
[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Leo kept an eye on magical internet activity and even what Ministry info he had access to while events were playing out. He wasn’t at his former school when it was attacked but it did concern him and the explosion after the Triwizard Tournament had him a bit rattled since he hadn’t expected that. But he keeps his head down and continues to help with this clandestine site, he doesn’t pick sides even if some of the causes make sense to him but in public he does not want to be a target. Whether or not the elements at play have used his site for its black market potential he doesn’t know, not that he would particularly care--its just a tool and its still small as not all of the Wizarding community trusts technology, though it grows over time. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]vanessa[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote].....[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]PST[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]a stranger gave me candy to get into their van[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@vanessa    , @anastasia    , @layla    [/blockquote][/div][/div]