[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt=" " src="https://64.media.tumblr.com/74d562385d4b5580f98324e8eb3590d2/tumblr_pltqv5pLKT1vihiw4o1_1280.jpg" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]finn kylie nottingham[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]fin[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Fi.[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]24
September 24th, 2001[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Female. She/Her/Hers[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]No-Maj born[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Straight.[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]10 inches, swamp mayhew, jackalope antler, rigid. [/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Lights Poxleitner.[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]5’5”. Her tattoos are exactly the same as playby. She has a nose ring. Likes to change up her hair color on occasion for something new, so red and blonde isn’t uncommon for her. Clothing is also pretty much the same. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Ilvermorny. Wampus.
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduated 2019.
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]MACUSA Auror.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Coffee, pizza, dogs, listening to music, sleeping during days off, doing a good job at work, playing video games, reading comics, snow, being cold.[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]One-track minds, people that aren’t flexible, rubber bands, being woken up, someone cramping her style, ‘the good old days’, humidity and hot weather, swimming.[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]To fix things in the present to make a better future for everyone.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Cold morning air, steak, charcoal, pine.[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Drowning. The unknown below large bodies of water.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Finn likes being in charge. Being a natural leader (which is hard to imagine for some, based on how she looks), she enjoys when everything works out exactly how she plans. Obviously that isn’t realistic most of the time, so she’s flexible when it comes to virtually everything. This isn’t to be mistaken with going with the flow. There’s still a reason for everything she does, even if the original plans fall apart. Because not everyone works in this same manner, Finn has gotten used to being able to do things on her own, generating a high level of independence. The freedom to express herself how she wants to is only solidified through that. 

Her rougher side came with her job as an auror for MACUSA. Being a rather unassuming girl meant that she could basically do whatever she wanted, and that soon gained her notice. She knows that telling people to do what is best for them isn’t always accepted, and that’s fine, just that there are natural orders to everything, and having the knowledge to exploit and gain from that is important. If there is a way to get to a greater good through her actions, she has no problem taking that route. Morally ambiguous situations mean nothing to her, and she understands that sometimes it is necessary to fight along the same guidelines as the enemy if it means being able to overcome them. 

Outside of work, she likes to lay around and continue to do her own thing, never being one to follow the crowd. Hanging out at home is more common for her than going out to eat and drink is, even if it were to be with good friends. She enjoys her time alone and can go days without human interaction without even realizing it. Because of this part of her, it took her quite a few years to realize that she also had the knack to lead people, despite always being told that she had a way with people. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Sleepy Hollow, New York, USA[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]julie nottingham, 53, secretary, no-maj
robert nottingham, 56, contractor, no-maj
ellie nottingham   , 17, 7th Year Ravenclaw (Ilvermorny transfer)[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Alfred, screech owl
Bruce, husky [/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Being born into a rather normal family in a small town in the state of New York, the only strange thing in Finn’s life was her first name. Aside from that? Perfectly normal. Her parents had typical jobs and everything was simple. She was a bit of a tom boy through elementary school, but started to pull that back in once her younger sister was born. Finn enjoyed having someone smaller than her to tell what to do, even if Ellie was too young to fully understand. Those first eleven years were nice. A couple weird things here and there, but it was small town America, and there were always odd things happening. Except that they were mostly around her, and exclusively her. Following her eleventh birthday though, things started to make more sense. There were people and letters; conversations with her parents, explaining that they were something called No-Majs, short for none magical, and that she had magic, so that made her a witch. All that was supposed to be only in fantasy books and movies, and yet it was actually real all along.

The next year was strange. She didn’t have to go to the school that housed other magical children like herself, but she was interested enough in it that she decided to give it a shot anyways. The September of her twelfth birthday was her first true introduction to the magical world and to Ilvermorny. Finn was sorted into the house called Wampus. She had no idea what a wampus was, but there were tons of other children with similar abilities as her new ones and they all were expected to live together. It was a little overwhelming at first, but she quickly adapted, learning that they were all new to it. Even the ones that had apparently grown up knowing about magic their whole lives. She figured they would have an advantage, and while some did, not all were as naturally inclined as others. Finn caught on quick though, and had no problem immersing herself into the magical world as much as she could.

School went by quickly. Upon her sister’s eleventh birthday, the Nottinghams received yet another letter, this time signifying Ellie's entrance to Ilvermorny. By that point in time, Finn understood the odds of magical blood flowing through both of them, being of no-maj descent, but that only served to make it that much better. She finally had someone at home to share the excitement with. Her final year at school was spent showing Ellie the ropes, and preparing her little sister for the coming school years, once she herself had graduated. It was by far her most memorable year at that.

Finishing off school in a blur, the next step was finding a job. Back to her home state of New York she went, though this time sticking to the city. MACUSA was looking to hire recent graduates for government positions, and she had qualified for training. She had no idea what kind of training it was until it was completed months later and she was hired as an auror, a sort of magical police officer. They had made brief appearances at the school over the years, but Finn had never actually contemplated becoming one until she had. Luckily she took to it rather quickly, and started to get a hang for the whole law enforcement thing. Busting criminals was fun, and learning how to take control of situations that would normally be beyond her was even better. She didn’t mean to create a reputation for herself, but the head-strong attitude and getting things done apparently looked good to the higher ups. Upon realizing this, Finn shifted her methodologies and began working towards become more of a leader. There had been instances in school where she worked on group projects for classes or clubs and was commended for it, but she had never thought about applying that in the work place. By the time she was twenty, she finally figured out how everything worked.

Two years ago, things started to change across the pond. She recalled reading about the issues that had plagued the UK decades earlier; dark wizards and wars, things that had the potential to spill over into other parts of the world if they weren’t careful, but had been stopped. First came the murders of students at Hogwarts. The first one didn’t spark any interest for the MACUSA aurors. The next one did. She was stationed at Ilvermorny with other aurors as a precaution. Nothing ever happened with them though, and it was seemingly a British problem once again. Except that wasn’t how Finn saw it. Her government was more concerned about themselves rather than helping their friends across the ocean. She didn’t know how to put that into words until the Ministry switched Ministers once again, and then their own aurors started being killed. Seemingly nothing was being done to solve the problem of the dark wizards openly roaming around England. And then they decided to host the Triwizard Tournament at Hogwarts. That was basically an open invitation for problems to arise and for more students to be harmed if proper security measures weren’t taken. Celebrating magic wasn’t going to fix the problems at hand.

So Finn quit her job as an auror and moved to London. It was an impulse decision, but she couldn’t stand to watch an entire government flounder around because it had no idea what to do next. The people in power were supposedly the same ones that had ended the last war, and yet they were no better than a chicken with its head chopped off. There was something wrong with that. A little digging around led her to discovering the Order of the Phoenix, the supposed group that had led to victory during the last war. As far as she could tell, they were no better than a group of friends that liked to get together every now and again and talk about the past. Looking back wouldn’t fix the present, and definitely wouldn’t help the future. 

Joining the Order seemed perfect for her, at least at first. The disappearance of Harry Potter soon after led the organization to spiral into chaos, mostly about what they should be doing next and who should lead in his absence. It seemed extremely disjointed to her, and apparently speaking her mind about what she thought should happen going forward led to a schism. The Order split into three: Finn’s newly named Ouroboros, Heliopath, and Satera, the latter of which merged with Ouroboros after some time. 

Finn had a problem though. While she had always wanted to be a leader, she still felt like an outsider. The problems befalling England and the magical community there weren’t inherently her problems to deal with. She became increasingly frustrated with how little she could do, and decided the best thing to do was to leave Ouroboros altogether, hoping that what she had created and the people that decided to follow ideals would be able to follow through with more than she could. 

The timing of her departure and the breakout of Azkaban were almost in sync, and the Ministry’s call for international aide reached her almost immediately. MACUSA, knowing that she was currently living in London, reached out to her and asked her to come back to work as an auror again, assisting in the capture and cleanup of the breakout. Finn accepted, and has since been working for MACUSA again.
[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Following the Azkaban breakout, Finn has been on high alert. With intel from both MACUSA and the Ministry, she feels like she’s in a better position than she was leading Ouroboros. She feels useful again. The explosion at the Quidditch final hasn’t set well with her either, but she knows that she has to continue her vigilance going forward. Whatever is going on out there isn’t over yet.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@colin          [/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]he/him[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]26[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]EST[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]Support[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote][a href="https://alohomorax0.proboards.com/thread/5759"]Link To Plotter[/a] [/blockquote][/div][/div]