[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://i.imgur.com/JM6Rsoo.gif"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Keir Malachy O'Dalaigh
[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]Kere (rhymes with here)
[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]n/a[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]42
31st of October, 1983
[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Male, he/him
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Halfblood, werewolf
[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Bisexual
[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]Rowan and unicorn hair. 
[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Geoff Castelluci
[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]He looks identical to his face, except he has scars running over most of the length of his back from when he was attacked by the werewolf. 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling &amp;amp;amp; status[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts alumnus, Hufflepuff
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Head of the Department of Magical Education &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;  2023 - present
NEWT exam council &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;   2015 - 2023
Artefact and Developments dept; improper use of magic off&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 2012 - 2015 
Muggle Coal Miner&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 2008 - 2012
Dept. Reg and Cntrl of Magical creatures; beast division&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 2003 - 2008
Dept. Reg and Cntrl of Magical creatures; intern&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 2001 - 2003
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Singing, Halloween, his family, School/Education, Beer, his parents, movies, therapy, helping people. 
[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Lycantrophy, Prejudice, Caramel, People that Cheat on tests, troublemakers, vampires, That inexplicable feeling he's missing something. 
[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Keir is a friendly man to all, as long as they treat him with respect. Despite a relatively difficult life after he got turned he had the positivity and resilience to always land on his feet. He's never been shy to seek help when needed and found that no challenge should be conquered alone. He hopes to be a role model to those that need one and has always opened his heart and home to those that needed help, although the logistics became more complicated after he had children. 

His biggest fear without a doubt his that he'd end up responsible for turning or killing his wife or children during one of his transformations. While he's come to terms with being a werewolf there are many aspects to it that he still feels anxious about and his lifelong battle to prove a werewolf can be more than a moster still lingers. Even if he's had some success he's mostly attempted to keep to the background in dealing with those that are prejudiced, trying not to get on their paths. 

Despite all this he's not afraid to step up to confrontation when he feels it's required. He's never shied away from rough work and while he doesn't have much of a temper he feels very strongly about treating people decently. His time working amongst muggles in rough working conditions shortly after being turned hardened him and he always kept a part of that time in his life close to his heart. He's very stern and unyielding when he feels it's needed and can be quite scary during those times. 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Ireland[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Aodh O'Dalaigh, father.
Caiomhe O'Dalaigh, mother.

&amp;amp;nbsp;Áine Siobhan Kirwan O'Dalaigh, 39/40, wife, Shop keeper
Bran Fionn O'Dalaigh, 20, son, Former Gryffindor, Dragon keeper.
Brígh Ennis O'Dalaigh, 18, daughter, Gryffindor 7th year
[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Life for Keir wasn't too interesting. He grew up much like any other magical kid, learning about his world long before he even got to Hogwarts. His parents were kind and supportive and always urged him work hard and support those in need around him. As an only child he got all the attention he needed, but was also expected to do well. Nothing really special was worth mentioning in terms of his youth. 

The most notable situation being the extreme hatstall he caused when being sorted at Hogwarts. The sorting hat took quite a while to decide if he needed to go in Ravenclaw or Hufflepuff, although eventually the latter won out over the former. Due to this delay in sorting many took a rather keen interest in his academic career. It went mostly as expected, he performed well, made many friends and was a fair and just student that tolerated no cheating. Despite his loyalty he wasn't going to keep cheating under wraps out of loyalty, believing there was more value in helping them achieve the education they needed. While some resented him for this supposedly un-hufflepuff behaviour they realised his parental loyalty at a later age. 

He kept in contact with multple of his school friends and went into a career in the ministry straight out of school. He started out in the department for control and regulation of magical beasts, where he keenly worked and applied himself happily. He believed in good and would seek hope to excuse beasts rather than condamn them. He was known as kind but fair and with heavy heart supplied his opinion that would result in death if given heed by his superiors. Sometimes he had to admit creatures were simply too dangerous to continue. 

He encountered a beautiful Irish beauty around that time and despite their different worlds the two of them fell head over heels in love with one another instantly. One thing led to another and the two soon married, although he told her the truth about what he was long before the wedding night. He was ready to oblivate her mind if needed, but he had full trust in his girlfriend. 

While still fairly young the pair began their family. It started with Bran just as Keir was called in for more regulier field work in examining dangerous beasts or rumours of their whereabouts. As he and his wife found out they were expecting another child they were overjoyed. Months passed mostly quietly but one night the high pregnant Aine found ministry officials on her doorstep rather than her husband. She took little Bran and brought him to the hospital where her husband had been taken in after an attack at work. A full moon and a werewolf had nearly killed him. He clung to life but ended up recovering, although things changed from that point.

For a while Aine doubted staying with Keir, although it was soon obvious that the man had changed little to nothing. He was the same he'd always been, checking himself into therapy as soon as he was able and doing all the research. He refused to be home around the full moon for the first years, missing a fair few firsts from his children just to keep them safe. Unfortunately the people at work no longer wanted him on their team and he was fired. Not deterred too much but still understanding both the danger he posed and the prejudice he'd face in the magical community, Keir decided to take up a job at one of the few places that would hire him. He had no muggle credentials and no wizard would hire him. 

For four long years Keir slaved away in a coal mine, working hard for little money while he watched his family slowly sink into debt. With two young children there was little choice but to keep working and watch their debts rise. Eventually Aine decided staying home with the children was no longer an option and she took a job in a shop to keep the family above water. Between the two of them they managed, although it was difficult. 

After these four years a magical anomaly in the coal mine caused the mine to collapse and while Keir managed to save multiple lives he knew this was at risk of&amp;amp;nbsp; becoming quite a catastrophe so even as he comforted his coworkers as first air he obliviated them one by one until they all believed the accident to be mundane. When the accidental magic reversal squad showed up they found Keir having done a lot of damage control. The leader of the squad was impressed and pulled a bunch of strings to get permission to hire Keir into their department. 

Escaping the coal mine he did maintain his friendships and many still frequently stop by the O'Dalaigh home to have a coffee and talk about the olden days. Meanwhile Keir worked harder than anybody to prove he was an asset and not a liability due to his condition. He sacrified some of his rights for sake of keeping his job and making sure his coworkers realised he was very serious about keeping them safe. He never spoke to the people of his old deparment but steadily met their very wary gazes whenever he met them on the floor. No, he had not forgotten, but he long since had learned digging up dirt wasn't going to get anybody out of trouble. 

As his first child went to school he managed to get himself hired into the NEWT exam council, where he was often asked to work from home. He didn't complain and did as he was told. Over the course of many years he managed to earn his stripes and impressed everybody with his genuine understanding of learning and his own willingness to do whatever was needed to succeed in life. He willingly and without complaint went to therapy where needed, took his wolfsbane religiously and never caused any trouble. His critical thinking and keen mind displayed a passion and understanding of education that slowly gained a deep admirationg amongst his peers despite his condition. 

While not all agreed when he got appointed the head of the Department of magical Education there were few that dared object based on his actual credentials. The prejudices were dismissed, saying he didn't pose a threat at all outside th full moon, when he'd be working exclusively from a safe space where he could hurt none and had a team at the ready to do anything in case he himself could not make any instant calls. While his opposition remains displeased nobody could deny the man had done a good job thus far in dealing with everything going on at the school and within the general field of education. While Keir hopes nothing at all will require him to step up to the plate fully, he knows he's more than capable of doing so. 

When Keir fell ill about a year ago, he attempted to work as much as possible and while at first reluctant to call his daughter home from school, he realised she was better off educated where he could see her learning, not to mention that she'd be far less distracted knowing that if his condition got worse she could say goodbye. His stubborn nature refused the option of dying, even if nobody could figure out exactly what ailed him. He is slowly recovering and while his health is still far from optimal he has resumed his work, much to the relief of many in the department, even a reluctant few that before so keenly opposed him. 

Now being on the mend, Keir worries his mysterious illness will return, this time wreaking far more havoc than before. He is determined to make the most out of life and leave a legacy for his children that is worth being remembered, although he hopes he'll be around more than long enough to see it himself. 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Seph
[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote].... Don't even..... the Jedi Council approaches. 
[/blockquote]
[/div][/div]