[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://78.media.tumblr.com/cbe6128aa4af439efe7a7ab2340ae1d8/tumblr_op02avY2DR1tks11lo2_r2_500.gif"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Heleen Arista Lisanne Oppedyk[/font][/div][hr]
[blockquote][b]pronunciation:[/b]
Hey-lane Ah-ree-st-ah Lee-zahn-eh Oh-peh-deek[/blockquote]
[blockquote][b]nickname:[/b]  Hel, Helly, Hella, Rissa, Lisa, Halo[/blockquote]
[blockquote][b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]May 5th, 24yo[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Female, she/her. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Halfblood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Straight, currently still exploring[/blockquote][b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]Yew, unicorn hair, 10 3/4 inches, slightly springy. [/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Lily James[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]5'7" tall. Usually wears bright colours. Rarely wears her hair down. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Homeschool till age 13, then beauxbatons. 
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduate/alumni
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]UK MoM, unspeakable, research. 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Puzzles, ballroom dancing, the muggle world, biology, potion brewing, sushi, the sound of rain and thunderstorms, bath bombs, D&D. [/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Cooking, cleaning, boring things or tasks, whistling, eggplants, age prejudice, mansplaining. [/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Happiness. Love, homely things but career success. [/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Pines, hearth fires, old books. [/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]The Void/Dark Ocean. Drowning, endless graveyard and hanging tree, relationships.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Heleen is curious to a fault. She's always pushing boundaries in both research and thinking as well as trying to explore boundaries of rules within society. She's a fierce feminist and fights a war for equality for all on a daily basis. She's extremely driven when she puts her mind to anything but can easily overstep and keep pushing if people don't give her a clear enough no. She loves her friends dearly and attaches to them, always trying to form deep and meaningful bonds. 

She can, at times, be a little snobby, being raised in a relatively rich household. She's stubborn but cares deeply and finds herself easily hurt in too many occasions. She can at times be prone to rather violent mood swings that originate in a solid depression stemming from the earlier years of her youth. She has both severe trust issues and abandonment issues, resulting in a sometimes volatile mixture of emotions. 

Heleen is usually a cheerful companion to be around. She will fight the established order if she feels it's faulty and always tries to keep any complications surrounding her friends in mind. She strives to create a safe and happy environment for all those she cares about and will go out of her way to provide such things for those she cares about. Be it allergies, physical comfort, emotional support or other things. She often exhausts herself caring for others and is unlikely to put herself first.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]The Netherlands[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Name - relation to character, age, any other relevant info.
Jocelyn Atwood - Mother, Gryffindor alumi, socialite, human rights activist.
Johannes Robertus Oppedyk - Father, Durmstrang Alumnus,head of a large magical company. 
Jitske Ingrid Amarantha Oppedyk - Older sister, Homeschool Alumni, Dutch MoM official.
Epke Umberto Richard Oppedyk - Older brother, Beauxbatons alumnus, Dragon Keeper

[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Gekko named Spock[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Heleen was the youngest of three in a mostly magical household. While her father was muggleborn and her mother a halfblood they still kept a very close connection to the muggle world since her fathers family held quite the esteem and money. Her mother, also the daughter of an influential politician was naturally attracted to his sophistication and charm as well as his impecable manners. While these traits carried over well to the eldest daughter it never quite stuck to both Heleen and her brother Epke. While Jitske was fine being homeschool, Epke caused quite the uproar about it from the age of fourteen and as soon as he got his way at fifteen, Heleen was offered the choice and she choose to also go to Beauxbatons. 

At school her small world that had once been filled with other children from well off families expanded exponentially and Heleen came to realise exactly why work such as that of her mother was needed. As a human rights activist Jocelyn had always raised her children to be kind and respectful of others and to help out where possible. Heleen figured that if she ever could impact lives in a way similar to that of her mother, she would. This mostly started out differently, as Heleen turned out to be more suited to feminism and small time equality and issues that mostly were unfair.

Her closest friends while in school were both neurodivergent types, people with allergies and some girls and boys with dreams and ambitions that did not suit the wishes society had. So to make sure that she did all she could, Heleen made sure to always prepare food safe for all her friends to eat. She convinced her male friend he could join the ballet if he wanted to and called people out when they tried to force her friends to look or dress a certain way. 

Naturally this meant plenty of other battles and years of bullying that started from the fact she was home schooled left a deep impact. That started the spiral down into her depression and while her friends helped her out for the most part, one of her deepest fears is spiralling into that depression again. 

Just before she graduated she met a boy. The two fell in love, or at least she did. He mostly used her and used techniques meant to emotionally manipulate her to do as he felt was best. For almost a year Heleen stayed with him, poisoned by his whispers and stuck in a dead end job her dad arranged for her at the ministry. It wasn't her passion and she was deeply miserable, turning self destructive in several ways. He supported her, or so she thought at first. By the time she realised what he'd been doing she packed her bags the same day and left the small apartment they had together. She talked to her father and he arranged for her to transfer inside the ministry to a job far more suited to her. She started in the department of mysteries and while her father and mother worried consistently, Heleen did not let it stop her this time.

After several years Heleen started to grow restless, searching for a new challenge that offered itself in shape of a job in the UK ministry, doing a much similar thing but with far more investment opportunities. To Heleen this meant leaving her life behind and investing in a new country. While scared and more than a little terrified, she moved to the UK, ready to start on the new job. Even ready to invest in a relationship again, even though the prospect frightens her. [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Due to her choice to move to the UK to further her possibilities in her field of choice profession wise, the news that the massive break out in Azkaban took place greatly unsettled Heleen. Though she was determined to not let it affect herself or her career the prospect frightens her beyond compare. Due to past events she's read up on concerning unspeakables in the past she's worried to get picked out of a crowd. She has not let it impact her life much but has taken up the habit of sleeping with her wand under her pillow, just in case. She's also put more protective measures on her small apartment.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Seph[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]27[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]GMT+1 (sometimes +2)[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]A lot of searching... [/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]
None[/blockquote][/blockquote][/div][/div]