[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" alt="" src="https://www.celebinvestigator.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/Karen-Gillan-religion-political-views-beliefs-hobbies-dating-secrets.jpg"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Alyra Rose Pond[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]Uh-Lee-Ra Roe-s Ph-on-duh[/blockquote][b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Alyra, Lee,&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]28
September 1st[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Female | she/her[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]halfblood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]hetero[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]11 and 5/8th inches, Fir wood, Dragon heart string core[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Karen Gillan[/blockquote][b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Alyra is 5 foot 7 inches tall. She has deep red hair and a pale complexion. Alyra has green eyes and often feels like her nose is too small for her face, but tries not to think about it. She has a lean build and is fairly strong under it all from her training for work and her other activities.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Ilvermorny - Thunderbird&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduate[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Foreign aid [b]investigator[/b] sent over by MACUSA after the Azkaban outbreak&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Chocolate
Cakes
Biscuits (Okay really all sweets, let be real. But Chocolate in particular)
Travel
Work
Friends
Family
Domestic animals&nbsp;
Summer/warm weather
Punctuality[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Snow
Delays
Fish (as food)
Cheese
"Killing time"
[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Alyra has a few main goals. Right now, her goals are to do her job well and help the English Ministry fix their problem. And, she also wants to reconnect with an old friend whom she hasn't seen since she was a young kid.&nbsp;

Her future goals include stability and success in fiance/career, and family, possibly marriage and babies, if the mood strikes her.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Grapefruit
Oranges
Lemons
(citrus fruits)[/blockquote][b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Alyra's biggest fear is failing because of her own fault. She wants to be prepared for whatever her line of work throws at her, and her biggest fear is getting herself captured or beat by a better wizard because she just wasn't good enough, or, because she did something stupid to make herself fail.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Alyra is a strong and capable individual. She knows what she wants and is headstrong enough to go and get it, no matter the costs. She is very opinionated and fairly picky, especially when it comes to food. Pineapple does not belong on pizza. A hot dog is not a sandwich. Fish and cheese both smell too weird to be eaten and gross her out. She's not afraid to send something back at a restaurant if it isn't what she ordered or up to her specifications.

That being said, she's not rude. She's a friendly and happy woman, however, she just doesn't take any crap from anyone and doesn't see why she should have to. She's confident in her career and doesn't let anyone push her around. She can be a little blunt and sometimes lacks a filter, but she usually ends up feeling badly if she feels like she was too honest, or, forgot to think before she spoke, which sometimes ends up happening.

Alyra has a good sense of humor and loves to have a good time when she's off the clock. On the clock, at work, she doesn't joke around and takes everything very seriously. She was sent here for a reason and she wants to get her job done and aid the British Ministry in finding the answers they want. However, she loves people and she loves going out and letting her hair down.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Born in England. Her family moved when she was 8 years old to California, USA for her fathers job.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Maggie Jane Ghomes - Mother, 60 years old, halfblood witch
Willie Oliver Pond - Father, 58 years old, muggle

Little sibling Pond -- 22. Ilvermorny grad
Little sibling Pond -- 17, current student (6th year)[/blockquote]
[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]no[/blockquote][b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Alyra was born in England to two loving parents, one a with and the other a muggle. However, they were very much in love regardless and her parents inspired her to love someone for who they were and not for what they were. She never feared falling in love with a muggle and knew, from her parents example that love conquered everything else.&nbsp;

As a kid, Alyra loved structure and loved being in charge, she was always rather bossy with her parents and with her friends. So much so that only one friend really stood with her, a young boy named Rory. Rory was easy going and didn't mind Alyra being strong and in charge. He was happy to go with the flow and follow her. Alyra loved him and loved being friends with him, but their friendship was shaken when her parents announced that they were moving across the world to a state called California in America, where her father's job was being transferred.&nbsp;

Growing up in California was so much better than growing up in England, at least for the little red head with an affinity for the sun. Lee hates snowy weather and loves the sun and the heat. She'd rather be outside than inside and spends as much time as she can soaking up the sun. At the age of 11 she went to Ilvermorny, across the country in one of the colder states where, once again, there was snow. She couldn't get away from it.&nbsp;

Lee's school years were fine. She was a friendly girl and made friends in her house and in her year, but she spend most of her time studying and playing Quadpot. Lee was always an energetic and athletic girl and loved playing the game. She also knew that she needed high marks to get into the job that she wanted, which, she wasn't always sure about. She knew that she either wanted to work in politics so that she could travel for work, or, she wanted to help catch bad guys in some way. She ended up being able to do both, but it took her a while to get there. In school, she wanted to do well in every subject in case she changed her mind about her career and needed a different subject.&nbsp;

Upon Graduation, Lee trained as an auror for the MACUSA and then decided to join the detective agency rather than go on the field as an auror. She wanted to work more mentally and found out during her training that she was good at puzzle solving and coming up with creative solutions. She'd pass all of the theory and written bits with flying colors and knew her skills were better used in the office than on the field. Though, she still was sent out, under cover or to investigate when she was needed and she was confident while doing so. Lee always felt confident using magic and bonded quickly with her wand, when she received it, because she was told that it was a wand given to those who the wand knew could handle the power and strength it possessed.&nbsp;

[/blockquote][b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]The Ilvermorny attack hit close to home for Lee. She loved the school and had loved her time there. She still had a younger sibling who was going back for their final year and now would be going to England to be schooled at Hogwarts. Lee had been hoping to be put on the Ilvermorny investigation case, and she was, briefly, but...

The day after the attack on Azkaban prison in England, her boss pulled her aside and told her that she was going to be sent to England to aid the Ministry in their efforts to fix the problem and recapture their criminals. While Lee didn't want to go back to the cold, she was excited to return to the place of her birth. She had never been back since her family left and she was eager to reconnect with her old friend (who she had kept in vague contact with via email and muggle post through the years), and she was excited to help and clean up the mess.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Ali[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]23[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]PST[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]Who knows[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@rosie       @sav        @riley        @angie        @natalie        @lucyweasley        @lusie        @jack        @claudia       [/blockquote][/div][/div]