[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt=" " style="max-width:100%;" src="https://64.media.tumblr.com/5b9bab16fa9c4d269ffcfb0c9e6d33b2/tumblr_oodoe48sUv1ua1nbgo1_500.gif"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]elliot phillip porter[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]el - leo - t | fi - lip | port - er. [/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]eli.[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]nineteen.
29th june.[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]he/him.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]half-blood.[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]straight.[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]black laurel, dragon heart string, 10".[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]brandon flynn.[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]he stands at about six foot, blue eyes and brown hair and he's got a solid build from years of playing qudditch and a few scars adorn his body from various small falls and accidents from when he was learning to fly. he tends to keep things casual when he dresses and he's not one for fancy clothes and anything with airs and graces. he can slip into a crowd easily and doesn't stand out too much in looks or stature. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]hogwarts | slytherin
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]graduate
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]magical interpol.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]quidditch, halloween, his family, animals, stargazing, old movies, travelling, getting a job done, time away from home, laying on a beach, annoying dusti.[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]being treated like a child, talking about feelings, losing, cats, spiders, sleeping in, melted chocolate, public displays of affection, being cooped up indoors.[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]to work in law enforcement till he retires.
a white picket fence and a few kids.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]moss, pine, spearmint, apple and vanilla.[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]cats &amp; spiders[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote][b]charming[/b] | what slytherin can't be charming when they want to be? it's one of the reasons they get put into the house of green and silver. eli can usually charm his way into and out of any situation that befalls him though there are some people that are immune to his charm.&nbsp;
[b]sarcastic[/b] | he can be sarcastic. most of the time it's hard to tell if what he's saying is sarcastic or what he means.
[b]protective[/b] | his family and friends mean the world to him. he'd do anything for them and that means anything. he doesn't care what would happen to him if he did something that wasn't allowed but he'd do it to save any of them. not that he'd tell them because that makes things awkward.

[b]aloof[/b] | while he's okay with his family and the people that have chipped away enough of his outer armour to be considered his friend, he can appear very cool and unfriendly. it's not that he is, he can actually be friendly when he puts his mind to it and around his family he's better but he isn't one to approach people or try very hard to make a connection with someone.
[b]distant [/b]| he can be very distant even to the people he loves. he doesn't like talking about the emotions that run through his head and he hates letting people know anything that might make him look anything like being vulnerable and like he needs a helping hand. one thing eli can't do, is ask someone for help. he feels he should always be the one to help out his family.
[b]emotionally challenged[/b] | he's not good at expressing his emotions either. he doesn't like public displays of affection from anyone really. though he tolerates hugs from his mother, father and siblings when they are forced on him that's about it. he's never been one to want attention when he's feeling down or ill and he likes to keep up a pretence of always being okay.

[b]patient[/b] | he's got the patience of a big cat that's waiting to stalk it's prey. he doesn't like to rush things like homework or things he has to do and he doesn't mind waiting on people if they're late or if he's in a queue he doesn't let it bother him and he can usually take most things people say to him and let them roll off his back.
[b]temper [/b]| that being said he was a slytherin. he's got a temper on him and it can be a doozy. on the odd occasion when things push him too far he can fire up and it's usually an impressive explosion. when he's angry his magic becomes stronger and a little more out of control and his spells usually pack a little more of a punch. he's not quick to fire up but he takes a long time to calm down and he doesn't ever let go of a grudge.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]surrey. [/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]hal porter | magical lawyer | 49.
gemma porter | healer | 49.  

jackson porter | hogwarts graduate | 21.
lexie porter | hogwarts student | 17
[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]none, but he wants a dog.[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]so this here is eli porter. middle child of hal and gemma and older brother to lexie and younger brother to jackson. his life started out how most babies start out life. as a baby he was quiet, he didn't cry much unless he needed something and as he grew up he stayed that way. but that's not to say he didn't cause trouble. he was always getting into things and from about the age of two he stopped needing his parents help to get himself out of them. there wasn't a bookshelf he climbed up that he couldn't get down from, there wasn't a place he got stuck that he wasn't able to escape from and there wasn't a nook of the house and land they lived on that went without being explored by eli. however when lexie was coming into their lives he struggled a little. he was too young to understand what as happening and why there were all these gifts coming into the house and why every teddy he fell in love with got taken away and put into the new babies room. but once lexie was home and everything settled down so did he and he started to like the idea of having a younger sibling. not that at two he could fathom it really but he settled down a little.

as he and his siblings grew eli knew he was different than them. they were outgoing and they liked pulling pranks and getting themselves into trouble. eli didn't really. he didn't pull pranks because he soon grew to think of them as childish as he was quite often the butt of pranks pulled by his siblings. his parents learned what they had always assumed to be true when he was five years old. of course it was late for a wizard to show his magical ability but that was eli, taking his own time to do things. he was fighting with jackson for some reason, he and his parents can't quite remember what it was about but eli had slammed his hand down onto the table and flames had exploded from underneath and burned his palms. he'd been shocked, his parents had been torn between anger about their table being ruined or happy that eli had used his magic for the first time. he got sent to his room so he figured it wasn't the latter.

when he was eleven, he got his hogwarts letter. he was excited about going off to school for the first time, after all he'd heard about it from his parents and his brother but he knew those stories wouldn't compare to actually seeing it himself. once at the school, sitting under the sorting hat he closed his eyes and hoped for the best. when the hat called out slytherin he really wasn't surprised. he wasn't the first in his family to be placed in the house, his mother had been a slytherin too, so he wasn't upset about it. he took school in his stride, though he did find it a little hard to make friends. he didn't need the connections and he didn't need to have other people in his life but slowly and surely connections started to form, namely in the form of dusti flint. 

she was his best friend, she was the one he stayed up late talking to, the one he shared things with and the strongest connection he'd ever felt in his life. when they were in their seventh year they started dating, letting that connection turn from friendship into romantic and while they were together it was like something cosmic pulling them together. his seventh year was the most tumultuous of his life. there were murders and kidnappings and the tri wizard tournament to live with. he also had to help his girlfriend through something he'd never expected, the discovery that she wasn't who she thought she was and the ultimate death of her parents. 

he was glad when they graduated as life settled into something that was almost normal. he and dusti got a place together, started their respective jobs and for a while things were good. he was working at the ministry with the magical interpol, training with them and learning the jobs they did and dusti was working at the hospital. they were busy but they were making it work.  that was until the mass break out at azkaban. eli was called to help hunt down the dark wizards that had slipped past the borders. there was no end date, he just knew that he'd have to leave the country and not come back till their job was done. he wanted to go, it was part of his job but it caused problems with dusti. 

she didn't want him to go, he knew he couldn't stay and while it almost broke him he had to leave. they left things on bad terms, their relationship in tatters and it took everything in him not to fall apart while he was traipsing around europe trying to find escaped prisoners. he tried to write to dusti but everytime he tried the words escaped him. what could he say? sorry i left you? he couldn't find the words to put from quill to parchment and eventually he just stopped trying. he's been away hunting them for the last six months, though he's hoping the end is drawing near. 
   [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]eli does what he can to block out the events that happened while he was at school. there's too much trauma there to think about so he does his best not to. the only current event he allows himself to focus on are the missing prisoners because he's been helping track the ones that have slipped away to other countries. he was shocked by the death of the minister because it wasn't something he saw coming though he thinks krum might be a decent leader, it's just going to be a waiting game to see if things change for the better or if they keep changing for the worst.   [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]shadow[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her.[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]27.[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]awst.[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]magic.[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]lucas weasley, edward lupin, sunday weekly, calder mugwump, katiya krum, sutton avery &amp; aymeric courtemanche.[/blockquote][/div][/div]