[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://78.media.tumblr.com/cf7cdaf4659a1dcf86a34e346a1bc9c6/tumblr_mf9rjn9Rjc1rj1brbo1_500.gif"][/div]

hello there, my name is [b]albus potter[/b] but [b]al[/b] is just fine. i'm a [b]interning Auror at the Ministry&nbsp;[/b]and [b]18[/b] so that makes me a [b]graduate[/b] of [b]Hogwarts[/b]. You could say I'm [b]cunning, ambitious and prideful[/b] but I personally think that I am [b]sarcastic, reserved and indecisive.[/b]&nbsp;People say I look a lot like [b]logan lerman[/b], but I don't really see it...

[div align="center"][font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][i][b]albus severus potter[/b][/i][/font][/font][/div]

[b][i]pronunciation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]al-bus[/blockquote]
[b][i]nickname:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]al, alby&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]18[/blockquote]
[b][i]date of birth:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]16th of July 2006[/blockquote]
[b][i]gender &amp; pronouns:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]wizard - he/him.[/blockquote]
[b][i]blood status:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]half-blood[/blockquote]
[b][i]sexuality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]undecided, questioning.

[/blockquote]
[b][i]schooling:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]hogwarts alum - slytherin

[/blockquote][b][i]occupation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]trainee auror at the ministry of magic[/blockquote]
[b][i]wand:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]9'5" inches, birch, phoenix feather - whippy[/blockquote]
[b][i]playby:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]logan lerman[/blockquote]
[b][i]appearance:[/i] [/b]
[blockquote]much like his playby, albus has fair skin, dark brown hair and stands slightly shorter than average at 5'7". he is often compared to his father in appearance, lacking the weasley's red hair and sharing the same startling green eyes as harry, for which he is often reminded. with a slim build and a stillness about him, he has often felt rather plain and unassuming. not unwilling to blend in to the background, albus will usually avoid the limelight and so is often found in plain, fitted suits for work and comfortable jumpers casually. most recently, albus has begun to require glasses, though he prefers contacts over frames. while he does not hate his father, albus does not enjoy being constantly compared to him.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personality[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]likes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]
[ul type="disc"]
[li]new books[/li]
[li]potions[/li]
[li]journals[/li]
[li]hogwarts library[/li]
[li]jazz music[/li]
[li]self-inking quills[/li]
[li]buttermint tea[/li]
[li]ghosts[/li]
[/ul][/blockquote]
[b][i]dislikes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]
[ul type="disc"]
[li]being compared to his father[/li]
[li]being wrong[/li]
[li]rats[/li]
[li]overthinking things[/li]
[li]his tendency to be socially awkward[/li]
[li]having to filter his thoughts[/li]
[li]the uncertainty of his future[/li]
[li]failing at a goal/ambition[/li]
[/ul][/blockquote]
[b][i]erised:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]to be appreciated professionally for something other than his family's accomplishments.[/blockquote]
[b][i]amortentia:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]a biting winter frost, the smell of fresh laundry, tea and a musky perfume.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b][i]boggart:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]albus fears his own inadequacy. it is hard being the mirror son of The Chosen One.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b][i]overall personality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Albus has a mixture of his father's arrogance and his mother's kindness, but it would be unwise to tell him this. With an almost obsessive desire to break away from the reputation his parent's have earned, and forge one of his own, Al struggles to appreciate the privilege he was born in to. To him, it is a burden that he has bore since the day he was born, and the fact that he bears such a striking resemblance to his father has not improved this burgeoning resentment. In fact, it encouraged Al's crippling anxiety at being noticed as he grew up, always for the wrong reasons. Never for himself. 

As a child Al was as playful and active as any, but as time went on and he realised the scope of the Potter name, he began to feel an overwhelming desire to run from it. It didn't help that he has always struggled to express himself emotionally, hating the spotlight so much that it filled him with panic. Over time, Al found solace and understanding in books instead, burying himself in dusty old tomes and ancient scripts. He dedicated a lot of time to his academic interests, all in an effort to absorb something completely his own. 

At the bear bone, Albus is a young man searching for himself. He easily comprehends confusing potions and complex defensive spells, but he has never understood the mechanisms of his own weaknesses. His pride, his judgement and his suspicious nature. All traits that help him as much as they hinder him. 

However, Albus is not all seriousness. He can be incredibly funny and light-hearted. You don’t grow up with Lily and James Potter without absorbing some of that natural wit. Though, Albus’s strength lies in his whip-quick sarcasm. A look he dolls out with a simple roll of his eyes and a slack look on his face, cutting to the bear bones. To his friends he is funny and oddly observant. As a teenager, he had a great knack for accents, though only a select few could goad him in to performing. But, it really just depends on the day. 

Albus Potter is as ambitious as he is compassionate, he simply struggles to show the good in him as he favors his personal success and comeuppance over the thrill of moral kindness. Break apart the walls he has carefully manufactured for himself and you will find a boy who simply does not know who he is, or who he wants to be. It seems he as spent so much time being told who he is that it has erased in him his ability to identify his own emotional strengths. He’d rather simply avoid them for now. I mean, it’s worked so far, right? 

[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personal history[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]mother:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]ginerva molly "ginny" potter nee weasley, 42, daily prophet writer[/blockquote]
[b][i]father:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]harry james potter, 43, MIA - presumed dead

[/blockquote][b][i]siblings:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]james potter, 19, professional quidditch player
lily potter, 17, student[/blockquote]
[b][i]pets:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]remy, snowy owl[/blockquote]
[b][i]history:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Ask anyone, Albus Potter is the spitting image of his father. Ever since he was born, on a sweltering day in the middle of July, little Alby Potter has been told the same thing. With his unkempt dark hair, piercing green eyes and pale, round face, he is a reflection of the infamous Harry Potter. But, he had none of his father’s sociability and adaptive nature. Rather, Albus was very much content to spend his days reading and listening to music. It quickly became apparent that he had none of his mother’s sporting talent, and none of his father’s confidence. Instead, he was studious and quiet, so withdrawn at times that his parent’s often worried after him. It was difficult being the son of two people who had seen and accomplished so much, and this did not escape Albus. He didn’t look upon his parent’s achievements and think in wonder and admiration. he looked upon them and felt an undeniable dread: ‘However will I live up to this legacy’. In short, he did not think he could. And it did not help that he was named after two people whom were viewed upon as heroic and unforgettable figures within the Wizarding community. Wherever Albus looked he saw extraordinary talent, except when he looked in the mirror. 

Though, growing up, Albus lived a rather typical life. His childhood was privileged and comfortable. Albus had very varied interests as a child, each of which his parent’s encouraged and endorsed in every way possible. From flying to piano to painting. This was all a concentrated effort from Albus, as he searched for the one thing he was unflinchingly good at. As it turned out, he was quite frustratingly average at everything, except for his unquenchable thirst for knowledge and understanding, which he retained with an impressive recollection. Albus’s biggest flaw was realization where his strengths lay, always searching for them outwith himself. 

His acceptance letter to Hogwarts was as expected as it was exciting. He’d already displayed a magical propensity in his youth, that quietness about him almost palpable at times. Especially when goaded by his loud and overbearing siblings. He entered his first year at Hogwart’s with insurmountable expectations for himself and his abilities. Though, being sorted in to Slytherin was perhaps his saving grace as he trundled towards an overwhelming ledge. By being placed so, he avoided the burden of greatness within Gryffindor’s mighty ranks, where his father might as well have been a Saint or a God. He need not be terribly brave, nor chivalrous. Instead, in Slytherin they helped nurture his hungry ambition and natural resourcefulness. Though, unfortunately it also helped Albus isolate himself further and further from his father’s name and legacy, perhaps to his own detriment. Over time it fueled this desire in him, giving it fire where thing need not be burned. 

However, it came as an unfortunate realization as time went on, that Albus realized that he wasn’t as talented as he hoped he’d be. Albus could not contain his desire to be good at everything, all in a vain attempt to find a place for himself within himself, as a singular and not an extension of Harry Potter. He failed to impress in Divination, Astronomy and Charms. He did not garner negative attention per say, but the lack of impression at all came as something of a shock to him. He was not especially smart in anything, bar in Defence Against the Dark Arts and Potions. Where his talents were remarked upon by his professors. The former was met with an almost disgruntled acceptance, as Albus realized he could not escape the comparisons to his father even as a Slytherin. This did not mean that he did not reap the rewards, as it was the only class that Albus felt truly at ease. Except perhaps Potions, which was the only place that he could work without his father’s shadow hanging over him. There, he was simply Alby, with a deft talent for measurements and speed. It was the only class that Albus enjoyed virtually guilt free. Though he could not escape completely, as more than once he was reminded that he bore the middle name of one of the most impressive Potioneer’s in all of recorded time, Severus Snape. If it wasn’t one thing, it was another, or so Albus thought. 

And while beyond his own machinations in self doubt and resentment, Albus’s time at Hogwarts was reasonably unremarkable. He enjoyed his solitude, where he found a talent in journalling and potion recipes, but he was not so quiet that he had no friends. In fact, Albus had quite a few, his natural sarcasm making him a funny mate when given the chance to break free of his awkwardness. And his summers were spent with family, working at the Weasleys’ Wizard Wheezes, surrounded by laughter and friends. In the end, Albus made it all the way to graduation without self-destructing, which was almost as surprising to him as it was to everyone who knew him. He graduated from Hogwarts and almost immediately fell in to an internship at the Ministry as an Auror In Training, just as his father had done before him. But still, that shadow of expectation follows him whether he likes it or not, but in time he has grown to desire not just to out run it, but overcome it. 

Albus was barely in to his training at the Ministry when tragedy hit the Potter’s in a way he was not prepared for. When it was reported that his father was missing, Harry heard it from work before he heard it from home. The owl from his mother unnervingly calm, as if for her children’s benefit. Details revealed that his father had simply gone out one morning to work and he had not showed up, or returned. Nobody knew where or why or how. Albus wondered if his father had simply had enough. That the return of darkness in a world where he had already seen so much had overwhelmed him. Those first few weeks were an emotional rollar coaster as Albus struggled to juggle his own grief and confusion with his mounting frustrations. He could not help but mask it all with a simple assumption. It was Harry Potter’s own fault.

Burying himself in work, Albus soon adopted an appearance of aloofness. He could not afford to be weak as James soon followed their father in a vain attempt to find him, and Lily grew wilder and wilder without Harry’s steady hand. Albus would remain collected, unmoved by this new arrangement. Or so he told himself. More and more his mask is chipped away, first by the confusing return of James and then as their father was officially presumed dead. Though he did find some solace at the bottom of a glass or in a pretty face. He was not, after all, made of stone.[/blockquote]
[b][i]site events reaction:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Albus was not untouched by the tragedy that has befell the Wizarding community. From before the birth of the terrorist organization, The Purifiers, he saw his brother’s trauma from finding one of the many muggleborn victims killed in the spree at Hogwarts. This birthed a sense of duty in Albus as he saw the damage that was done, feeling a desire to do something about it, however small. This was only made more aggressive when the visiting students from Beauxbaton and Durmstrang were bombed following the Tri-Wizard Tournament. Dark times were upon them. Proven even more so as he was hit very close to him, Harry Potter’s disappearance - now  presumed dead - not only shaking the Potter’s, but the Wizarding Community as a whole. It seemed as if everything went even further down hill from there as the summer ended with an explosion at the American school of magic, Ilvermorny, forcing the transfer of many students. It has all come to a head as the infamous and revered Harry Potter is presumed officially dead. Albus does not know what he can do, only that he must do something.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]alias[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]name:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]chanel[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]22[/blockquote]
[b][i]time zone:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]GMT[/blockquote]
[b][i]reference:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]can't get rid of me[/blockquote]
[b][i]other characters:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]uuuh, lots. tia, ondina, aaron, elijah, jimmie, nate, elliot, ana, donna[/blockquote][/div][/div]