[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;background-color:#B6B6B4;border:4px solid #B6B6B4;border-radius:10px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://78.media.tumblr.com/d02e96c168b89292cd4cc15470616ebf/tumblr_otql13Xypl1ut8uwjo1_500.gif"][/div]

hello there, my name is [b]Ezekiel Deon Walker[/b] but you can call me [b]Zeke[/b]. i'm a/an [b]Hufflepuff[/b] and&nbsp;[b]17[/b] so that makes me a [b]7th year[/b]&nbsp;at [b]Hogwarts, transferred from Ilvermorny[/b].&nbsp;You could say I'm [b]hard-working, patient, and loyal,[/b] but I personally think that I am [b]kind-hearted, entertaining, and accepting[/b]. People say I look a lot like [b]Khalid[/b], but I don't really see it...

[div align="center"][font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][i][b]Ezekiel Deon Walker[/b][/i][/font][/font][/div]

[b][i]pronunciation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]/ˈɛzɪˌkil ˈdaɪən ˈwɔkər/[/blockquote]
[b][i]nickname:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Zeke[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]17[/blockquote]
[b][i]date of birth:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]September 28, 2006[/blockquote]
[b][i]gender &amp; pronouns:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Cisgender male; he/him pronouns[/blockquote]
[b][i]blood status:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]No-Maj-born (Muggle-born)[/blockquote]
[b][i]sexuality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Pansexual[/blockquote]
[b][i]schooling:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Ilvermorny - Pukwudgie (home institution)
Hogwarts - Hufflepuff (2024-2025 academic year)[/blockquote]
[b][i]occupation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Entering into his final year of school, Zeke thinks that he might enter the Auror training program for MACUSA once he graduates, since he is (or was, under the American system) on track to meet the prerequisites.[/blockquote]
[b][i]wand:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]13 inches, spruce, Snallygaster heartstring core, reasonably supple (original)
11 ¼ inches, pear, dragon heartstring core, solid[/blockquote]
[b][i]playby:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Khalid[/blockquote]
[b][i]appearance:[/i] [/b]
[blockquote]Zeke stands at about 5'10" inches tall and has a muscular and slightly imposing build. An African-American, he has dark skin, black hair, and brown eyes. He usually keeps his hair in a flattop style, and he is rarely—if ever—clean-shaven, making him look older than he actually is. When he smiles, which is fairly often, the gap between his front teeth becomes apparent.

As far as Zeke's clothing goes, he doesn't really wear robes besides his school uniform. Being a No-Maj-born, he prefers non-magical clothing and usually opts for brightly-colored athletic wear for everyday life. It isn't often that Zeke gets dressed up for an occasion, but he doesn't mind it when he does.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personality[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]likes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Southern cooking, politeness, R&amp;B music, dueling, dogs, Home Economics, making others laugh, his younger sister, sleeping in, cars[/blockquote]
[b][i]dislikes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Blood prejudice, hurting others, basketball, waking up early, fast food, heights, airplanes, roller coasters, animal abuse, green beans[/blockquote]
[b][i]erised:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Zeke's goal is to become an Auror someday. In the Mirror of Erised, he would see himself as an Auror, standing alongside his family and friends.[/blockquote]
[b][i]amortentia:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Macaroni and cheese, cinnamon, and new sneakers[/blockquote]
[b][i]boggart:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Zeke's greatest fear is heights; however, he also fears that something will happen to his family while he's at Hogwarts.[/blockquote]
[b][i]overall personality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Although he might come across as a tough guy because of his appearance and love for dueling, anyone who has known Zeke for more than a few minutes knows that he's really nothing more than a giant teddy bear. He acts from the heart and will gladly step in to help a friend out of a jam or to cheer someone up with a joke on a bad day. When he was younger, he was quite the “class clown” type, and—though he's learned not to clown around so much and to focus on his schoolwork—he wouldn't make a bad comedian.

Zeke is as loyal a friend as anyone could want, and he would be happy to lend someone the shirt from off of his back if they were in need of it. His generosity extends to nearly everyone; in fact, he rescued his dog, Peanut, as a stray. He is also very polite, and he does refer to his elders as “sir” and “ma'am”.

Like anyone, Zeke has his insecurities. He's pansexual, a realization that shaped his views of both the magical and non-magical worlds he has to straddle. He finds that he gets more nervous when he's attracted to those who aren't cisgender females, since he knows that he doesn't exactly seem like a member of the LGBTQ+ community and doesn't want to be judged for it. Unrelated to his sexuality, Zeke is also terrified of heights, which means that flying on a broomstick is out of the question for him.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personal history[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]mother:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Angela Walker (née Robinson), 51, high school English teacher, No-Maj (Muggle)[/blockquote]
[b][i]father:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Byron Walker, 55, police detective, No-Maj (Muggle)[/blockquote]
[b][i]siblings:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Imani Ruth Walker, 9, elementary school student, No-Maj (Muggle)[/blockquote]
[b][i]pets:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Peanut, unknown, male terrier mix, at home[/blockquote]
[b][i]history:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Growing up in the suburbs of Atlanta, Georgia, the last thing that Ezekiel Walker ever expected was that he would turn out to be a wizard. He imagined that he would likely grow up to be a teacher or a detective, like his parents, or maybe a doctor or a lawyer. The only things that Ezekiel knew about wizards and witches were what he had read about in some of his books. From that, he knew that wizards and witches were generally old, often ugly, and [i]certainly[/i] not normal kids from Georgia. He had done a few strange things from about kindergarten onwards—things he hadn't been able to explain to his parents—but those got laughed off and attributed to the “ghosts” that must have been haunting their home.

They weren't ghosts, though, as Zeke found out a few years later. He had been a good student in elementary school, so he was looking forward to entering middle school and getting all of the cool perks that came with it—a locker, possibly a cellphone—when he received the news that would change his life as he knew it: He was a wizard, an eleven-year-old wizard with magical powers that he needed to learn how to control at a special boarding school for wizards and witches, a place in Massachusetts called Ilvermorny.

Zeke wasn't sure how he would like boarding school. It meant leaving his home and his parents and his little sister, which he had never done before. Nevertheless, he went to Ilvermorny, wand and all, to start his life as a [i]real[/i] wizard.

After being chosen for Pukwudgie House, Zeke thought that he would begin to feel at home at his new school, but he found that that wasn't entirely the case. Being treated with suspicion for being No-Maj-born was definitely something that Zeke hadn't expected to happen at Ilvermorny, but he was also used to people's presumptions about him back at home because of his race. As he started getting more comfortable with his own abilities and started to make friends, the biases bothered him less and less. He was a wizard, and he thought that that was pretty great.

As the years went by, Ezekiel got used to his routine—summers and Christmases in Georgia and the rest of the year at school. It was weird to be away from one place or the other for too long; his friends grew up and had moved on to football and dating and the excitement of starting high school. He understood their excitement to some extent, because he had once thought about what it would be like, but he realized that he missed Ilvermorny—having his wand and getting to hang out with his school friends every day—even more.

Being from a non-magical family without any connections to the magical community in Britain, most of the news that Zeke received about Hogwarts came in his sixth year, when the Triwizard Tournament was being held. Although Ilvermorny had no involvement in it, he followed what the [i]New York Ghost[/i] had to say about it. He had never quite understood the magical world's obsession with putting people in dangerous situations for sport, but he wondered if that was just his aversion to heights talking.

When the news broke that both the Durmstrang Ship and Beauxbatons Carriage had exploded, Zeke was shocked. It wasn't the first time that something bad had happened at Hogwarts, but he felt like he knew the Champions from everything that he had read about them over the course of the year.

Going home for the summer felt like any other summer before it, until he heard from a friend that their school was in ruins and that anyone whose wand was still at Ilvermorny was wandless. The shock that he had felt about the Triwizard Tournament disaster was only amplified. [i]His[/i] school had been attacked this time, and he felt hurt and angry that it had. The only good news in all of the mess was that Hogwarts had extended an invitation to anyone from Ilvermorny who wanted to continue their education there.

Despite the distance and the dangers that would probably face him in Britain, Zeke decided that he would take up the offer. He had no other way of finishing his magical schooling, which he needed if he was going to train to become an Auror.

Opting to arrive in Britain ahead of the school year in order to get everything that he needed, Zeke didn't have much re-packing to do, though he was relieved that he was able to arrange for a Portkey through MACUSA instead of needing a flight to London.

The city isn't anything like he expected it to be, although it isn't bad at all. Upon his arrival, Zeke had been staying in a youth hostel but lucked out after his first few weeks and has been staying with a classmate in Diagon Alley ever since, making it that much easier to run his school-related errands without running into any hiccups. He is looking forward to the start of the school year, though he's cautious about what might happen at Hogwarts next.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]alias[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]name:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Audrey[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]20[/blockquote]
[b][i]time zone:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]US/Canada Central/Eastern[/blockquote]
[b][i]reference:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Current member![/blockquote]
[b][i]other characters:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]@maxima , @parvati , @oona , @honey , @kaylee [/blockquote][/div][/div]
