[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;background-color:#B6B6B4;border:4px solid #B6B6B4;border-radius:10px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://i.imgur.com/8I4BsGV.gif"][/div]

hello there, my name is [b]ondina nell weasley.&nbsp;[/b]i'm an&nbsp;[b]alumni&nbsp;[/b]and [b]18&nbsp;[/b]so that makes me a [b]graduate[/b]&nbsp;of&nbsp;[b]Hogwarts[/b]. You could say I'm [b]cunning, resourceful and ambitious[/b]&nbsp;but I personally think that I am [b]selfish, obsessive and inescure[/b]. People say I look a lot like [b]madelain petsch[/b], but I don't really see it...

[div align="center"][font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][i][b]ondina nell weasley[/b][/i][/font][/font][/div]

[b][i]pronunciation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]on-dy-na nell weez-lee[/blockquote]
[b][i]nickname:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]people have attempted to call her dina, with very limited success.[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]18[/blockquote]
[b][i]date of birth:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]31st of January, 2006[/blockquote]
[b][i]gender &amp; pronouns:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]she, her[/blockquote]
[b][i]blood status:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]pureblood[/blockquote]
[b][i]sexuality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]bi

[/blockquote]
[b][i]schooling:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts, Slytherin&nbsp;

[/blockquote][b][i]occupation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]intern at the department of international magical cooperation&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b][i]wand:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]12 inches, cherry, dragonheart string, unyielding.[/blockquote]
[b][i]playby:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]madelaine petsch[/blockquote][b][i]appearance:[/i] [/b]
[blockquote]ondina is approximately 5'4" with a very pale complexion due to illness and a chronic lack of oxygen, of which she covers up with heavy make up and sometimes sunglasses. she has brown eyes and bright red weasley hair. often times her eyes are ringed with a slight red, and sometimes around her nose, too. both of which she goes to great lengths to cover up, but that some times slip through observation.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personality[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]likes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]charms

transfigurations

photography

dragons&nbsp;

rain on a roof

nonverbal magic - of which she's very talented at

any muggle movies, of which she grew fond of while stuck at home

board games

reading

[/blockquote]
[b][i]dislikes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]any animal that has fur

potions

herbology

seasons changing (spring/fall)

sports[/blockquote]
[b][i]erised:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]to be completely free of illness[/blockquote]
[b][i]amortentia:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]peppermint

the smell of the air after a great spell has been cast

fresh snowfall
[/blockquote]
[b][i]boggart:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]dying by a severe asthma attack and drowning as she never learned to swim[/blockquote]
[b][i]overall personality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]In short Ondina is a spoiled girl who never learned the word no. So sheltered from a life indoors that at times she can be extremely out of touch from the outside world. But, she is a master manipulator at heart, who has learned to use her vulnerability and common pity to her advantage, though she despises both of these things. Her parents doted on her above her two siblings, and so camaraderie is not Ondina's first instinct. She knows only what it means to win, and almost everything is a battle to her. A battle of wills, wits and guile. But not physically, because physically Ondina is at a great disadvantage. 

However, due to this constant over-protectiveness, Ondina is extremely paranoid about her health. While she despises the reality of it, Ondina has never wavered in her constant tick of medicines and rituals. She will not shake hands, although this is quite alright with her, it gives off the impression she so desires. She is very wary of dirt, germs and the foods she consumes. Her immune-system naturally compromised. She keeps a diary of her every meal and medicine, along with a note of her heart rate and core temperature every day. Just like her mother used to before Ondina stopped allowing her to interfere. But overall, Ondina hides this vulnerability as much as possible. So, where people call her private, cold and impersonal, three things she most definitely is, this is more to keep up the pretence of carelessness. She never runs because she's simply at leisure, not because the notion alone makes her chest feel tight.&nbsp;

Alone, Ondina practices non verbal spells. Her breathing is often so choppy that saying a spell with complete conviction can fall flat. So, early on Ondina realised that if she wanted to be a great spell caster, she had to learn how to do it without speaking. Of which she is quite gifted at, and uses to her advantage. Both socially and academically. And while potions or herbology had never been a strength of Ondina's, she excels at Charms and especially Transfiguration. To which she has gotten herself in to trouble practising on many occasions - often on unwilling participants.&nbsp;

Overall, Ondina can be extremely spiteful and relentless. Once a person wrongs her, in her eyes, she will often seek to destroy them. This stems from a selfish, doting childhood, but also from insecurity. Ondina needs to maintain this appearance of strength. Her physical health is so at odds, she often overcompensates in every other aspect of her life. But she is also self-serving and cruel without even trying. It is only second nature to cut a person down to the bone with a flyaway remark. Her apathy when it comes to others is something of which she has never really sought to change. She feels no desire to be compassionate. What idiot wishes to waste time thinking about anyone but themselves? That's how you end up dead. And while this attitude has served her well personally, it has greatly effected the relationships between her and her family. She feels no desire to connect to them, and often uses them for her own gain. Again, she is a great manipulator. This is greatly due to the fact that Ondina has always felt like the odd one out. The little sick girl, a mistake on an otherwise gifted family name. She resents this, and the pity it insights. But, over time and with the company she tends to keep, a lot of her extended family have all but lost patience with her completely at times.&nbsp;

However, beyond the thoughtless cruelty and ruthless ambition, Ondina is extreme insecurity has shaped her. She is aware of her weaknesses as if they are a collar around her neck, attached to a chain that pulls her further and further in to the ground. She feels her days are numbered, and nothing scares Ondina more than a meaningless death. While she naturally craves attention, Ondina doesn't wish to be seen as the sick girl her family sees her as. So, she keeps company that might see her differently. Even if for the wrong reasons. Ondina isn't a Blood Purist. She is but a scared little girl desperately searching for health and fulfilment in all the wrong places.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personal history[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]mother:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Natalie (McDonald) Weasley, 39-years-old, stay at home mother[/blockquote]
[b][i]father:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Charlie Weasley, 47-years-old, dragonologist

[/blockquote][b][i]siblings:[/i][/b]
[blockquote][/blockquote]&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Harper Io Weasley, 19-years-old, metal charmer
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Xavier Jane Weasley, 15-years-old, ravenclaw student
[b][i]
pets:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]none, ondina is allergic to most animal dander and so tends to avoid them as much as possible for fear of a reaction.&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b][i]history:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Ondina Weasley had heard the story of her miraculous birth a million times, and each time her parents told it, it grated just a little thinner. She’d been born second to her sister, Harper, after a tumultuous pregnancy that had been incredibly difficult for her mother Natalie. In fact, her mother had been advised to lay up in bed for weeks after a particular scare that always made Natalie Weasley a little grey when she recounted it. ‘You were always my most theatrical child, Dina. So impatient’. Of which Ondina used to preen at, but which grew old the older she got, mainly because it lost its sweetened edge the more theatrical Ondina became out of the womb. Born very premature, Ondina spent the first few weeks of her life in a hospital, a place she would later be so familiar with it was almost her second home. 

A very sickly baby, her parents quickly realised that Ondina hadn’t only been impatient in the womb, she was impatient out of it, too. Crying for days straight, until her pale skin grew blue and it was back to the hospital again. Her lungs never had developed properly, of which would follow her in to young adulthood. And no magic, no matter how hard they tried, could feasibly cure Ondina of her asthma. But, where Ondina’s health had failed her, her parent’s overcompensated in every other aspect of her life. 

Natalie blamed herself, she hadn’t rested long enough. As a mother it had surely been her duty to create a healthy baby, but it was simply not the case. And with her misplaced guilt, Natalie threw every ounce of her attention in to providing Ondina with every whim and want she desired. She was, to put it quite plainly, rather spoiled. With two parents at her beck and call, Ondina quickly grew quite accustomed to getting exactly what she wanted, when she wanted. Perhaps to the detriment of her two other sibling, Harper and Xavier. But, where materially Ondina had whatever she wanted, there were other things she soon realised would always be out of her reach. 

In summer, Ondina had to watch from her window as her great gaggle of cousins and her two siblings all played together. Running until their faces turned red, until they fell over and laughed. All Ondina wanted was to be a part of those foreign adventures. But, her chest was no better as a child as it had been as an infant. She was a wheezy little thing, with an array of medicines to be administered like clock work, lest she fall gravely ill. Along with a severe case of asthma, Ondina had allergies. Pollen, gluten, nuts, dairy, animal dander. Her life was a countdown of various things she couldn’t do. Her immune system wasn’t like the others, she was told. It was always better if she stayed in, there was never enough adults to supervise Ondina. Never enough eyes checking her colour, fingers prodding at her head and neck to check her ever wavering temperature. Even her cousins looked at her oddly, like she was an alien among men. No they couldn’t sneak her out, no it was better if she stay with mum. She didn’t want them to, anyway, Ondina told herself. Xavier was just jealous, and Harper was a bore who only ever spoke about Muggle tech.  

And so, Ondina grew to entertain herself in other ways. She had a voracious appetite for reading and writing, filled notebook after notebook with nonsensical magic that she picked up from great leather bound beasts. One thing about the Weasley’s, there was plenty to read around them. Ondina went through everything from her fathers guides on Magical Creatures, to old spell books and knicked school work books. She had something of a head start in many magical subjects, and from a very young age astounded family members with her excellent instincts and premature abilities, but also her terrifying control. She couldn’t play, and so she learned instead. Adding to the fact that Ondina was often in the company of witches and wizards far beyond her age. Stuck to her mother’s side, she went wherever Natalie went. And so Ondina felt ‘mature’. She wanted to be just like them, watched them perform magic and desired to know all the knew. The Weasley’s fielded a lot of questions from a young Ondina, and none seemed to really deny her when she inquired. Who would deny a sickly child a simple answer? And so, Ondina knew magic well beyond her years. She was… special. But, of course, underage magic was prohibited and so a lot of Ondina’s ‘lessons’ were done out of sight as much as possible. She was a wily sneak when her brother wasn’t tattling. 

Soon enough Ondina became of age, and like Harper before her, surely she would be headed to Hogwarts. But there had been doubt as to whether or not Ondina would even receive a letter. She was so frail, prone to sickness and fatigue. Would her health pose a problem? Natalie and Charlie seemed to think so, but a letter came all the same. Much to Ondina’s great relief. She had been talking about the school for years, even as her parents grew quieter, concerned that their tantrum-prone daughter would not get what she wanted for the first time in a long time. So, when her letter arrived, celebration was due. Natalie worried, of course, Ondina hadn’t been out of sight since her birth. To a school so far from home, where something could so easily go wrong. But, Ondina wouldn’t listen to any concerns. She felt invincible, finally able to learn with other students. Not cooped up at home, in her clinically clean bedroom. 

Sitting on the stool to be sorted, Ondina had surely expected to be sorted in to Ravenclaw or Gryffindor with many other family members. However, when Slytherin was called, well none was more surprised than she. But, deep down it wasn’t much of a shock at all. Ondina had always been a little cunning. Ambitious well beyond her capabilities, and resourceful. But, there were great prejudices held against the house, and Ondina’s sister hadn’t been placed there. She’d be alone. Her mother despaired at the fact. Natalie even going so far as to consider speaking to the Head about reconsidering. Her daughter wouldn’t be safe in Slytherin, they were… ruthless. But, to her own shock, Ondina quickly found her place among fellow Slytherins. Despite her family’s disapproval, deep down she knew… it was the place for her. No matter the reputation, no matter her mothers concern. But, in a house where often weakness was not tolerated, Ondina felt a growing desperation to shed her illness in every way possible. 

She adapted quickly, found ways to hide her pale skin with warm make up and a light blushing spell. She never ran anywhere, and always had a note to get her out of any sport. It wasn’t her thing, she had a… friend high up, she would tell other students. Ondina could weave a tale, and as far as many were concerned she was perfectly fine, despite maybe a ‘light’ case of asthma. She was a neat freak, a germaphobe and a ‘picky eater’. The only people who truly knew the extent of Ondina’s many ailments were her family, and a big family at that. But, after a particular incident where a cousin inquired of her health, with compassionate concern, Ondina snapped so viciously that it soon became common knowledge not to bring the subject up. An unspoken agreement, lest they incur Ondina’s cruel temper. 

As the years passed, Natalie still threw hints whenever Ondina was home that a change might be for the better, and when she wasn’t home there wasn’t a day that went by without a letter from home. How was she keeping, was she taking her medicines, what had her temperature been the previous night? Soon enough, as Ondina grew older, and perhaps colder and she eventually stopped answering her mother’s letters as frequently. Where once Ondina preened for her mother’s infinite attention, at Hogwart’s she garnered new interest, pretty boys and mean girls. She could be the center of attention in other ways. Through her impressive nonverbal spell work and harsh remarks. Oftentimes, Ondina was a bit of a bully. It was only second nature for her to become extremely defensive whenever she felt threatened, and pity the fool on the other end because she had never been the type to go easy on anything, apart from running. And soon, as tensions grew at Hogwart’s once again, Ondina fell further  in to dark company, blood purists with grand ideas, she went so far as to spike a fellow student with a love potion. It had seemed fun at the time. Because Ondina wasn’t just in with a bad crowd, she [i]was [/i]the bad crowd. Her parents long since giving up the notion that their precious daughter was not Slytherin bound. 

In Ondina’s sixth year dark times befell Hogwarts as multiple students were murdered in vicious attacks. But, as crass as it may sound, they were ‘just Muggle-borns’, so Ondina found herself almost apathetic. Better them than me. Ondina was a selfish being, she cared more about herself and her own well being than any other. So, as people were targeted, Ondina padded herself with others and the comfort of her convenient pure-blood. 

However, it didn’t end there and Ondina soon realised that something was coming. A change. But Ondina expected it, she had long since swept aside the reality that most of her friends were blood purist’s with big ideas. So, when fellow Slytherin Elaine Dupree confessed to the muggle-born murders and a group of students were kidnapped soon after, Ondina knew that sides would need to be taken. As always, Ondina favoured strength. She wanted to be healthy, she wanted to be powerful. All the things she had never had the opportunity to be as a child. And when the attacks did not stop, but rather escalated - King’s Cross being targeted and students getting gravely hurt or dying, Ondina realised that perhaps her side wasn’t with the Order. Where most Weasley’s would surely turn. No, Ondina found commonality with the named ‘Purifiers’. She’d known Dupree in school, had even helped her with some sinister experiments. It seemed… inevitable. 

Along with the previous attacks, the schemes and tension surrounding the Triwizard Tournment never really excited Ondina much. It was all an afterthought, as often things were when related to any sport of any kind. But, Ondina simply wanted to stay in cahoots with The Purifiers, though she had no interest in the purity of blood, other motivations spurred her on. She made herself useful as much as  possible, a convenient piece in a game of chess that often ended people’s lives. But, that didn’t so much concern Ondina as school continued and the Tournament progressed. She knew it was coming when the foreign students were targeted. She could have told, but she didn’t. It was important that she kept quiet, to earn the trust of her counterparts. The parts that Ondina was beginning to think might win after all. 

Ondina graduated amid great sorrow and strife and began an internship at the Department of International Magical Cooperation, a place her father had put in a good word for her to get. But, the thought still lingered, and ties grew stronger as Ondina sought to stay in touch with many members of The Purifiers. Even as family friend and her uncle Harry Potter disappeared from the face of the Earth, leaving nothing but a broken wand behind. Ultimately, though, Ondina’s true motivation is to find a spell or elixir that will once and for all restore her health. So perhaps her loyalty is tinged with self-serving purposes. Then again, when has it ever been about anything else for Ondina? 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]alias[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]name:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]chanel[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]21[/blockquote]
[b][i]time zone:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]GMT[/blockquote]
[b][i]reference:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Rissy       [/blockquote]
[b][i]other characters:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]@tia[/blockquote][/div][/div]