[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt=" " src="https://thenetline.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Abigail-Cowen.jpg" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]harper io weasley[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]har-per[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Harp.[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]21
April 28th, 2005[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Female. She/Her/Hers[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Pureblood.[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Bisexual.[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]11 inches, mahogany, centaur tail hair, pliable.[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Abigail Cowen.[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]5’6”. Basically same as playby. She rides a motorcycle often, so it’s common to find her with a leather jacket, helmet, etc.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts. Gryffindor.
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduated 2023.
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Magical Artifact Development and Testing Office: 2025-Present
Metal Charmer: 2023-2025[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Muggle everything!, motorcycles, hot chocolate, stuffed animals, fireplaces, being warm, oversized sweatshirts, sleeping in, low-fi hip-hop, using her hands.[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Rain, waiting in lines, being sick, pretentiousness, not being able to ride her motorcycle, when someone cuts her off while she’s talking, getting interrupted while working.[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]To continuously integrate muggle technology into the magical community.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Burning wood, gasoline, metal.[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Ondina screaming when Harper accidentally dropped a motorcycle on her when they were kids. Accidentally breaking the statute of secrecy with her meddling in muggle tech. [/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Harper loves life, and she likes to think that it loves her back. Being thoroughly inquisitive all the time, her intense interest in muggles (in the same manner as her grandfather, if not better at it than he is). She enjoys everything they do and wants nothing more than to integrate their ideas into her own society. Quick to defend muggles and muggle-borns when they are heavily criticized, she knows she has enough proof and references that magical folk need their non-magical counterparts more than they think. At times, this blind devotion for them makes it hard for her to see the other side, and how total assimilation could come with potential problems of their own. Still, she keeps up her positive, upbeat nature that maybe one day it would be possible without a hitch and that she could be one of the ones to potentially build the bridge that does so.

Outside of her passions (which include muggles and motorcycles), she can be found to be extremely relaxed and that she normally goes with the flow. She likes to think through things logically, coming up with the best possible outcome before jumping in head first. Her profession as a metal charmer goes along with this, allowing her to pull pieces of technology apart and do her thing on them piece by piece. Not everything fits the first time, so breaking down problems figuring out where everything went wrong is a common thing for her. While frustration is a common occurrence in her field, with everything being experimental, she tries to replace the negativity with the potential positive impacts that her job would have on other lives.

She tries to carry this over to her social life as well, especially when it comes to her family. Trying to be as optimistic and caring as she can be towards her siblings, she comes across as a push-over. Whether she is or not is up to the person debating her, because most of the time she doesn’t see the need to keep arguing with someone that isn’t going to change their mind. The most she can do at that point is to present her points and leave them with that. At the end of the day, she still cares about those closest to her, even if they don’t agree with her, and will do whatever she can for them. She won’t hold their flaws over their heads for vindictive reasons, because that isn’t what family is about. Friends would call her selfless, and while that has the propensity of leading her into a life of dissatisfaction within herself, she still believes that helping others over herself is a better path towards personal happiness. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]London, England[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Charlie Weasley, father, 53, dragonologist
Natalie Weasley, mother, 42, dragonologist 
@ondina , sister, 20, intern at the Department for International Magical Cooperation
@luke , brother, 18, auror in training
[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]n/a[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]The oldest of Charlie and Natalie’s children meant that Harper had the joy of seeing both of her younger siblings grow up, even if they were only a few years apart. Quickly becoming accustomed to the attention placed on her sister due to her health issues, Harper decided at a young age that she wanted to be the leader and protector of her siblings. Her brother, Xavier, seemed to have a different idea about what his role was, trying to gain their parents’ attention, thus becoming the opposite of her. She learned that she was a bigger help staying out of the way of the adults and playing by herself if she wasn’t needed then and there. That was why going to her grandparents was always fun. She was allowed to go wherever she pleased, instead of staying under a watchful eye all the time. Getting into her grandfather’s garage that housed all of his muggle gadgets and things absolutely fascinated her and she would find herself digging through it all day. 

This captivation of shiny, metal objects and their origins would only grow as she got older and started to understand their greater role in the life she would never have. Magic never really interested her past the ability to fix things and manipulate them to whatever she willed, so most of her time was spent wanting to wander around with muggles and to learn about what made them tick. Tagging up with her grandfather to tinker and build things was her favorite thing growing up, and she probably looked just as fanatical as he did at times. Everything about using her hands to put things together captivated her, and most of her toys were either building blocks or models of sorts. The constant questions about how muggle things were built and why they did the things they did were always a drain on her parents following a long day of dealing with her sister. Anything that allowed her to build and keep quiet for a few hours out of the day was a blessing.

Going to school stopped a lot of that though. She was on her own for her first year (minus cousins already there), and the lack of acknowledgement towards muggle society made her feel misplaced. It didn’t stop her from blabbering on about her favorite cars and computers, and usually left her friends wondering what she was going on about. As for the school part, she did fine the first few years. The introduction of the muggle studies class meant that she could finally talk in a place where people would understand what she meant and she absolutely loved that. Charms also came natural to her, since it was something she could use to manipulate her little building sets, as well as the wonderful objects she found at her grandparents’ garage. The introduction of her siblings into Hogwarts the following two years also meant that she could finally share with them all of the awesome things she had learned already. By this point in time, they both had their own distinct personalities and were placed in houses different from hers – and she felt like her chance to leave a positive influence on them had gone out the window at the same time. All three of them having varying interests meant that she wasn’t always able to keep a watchful eye on them like she once had, and when she could, they didn’t always want it.

So Harper let them be their own people as she tried to find herself at the same time. School went on, with her summers spent building bigger mechanisms, including a motorcycle bit by bit, and then her seventh year came around. Everything had gone by fast and Harper found herself nearing the end of her fun at Hogwarts. The end of the year took a twist though; the killings of muggleborn students that had happened at the beginning ended with kidnappings, and Harper found herself with a Hufflepuff girl a year younger that she had been enamored with for a while. Graduation and her new relationship with the Greyback girl made the following summer easily the best one she had had yet. But not all good things could last, and with the start of the new school year as well as her job put a strain on it, and it ended mutually. 

Being a beginner metal charmer meant closing herself off to the going ons of the magical world around her. She knew that the Triwizard Tournament was going on, and while she wanted to go see her cousin participate in it, she also had a duty to do her job. Involving herself in research of muggle items, as well as magical ones that needed to be re-charmed, meant a lot of time spent at work. She watched the papers closely, the adrenaline of popping the pages open to see the results being the same kind she would have had if she had been there in person. The distraction of the tournament had been a good idea, in her opinion, especially following the year Hogwarts previously had. Introducing the students to other cultures and students of differing opinions meant they would see how things were outside of their bubble, and she assumed it would be similar to how she viewed muggles.

But just like the year before, things came crashing down fast. While her cousin, Anna, had won the tournament, the attack brought on the other two schools as they tried to go home left her broken inside. She couldn’t understand how such a senseless act of violence could be carried out against innocent people. It was like reliving the kidnappings all over again, just tenfold this time. At the same time, her own family took a hit with the disappearance of her Uncle Harry. The official, public report of him missing brought on questions form others that she didn’t want to answer. The uproar it caused within the family completely eclipsed the incident in America concerning Ilvermorny, something she had read but couldn’t bring herself to care about all that much since there were more pressing matters at hand. Some in her family had different ideas of how to get Harry back, while she didn’t necessarily like the idea at all. Dividing forces while they should be united as well as combining societal issues with family issues has her confused on where to go next. She just wants the best outcome possible, and that seems like it’s becoming more impossible every day. 

At the start of 2025, with more muggle tech being integrated with magic, Harper changed careers and joined the Ministry department that best suited her: the Magical Artifact Development and Testing Office. She has finally felt fulfillment that being a metal charmer never gave her, and working with both muggle tech and charms makes her feel right at home.[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]The explosion at the Quidditch final meant that her aunt Hermione died. Harper has been broken up about the loss for months now, being the first family member that she has lost. She’s turned a lot of her grief into working harder, leading her into quite the burnout by the end of 2025.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@colin        [/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]he/him[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]26[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]EST[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]Support[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote][a href="https://alohomorax0.proboards.com/thread/5759"]Link To Plotter[/a] [/blockquote][/div][/div]