[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;background-color:#B6B6B4;border:4px solid #B6B6B4;border-radius:10px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" alt="" src="https://media3.giphy.com/media/oPp3x69Q2XmaQ/source.gif"]
[/div]

hello there, my name is [b]sybil windsor[/b]&nbsp;but you can call me [b]sybbie,&nbsp;[/b]i'm [b]17&nbsp;[/b]so that makes me a [b]6th&nbsp;[/b]year at Hogwarts, where I reside in [b]Ravenclaw[/b] house. You could say I'm [b]intelligent, knowledgeable, &amp; witty[/b]&nbsp;but I personally think that I am [b]confident, motherly and sensitive[/b]. People say I look a lot like [b]Claire Holt[/b], but I don't really see it...

[div align="center"][font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][i][b]sybil victoria windsor[/b][/i][/font][/font][/div]

[b][i]nickname:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]sybbie by her siblings only[/blockquote][b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]17[/blockquote]
[b][i]date of birth:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]12th february, 2006[/blockquote]
[b][i]gender:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]witch&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b][i]blood status:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]muggleborn[/blockquote]
[b][i]sexuality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]straight[/blockquote]
[b][i]house:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]ravenclaw[/blockquote]
[b][i]occupation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]for adults only[/blockquote]
[b][i]wand:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]cedar &amp; dragon heartstring, 12 1/3 inches, swishy
[/blockquote]
[b][i]playby:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]claire holt[/blockquote]
[b][i]appearance:[/i] [/b]
[blockquote]short and slim, sybil is approximately 5'3" with long blonde hair & and blue-grey eyes. &nbsp;I have pale skin with a smattering of freckles over my nose and cheeks. &nbsp;I have a birthmark where people do not normally look in the shape of (what she thinks is) a crown at the small of my back. &nbsp;She also have what people call a bubble butt, though she's &nbsp;still not sure why they call it that[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personality[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]likes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]transfiguration, animals, books, archery, clothes, makeup, jewelry, balls and parties[/blockquote]
[b][i]dislikes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]childish games, thunderstorms, the color orange, mud, television, people who speak ill of her father[/blockquote]
[b][i]erised:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]when she was a child she wanted to follow in her fathers' footsteps in parliament but now since she knows shes a witch she wants to join the ministry, hoping to become the minister of magic - if victoire weasley can do it at her age, why couldn't she aspire to be like that? &nbsp;That's what she sees in the mirror[/blockquote]
[b][i]amortentia:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]old book smell, her floral shampoo, pine trees[/blockquote]
[b][i]boggart:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]a masked man with a knife trying to kill her[/blockquote]
[b][i]overall personality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]If there were superlatives for "most transformed" sybil would certainly be in contention of it. &nbsp;She used to be quiet, shy, bookish and soft-spoken when she was younger and to a degree she still is. &nbsp;She prefers to read than to play games and still has a preference of conversing with animals or practicing archery over humans. &nbsp;She might come across as cold and aloof but really she just prefers letting other people carry the conversation. &nbsp; She is very clever and intelligent, almost to much so for her own good as her explanations on things tend to be over-winded and long.

Ever since she entered her teens, susan has been more into makeup, hair, clothes and boys. &nbsp;Some may say it's a bit superficial of her but she feels like she's really living for the first time. &nbsp;She's become very material and is very gleeful when people compare her sister Lusie to her; she's beginning to love that spotlight.

Since their parents were busy most of their childhood, Sybil has held a mother-replacement role within the four siblings, and that will never change. &nbsp;She prefers to watch them play games instead of joining in, enduring the teasing that shes simply just not imaginative enough. &nbsp;She is very bossy and dominant when she wants her younger siblings to do something for her, and isn't afraid to hold things over their heads (not physically she's too short for that). &nbsp;If one of her siblings is really in trouble, or is upset or angry, she shows her rarely seen soft side and talks them through everything. &nbsp;She cannot stand to see any of her siblings in pain[/blockquote]
[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personal history[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]mother:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Prewitt, Hannah, 43, in hiding, lawyer, muggle
[/blockquote]
[b][i]father:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]windsor,william henry, prince, 4th in line for the throne,  deceased, muggle[/blockquote]
[b][i]siblings:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]william peter, 21, former gryffindor, curse breaker
edmund michael, 17, slytherin
lusie katherine, 16, hufflepuff student[/blockquote]
[b][i]pets:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]an eagle owl named Amelia[/blockquote]
[b][i]history:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]For once, my sister Lusie has put our family story into perfect words:


“It all started with a look. But that is how most things start. Hannah Prewitt was out for a walk when she met Prince William Henry Windsor of England. Of course she didn't know he was a prince til they actually started dating, it happened kind of like a fairy tale. They started seeing more of each other and then one day he drops this bomb: "by the way, I'm a prince." She didn't believe him until he took her to meet his family. After all that pomp and circumstance, there was nothing she could do but believe him!  Eventually they got married, it was a really romantic ceremony and I am pretty sure the entire world was watching either on TV or on the internet. Maybe I should mention, they are both Muggles. So far as we know, no magical blood in the family except for me and my sister and two brothers. 

Many people think that royal life is easy and just like a fairy tale. Well I can tell you, it is rough work. My father, William, was not even the crown prince but he had just as much responsibility as my uncle. He worked in the parliament and my mother was a lawyer for the royal household. They tried to live their lives as ordinary as they could, so that was where children came in. Over the years they had four kids. William Peter,  then me, then my little brother Edmund, and then little Lucy Jane the youngest. We lived in a modest muggle home in the country. My mother insisted that we didn't live in the city or the palace, she said she didn't want us to end up being spoiled. But we still spent plenty of time in the palace visiting cousins and spending long weekends there. It was especially common to stay at the palace during times of crisis or election times. I always hated elections. 

One year, we were staying at the palace for a big party my grandparents (the king and queen) were throwing. I had always thought the parties, fancy dresses, hair styles, and the make-up were a bit frivolous, but this one seemed different. After we were ready to go my dad said he had something he needed to take care of and would meet us there.  We arrived at the party and sat down for dinner. It was always my dad's job to give some sort of speech before dinner and so we looked for him. He wasn't there yet. My grandma sent someone to look for him. When the guard came back  his face was pale. The next few hours were a blur. My mom rushed me and my siblings into a different section of the palace and told us not to leave the room. Then she left. I didn't even find out until the next day that my father had been assassinated. 

The palace put the whole royal family into protective custody for a few weeks while they figured everything out. We were moved to a summer home on the coast. That was when things really changed. Peter got it first. Weird things started happening around him. Once the maid's skirt turned blue, another time a dog that was barking at him ended up on the roof. It was almost like he was sick because it wasn't long after that Lucy, (Edmund) and myself all started having weird things happen around us as well. 

No one knew what was going on until a representative of some place called Hogwarts, came to talk to our mother. She wouldn't let us in the same room as she talked with him, but after he left she told us. We had magic. All four of us. He said that it was rare to have 4 muggle-borns in the same family, but not impossible. He also gave my mom two envelopes for Peter and I. On September 1st, they got to go to Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry. My mom wasn't too keen on the idea at first, but eventually they convinced her that the safest place they could be was at a school with magic! "

And that's how we got to Hogwarts. &nbsp; Peter was sorted into Gryffindor where "dwell the brave at heart" - it fit him perfectly. &nbsp;Me, I ended up in Ravenclaw with the other wise and clever students. &nbsp;Finally, I was surrounded by people who were at my level of intelligence! &nbsp;I never liked to play the silly "imaginative" games my siblings did at home; I'd prefer to read a book out of our parents vast library or write down my thoughts in a journal. &nbsp;Not &nbsp;that I didn't have much to learn; I was a year behind everyone else and there were so many subjects! &nbsp;I immediately took a liking to Transfiguration; to be able to turn into an animal at will and transforming one object into another was simply fascinating from a Muggleborns standpoint. &nbsp;Potions was by far my weakest subject - I even blew up the lab once (and we all swore to not tell our mother). &nbsp;When third year came around, I signed up for Care of Magical Creatures, thinking it'd be like taking care of a unicorn like one of the puppies I had as a child. &nbsp;While that could not have been further from the truth, it quickly became my second favorite class - I even used to spend free periods down caring for some of the smaller, less dangerous animals. &nbsp;Recently, as I've gotten older, I've been paying better attention to my looks. &nbsp;A housemate of mine introduced me to Slezeakys and I can finally get my curly hair straight sometimes! &nbsp;A little makeup, and I feel that boys are beginning to notice me as more than just a bookworm animal lover (don't tell William)

Edmund and Lucy followed in my third and fourth years and were Sorted into Slytherin and Hufflepuff respectively, which again suited both perfectly. &nbsp;We were still a tightknit group from growing up close together in age. &nbsp;That bond has proven useful this past year when the Muggleborn killings started. &nbsp;William writes every day to make sure we're all safe, and Lucy &amp; I &nbsp;put our heads together on how to tell our mother about what is going on. &nbsp;I passed my OWLs and have no intention of leaving Hogwarts - if she finds out however, we'll be gone in a minute. &nbsp;I will finish my magical education though - one way or another
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]alias[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]name:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]lisa[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]26[/blockquote]
[b][i]time zone:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]eastern[/blockquote][b][i]reference:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]the force[/blockquote][b][i]other characters:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]irina krum and hermione granger[/blockquote][/div][/div]