[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;background-color:#B6B6B4;border:4px solid #B6B6B4;border-radius:10px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][/div][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" width="342" alt="image here, do not stretch" src="https://68.media.tumblr.com/9f62ce5c31418738cef33b39a52951c9/tumblr_nudsh49s9r1qgimivo4_400.gif" height="215"]
[/div]
Hello there, my name is [b]Shawn Ashcroft[/b] but you can call me [b]Shawn[/b]. I'm [b]twenty-seven[/b] so that makes me a [b]Graduate[/b] of  Hogwarts, where I resided in [b]Hufflepuff[/b] house. You could say I'm [b]hard working, patient, & loyal[/b] but I personally think that I am [b]Silly, fun loving and determined[/b]. People say I look a lot like [b]James Roday[/b], but I don't really see it...

[div align="center"][font size="6"][font face="times new roman"][i][b]Shawn Lesley Ashcroft[/b][/i][/font][/font]
[/div]
[b][i]nickname:[/i][/b] Lesley (Typical only by close friends when messing with him about his middle name.) 
[b][i]age:[/i][/b] 27
[b][i]date of birth:[/i][/b] July 16, 1996
[b][i]gender:[/i][/b] Wizard
[b][i]blood status:[/i][/b] Muggle born
[b][i]sexuality:[/i][/b]  Straight 
[b][i]house:[/i][/b] Hufflepuff
[b][i]occupation:[/i][/b] Transfiguration Professor 
[b][i]wand:[/i][/b] 9"5', Ebony, Dittany Stalk
[b][i]playby:[/i][/b] James Roday
[b][i]appearance:[/i] [/b]

Shawn stands at 6'2" with a very athletic build as he's always staying active when not busy or running somewhere. He also has several visible scars along his arms and some on his back. Shawn is typically in muggle attire unless working or has a good reason to be in robes, feeling most at home in a shirt and jeans.

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personality[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]likes:[/i][/b] 

Having a good time, jokes, Being around other people, magic, the outdoors, transfiguration, animals both magical or non-magical, free food.

[b][i]dislikes:[/i][/b]

 Unnecessary violence, pain, boredom, people who can't take a joke, his family or talking about them and abusive people.

[b][i]erised:[/i][/b] 

To be a successful professor with students who actually enjoy his class rather than some of the boring ones he remembers from his years at Hogwarts.

[b][i]amortentia:[/i][/b] 

Ocean air, fresh baked cookies, Italian food.

[b][i]boggart:[/i][/b] 

A large shadowy man with a belt in hand.

[b][i]overall personality:[/i][/b] 

Shawn is always moving, always laughing and always trying to have a good time while also trying to help others do the same. He cares deeply for anyone in need and is always willing to help anyone out when need be. He's also been known to not know when to stop with a joke. He's pushed things to far and made it awkward or annoyed someone but figures that's the risk you run when you try to have some fun. If he is ever down he tries to hide that till he's alone as to not worry or cause anyone else to have to deal with the problems he might be facing. 

For how open Shawn may seem he keeps a lot of things to himself, either because he finds them too personal for anyone he doesn't fully trust or so he can try and ignore them himself and try and just have fun being who he is and where he is. Preferring to just be the goofy person everyone has come to expect and who he enjoys being.

All that isn't to say he doesn't have a mean streak, if anything all the goofiness is to hide how angry he can get if the occasion calls for it. There haven't been many times he couldn't control his anger or when he willingly let himself get that angry but each time he had gone well beyond any expected levels of force or action. Typical it's in the name of defending others from harm or himself but there have been times not that serious of issues have gotten him unnerved enough. 

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personal history[/i][/b][/font][/font]
[b][i]mother:[/i][/b] Helen Ashcroft, 50, house wife.
[b][i]father:[/i][/b] Alan Ashcroft, 53, muggle store manager.
[b][i]siblings:[/i][/b] None, that he knows of.
[b][i]pets:[/i][/b] An eagle owl named Benny.
[b][i]history:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]

Shawn's life hasn't been as joyful as he tries to keep it now. He was born the unwanted child of muggle parents who were already barely scraping by as it was. His father worked in a store and his mother was a house cleaner at the time. His parents could barely afford to raise him and his father especially resented the extra burden put onto them. Alan was a man with a huge temper and little control over it when it came to Shawn, the source of their problems. Shawn was used to his outbursts over any little thing he did wrong or mistake, even the physical violence didn't feel out of place as he grew up. His mother, Helen, would try to calm her husband down but it rarely worked and luckily for her she was never Alan's target when he lost control. 

Once Shawn was eleven he received his to Hogwarts and a new world opened up to his family and him. Shawn was excited for what all this meant but his father was even more so. If magic was real and his son could do it then his life would finally be on easy street. Alan's imagination filled with his son just making money out of thin air so he wouldn't be poor ever again. It was one of the rare times Shawn saw his father happy about something that involved him. His parents gathered what small amount of money they could and Shawn was sent to get the things he needed for school. 

All he could afford were beat up second or third hand versions of the items he needed. He was used to that from his years of just getting by, still it hurt when the only wand that he could get looked damaged and possibly had teeth marks from the previous owner. This had been what he had most been looking forward to but the shop owner said it worked it just wouldn't be the best fit for him. Shawn just smiled about it even though it hurt, he was used to this after all at this point and focused on what he did have. He had a whole new life waiting for him and he took that idea quite literally. 

His first year was met with the many things he had already dealt with in muggle world as he was quickly sorted into Hufflepuff. Being teased for his upbringing, status and the worn down clothes and items he had to use. If the other students thought they were being original they were sadly mistaken but Shawn wasn't going to let that stop him or slow him down. This was a new life and even if he had to lie he was going to make it a life worth living. His wand wasn't damaged or second hand trash, it was passed down to him from a very adventurous wizard. His uniform wasn't too big and covered in patches cause it wasn't new, it was just battered down from all the trouble he got himself into. At Hogwarts his home life was something he filled with adventurous lies, both to distract himself from the reality but to also appear better off than he really was.

His first year was an amazing experience filled with as much learning as possible and as the school year drew closer to the end he could feel the same uneasiness returning. He would have to return home after this, he hadn't returned for a single holiday, he had hardly even written home but now he was forced to return from a place he had friends and safety. Not even home for a second and his father was already demanding that he make things happen. When can Shawn get him a better job, when can he just make money appear. His father just wanted money and objects while Shawn just wanted to return back to Hogwarts.

Shawn bought time saying they didn't teach that yet and his father believed him, with the idea that his life would be easy soon enough. Over the years Shawn made plenty of friend and people he trusted deeply enough to tell them the truth about his situation and he was happy to see his trust wasn't misplaced. He also found himself fixated on the subject of Transfiguration, the very idea of changing something into anything else intrigued him more and more. Possibly cause he thought about changing his own life more than enough that it seemed so fitting to him. He studied everything he could and while his wand didn't help him any with enough practice and studying he was able to make it work like the shop owner told him. 

His after his fifth year was over and he returned home his father had, had enough. Alan was done waiting and while over time his job and the financial status of the family improved he was still fixated on the easy life his magical soon was suppose to provided him. Shawn was also done lying to the man and said he would never just make something like that appear for him. Not only was it illegal in the magical world but he just wouldn't do it because that was all Alan cared about. This set Alan off, unable to control his temper he proceeded to beat his son. Leaving numerous wounds over his arms and back as Shawn tried to protect himself. His mother just locked herself in the bed room and did nothing, something Shawn would never forget. 

Shawn didn't know where he found this sudden anger in him but it was swelling up as he stood up and grabbing the belt with one hand and his wand in the other. The rules and laws of both worlds didn't matter right now, making this stop did. Casting Incarcerous at his father a thick rope shot out and restrained the surprised Alan as he fell to the floor. That would have been enough but Shawn didn't stop, he couldn't, as he tightened the ropes more and more. It wasn't till his mother emerged from her hiding place and screamed for him to stop did he come to his senses and release his father. The fear in the mans eyes as he could finally breathe once more scared Shawn more than the actual beating did, that he was capable of such anger. 

Shawn didn't say another word, he grabbed his things and ran out of the house all the while his father cursed and threw things telling him never to come back. Finding the night bus he hitched a ride to his best friends house. It didn't take much convincing to allow him to stay for awhile while things got sorted out especially after they saw the marks and cuts along his arms. Hours later after finally getting calmed down and healed the scars remained sadly but he didn't mind too much, Shawn said it made him look cool but it was more a reminder of who he could and never wanted to be. The next day Shawn received a letter from the ministry and he knew what it was about and he was truly scared at the idea of losing the life he had come to love so much. 

The letter stated he was to have his wand destroyed and he would be held till his court hearing. When the officials arrived that was just what happened his wand was turned to ash before his eyes and his heart sank. He had hated that wand for so long, he didn't work right, everything was harder because of it but still it was wand for many years and he had grown attached. The court date arrived quick only a two days later, finding himself in an imposing room with a number of men and woman in robes. Shawn explained what had happened, he didn't dare lie as these were the men and woman who decided if he could return to Hogwarts and a life of magic. The trial was short given the statements taken from his mother, the scars on his body and his history of this never happening before they called the matter self defense but for everyone's safety he was no longer allowed to return home. Something Shawn was fine with. 

His life improved from there, he was allowed to stay with his best friends family till he was old enough to be on his own and they became a second family to him. Shawn also received an actual new wand and while he couldn't use it till he was in school he couldn't wait to see the difference. The next two years in Hogwarts were much the same as before as he focused on his studies, especially in Transfiguration and after training most of his sixth year Shawn mastered the ability to become an animagi. Surprised to take the form of German shepherd, He had always thought it would be a bird of some sort or that was possibly just him hoping but he loved it no matter what. 

Graduating Hogwarts with high grades all around especially in his class of choice, transfiguration, he started to travel the world a little. There was so much to see and while he didn't have much to his name he could work odd jobs both magical and muggle to keep him going money wise. It was a wonderful experience but his home and friends were all here in Europe so he was going to return of course some day. Two years before the actions of the Purifiers Shawn returned to London on a more permanent basis, sleeping on the couch of his best friend till he could find his own place. Making money once again with the odd job. It stayed that way for awhile and he still didn't bother to look for his own place till he was almost kicked out. Around this time the Head of the ministry was found murdered, incredible unsettling news if someone like the head of ministry could be killed it was a dark sign Shawn thought. 

In the following school year at Hogwarts three students were killed through out the year. Shawn kept glued to any new that he could about what was going on. He loved his old school and had a personal stake as he was a muggle born too after all. The news only got darker and as students were then kidnapped from Hogwarts. Claiming  they wish to enslave all muggles and keep magic just to the pure-bloods. There wasn't much he could do from where he was but he grew more angry at the situation. He didn't like his parents especially his father but he didn't want them harmed by any of this and he wasn't about to have his life of magic taken away. 

Unsure if it was because of the attacks on the school or just coincidence but Shawn soon found himself learning that there was a position for a new Transfiguration Professor opening. He jumped at the chance, he wasn't even sure how but he landed the position after he applied. There was a slight chance no one else had tried with all the danger involved with the school right now. Even as another attack resulted in an explosion at kings crossing he wasn't shaken. He was determined to help keep the school he loved going and pass on the craft he knew and loved so well and if he could protect the students there as well that was just another bonus to the job.


[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]alias[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]name:[/i][/b] TJ
[b][i]age:[/i][/b] 29
[b][i]time zone:[/i][/b] est
[b][i]reference:[/i][/b] Hi!
[b][i]other characters:[/i][/b] @crimson1         

[/blockquote][/div][/div]

((I am super duper sorry I got carried away with the background.))