[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://64.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_mes28sPjog1raoz4m.gif" alt=" "][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]aymeric thierry courtemanche[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]ay - mer - ick | tee - eh - ree | cour - tee - man - che.[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]meric or ric. [/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]twenty nine.
october 30th.[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]male | he/him.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]pureblood.[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]heterosexual.[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]walnut, unicorn hair, 10" | rigid.[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]colin o'donoghue.[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]aymeric stands at 6'2, with dark hair and bright blue eyes he can look like he's furious with you one moment and happy with you the next. his eyes are expressive and often say more than he lets his mouth give away. he doesn't like to dress in anything other than plan clothes and he's never been a fan of robes. they're all just a bunch of fabric that engulfs and hinders any sort of natural movement. .[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]hogwarts alumni.
ravenclaw.
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]graduate.
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]previously: curse breaker.
previously: part time potion maker. 
current: artefact dealer (mostly above board). 
current: potions professor at hogwarts.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]sunshine, fried food, honeydukes chocolate, creating potions, the smell of old books and boxes, his son's laughter, embarrassing his wifes siblings at school, log fires, roasting marshmallows, dogs, when his students challenge authority in a healthy way, napping. [/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]disrespectful students, cheating, when potions don't work out, when an old box is just an old box, birds, small spaces, being underground for too long, salad, people who take the easy way out, burning his mouth on hot food. [/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]his family together and smiling.  [/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]his wifes shampoo, ink, dust and steam.[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]being disconnected from his son.
enclosed spaces.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote][b]steady |[/b] it's never been easy to shake meric. from a young age he'd has to take responsibilities onto his shoulders that shouldn't have been his but he took it in his stride and ran with it. he had to care for his younger siblings when they were little while his mother couldn't and he knew he needed to be there for her. he'll let people lean on them and do what he can to try and stop them feeling like they're drowning, if they'll let him. 

[b]creative |[/b] his mind can move a million miles an hour at the best of times. whether he's thinking up new potions, trying to perfect the ones he already knows or laying in the living room colouring pictures with his son, he's never short of inspiration. he's somewhat of a dreamer but he's also a realist when it comes to achieving those dreams but he won't stop himself from wondering. any chance he gets to do hands on work, he jumps at. 

[b]tenacious |[/b] he doesn't know the meaning of the words 'give up'. if there's a spell to break or a potion to learn or a recipe to make, he'll keep at it till he's got somewhat of an understanding of it. he can't stand the feeling of giving up, it's how he felt when his mother died, that he gave up on trying to help her and since then it's a feeling that's made him sick to his stomach. he'll always keep trying to complete a task, even past the point of it being hopeless at times. 

[b]stoic |[/b] he internalises how he feels. falling to pieces never helps a situation in his opinion so he does what he can to avoid it. though it's gotten a little harder now he's a father and responsible for lives other than his own, there are cracks in the armour that are starting to show but he's doing his best to keep it together. 

[b]lighthearted |[/b] he doesn't like to be too serious. he'd rather laugh a person through a bad situation than let them wallow in misery but he doesn't push it on them. he doesn't want his son to grow up seeing much sadness like he and his siblings did with their mother, he wants to make his son laugh as often as he can because the sound is like a drug to him. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]france.[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]adriana eloise courtemanche nee du lac | mother | deceased
gregory apollo courtemanche | father | ministry official

auguste benoit courtmanche | brother | 24 | superstar 
alix --- courtmanche | sister | 23 | tbd

aurum victoria du lac | cousin | 15 | ravenclaw
argentum odin du lac | cousin | 15 | ravenclaw 

--- --- courtmanche nee loche | wife | 28 | muggleborn | witch.
--- --- loche | brother in law | 20 | wizard.
--- --- loche | sister in law | 17 | witch.
--- --- loche | brother in law | 15 | wizard.
--- --- loche | brother in law | 14 | wizard.

raphael enzo courtmanche | son | 3[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]2 dogue de bordeauxs | asterix (m) &amp; ambre (f)[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]aymeric had six years of being the sole focus of his parents before they added to their family. for six years it was him making his mother smile, listening to his father's stories and waiting for him every night to get home from work. though when gus came along the dynamics in the house changed. his mother had always been sad sometimes, he'd seen her hide her face while she'd been crying and he'd seen her close doors to hide her tears but when his little brother was born it seemed to get worse. aymeric was often the one that took care of his brother when their mother was suffering through her bouts of depression and then when alix was born he did what he could to take care of her too when their mother couldn't. he didn't mind most of the time but there were sometimes he felt jealously towards the seemingly close relationshop between his mother and his brother and then his brother and his sister. aymeric himself was closer to his father. for years his father was the parent that aymeric saw as steady, even though he wasn't home all that much. when he was home aymeric didn't have to look after anyone, he could be a normal kid like he thought his siblings were but then his dad would always have to leave again for work. 

this went on until aymeric turned eleven he'd long told his father that he didn't want to go to beuxbatons. he wanted to go to hogwarts. he'd read about the school in books and it almost called to him. so his letter arrived and he was excited. probably too excited for his own good because he'd be off on his own, somewhere new and exciting. leaving was hard though, he hadn't thought about his siblings being left with their mother till he was getting on the train but as his mother hugged him goodbye he told himself that she'd look after them. she'd be there. with one last hug he was off to a foreign school, in a foreign country. luckily for him he'd also learned english as a child so the language barrier wasn't as big as it could have been but it did take him a while to get the hang of how school worked. 

he was sorted into ravenclaw, and slowly settled into the routine of class. his favourite subjects were potions and ancient runes. the art of mixing substances together to create something different, something with a specific purpose was something that he loved and he started trying to create his own potions in his spare time. some of them worked, some of them didn't and there was even a time when he'd gotten into trouble for making a potion that he'd hidden under his bed. it had burned through the bottom of his cauldron and had started burning a hole in the floor beneath his bed, it was only when the foot of his bed had fallen through the floor had anyone noticed. he figured it was worth the week of detention to discover what the potion had done. 

being so happy and settled at his school came at a cost. and that cost was his mother. he'd started going home less and less. the journey was long and the only holiday he returned home for was the summer because he wasn't allowed to stay. it cost him his relationship with his siblings too, though mostly gus. he'd write owls when he remembered but as the years went on they got fewer and fewer throughout the year the busier he got with classes and the closer he got to graduating from hogwarts the more distant he became. he didn't want to admit out loud that he was worried when he graduated he'd have to go home. he'd have to go home to help his mother with their younger sister because the year that aymeric was going to graduate was the year that gus was headed off to school so their little sister was left alone with their mother. he wrote his father and told him that he wouldn't be coming back to france after he graduated, he wanted to stay in britain and work with gringotts bank as a curse breaker. 

it would be a choice he'd like to regret because he'd never see his mother again because of it. after his graduation he'd been offered a job at gringotts bank and he'd taken it. starting his job as a curse breaker, throwing himself into the job as he learned the tricks of the trade, finding artifcats and learning to break curses on them. it took him to far off places he had to deal with things he'd never heard of before. it was nothing he'd imagined it to be but he loved it. he met a girl while working with the bank and things between them became serious. two years later he got the message he'd long been expecting about his mother. she had taken her own life. as much as he'd expected that that's how she would leave the world, it shook him to the core that she'd actually done it. taking leave he'd gone home to grieve and see his family, something he hadn't done in a long time. things felt disconnected and he felt like an outsider to his own family but he knew it had been his choice. he couldn't blame anyone but himself for it.  

once back at home in england, he asked his girlfriend to marry him. his mother's death had made him see that life was short and he didn't want to wait. he'd met the girl he wanted to spend his life with and she felt the same. they married six months later in a small ceremony among grapevines near his hometown and for a while things were great. six months into their marriage, when he was twenty one, things changed again and suddenly. his wifes parents had been killed in car crash, leaving her younger siblings without anyone to look after them. aymeric and his wife took responsibility for them, moving back into her childhood home so they could raise her siblings. life became chaotic but settled. he continued working as a curse breaker, travelling away from home often like his father did before him but he tried his best to be home as much as he could, even if it was for the smallest amount of time.

things went up and down from there on in. there was good but there was also bad. his mother's sister, her last living relative died which his brother didn't take well, an owl from his father had told him that much. he felt for his cousins, he'd known the pain of losing a mother and it wasn't a type of pain he'd wish onto his worst enemy. not long after that he received an owl that his brother had overdosed on a sleeping draught and was in the hospital. aymeric rushed to visit him but gus had still been out at that point and aymeric hadn't been able to stay. it had pained him to leave without talking to his brother but assured by his father that he was going to be okay, aymeric had left before gus had woken up. 

but three years ago, the most wonderful happened. his son was born. bright eyes and a set of lungs to match, rafe made his way into the world and aymeric's focus shifted. he knew he needed a job that wouldn't put him in danger as much as being a curse breaker did. he didn't want to leave his son without a father like he'd been left without a mother. he didn't want to do that to him so he quit his job as a curse breaker, though he kept his connections and helped move the odd artefact through the borders of england. He started making potions to help tide things over. 

a year ago, he got offered the postions professor at hogwarts and after much deliberation with his wife about the hours and the fact he'd need to be away from home more than normal, he took it. they moved the family, with a lot of complaints from her siblings, to a property just outside of hogsmeade so that his wife and son wouldn't be far away and his wifes siblings would be close by even as they all went to school and he's been splitting his time between the castle and home for the last year. [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]aymeric thinks the world has gone mad. he's wondering if someone's opened a pandora's box style and failed to put the curse back in the box. he's done his best to only focus on the aspects that directly affect him and his family and luckily enough that hasn't been many. they tried their best to shelter the kids in the house from the horror's going on in the world around them but they haven't been able to protect them from everything. he's hoping all the azkaban prisoners are caught and put back where they belong because he doesn't think he'll get more than a few winks of sleep a night until he can be sure his wife and child are safe.   [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]shadow.[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her.[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]27.[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]awst.[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]magic.[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]lucas weasley, edward lupin, sunday weekly, calder mugwump, katiya krum &amp; sutton avery.[/blockquote][/div][/div]