[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;font-size:10px;"][div align="center"][img alt="" src="https://i.gifer.com/9ZKE.gif" style="max-width:100%;"]
[/div][div align="center"][font size="5"]frank edward lancaster[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]frank ed-ward lan-cas-ter[/blockquote][b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]just frank[/blockquote][b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]37
november 1st[/blockquote][b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]male, he/him/her[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]halfblood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]heterosexual[/blockquote][b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]oak, unicorn tailhair, 13 inches[/blockquote][b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]nikolaj coster-waldau[/blockquote][b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]frank looks like his playby, but he is roughshaven and walks with a slight limp since the Quidditch explosions that killed his wife[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling &amp; status[/b]
[blockquote]hogwarts - ravenclaw - graduated 2006[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]ancient history professor at hogwarts
former auror
archaeology hobbyist[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]archaeology, history, books, his children, hogsmeade village, a good firewhiskey, the smell of the air after a thunderstorm[/blockquote][b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]quidditch, nightmares, people pitying him for his limp and his wife's death, fire, bullies, slackers[/blockquote][b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]frank comes off as a gruff, slightly jaded, but wise man.&nbsp; he is introverted but not shy, just prefers his own company to large gatherings.&nbsp; he doesn't have interest in anything anymore, except for history and his children.&nbsp; he pores through his books while he's at the school, learning everything he can, and rereading what he knows, just to see if he missed anything the first few times around.&nbsp; only his children, or a being from somewhere completely foreign can bring him out of his shell.&nbsp; he'll listen and engage in a spirited conversation when it comes to them.

he comes off a near twenty year career of being a famed Auror team with his wife.&nbsp; before the quidditch final that changed everything, frank was quick to laugh, tease and joke with everyone he met.&nbsp; he was bold and brave, confident in his own abilities.&nbsp; he was naturally curious, about everything and anything.&nbsp; his father had been an archaeologist and had taken him on many digs as a child before he went to hogwarts, and during his summer holidays.&nbsp; he thirsted for the knowledge these digs gave them; he was driven to learn everything about the past, both magical and muggle.&nbsp; he knew he made his wife mad with his soliloquies about history, and he loved her more for listening to him.&nbsp;&nbsp;

frank thinks back to the years when his wife was alive and with their family, and he feels a deep sadness and longing to be the man he once was.&nbsp; he knows he shows a shell of his true self to those around him, and he keeps a glimmer of hope that one day, he'll be that man again.&nbsp; he just doesn't know how to be him right now.[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]born in london, england but raised all over the world due to his fathers profession[/blockquote][b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]reginald edward lancaster - father, 68 - muggle - archaeologist
ainsley elspeth macdougal-lancaster - mother, 60.- halfblood witch - howarts gryffindor -&nbsp; homemaker, her husbands travel companion

malcolm james lancaster - brother, 42, halfblood wizard - hogwarts, gryffindor - department of mysteries
evanna jane lancaster - sister, 41, halfblood witch - hogwarts, ravenclaw - chaser for the montrose magpies
iona mary lancaster - sister, 36, halfblood witch - hogwarts, gryffindor - healer at st. mungos

catriona macleod-lancaster - wife, deceased, halfblood witch - hogwarts, gryffindor - auror at her time of death

________ lancaster - daughter, 15-16, hogwarts, twin to son
________ lancaster - son, 15-16, hogwarts, twin to daughter[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]great horned owl named Circe[/blockquote][b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]frank was the third product of the great love of reginald lancaster and ainsley macdougal.&nbsp; reginald was a muggle who had traveled to scotland an apprentice to an archaeologist, who had discovered remains of a gaelic civilization in the highlands.&nbsp; while there, he came upon ainsley, who had been going for an illicit broomstick ride that evening.&nbsp; reginald was twenty-five, ainsley seventeen, but in his heart he knew he had met his match.&nbsp; he had not seen her ride, but she couldn't hide the broomstick behind her back very well, and ainsley was not the best liar.&nbsp; reginald did not pressure her into revealing the truth though, and simply asked if she was hungry.&nbsp; they shared a meal and a conversation that went to the small hours of dawn.&nbsp; when she left, they had promised to write, for she was to go off to school the next week for her last year, a boarding school in scotland.&nbsp; the letters started friendly, but soon turned romantic, until chrismtas, when ainsley was home, she met with reginald and told him the truth of her wizarding background.&nbsp; instead of fear or distrust, ainsley was met with delight from reginald.&nbsp; after spending a week together, ainsley went back for her last term, a diamond ring glittering on her finger, a promise from her reginald of his intentions.

frank was the third of four children of the blissfully in love couple, born four years after his sister, five after his elder brother.&nbsp; his youngest sister iona was born just eleven months after him, and they shared a close friendship that his elder brother and sister shared.&nbsp; malcolm and evanna took after their mother with the scottish fare, and would play quidditch with her in the field behind their home near richmond, on the outskirts of london.&nbsp; frank however, wanted to learn about the work that kept his father away for months at a time.&nbsp; reginald would come back with so many stories to tell, and frank would gobble them up, attentive and alert to every detail.&nbsp; when he turned seven years old, reginald took the young boy with him to greece, to a dig.&nbsp; he delighed in actually seeing what his father told him; holding some of the artifacts with his fathers' permission, and learning about the ancient cultures and civilizations that lived here centuries before they set foot on the ground.&nbsp; he was allowed to go on digs twice a year, until he turned eleven and it was his turn to go to hogwarts.&nbsp; his mother had expressed concern about sending her son to hogwarts - it had just been one year since the battle for hogwarts, and while her elder children had been sheparded to safety before the battle had commenced, she had soothed their nightmares the past two summers.&nbsp; both her elder children were adamant; if they could go back and start again, frank should go too.&nbsp; it was one of the first times that they had stood up for their younger sibling, so their mother relented and he was off.

frank was sorted into ravenclaw house, like his mother and sister before him.&nbsp; both of his elder siblings had made a name for themselves on the quidditch pitch, and it was expected that frank would join their ranks.&nbsp; frank tried out in his second year, after his sister had been sorted not into ravenclaw, but gryffindor, and made the team as a reserve.&nbsp; it was during one match where a chaser had been taken ill that he faced off against the fiery gryffindor chaser under his brothers captainship, catriona macleod.&nbsp; he didn't know it then - he was all of thirteen by this time after all - but this would be the girl he'd marry.&nbsp; they were the same year, and had shared classes, but had never been paired up in class.&nbsp; until they both decided to take ancient runes in their third year.&nbsp; both shared a keen interest in the subject, and ended up spending many nights together over the years in the library, doing their homework, checking each others work, and a bit of light flirting.&nbsp; one time, during their OWL year, they had been chased from the library for laughing too loudly.&nbsp; catching their breath in a deserted corridor, frank looked at catriona, and realized that he was in love with her, perhaps had been since he met her that day on the quidditch pitch.&nbsp; seized with boldness, frank kissed her, and she kissed him back to his great delight.

after hogwarts, both catriona and frank applied and entered the auror training program.&nbsp; for three years, they trained together and on the day of their inauguration to become full fledged aurors, catriona surprised him with a secret - she was pregnant.&nbsp; they were married the next week, much to his parents dismay; his brother malcolm was not marrying anytime soon, and evanna was content to live with her partner and never marry.&nbsp; with catriona and frank, his mother saw the opportunity for a big and splendid wedding, scottish and english traditions to the brim.&nbsp; so they let her in on their news, and agreed for a second wedding after the baby was born, that she could plan to her hearts content.&nbsp; baby ended up being babies, and catriona gave birth to twins, a boy and a girl.&nbsp; frank was overjoyed - he was an auror, with his wife, and they had two beautiful children.

the years went by, and frank and catriona fell into a comfortable, loving way of life.&nbsp; frank would go with his father still on digs, and catriona would ensure she was on desk duty during these times, so one of them was home with the children.&nbsp; when they were out on the field however, they always went together - ainsley would care of the children then.&nbsp; &nbsp;their children grew up happy, and when they turned eleven, they too went to hogwarts.&nbsp; frank was able to go on more digs with his father, though he ended up doing much of the physical labor as his father was getting old and readying for retirement.&nbsp; he and catriona took more missions, especially when the purifiers began to gain a following.&nbsp; he had seen as a young boy the corrosive nature of purebloods first, and he was not of a mind to let a third wizarding war happen again.&nbsp; they were sent to hogwarts after the explosions of the durmstrang ship and beauxbatons carriage to investigate, and he was angered that so many young lives had been snuffed out in an instant.&nbsp; his wife held the same fervor of her husband, and were both on hand when elaine dupree was finally captured and killed.&nbsp; frank did not issue the curse himself, but he congratulated the man who did.

then...the quidditch world cup final.&nbsp; his children had begged them to go, and after discussing it privately, frank and his wife got the tickets for the match - of course, letting their children wait in agony over their mullings for a little while longer.&nbsp; the day before the match, catriona learned she was to be on duty in the ministers box.&nbsp; frank was surprised that he wasn't asked, but his wife had told the head auror that they were taking the children to the match, so he only asked for her.&nbsp; grumpy about the decision, frank begrudgingly agreed.&nbsp; they arrived together, and frank kissed his wife goodbye in a way that made his twins eyes roll.&nbsp; they made their way to the box, which was just three boxes down from minister granger and his wife.&nbsp; the. match started off exciting, and his children asked if they could get food from the vendors and say hi to their friends, who were sitting much further away.&nbsp; frank gave them the money and they were off.&nbsp; he thanked merlin daily that he had allowed them to go off to the other side, for not five minutes later the explosions happened, right under the ministers box.&nbsp; frank was caught in the blast, a large piece of splintered wood pieced his right thigh.&nbsp; but he did not know this for some time, as he fought to get to the ruined box for signs of his wife.&nbsp; catriona was smart and strong; she wouldn't have gone down without a fight.&nbsp; but there was nothing of her left to find.&nbsp; frank flew into a rage, and had to be restrained by the mediwizards who had been dispatched onto the scene.&nbsp; he twisted and fought them, screaming catriona's name over and over again, until a potion was forced down his throat and everything went black.

when he came to at saint mungos, the healer who was watching over him was his sister, iona.&nbsp; her puffy, bloodshot eyes told him at once that the explosions had not been just a nightmare.&nbsp; his wife was dead, she confirmed, her eyes filling with tears once more.&nbsp; his children, frightened but unharmed, had been with their friends by the time the explosions happened, and their friends parents had ferryed them to safety.&nbsp; she told him she was able to heal the damage the splintered wood had done to his leg, but he may walk with a limp; there were limits, she reminded him, to magic.&nbsp; frank said nothing; a limp was nothing compared to a life without his wife.&nbsp; the day he was finally released, he resigned from his position with the auror department, and spent the next month in a dark, drunken haze.&nbsp; he saw the days pass by him as if he was watching a film; his wifes funeral, an empty casket as there was nothing left for them to bury, his parents and sister moving into the house to help care for his children, and so it went on.&nbsp; until one day, malcolm, the eldest, came to see him.&nbsp; he dunked franks head in a bucket of cold water, then told him a new post had opened at hogwarts.&nbsp; ancient history, and who better to teach it than frank?&nbsp; frank couldn't imagine the possibility, because it meant moving forward from his wifes death, which he did not want to do.&nbsp; malcolm, always blunt and to the point, told him that he was not honoring his wifes memory by getting drunk every day and neglecting himself, and his children.&nbsp; at hogwarts, he would always be with them,&nbsp; that catriona lived on in them.&nbsp; if he would not live for himself, live for his children.&nbsp; after that, his father came to him.&nbsp; reginald was a muggle, and never claimed to be an expert of anything magical, but he agreed that this position was the best thing frank could do for himself and his children.&nbsp; it was what catriona would have wanted.

and so, this new adventure began, and as frank settled into being a professor, he began to slowly open up again, first to his children, then to the druids that had come into their world after the wyrdness showed itself to the wizarding population.&nbsp; he began to feel that itch and thirst for knowledge again, knowing that this time, it would truly be something he never could have dreamt of before.


[/blockquote][div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]lisa[/blockquote][b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote][b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]jedi master on the jedi council[/blockquote][/div][/div]