[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img style="max-width:100%;" src="https://i.ibb.co/ZGSJ43Y/alfie.png" alt="(image here of playby)"][/div]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alfie edward o'callaghan[/font][/div][hr]

[b]pronunciation:[/b]

[blockquote]Al-fee | Ed-ward | Oh ' Cal-uh-han[/blockquote]

[b]nickname:[/b]

[blockquote]Al, Professor O'Callaghan, [s]Man of your dreams[/s][/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]34
February 15[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]

[blockquote]He/him/his.[/blockquote]


[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]

[b]blood status:[/b]

[blockquote]Halfblood.[/blockquote]

[b]sexuality:[/b]

[blockquote]Heterosexual.[/blockquote]

[b]wand:[/b]

[blockquote]10" chestnut unicorn hair - quite bendy.[/blockquote]

[b]playby:[/b]

[blockquote]Adam Brody.[/blockquote]

[b]appearance:[/b]

[blockquote]Alfie stands at 6'2" with a slender build,&nbsp; shoulders always up and standing tall. His hair is typically a messy nest of relaxed curls that cannot be tamed most days. Alfie has warm hazel eyes and thick eye brows. There's stubble on his face by the end of each day. A smile is usually gracing his face, unless if it's getting close to a Full Moon - it takes a little more effort.

On Alfie's back left shoulder he has faint claw and bite mark scars from when he was attacked by a werewolf at the age of 20. Through the first years of transformation he would cause self inflicted wounds from not being able to hunt.&nbsp;After many years of his friends healing him, they have finally started to fade with the help of magic but they will never disappear fully.&nbsp;

While at work Alfie tries to keep a more professional appearance but being in the greenhouses all day could get pretty messy. He often has dirt on his clothes and doesn't realize it.&nbsp;In 'teacher mode' he always has a pencil tucked behind his ear and he wears glasses.


[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]

[b]schooling:[/b]

[blockquote]Ilvermorny - Horned Serpent

[/blockquote]

[b]schooling status:[/b]

[blockquote]Ilvermorny Graduate

[/blockquote]

[b]current occupation:[/b]

[blockquote]Herbology Professor Ilvermorny, now Hogwarts.[/blockquote]



[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]

[b]likes:[/b]

[blockquote]+ Plants &amp; herbs
+ Teaching (when something 'clicks' for a student)
+ Dark Beers
+ Affection
+ Rock music
+ Flying/quidditch/quodpot
+ Playing guitar &amp; drums
+ Camping
+ Stacking items on people when they sleep (especially students)
+ Smoking cigs [s]and other things[/s]&nbsp;
+ Reading
[s]+ Getting weird[/s]

[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]

[blockquote]- Students asking for extra credit when they didn't do 'regular' credits
- Teaching at Hogwarts (he pretends for the sake of being professional)
- Television
- Messiness
- Tomatoes
- British cuisine
- Being told not to do something (stubborn AF)
- Lollygaggers
- Prissy women
- Gossip
- Cats - they don't like him[/blockquote]

[b]erised:[/b]

[blockquote]- Find a cure for a major illness
- True love
- Have a large family of his own[/blockquote]

[b]amortentia:[/b]

[blockquote]Patchouli, fresh cut grass, coffee.[/blockquote]

[b]boggart:[/b]

[blockquote]- Bees [s]or any flying insects he thinks are bees[/s] (allergic)
- Wolfsbane not working
- Becoming a raging alcoholic cheater like his father[/blockquote]

[b]overall personality:[/b]

[blockquote]Alfie is the type of person to always be in a good mood. Most of the time he fakes smile until it becomes real because it's easier than explaining why he wasn't smiling. He isn't afraid to make a fool of himself for the sake of a joke, or to teach a lesson, and he will always go out of his way to help someone in need. At times his kindness has hurt him because he became quite the 'Yes Man', often agreeing to commitments he had no intention of pursuing. He is sensitive, stubborn, impatient, and tends to jump to conclusions when he thinks he's right. Admitting he's wrong is a whole other story.

Ever since Alfie was young he was a lover of learning and questioning everything. Knowledge is his favorite weapon. At times while in school classmates would think he was a snob because he knew more than them. It was just hard for him to sugar coat or dumb things down for them. As he got older he learned how to hide what his face was thinking, or replace it with a fake smile instead. Alfie is a dork through and through, a lover of video games, comic books, and playing any instrument he could get his hands on. He will always be a kid at heart and tends to joke at the wrong moments. His personality can be addictive at times and Alfie often battles depressive episodes.

As 'Professor O'Callaghan' he is stern but fair, always trying to develop healthy relationships with his students. He has an 'open door policy' with his students where he tries to build trust, as well as offer a safe and fun environment to learn about Herbology. He likes them to know that they could come to him with problems, questions, or concerns, no matter what. As long as students aren't hurting themselves or anyone else he won't tell anyone. Alfie mainly wants the kids to know that they have a 'cool adult' that cares about them if they need things.

When students misbehave in his classroom, especially during lectures, it's a one strike policy. He is very stern and enjoys giving "free detentions" because it means he gets help deep cleaning the greenhouses - or his favorite - scooping dragon dung for fertilizer as discipline for being a little shit. ("Don't test me - I'm sure Professor King would love some help and I need some dung for these Fanged Geraniums.")

[/blockquote][div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]

[b]origins:[/b]

[blockquote]Denver, Colorado. USA.[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]

[blockquote](Divorced)
Rebecca Thomas - Mom - Muggleborn - Music Teacher
Oleg O'Callaghan -Dad - Muggleborn - MACUSA Obliviator


&nbsp;Tracy O'Callaghan - Step Mom - MACUSA Secretary
Step Sibling 1 &amp; 2 (School Age)

Esther - Bestfriend, roommate, co-worker[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]

[blockquote][a href="https://i.pinimg.com/originals/b2/c0/28/b2c028e73ff9e29a8fb73dc92336ef82.jpg"]Owl[/a] named Elvis[/blockquote]

[b]history:[/b]

[blockquote]WARNING: Mentions of depression &amp; drug use

Alfie O'Callaghan was born and raised in Denver, Colorado. He grew up as an only child, often begging his parents for siblings. Sadly they never delivered his wishes. For good reason. Rebecca and Oleg had been in an unhappy marriage for years. They just didn't know how to break it to their only son. When Alfie went to Ilvermorny, he was sorted as Horned Serpent. By Christmas they were already separated. His first Christmas celebrating two christmases was the hardest and most shocking. By the time it was summer, his dad had a new wife and Alfie was pissed. She was in her late twenties and he was already trying to have more kids! Soon Alfie had two step siblings. Alfie was an angry preteen. He took&nbsp; most of his anger out in Quodpot or music. Before attending Ilvermorny his mother had him enrolled in a children's music academy, where he learned to interact with Muggles at a young age.&nbsp;

Through the years at Ilvermorny Alfie was a great student. He scored top in his class in academics and was a solid player on his houses team. Alfie was always very hard on himself, always striving to do better. He was distracted easily by girls, often crushing on multiple girls at once, until he met Rose. Alfie and Rose dated third through seventh year and he was madly in love with her. Her Pureblood parents didn't approve of his Muggleborn status and threatened her inheritance if she didn't break up with him. After graduation Alfie never saw her again. He was devastated. That same year he went for the National Quodpot team in America and didn't get it either. It led him into a&nbsp; downward spiral of depression. He spent a lot of time numbing himself with substances and reckless behavior but he never missed class. Alfie always went to school, even if he was hungover, or nearly dying. School was the one consistent thing in his life. He obtained his teaching degree within a 4 years and worked hard on honing his craft of Herbology.

Alfies first job was at an Apothecary in a wizarding town on the outskirts of Denver. He was a cashier and helped handle and organize product.&nbsp;It was a great place to learn life skills and he made many connections. Many connections that would later on get him a job at Ilvermorny. During this time he was involved in backdoor sales of cannabis and magic mushrooms which was a great way to make extra income on the side.

On the week of his 20th birthday, his life was changed forever. While Alfie was still in his reckless party phase, filled with under age drinking and debauchery, his life came to a crescendo. He was attending a Full Moon party in a forest where people were using mind altering substances and a werewolf came through. No one knew what was going on. A bunch of Muggles died right before his eyes. Alfie didn't have a chance to run, he got bitten and his life was flipped upside down all over again. The stress of learning about the transformation, moon phases, Wolfsbane, and everything else, really overwhelmed Alfie. And his entire body was enduring excruciating pain. He had the confidence that he could figure it all out within time but it took over a year of solidarity and learning about his beast.

After a year Alfie was comfortable enough to come out of his cabin. He was so relieved to be back to work at the apothecary...he was tired of having to be some sketchy street dealer to make money. He worked there for five years while working on pursuing a Masters of Herbology. His sixth year at the Apothecary, at the age of 28, he was offered a paid Apprenticeship at Ilvermorny. The Professor was planning on leaving the upcoming year and they wanted to have the next Professor familiar with the school for a smooth transition. Alfie took it and it was the happiest he had ever been. Teaching was fulfilling, he couldn't wait to have his own classroom and students.&nbsp;

His first year teaching at Ilvermorny was hard work but he enjoyed every moment of it. There was blood, sweat, and tears shed, but it was easily the best year of his life. He loves to work and being in the greenhouse all day uplifts his soul. The staffs dynamic at the school was sensational and it was great to be back at his alma mater. He was able to take his wolfsbane and&nbsp;work around the Full Moons without it affecting lessons too much. In the Spring of 2023 he received his Masters of Herbology.

On the summer of what was supposed to be his forth year teaching at Ilvermorny tragedy struck. The school was under attack and was deemed unsafe to attend for the 2024 school year. Alfie felt like his life was about to take another 360 after finally getting good again. He was devastated. Shortly after he got news about Ilvermorny, he was contacted about an Herbology position opening at Hogwarts. He went for it. This could be a new start. Nothing would replace his beloved Ilvermorny, but more opportunities sprouting up were promising.

Alfie spent his first year at Hogwarts and it was chaotic getting to know a new school, new staff, new students, new tradition and formalities. Everything was extremely overwhelming but he was satisfied with the resources of the school. His greenhouses were a little outdated but he was happy to teach a more 'traditional' method. During this time he reunited with Ilvermorny friend Esther, who had been a Head Healer at Hogwarts for a few years now. Small world. They were instantly drawn to each other. It was nice to have a piece of home, a blast from the past even. Esther was his ex-girlfriend Rose's best friend and they were friends through her, so it was crazy to see her across the pond. They have become very close friends through the past year. Their relationship thus far in the UK has been purely platonic and always trying to keep it professional. He has f0und comfort in her comondarie and friendship. Since the borders are shut down and they are tired of staying at the castle, they rented a flat in Diagon Alley together for a couple of months before school starts up again.
[/blockquote]

[b]site events reaction:[/b]

[blockquote]During the summer of 2024, Ilvermorny was under attack. The school wouldn't be opened for the upcoming school year due to extensive damages which really bummed Alfie out because he found Ilvermorny home for many years. It ached not to return to his old classroom and greenhouses. Hogwarts opened their doors to students and select positions for Professors, Herbology was open. Alfie took the opportunity because he wanted to continue teaching and honestly life was feeling a little stagnant before the craziness happened.

Alfie was present during the dragon attacks. Since it was during holiday break he was enjoying scoping out the area for the first time. He sustained only minor injuries (bumps and bruises) while trying to rush to the aid of his students and friends.&nbsp;&nbsp;

Now that the borders are closed off with no sign of opening soon to go home to America... Alfie is frustrated. He figured the time at Hogwarts would be temporary and he'd be back in his classroom in a few months.. That's not the case. He would also like to visit his Muggle mother back home in Colorado who he misses dearly. For the summer Esther and Alfie rented a flat in Diagon Alley so they could stay close to the school.
[/blockquote]


[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]

[b]name:[/b]

[blockquote]@dez                          [/blockquote]

[b] pronouns:[/b]

[blockquote]She/hers[/blockquote]

[b]age:[/b]

[blockquote]29[/blockquote]

[b]time zone:[/b]

[blockquote]PST - CA[/blockquote]

[b]reference:[/b]

[blockquote]Carole Baskins[/blockquote]

[b]other characters:[/b]

[blockquote]@tobias                            @joseph                            @simon                            @travis                            @gideon                            @lulu                           [/blockquote][/div][/div]