[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://66.media.tumblr.com/276f443531499853c9ae91e678848ad4/508798edc9973547-9d/s540x810/b2472eeca0f579eff42b45908c2d189f30422e20.gifv" alt="" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]renfri eloise selwyn[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]ren-free&nbsp;[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Ren, Re-re (to her family)[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]25
January 2, 2000[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Female
She/her[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Pureblood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Heterosexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]12 3/4 inches, cypress wood, unicorn hair[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Riley Voelkel[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Height: 5'9
Renfri naturally has dark hair and brilliant green eyes. In recent years she's taken to dying her hair blonde prefers to keep it shoulder length or shorter.

Renfri's dressing style is hard leathers, and jeans. She likes sturdy clothing that won't tear easily and can handle some heat, so dragon hide is a favorite. She also likes flexible and non-restrictive clothing. Something she can move in.

Renfri's left arm is badly burned. She has to wear a sling at all times. While use may eventually return to the arm, it's currently pretty much dead. It'll take years of magical therapy until use returns.[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts - Hufflepuff[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduated[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]History of Magic Professor (beginning 2025-2026 school year)[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]puzzles
mysteries
hiking
climbing
curses (breaking them, especially)
anything new
libraries
books
illusion magic
[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]being told no or that she can't be something
restrictions
people that don't appreciate history
being inside too long
unsolvable puzzles (what's the point if there's no answer?!)
pureblood supremacy
lectures
not knowing the answer
FIRE

[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Renfri's&nbsp;original dream, to be the first person to unlock the most dangerous mysteries in the wizarding world, has recently been crushed due to the... incident. Now, she strives to pass this dream onto the next generation... Meanwhile she has yet to find anything concrete to aim for.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Old parchment, dust, pine, and sage.

[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote][strike]Having to retire early [/strike]Oh wait, that already happened!

She's developed a phobia of fire.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Renfri is an adventure seeker and a bit of a daredevil. She lives life to the fullest, and on the go. She's the sort of person that, unless something is holding her attention, can't sit still for long. Though if you put a history book in front of her she can sit for hours. She's also quite fearless, willing to try anything and everything. She's accept almost any dare you send her way.

Renfri loves mysteries and puzzles. Anything unknown that needs to be solved or discovered. Her curiosity is practically legendary and completely insatiable. She digests information at an alarming rate.&nbsp;

When it comes to people, she's the type of person you'd take out drinking. Have fun, nothing serious, sing bar songs, and say hi to the next day. She gets along with most people, but she doesn't necessarily form deep connections because she's always been on the go. Even other curse breakers never really became "close" friends with her because she was more focused on the job then getting to know them. It made her good at her job, but bad at being a good co-worker.

Deep down, Renfri is a compassionate and loving person. She cares deeply for those that do form lasting relationships with her. She just hides it behind her work-a-holic attitude.&nbsp;[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Little Hangleton, England[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Astrid Selwyn (nee ivanova), mother, deceased
Vladimir selwyn, father, deceased

Belam Selwyn, half-brother, born in 1990, open job
Titus Selwyn, half-brother, born in 1992, open job
Kalique Selwyn, half-sister, born in 1993, unemployed psycho
Camari Selwyn, sister, born in 2005, open job *
&nbsp;Cree Selwyn, brother, born in 2005, open job *[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]A black cat named "Snootie".[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Renfri was a rambunctious child from the moment she was born. She was crawling and walking terrifyingly early, and no place in the Selwyn home was safe. She got into every nook and cranny she could, discovering every secret the house and family held. This, of course, often got her in quite a bit of trouble, though no permanent damage was done aside from her parents having to constantly find new hiding places for Christmas presents.&nbsp;

Her childhood, otherwise, was quite normal for a rich girl. Her family's wealth and blood lineage was nothing to joke about. She grew up being told that this somehow made her better than everyone else, a concept that confused young Renfri. Thankfully, the girl had better things to do than focus on her parent's attempts&nbsp; to teach her blood purity. Like many of the Selwyn children, her parents got a&nbsp; tutor to teach the girl at a young age, though this tutor did a pretty poor job. They couldn't get Renfri to sit still long enough to learn anything that they wanted.&nbsp;

Going to Hogwarts was the first time that Renfri had to sit still and learn, and it was very hard. Her first night the Sorting Hat was torn over how to sort her, unable to decide for several minutes between Gryffindor and Hufflepuff. She was adventurous and daring, with nerves of steel, but she was also loyal and compassionate. She would do well in either. Finally though it decided on Hufflepuff, feeling that as she grew up humility and compassion would be important skills to develop.&nbsp;

Her first year was absolute hell... For the teachers. The poor blokes had to somehow get this wild child to sit still and focus. Well, all the teachers except for History of Magic. That was a shock to everyone. For some reason Renfri became enamored with history. Her friends would often come to her for homework help because Renfri had a way of making history come alive.&nbsp;

As she grew older and progressed in years Renfri slowly learned some self control, at least enough to get through her lessons and learn productively. It soon became clear that the girl had a knack for mysteries and puzzles, skills highly sought after in the curse breaker field. When she finally graduated she was quickly snatched up by Gringott's.&nbsp;

Unfortunately, during her final years of Hogwarts her parents died. There are still many mysteries around their deaths but no one has been able to say for sure if it was murder or an accident. The news was hard, but only motivated Renfri to get out of England.

Over the next few years she completed her training, and started bouncing around the globe, breaking magical puzzles and uncovering magical artifacts.&nbsp;

In Spring of 2025, Renfri was in an.... accident. She and a fellow curse breaker were working on an ancient magical vault in China. While trying to decipher the charms on the vault, the other curse breaker recklessly touched one of the seals. The statues in the vault came alive, called him unworthy, and unleashed a wave of fiendfyre. Thankfully, the pair managed to survive the ordeal but magical fire is a very dangerous thing to play with. Renfri and the other cursebreaker were badly injured and had to be emergency evacuated to St. Mungos for treatment. A long, and painful ordeal, as fiendfyre is one of the most dangerous magical substances in existence. The fact they survived is a miracle unto itself. While in the hospital, both cursebreakers knew their curse breaking days were over. There was no way they'd be able to work in the field.

Renfri took the news especially bad. Curse breaking was her life. Now... what was she supposed to do? That was when an elderly woman visited her. Minerva McGonnagal, Headmistress of Hogwarts. Offering her a job after summer as the new History of Magic teacher. Renfri wanted to say no at first, but finally decided to accept. If she couldn't live her dream, maybe she would at least help the next generation live theirs.[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Renfri hasn't really bothered to keep up with news from back home. Hasn't really thought much of it since graduating actually. She's been too busy doing what she loves. Since the accident though she's been transported back to her home country and been catching up. She's shocked, and disgusted by how things have turned out. The quarantine and quidditch event haven't really affected her personally, except for St. Mungos being quite a bit more congested then before.
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Sora[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]She/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]28[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]Mountain[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]I live here[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]Lots.[/blockquote][/div][/div]