[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt=" " src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/sarcasticmoth/proboards-templates/main/pics/octavian/octavian_app_header.gif" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]octavian archimedes vector jr.[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]awk-tay-vee-uhn
[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Octavian - only in a professional capacity
Archie - everybody
[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]twenty-nine
14 march 1996
[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]male, he/his[/blockquote][div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]half-blood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]bisexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]12' red oak, dragon heartstring, rigid[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]boyd holbrook[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Archie stands a few inches over six feet tall. Fitting, as his father was quite tall. His hair is blonde but can often appear a darker blonde or even tinted red in the right light. Either way, when he keeps it short it tends to look a bit more disheveled than when it is grown out. There are pictures that exist of his unfortunate mustache phase that thankfully ended and nowadays he supports an unshaven look, a small beard, or on occasional clean-shaven. From his previous work, he has many scars from smaller injuries and a few from larger ones. Since they were all magical the scars didn’t quite fade like the papercut on parchment at the museum. 
[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling &amp; status[/b]
[blockquote]hogwarts 2014, ravenclaw[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]2014 - 2016: Curse Breaker in Training
2016 - 2018: Curse Breaker
2018 - 2021: Merlin’s Mystical Museum of Magic Assistant Archivist
2021 - Present: Professor of Arithmancy, Hogwarts
[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Reading
Math
History
Quidditch
Dueling
Cupcakes

[/blockquote][b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Whisky
Cooking
Onions
Coffee
Snakes[/blockquote][b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]When the sorting hat was placed on Archie’s head, there was a pause. While generations before him had been placed in Ravenclaw or even Hufflepuff (his grandfather), the sorting saw a particular set of qualities in the young man. There was an ambition and a drive, but it wasn’t to rule the world or anything that grand—Archie just wanted to feel good enough to be noticed and acknowledged. If you asked his father, the acknowledgment was enough that he had passed on his name: Octavian, to the young boy, though he went by “Archie” (a shortened version of his middle name) to differentiate the two. By the time Archie sat on that stool with the hat on his head, he was courting wife number three. There was a younger half-sister who was too young to understand the situation, but really, Archie didn’t see his father that often and had been dumped with his Aunt instead. But Archie was bright. He was an intelligent kid whole liked to plan his next steps. Often times he was lost in his own mind trying to figure how what that next step was and what the result might be. 

Archie has a true ambivert personality. He can socialize as needed but also enjoys his quiet time.  Truthfully, however, it doesn’t bother him one way or another as long as you aren’t in his way. One of his best skills was with numbers, which was unsurprising considering his heritage and his name—his grandmother had once been a Professor at Hogwarts, and he practiced when helping his Aunt in the shop that his grandfather had created long ago. Numbers required patience and required observation. Patterns were never obvious right away, which was essentially the type of person Archie was. Observant and meticulous. These traits convinced the Sorting Hat he belonged in Ravenclaw, although Slytherin was not too far behind considering the boy’s drive and aspirations. Really it was the longing for a family that kept him going, hoping that his talents would be noticed or his displays for attention. 

During his early school years, that was what he did. He was the class clown briefly—maybe letters from his Professor would do the trick. No? He joined the house Quidditch team as a Chaser, that didn’t do it either. And then he focused on his grades and the Prefect badge on his chest, but his father didn’t seem to quite care about that either. Instead, he focused on Archie’s younger half-siblings (a set of twin girls) and then-wife number four. The more that Octavian Sr. moved down his list of wives, the more resentment grew inside of Archie. The harder he tried to make something of himself, to impress with OWLs and later his NEWTs the and then a choice of a fantastic career, the more it did the opposite. Although Archie grew older, he realized that living a life for his father would not bring him anything but pain, but what was he to do now? Plus, his father had left a trail of other children before his death, although he’ll never admit the jealousy he has for his younger half-brothers. They will never have to feel that abandonment if their father had gotten a chance to move to wife number five. 

As he grew older, Archie focused on what he could control and what made sense. He wasn’t angry enough to fall into some pit of despair at the bottom of a bottle of whiskey, but he did shift his life accordingly to try and find some purpose in it. In fact, Archie does not drink and prefers tea in most cases. If he’s at the pub with his friends, he certainly isn’t drinking there either. It was not something that never grew on him as it did his friends. Despite all that he had experienced and seen in his life. And while he is a friendly sort of guy, personable in that quiet kind of way—having inherited some of his father’s charisma, it did take him some time to open up to his younger half-siblings at the encouragement of his aunt. 

[/blockquote][div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]London, UK[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Septima Vector - Grandmother, deceased, Former Professor of Arithmancy
John Smith - Grandfather, deceased, Baker and Shop Owner

Octavian Vector Sr. - father (twin), deceased, con-artist
Decima Vector - aunt (twin)
Sarah Whitehouse - mother, deceased/missing

@nova   - half-sister
Ada Vector - half-sister (twin)
René Vector - half-sister (twin)
Isaac Vector - half-brother (triplet)
Alan Vector - half-brother (triplet)
Leonhard Vector - half-brother (triplet)
[/blockquote][b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Apollo, Eagle Owl[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Arithmancy—the prediction of the future using numbers. Numbers were static, they didn’t change, and they had patterns. They were consistent. But for the Vector family, one still couldn’t quite calculate the odds of this particular series of events occurring and how they would occur. Archie was born when his father, Octavian, met a wealthy woman named Sarah. Now, Archie isn’t quite sure if his father really had feelings for Sarah, she was the only daughter in a moderately wealthy family after all, and he was a charmer looking for the path of least resistance. Octavian Sr. was the son of former Hogwarts Professor Septima Vector and John Smith. Archie’s grandfather, who hated his very fake sounding and plane name, was related to the Smith family. And as such, John was a natural in charms—food-related charms. It seemed that the knack for such charms ran through the family. When Octavian Sr. was born, John opted not to pass on his own name in favor of his wife’s to distinguish his descendants where the name Smith might have not. 

Archie never met his grandparents, but he had grown up in the shop that his grandfather had founded and grown. By this point, his Aunt Decima (his father’s fraternal twin) had taken over and had seemingly inherited her father’s family ability. Archie’s father, however, had not, and he was less interested in the work required to make an honest living as he found that his charm typically helped him get his way. This was how he met Sarah, and after they were married, Sarah gave birth to a son. Octavian Archimedes Jr., who they dubbed Archie. For a few years, it seemed normal. They were a happy family, and Archie remembered time spent with both parents until he was five when suddenly his mother disappeared. When he was older and had a chance to review records and understand a bit more, Sarah had gone missing and then been presumed dead. However, not a year after his mother’s disappearance, his father remarried. This had confused the young boy who had now almost permanently moved in with his Aunt by this point, and his new step-mom didn’t seem all that interested in raising a six-year-old boy alongside her newborn daughter. 

Octavian Sr. still came around to visit his son, almost out of obligation at that point. Though the visits increased in frequency after Archie’s step-mom, Elora suddenly vanished. Archie was ten, and his younger half-sister was three. Archie had grown accustomed to living with his Aunt, a sweet and wonderful woman who was quick to bake his favorite cupcakes after a disappointing day with his father. But after Elora disappeared, his father came around more often and even accompanied him on his first official trip to buy his supplies for his first year at Hogwarts. But then it all went back to the normal that Archie knew, and suddenly he had a stepmother again. Just his luck and his sister’s apparently as well as she was now living with them. Aunt Decima never complained. She always smiled and focused on her niece and nephew and the shop while her brother always walked the tightrope his scheming created. 

Archie went off to Hogwarts, where he was sorted in Ravenclaw. His Aunt had not been surprised though his father didn’t seem to remember what house his son was in most of the time. The name was familiar to some of the older staff, but it was hard to gauge whether he would have the same abilities that his grandmother did as a first-year. Archie did well in his classes, but as he found his footing among his peers, he became a bit of a class clown. Not to the extent of some of his Gryffindor peers but in his sarcasm and unsolicited comments, there were a few letters home from his Charms Professor, but his father never responded to those. It wasn’t until his second year after his father had married yet again, and now he had twin younger half-sisters, that he learned his Aunt was now his legal guardian. This didn’t make sense to him—his father was alive and well. Why wouldn't he claim him like any other parent would? 

It was a confusing time, as it would be for any pre-teen, but Archie looked around at the different school activities he could participate in and hoped that perhaps some achievement in one of those would garner his father’s favor. As a second-year, he was now old enough to join Quidditch, and he was successful in trying out for the House team. This seemed to garner some praise as his father had also played Quidditch himself, but it was short-lived. All of his father’s attention seemed to be toward his youngest daughters, and Archie pushed himself hard in Quidditch to garner that praise—but it never arrived. During his third year, however, things in his life shifted again when his stepmother disappeared. Maybe because he was still young, he didn’t find it odd, but more like his father had some bad luck, and by proxy, so did he and his siblings. However, Archie didn’t really feel a closeness to his sisters as he did Nova because of the huge age gap. She was seven years younger than him, but they still spent time together when he wasn’t at school. 

Again, however, and certainly not to Archie’s surprise, his father remarried once more and very quickly. Harmony, now this stepmother Archie did meet a few times. And the sarcastic fourteen-year-old that he was, they did not get along. There was something about this stepmother that only garnered negative feelings from him. Though she didn’t seem to like him or his sisters very much either. Her personality was that of a typical heiress type. Grew up with money and servants and men begging for her attention. Somehow his much older father, his air sprinkled with gray at this point, managed to charm her way into the life of this nineteen-year-old. Though the only discomfort Archie felt was that he recognized his new stepmother, she had been in Slytherin years ahead of him, having just graduated. This part did confuse Archie a bit. Why would he marry a young woman that was close to his eldest child’s age, and [i]how[/i] had he met her in the first place? 

He didn’t want to think about it more than he needed and especially when a year later, Harmony gave birth to three boys—triplets. That was a first, the family was scattered with twins (their father was one, and so were his sisters), but triplets were new. Still, at the age of fifteen, Archie didn’t feel much connected with these brothers, just as he hardly felt with his twin sisters. He continued his studies and playing Quidditch, eventually becoming a Prefect during his fifth year. When his father heard the news, he made an appearance at the bakery to congratulate him, but it felt empty and forced. Archie wasn’t dumb. He figured his Aunt had pushed him to come to visit, and after he’d left, Archie remembered the numb feeling afterward though he wasn’t sure what he should have expected at that point. 

To nobody’s surprise, Archie excelled in Arithmancy and really all the subjects he needed to either become an Auror or Curse Breaker. But he was fascinated with artifacts and especially Egypt and their use of mathematics in the ancient tombs. Very quickly, he chose this as his future profession despite its dangers, at least it would be with purpose—in the pursuit of knowledge. After avoiding his stepmother for a few years now, Archie realized one day that this was likely the longest his father had been married—ever. But the triplet’s mother was a force to be reckoned with. Soon after Archie turned eighteen, he graduated from Hogwarts, planning to begin his training after helping his Aunt get Nova ready for her time at Hogwarts. His father attended his graduation alone—sans stepmother, a gift to Archie in itself, and he began his Curse Breaker training. 

The training was rough, with a lot of sand in places it didn’t belong, such as his ears and nose, but he learned a lot. Often times he was focused on the goal and not his surroundings which had left him with some unfortunate incidents with moving walls. But overall, he enjoyed his time in his work. When his training was complete, he visited home to check on his aging Aunt and sister, who was in her second year at Hogwarts—but his father doted on the triplets instead, who were around five at this time. Two more years as a Curse Breaker brought more interesting experiences, injuries, and overall weariness for the job. Archie was tired. He was pushing himself hard and harder, creating a name and image for himself and for a man that barely spoke to him and a stepmother that only looked at him with daggers in her eyes. Plus, there was nothing like a brush with near-death to push one to evaluate their life’s choices. 

Archie left the bank and his career after two years and decided for a quieter life working for the museum. His job there was the other side of his Curse Breaking work, where he inspected and evaluated the artifacts that were retrieved, and this was something calm in his life. Plus, Archie could get back to visit his sisters and Aunt much faster than before. By this time, his twin sisters were nearing the age of when they would attend school, and ever so slowly, he would take some time to visit them, though he wasn’t sure what he was supposed to talk to them about if he was being honest. However, his quiet life changed as suddenly he heard the news that his father had died. It hurt, but also it didn’t. It was a confusing feeling, but Archie did what he was supposed to and attended the funeral with his siblings and Aunt. The twins had just started at Hogwarts and the triplets would soon. 

Again death played an important part in his life choices. He decided to leave the museum and accept the recently vacated posting of Arithmancy professor. Nobody was shocked, and it seemed fitting for a Vector to fill the post once more. His first year teaching was an adjustment, the younger students merely needed an elective, and he found it hard to have the motivation to teach a subject he was passionate about. Until he began teaching the NEWT level course, where he felt at home and that he was in the correct place. However, things began to get interesting during his second year as a Professor. The Minister of Magic was killed and suddenly, students were being found dead on the train and even on the grounds of Hogwarts. Now, Archie had been a baby when the previous war had raged on and ended, and aside from his previous Curse Breaking work, he had not been accustomed to being around such things. But he was vigilant along with the rest of the staff in trying to protect their students. 

However, the Purifiers emerged after an attack and kidnapping of students, and there was hardly a reprieve as Kings Cross was bombed, and then the Tri-Wizard Tournament was announced. Archie hoped that the tournament would help distract and settle things down. The presence of staff and students from abroad might help deter an attack though it could also welcome it. Otherwise, that year was quiet at the school. Archie wasn’t worried much about politics and even the changing of Headmasters as McGonagall returned. And then the students from Beauxbatons and Durmstrang were killed as well as Harry Potter going missing. This prompted Archie to get to know his younger siblings a little bit better as they were young and experiencing these things firsthand while he was much older and a bit frightened. When Dragon’s attacked the village, and the prisoners escaped, Archie realized he had made the right decision to stick by close to home. He worried about his Aunt, who was getting on in years, and his siblings, though at least when Hag’s fever swept the Isles, it didn’t scare him as much as a possible terrorist attack might. 

Nova began to work at the shop with their Aunt. She appeared to have the same gift that Decima did that was inherited from the Smith branch. The Quidditch explosion was probably something that alarmed him the most. He was a lifelong fan and played on his house team. Archie focused on what he could control, and part of that was his work and the numbers. They didn’t care what was blown up, they didn’t change, and something calmed about that. Things seemed to settle after that or begin to, at least until the appearance of some mysterious island. The Curse Breaker that he had been was curious about this, and he tried to turn to Arithmancy for answers, but there weren’t any to be found—at least not yet.
[/blockquote]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@thevanessa [/blockquote][b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote][b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]jedi master[/blockquote]
[/div][/div]