[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="http://www.geekchicelite.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/Kris-Holden-Reid_01.jpg" style="max-width:100%;" alt=" "][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]charles septimus weasley[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]char-uls[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Charlie[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]53
December 12th, 1972[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Male. He/Him/His[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Pureblood [/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Straight [/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]8 inches, Hornbeam, Dragon Heart-string, flexible [/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Kris Holden-Ried[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Around 5’9”, he looks exactly like his playby. He has since kept his hair short, after constantly having his mother cut the long locks of his youth off every time he came home. He also has numerous scars and burn marks all over his body from dealing with dragons over the years. While he could have them removed, he’s opted to keep them because it shows the adventures and trials he’s had in his field of work. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts. Gryffindor.
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduated class of 1991.
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Care of Magical Creatures Professor. Dragonologist. Author.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Dragons, his kids, Romania, traveling, watching pro-Quidditch, black coffee, being outside, teaching, writing about dragons[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Apparating (a broom is so much better!), unruly dragons (they remind him of hangry toddlers and Ondina), being burned, garden gnomes, dragon egg smugglers[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]To provide a safe environment for dragons at every reserve around the world. To teach Hogwarts students how to safely interact with magical creatures.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]campfire smoke, fir trees, humidity, coffee[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Garden gnomes trying to bite his toes off. A more realistic and possible fear would be for a dragon to escape into a muggle area and causing havoc.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]A little wild in his younger days, Charlie has always been one of the more upbeat and energetic Weasleys, Fred and George taking the number one spot. His love for flying, Quidditch, and the outdoors has led him to always seek out new thrills and adventures, only truly feeling alive when working with dragons. From this, his school and young adult life were mostly spent putting his life on the line almost every day, since anyone crazy enough to work with dragons has to do that. While his time as a Gryffindor has definitely shown in his choice of career, Charlie’s easy-going, laid back lifestyle was enough to allow him to calmly work with his beasts with little to no risk.

Trying to always keep optimistic about life and the things that go on around him, he tries to look for the best in people, as well as always being happy around others. This upbeat attitude led many that worked with him to believe he was just crazy, but they soon realized that his care and positivity were essential when studying and working with dangerous animals. He has since brought this attribute over to his family, and while it worked when the kids were young, it has become increasingly harder for him to sympathize with them, or at least make them realize what they are all capable of. Despite mostly falling on deaf ears, Charlie has maintained his optimistic outlook on everything in the hopes that his kids will take after him in some way.

Having dealt with dragons for so many years, he has also come to realize that he doesn’t exactly have a filter when it comes to danger. While some would call him courageous for jumping in head first, Charlie (and his wife), would call it foolish. This strong headedness has dwindled in the last few years, now taking a back seat when dealing with dragons and other animals, but if the right moment provided itself, it would probably reemerge in no time. Along this same vein, when anything comes to his family, meaning all of them, extended included, Charlie has become extremely protective of them and is always trying to wiggle himself back into existence, just to check up on everyone. He feels like it’s necessary now that he’s grounded back home, instead of being off somewhere in Romania worrying everyone about his own safety. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]The Burrow, Ottery St. Catchpole, Devon, England[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]mother – Molly Weasley, 75, homemaker
father – Arthur Weasley, 75, retired
wife – Natalie Weasley, 43, magical vet

children
@harper  , 21, ministry employee
@ondina  , 20, ministry employee
 @luke  , 18, auror-in-training

siblings
@ginny  , 42, flying professor
Ronald Weasley, 45
Fred Weasley, would be 47, deceased 
George Weasley, 47, weasley wizard wheezes owner
Percy Weasley, 49
Bill Weasley, 55

other family members
@harry  
@lily  
@jamesp 
@albus  
[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Balaur, a 2 year old Newfoundland[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Born as the second child to Arthur and Molly Weasley, Charlie followed his brother Bill and their parents before them, into Gryffindor for his years at Hogwarts. He quickly fell in love with both the outdoors and Quidditch at the same time, taking up the mantel as both the seeker and captain of the Gryffindor team, as well as excelling in Care of Magical Creatures. By time his seventh year came around, Charlie had also become a Prefect. From here, his aspirations to work with animals took him all the way to Romania, where he ended up dealing with dragons instead. Studying them throughout the years, he made trips back and forth between home and Romania, only to always miss the fun stuff.

Meeting Natalie McDonald for the first time was an experience for Charlie. He had spent so many years worrying about his own studies, work, and his family back home, that he had never even contemplated spending the rest of his life with anyone or anything other than his dragons. Despite their relatively large age difference, Charlie was able to win Natalie over, and they were eventually married, three children following soon after. A year apart each, Harper, Ondina, and Lucas were everything to Charlie and Natalie when they were born. Harper, her outstanding energy and enthusiasm rivaling a much younger Charlie, and Lucas with his creativity and will to protect his sisters at a young age were much easier to raise than Ondina was. Her terrible health problems ended up keeping her inside the majority of her childhood and under close watch, something that Charlie hated doing to her. He had always hoped to share the animals and outdoors that he loved with his children, but Ondina wasn’t able to do that, limiting how much they could do with the other two as well.

It soon became aware that the amount of time and effort that he and Natalie put into taking care of Ondina had affected the other two children differently. Harper, seeming to understand everything even at such a young age, started to act just like Charlie’s brothers Fred and George, as well as take an interest in muggles once she was sent off to Hogwarts. Lucas, distancing himself more from Charlie than ever, once he entered school. And there was still Ondina, who had become a Slytherin when she was sorted. While shocked by this news, Charlie had come to accept it, realizing that the potential his middle child had shown fit along the lines of the house. 

Following all three children’s acceptance to Hogwarts, Charlie returned to work, guiding new potential dragonologists in the right direction, sharing his studies. He wanted to get back in the field with the creatures, but Natalie wouldn’t let him, afraid that after taking such a long break from them he would make a mistake, and it would cost the entire family. Working as an informant wasn’t a bad deal either, since it allowed him to be home whenever the children were from school. While all three kids were extremely different from one another, as well as from their parents, Charlie still hoped that one of them would take up his mantle as a dragonologist, or at least do something with animals. The older they got though, the less likely this seemed like it would happen.

After watching the events of 2023 unfolding, Charlie and Natalie became increasingly worried about the safety of their children at Hogwarts. They knew they were safe because of their blood status and the strength in numbers of their family there, it was still unnerving for them to sit back and watch students get killed again, reawakening the horrors they had lived through decades earlier. Not having a permanent job that he had to deal with, Charlie was intent on taking up a position at Hogwarts, but never ended up following through with it. Eventually the year ended, Harper graduated, and Ondina and Lucas still grew further away from their parents. Charlie was unable to understand the two younger children, one time equating it to being more difficult than training a dragon. The Triwizard Tournament returned to Hogwarts once again in 2024, and Charlie hoped the events of the previous year and the 1994 tournament wouldn’t repeat themselves, having witnessed parts of the prior tournament first hand. [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Since the explosive end of the Triwizard Tournament, a lot has happened in Charlie’s life. He had wanted to sit down and finish his Dragon Journal for a number of years, which had always existed in a series of leather bound (and fireproof!) notebooks that he had kept with him in the field throughout his whole career. With both Ondina and Harper graduated, getting Lucas off to school wasn’t necessarily a difficult task, so he finally took an official sabbatical from Romania and all work related to dragons in order to write his book. At least to the extent of handling them. 

The escape of several Hebridean Blacks from the MacFusty Reserve had him slightly unnerved. While it was possible for Hebrideans to act in that manner, he didn’t agree that the land surrounding Hogsmeade was particularly a prime place for the male dragons to lay claim to. Since he was able to get to Hogsmeade quickly once news reached him, he assisted in subduing the dragons, and quelling their attack with other dragonologists and members of the Ministry. With the extensive clean-up and the bureaucracy that followed, Charlie didn’t hear about the Azkaban for several days. Unnerved by this development, he cautiously returned to writing, always making sure to keep an ear out for more trouble with dragons.

The summer of 2025 was one of conflicting emotions. Harry returned, even though Charlie knew his disappearance had to have been one of great importance. Doubting a Potters’ gut instincts would be silly, after all. Despite the lockdown, he was able to finish the Dragon Journal and get it published. It should have been a time to celebrate and be proud of his success. But Hermione died at the Quidditch Cup accident. It brought back horrid memories of when Fred died, and Charlie spent the remainder of the year helping Ron and the rest of the family where he could.

And then there was October. The island of Hy-Brasil, which he had visited a few times over the years to study their dragons and how the local druids interacted with them, was suddenly bleeding magical creatures all over the place. Like he did during the Hogsmeade-Dragon debacle, Charlie stepped in and used it as a way to pull himself out of the funk he had been in since the summer. 

He would have liked to keep hunting down the creatures, since returning them safely was a huge priority. But he received a letter with a familiar wax stamp on it right before the Christmas holidays. Hogwarts was short one Care of Magical Creatures professor. The job had been within his reach several times before, but now McGonagall was actually offering it to him. How could he pass that up?[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@colin  [/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]he/him [/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]26[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]EST[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]PB Support[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote][a href="https://alohomorax0.proboards.com/thread/5759"]Link To Plotter[/a] [/blockquote][/div][/div]