[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt="" src="https://64.media.tumblr.com/3fd43645edb86d9f708e60ef33947ca0/abdc9740077accec-b7/s1280x1920/abc07846d85210d6fad8cc2c4a299c8dbf2769da.jpg" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Jasper Nyle Yaxley [/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]jas-per ny-le yacks-lee[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Jas
Some know him as Nyle[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]29
12 January 1996[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]he/him[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Pureblood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]bisexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]Rowan, Pheonix tailfether, 14.9"[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Andre hamann[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Jasper grew a lot after leaving England, mentally and physically. He now stands at 5’9 and will wear something more professional looking while teaching, but prefers relaxed clothing. He occasionally wears glasses, normally when reading, though he doesn’t need them for everyday things. During the many years away, he got a number of tattoos, from both magical and muggle artists. Most of his tattoos were done overseas, but a few of them were done during his time back at the Gringotts offices.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Slytherin Graduate
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduate
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]August 2014 - May 2025: August 2025 Curse breaker - Greece/Italy expert
Currently teaching Charms at Hogwarts[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Old buildings
finding artifacts
exploring a new place
curse breaking (though he can't do it anymore)
Greek and Italian culture and history
Learning languages 
reading, 
rain
sweets
Finding out how things work[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Bullies
Prejedus
Cold weather
Someone telling someone that they “cant” (for no reason)
Cheeze romance  novels
Expectations put on him[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]regaining lost love - though he will never admit it to anyone
Make a difference (now he can’t do it by finding something world changing, perhaps through a student)[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Campfire smoke
Rose’s
Alcohol
[strike]His ex’s perfume[/strike][/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]someone getting hurt because of him
His terrors being real (not waking up from them)[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Jasper had always had an ear for languages. Growing up knowing English and French, he quickly recognized the latin connection with spells. As he moved out of the country, he picked up Italian and some Greek quickly. When it comes to things that he holds dear to him, Jasper can become very passionate and protective, doing just about anything to make sure they are safe, even if it hurts him. He stands tall at the sign of danger, and rarely takes back his decisions.

He is comfortable talking with many people, though he doesn’t like to talk about the issues with his family, or the side effects of his recent accident. There are times, especially at night, when he would prefer to be left in peace. He’s not afraid of a friendly argument between two parties. He believes that it’s alright to discuss opinions, but if things start to get off topic, or too personal, he will simply walk away. He doesn’t like to lose his temper, and will do what he can to avoid it. While he has a longer fuse, if his temper is lost, he will often lash out physically, which again, he prefers to not do. He has only lost his temper so bad twice in his life, one time at school, and the other while working. Jasper is not the type to overreact to a situation, he has been trained to see the problem for what it is, and take it on through an analytical standpoint, rather than an emotional one. Trust is something he gives to everyone he meets, though, if that trust is broken once, there are no second chances. He will be cordial, but the trust will never return.

After awakening from his coma Jasper found himself plagued by shadows. He knows that they are not real, but his body and mind still react to them the same.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Wiltshite, England[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Terence Yaxley - Great grandfather
Anabeth Yaxley (nee Warrington) - Great grandmother
1884-1959-Arcturus Black - Great uncle
1899-1961-Lysandra Yaxley - great aunt
1919-1982 - Dionysus Yaxley - grandfather - r
Emma II Higgs (nee Yaxley) - aunt
Bertie Higgs - uncle
1956 - Corban Yaxley - Death Eater - uncle

1955 - Helius Yaxley Father (66)
1960 - Seychelle nee Volant(from france)

1983 - oldest sibling (42)
1984 - 1/2 sibling (41)
1989- middle sibling (36)
1989 - 1/2 sibling (36)
1995 - 1/2 sibling (30)
2002 - 1/2 sibling (23)
**Note: All Yaxley Siblings are unaware of their ½ siblings**

@beatrice  [/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]An Aegean cat named Tesoro
Tawny Owl named Nike (pronounced nee-keh)[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Youngest child of Helius and Seychelle Yaxley. Another pure-blood to fight for the cause. His father was often away for the first couple of years of his life. As he and his siblings grew up, they were taught to think that pure-bloods were better, and that muggle borns were thieves and less. They were trained to think that some wizards, those who chose to mingle were wrong. Jasper was taught many other things. He was given a jump start in his magical knowledge, never practicing, but learning through observation. He also grew up with those around him speaking both English and French.

As expected, and like his older siblings before him, his letter for Hogwarts came. He was told that he would have high expectations, both his siblings had done quite well in school. It was important to live up to the Yaxley name. He arrived at Hogwarts, spending the ride over with other pure-bloods of distinguished families. Entering the great hall for the first time was a normal, while still great experience. When it was Jasper’s turn to be sorted, he knew what house he would be in. It was the house of his family, and it was expected. The hat pondered putting him in Gryffindor. He was certainly brage, and would fit in nicely, but Slytherin was the only place for the youngest Yaxley. He stuck close with purebloods, along with others that he had known his entire life. It was easy to stick with those you already knew. Though, unlike many of them, as his first year passed, Jasper started to open his eyes. His second year of school, in his Carms class, a Ravenclaw girl seemed to have developed a crush on him. It was a great joke in his house for some time.

As expected, the boy excelled in his classes, but as the years passed, he started to change. The silly girl that fancied him in Charms seemed less silly. Though, he still had expectations to fill. He had to not only do the same as his older siblings did, but better. That was the expectation. To help with this, he joined the quidditch team for his house. The girl went to every one of his games, and that made him happy. But the girl was a muggle born, and that wasn’t acceptable for his family, so he tried to fight it. Though, he had started to see that some things he was taught were wrong. In their fourth year, after a heated argument between the two, they shared their first kiss. And that was it. The two continued their relationship. Fifth year, he was appointed as Prefect, and his seventh, he was a Prefect. During the years, very few were more lightening than spending some time with this girls muggle family. That was when he knew that he would be different. After graduation, their relationship was mutually ended. 

There were many reasons; jobs, family, expectations, tensions raising, wanting to keep her safe. After that, he went out for a job at Gringotts as a Curse Breaker. He had to get out. He left his family, against his father's wishes (which were to stay and find a pure-blood witch). His mother gave him a Tawney owl and he was off. As a green curse breaker, he happily left the country, and didn’t look back.

Eleven years after leaving home, Jasper worked primarily in Greece and Italy, having a nice small residence in Rome. In the beginning of May, 2025, while working in Greece, he was working on a cursed artifact in a less than safe room. Unsure of exactly what happened next, but there was an explosion, and everything went black.

More than a month later, on June 21st, Jasper awoke in a magical hospital in Greece. There was some time of rehabilitation and observation in the hospital, before they would let him go. Forced into an “early” retirement from curse breaking, He applied for a job at Hogwarts as the Charms professor. It was time that he returned to England, or thereabouts. The item leaves more than a great story of being comatose, but not all scars are seen.
 [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]As word of explosions, and dangers got to him, Jasper would reach out to his friends to make sure that they were alright. Though he was in another country, working, he still kept in touch as best he could. After the accident he seemed to miss many things, not wanting to upset his newly acquired condition, he tried his best to ignore all news from that time, though the surprise of Viktor Krum, former Quidditch star becoming Minister of Magic.

As a professor of Hogwarts, he helped the students with the creation and upkeep of Zombie Island. Glad to see so many having fun.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Sophi[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]Undetermined[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]Mountain[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]It’s been a while[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@dmitri  , @nixie  , @thursday   @torrian  , @lotten  , @fiona  [/blockquote][/div][/div]
