[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt=" " style="max-width:100%;" src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/4Cho526Z1N8/maxresdefault.jpg"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]blaise leo zabini[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]blaze[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]n/a[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]46
February 12th, 1980[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Male. He/Him/His.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Pureblood.[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Straight.[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]11 inches, vine, dragon heartstring, surprisingly swishy.[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Lenny Kravitz.[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]6'2". In shape. Likes to work out to keep up with his younger coworkers. Nose rings, ear piercings, some you can’t see. Wears lots of rings. Pretty much same as playby. While he prefers wearing formal clothes for events, work is more suitable with virtually anything. Blaise has numerous tattoos, all covered up for the most part. Most notably is one of a dragon that stretches from his left shoulder and onto his chest.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts. Slytherin.
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]Graduated 1998. 
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]Defense Against the Dark Arts Professor: 2024-Present
Hit-Wizard: 1998-2007, 2024
Obliviator: 2007-2024[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Work, exceeding expectations, traveling, music, guitars, whiskey, cigars, reading, his family, quietness, order.[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Failure, being looked down on, students/employees slacking, things being out of line, disruptions, impoliteness, criminals.[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]For his family name to continue as something bolder and greater than it ever has been before. Power, money, and intellect are how he views his family (ie children) to be perfect. He wants to continue to watch his children grow and become something far greater than he was, and his family members before him.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Whiskey, ink, crisp morning air.[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Losing everything. Being raised highly and to be the best, having all of that stripped from him would be the worst. This counts money and family alike. Eventually he would be left as a disheveled mess.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Blaise is extremely arrogant. From a young age, he was raised by his mother to believe that he was the epitome of great, pureblooded lineage. Wealth and intelligence can get him anything he wanted, so that’s what his focus has been in life. His mother was extremely wealthy from the get go, inheriting large sums from each of her seven ex-husbands. Blaise has inherited that as well, accompanied by the idea that he is of the most noble of lines because of the money. His intelligence goes hand in hand with his arrogance, seeing as one can’t get far without a little bit of the other. Gifted in potions, mainly, Blaise’s school years were shining examples of how smart he was, officially solidifying itself in his sixth year of school when he was accepted into the Slug Club. Common rabble could never make their way into that. His intelligence landed him numerous career opportunities befitting someone of his stature, but the extreme wealth that he would eventually inherit from his mother ended up placing him in an Obliviator position, where his intelligence and arrogance have continued to shine brightly as he modifies the memories of any muggle even thought to have witnessed magic.

As arrogance and intelligence do go hand in hand with each other, he also couldn’t survive without a certain level of narcissism. Blaise loves himself. It’s kind of hard not to be that way when everything in life has worked out perfectly for him. Brains and money are only part of the equation that leads to power, and being the best looking person out there as possible is the third part to complete it. He knows when and when not to have the appearance of a socialite, finding an even balance between work, play, home, and the high life. He believes that being perfectly groomed all the time eventually demands a level of respectability from his peers. While he has taken on an edgier look from when he was in school (the addition of piercings and tattoos), cleaning up is not an issue, and never will be. To him, the rocker look is what makes him stand out even more from the rest of his social class.

To wrap it all up, he has high expectations. Achieving perfection may not be possible for him to ever do, but his children definitely have a step up over him, and his mother before him. The ability to bring everything together and then show them what he expects is his greatest goal, and being prideful of their own achievements pushing towards that really affects him. These same standards are taken at work as well, preferring that his coworkers are on top of things to a T. Micromanaging isn’t far off from it, more so that complete and utter perfection must happen with him around. If they can’t do it, surely there’s no harm with him taking over and doing it himself. That doesn’t mean he can’t make mistakes, because they do still happen. Obviously lessons are learned though, and they don’t happen again on his watch. So to a degree, he can be lenient, hoping that his children and coworkers alike learn from their mistakes and improve upon them. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]London, England.[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Valentina Zabini, mother, 81, witch, socialite, retired
Roberto Zabini, father, 39 (at time of assumed death), magical philanthropist
Six Stepfathers, all deceased and not worth mentioning. Majority of his family’s money has been “inherited” through them. His mother stopped after her seventh husband in fear that it might look suspicious.
Daphne Zabini (nee Greengrass), wife, 46, actress
____ Zabini, 18-19, daughter, open occupation
____ Zabini, 16-17, son, open student
[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]n/a[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Blaise Leo Zabini was born to pureblooded socialites Valentina and Roberto, each of Italian descent. For whatever reason, his parents had attended different wizarding schools, his mother at Beauxbatons, and his father at Durmstrang. Highly educated and coming from money, they realized that their family name, while notable in their homeland of Italy, was nothing in England. So as to cement their name in the same mold as the high class pure-blooded families, they moved to London. While neither Mr. nor Mrs. Zabini really needed to work, they had to do something to make their name known in this new country, so Roberto began all sorts of philanthropic expenditures. One of these great businesses sent Roberto overseas, sometimes around Blaise’s 5th birthday, and unfortunately for the rest of the family, that was the last they would hear of Roberto. Whether or not he’s actually dead is a story for another matter, because Mrs. Zabini wouldn’t settle with the loss of her husband and her indispensable income. Thus, Blaise learned that some things in life didn’t need to be worked for in a normal fashion. Sometimes all it took to get more money was having six more fathers, or ex-step fathers, seeing as each met their grisly demise at some point or another. Quite tragic actually. His poor mother had become the embodiment of a black widow after all. She finally stopped remarrying by his 4th year at Hogwarts, the last husband leaving a significant amount of money to satiate her sorrows for decades.

Growing up in the midst of his intelligent father, his extravagant mother, and his six wealthy step-fathers, Blaise had his path in life paved for him. He really didn’t need to do much when it came to finding a job, or going to school for that matter, but he still needed to prove his family was just as great as the other purebloods. Come his 11th birthday, so did his letter to Hogwarts, and off he went that following September. School was easy. Too easy actually. He operated at a higher level than most of the students his age, even in Slytherin, which was where he started to learn about the other respectable families around him. Some he knew of already, through his parents of course, but there were others that were just as interesting. He never truly befriended them though, because in his mind, he was still better than each and every one of them. To have his parents come from a foreign country and to already be at the level of these other families was astonishing, and that meant somewhere deep down that he had to be better than them. When it came to picking sides in the second wizarding war, he decided that was beneath him. He wasn’t a Malfoy or Goyle. He was a Zabini, a name far more powerful and not fit to be ruled by someone else.

Not all connections to the Sacred Twenty-Eight were bad though. Blaise never paid much attention in school to his classmate Daphne Greengrass, but upon graduation it was a different story. Things went quick. She was from a respectable pureblooded family, and his was somewhat of an up and coming one, something that hadn’t been seen for a while. There was definitely a spark though, and while it had been ignored by Blaise during school, the same couldn’t be said by Daphne. Of course he was going to take every opportunity to better his social standing, and since there was already something there, it only made sense. They were married in 2004. From there, they worked, since that seemed the only right thing to do. Blaise took on a formidable position as a hitwizard, something he had been training for since graduation, Daphne continuing her passion as an actress. It wasn’t the most glamorous of jobs since it dealt with muggles, but holding down someone as glorious as her would never work. They didn’t need the money anyways, and she was rather good at the whole acting bit.

In June of 2006, after months of careful planning, their first child was born. Blaise had hoped for a son, one that could continue on with his lineage. Instead, he was granted a daughter, Liona. It was a struggle at first, but he soon realized that it was still his blood in his daughter, and that she could still be groomed to become better than he was, the same way a son could. Of course only a year later his son was born, but at this point he had his mind set up that giving them the perfect life would line everything up for them, the same way his mother had done for him. He switched professions to start; being a hitwizard with a young family was reckless, even for him, and so he became an Obliviator instead, so as to protect the world in which his children would become superiors in. Blaise was barely home, and the same went for Daphne as her own career took off. It hurt at first, leaving his children to be raised by nannies that weren’t of the best backgrounds, but there was only so much he could do without failing somewhere. The proudest moments of his life were when both children received their letters to Hogwarts, and subsequent sorting into Slytherin. They were about to start on the same journey that he had done almost twenty years earlier.

From there, not much has changed. The events of the previous year, deaths of muggleborns, only opened old wounds for many in his social class, reminding them of something they all witnessed decades before. In his opinion, these things were being conducted by a bunch of unruly children, unable to except that they wouldn’t make it anywhere in life without offing other children. He would have gladly still been a hitwizard so that he could do them the honor himself, because they were getting in the way of his children’s own successes. At the same time, the events didn’t both him in the slightest. His daughter and son were of great social standing and blood purity. He knew they were as safe at Hogwarts as he had been during his last few years there. Complete neutrality was how he made it to where he was now anyways. As for the Triwizard Tournament coming back, the same could be said for that. A competition of brains and brawn is intriguing, but it was only placed at Hogwarts again because of the issues from the previous year. The fame and glory from winning the tournament was only temporary anyways, so it was a waste of time by trying to build relations between schools that are vastly different one another.

With the attack on the Durmstrang and Beauxbatons transits, Blaise finally had the reason he needed to fully move forward with his transfer out of the Obliviator office and back into his old career: as a hit-wizard. He had been longing to make the switch for years, but the constant pressure from his wife, and the need to be alive because of the kids kept where he was, safe and sound as an Obliviator. His daughter’s graduation, and with his son nearing his completion at Hogwarts, he had a compelling enough case that Daphne couldn’t say no.

So transfer papers were filled out in a flash (or rather he had them filled out already, they just needed to be signed and dated), and within a few weeks he was situated back in his alma mater at the hit-wizard department. Having more hands on deck would help cull the problems more proactively, something he had gotten pretty good at as an Obliviator. The plan was to establish tighter security around Hogwarts once again during the upcoming year – the student population back to the normal amount. Of course, that wasn’t how things worked, and that awful deal with Ilvermorny following their own idiotic problem served to make things worse. The influx of foreign students and families entering his territory only means that he has to be more wary of who is doing what, and what that actually is. 

Except, being a hit-wizard again didn’t exactly scratch the itch that Blaise was looking for. To fix that, he took up the open Defense Against the Dark Arts position at Hogwarts. He had always enjoyed teaching new hit-wizards and witches and Obliviators, and the next obvious step was to work on the students at Hogwarts. While he dislikes the disorganization and ridiculousness of the students, it feels right to be teaching. Should anything happen at Hogwarts, he knows that he’ll be the first there to stop it, and that his decades of experience within various Ministry departments will help him.
[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]The Azkaban breakout more than ruffled a few of Blaise’s feathers. Allowing that to happen was a complete and utter failure on the Ministry’s part, and he let them know it. In a different universe, one where he never left the hit department and was presumably very high in the pecking order, he would have never let that happen to begin with. He could only yell at his former bosses and coworkers enough though, and being a professor at Hogwarts, there was very little he could do now aside from asking for more security around the school.

The summer of 2025 brought Hag’s Fever and, unfortunately, Blaise managed to catch it. He’s positive that he contracted it during the graduation ceremony, because there had been a very leaky, wizened warlock sitting directly behind him, coughing throughout the entirety of the event. He was stuck in St. Mungo’s for about a month, mostly because he couldn’t kick the nasty cough that accompanied the illness, and he didn’t want to return home until he was fully cured so as to avoid giving it to his mother. 

Now he has returned to Hogwarts for his second year of teaching, and is hoping that it stays just as quiet as the previous year.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@colin        [/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]he/him[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]26[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]EST[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]Support[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote][a href="https://alohomorax0.proboards.com/thread/5759"]Link To Plotter[/a] [/blockquote][/div][/div]