
[div align="center"][b]TW/CW:[/b] Child abuse, substance abuse, alcoholism, mentions of sex work

[div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://66.media.tumblr.com/42cc434983256bd82666255b8963350d/c1dc4b47d810b660-ce/s500x750/db524cbbaea09fdfd42a659da0d5d8af0be323fd.gif" alt="GIF" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]Daria Mikhailovna Krovopuskova[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]DAH-ree-yah Mee-KHAI-luhv-nuh KROVO-pisk-ov-uh[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Dasha (with most people in Britain), Dashyenka (by her siblings), Dashka (by her father)[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]15
March 3, 2010[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Cisgender female; she/her pronouns[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Half-blood[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Heterosexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]11 ⅛ inches, birch, dragon heartstring, surprisingly swishy[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Anastasia Bezrukova[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Dasha is 5'8" tall with a slim build. She has light brown hair that reaches past her shoulder blades and fair skin that tans easily in the summertime. Her eyes are grey-green in color, and she has thick, dark eyebrows. She has no prominent scars of which to speak, though she has a few here and there from her father’s abuse. The most visible of these are a series of small burn marks on her arms that have mostly faded. She also has her ears pierced once on each earlobe.

Dasha cares about her appearance, though she doesn’t fuss too much over it. Most often, she can be found wearing relatively casual clothing—typically Muggle in style—that is probably closer to what some might term “smart casual”. She is feminine, likes looking neat, and prefers to wear dresses and skirts when given the option.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Hogwarts; Ravenclaw (as of September 2025)

Homeschooled (2021–August 2025)
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]5th year (as of September 2025)
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Books; ribbons and bows; card games; Wizard's chess; pelmeni; cryptograms; thick sweaters; winged horses; summertime; staying up late[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Being around people who are drinking heavily; her father; Russian winters; mushrooms; wastefulness; using her patronymic; needless violence; snobbery; Bertie Bott's Every Flavour Beans; waking up early[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Dasha's greatest goal is to make sure that she and her siblings are able to live comfortably for the rest of their lives. She hopes to graduate from Hogwarts with the best marks that she can, though she doesn't know what she wants to do as a career yet.[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Fresh laundry, berries, and parchment[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Dasha most fears coming into contact with her father again. Second to that, she fears letting Dmitri down.[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote][b]clever[/b]

For most of her life, Dasha has had to rely on her intuition to understand the world around her. She is quick to piece together information based off of her previous experience, and she has also learned to look for patterns to make sense of what she cannot otherwise grasp. As she has gotten older and has studied more and more formally, her intelligence has moved beyond "street smarts", and she has proven herself to be very academically capable, as well.

[b]curious[/b]

Beyond mere capability, Dasha has a strong desire to learn new things. She wants to expand her horizons beyond the life that she knew in Russia. Whether she is learning more about the world and how it works or learning about other people's experiences, she will happily soak it all up.

[b]protective[/b]

Just as her older siblings were always there to protect her when she was too young to be able to defend herself, Dasha has gotten old enough to recognize just how much they sacrificed for her sake. Since she can't protect her older sister as easily as she can Dmitri, however, most of her protective streak is directed towards him. She worries about her brother's well-being, especially given his long hours at the Ministry of Magic.

[b]private[/b]

Although she isn’t necessarily aloof, Dasha is a very private person. She has learned to conceal the extent of her emotions and desires when necessary, lest her father or others use them against her. It probably doesn’t help matters that she has been physically isolated from most other people for a number of years or that her childhood was more turbulent than most, but she is trying to be more open.

[b]kind[/b]

For all of her distance, Dasha is also very kind. She might not make a big display of her affections, but she also isn’t the type to sit brooding in a corner. Even though she has done some questionable things, she doesn’t want to be defined by those. She is good-hearted and cares for others, and she hopes that that is evident enough to her peers once she starts school at Hogwarts.

[b]insecure[/b]

After having been mentally and physically beaten down for the majority of her life, Dasha has had to work on having more confidence in herself and her abilities. She has a tendency to doubt herself when it comes to matters related to her personal views and opinions, especially, and she would be more easily described as a follower than as a leader.

[b]rigid[/b]

Dasha prefers order to a lack of it, given her tumultuous upbringing. The upside to this is that she is often very diligent and disciplined, and can be found working on her schoolwork late into the night under her brother’s tutelage. The downside, meanwhile, is that she can often come across as being completely inflexible or bossy. This is the case particularly with those who don’t know her, but she’s really just trying to make some sense out of the chaos of the world.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Moscow, Russia[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote][b]mother:[/b]

Kseniya Yurievna Kiselyova, 1987–2010, prostitute, half-blood witch, identity unknown to Dasha

[b]father:[/b]

Mikhail Krovopuskov, 47, inmate at Russian wizarding prison, half-blood wizard, estranged

[b]half-sister (by father):[/b]

_____, 23, prostitute, Squib

[b]half-brother (by father)/guardian:[/b]

@dmitri, 22, Unspeakable, half-blood wizard

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A, though her brother owns birds.[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]While she knows that she had a mother once, Dasha has no recollection of the woman who bore her and abandoned her into the care of her father, Mikhail Krovopuskov. "Care", of course, was a loose term. Mikhail cared no more for Dasha than for the two children who had come before her and only viewed the infant—the result of a brief physical relationship—for the additional income that she might be able to earn for him. Any obligation to care for Dasha was placed upon her half-siblings, who—just children themselves—were hardly equipped to parent her.

Still, the presence of an infant wasn't a complete hindrance to Mikhail's alcoholic lifestyle and perpetual neglect of his offspring. Like her elder siblings before her, Dasha was sent out on the streets to earn their father the money that he felt he deserved.

Before she was ever capable of walking, Mikhail recognized that the trade-off of having another mouth to feed wasn't quite so bad. Carrying around an infant drew the pity necessary to bring in more money, which was about all that could be said for Dasha's addition to the family until she was old enough to understand what she was meant to be doing most of the time: earning her keep. Mikhail supplied only what was necessary to keep suspicions from being aroused about the state of his children, and Dasha attended magical and English-language schooling lessons alongside her elder brother as soon as she was old enough to sit still for them.

Most of what she learned in her earliest years was from her siblings, who had already learned how to survive both under their father's roof and without his guidance. She emulated what they did and how they were able to convince even grown-ups to part with their money. Sometimes, it was as simple as knowing what might pull at someone's heartstrings. On occasion, their targets weren't as willing, though Dasha viewed it as their own faults for being so obvious about where they kept their money.

There was a certain adrenaline rush that came with being on the streets, and it felt worlds better than the punishments that Dasha knew her father would dole out if she and her siblings didn't come back with enough money to suit his fancy—whatever that amount might have been on any given day. Although the circumstances were horrible, the need to come up with money fueled Dasha's creativity, and she picked up no shortage of useful skills to survive on the streets. She became aware of her surroundings and learned how to "read" people to know how gullible they might be (and which tricks were likely to work on them). It was helpful to be quick on her feet, too. As much as her siblings tried to protect her from their father's beatings, they weren't always successful.

Dmitri, by far, remained her biggest champion, though even he would spend more and more time away from the rest of the family as he entered his teen years. Dasha couldn't blame him for trying to avoid their father and his rage, even if he came back with more injuries than he had had the previous evening. She often dreamed of what it would be like to run away. Sometimes, she dreamt about finding her mother, until her father unceremoniously explained that the woman was dead. The fear of what their father would do to her if he caught her kept her from acting upon any of her fantasies about escaping for good.

Dasha continued her studies as much as her father would allow, though a handful of hours in a week didn't get her as far as she wanted. She continued to envision a life in which she might be able to escape to a dacha in the countryside or to one of the resort towns on the Black Sea—not because she had to, but because she [i]could[/i]. She wanted to make herself into something more than just the daughter of an intolerant and greedy alcoholic, as impossible as that seemed.

It took years, but Dmitri eventually became an adult. Although he didn't have much, he was able to free her from their father, for which Dasha was grateful. Their sister was able to get away, too, and she even moved to France to work as a model. For the first time, life seemed to be looking up.

Initially terrified that their father would demand her return, Dasha was provided with some closure when she learned that their father had been arrested—and eventually imprisoned. Eventually, too, she came to understand that her sister's modeling work wasn't as it seemed; she was in Russia and selling [i]herself[/i], rather than clothing or accessories.

After a few years with Dmitri, Dasha had begun to live the life that she had always imagined. It wasn't perfect, but it was worlds better than anything she had known before. Her brother was able to help her continue her studies. Dmitri, too, managed to make something of himself. He got a job as an Unspeakable with the British Ministry of Magic, and the two of them moved to a small village in the countryside—far enough from London to avoid the city, yet near enough for Dmitri to begin his work.

Dasha was hesitant to leave Russia; it was the only place that she had ever known, and she had heard that there had been a string of terrible things happening in Britain. At the same time, she remained hopeful; she had never had the opportunity to see the world before, and the closest she had gotten was through books.

Upon arriving in Britain, Dasha found that life for her wasn't too different from how it was in Russia. Dmitri went to the Ministry of Magic for work, but he would return to teach her in the evenings. The seclusion didn't bother her at first, but—as time went by—she began to entertain the idea of going to Hogwarts. As much as she loved her brother and couldn't imagine life apart from him, she wanted to learn more advanced forms of magic, too.

With the summer now ahead of her, Dasha has plans to attend Hogwarts in the upcoming school year in order to sit her OWLs. Having never attended a formal school in her life, she knows that she has much to prove but is eager to do it.[/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Having spent most of her life in Russia, Dasha only started to become aware of what was happening beyond her home country after her brother Dmitri became her guardian when she was eleven. She doesn't know every last detail of what has happened in the magical community of the United Kingdom over the past few years, though she knows that not all of it has been pleasant. She is aware that numerous politicians and students have been murdered, which does concern her; however, she has already lived a relatively rough life and knows that it cannot be any worse than what she has already dealt with.

Dasha is also aware of what transpired after the Triwizard Tournament, given the competition's international focus, and the damage done to Ilvermorny that resulted in their students' arrival to Hogwarts, although she was not living in Britain at that time. Given how dangerous things seemed, Dmitri chose to move away from London and to a smaller village to keep them both away from any trouble.

The destruction of Azkaban hit closest to home for Dasha, since her father is imprisoned in Russia. Fortunately, Azkaban was the only prison destroyed, which has given her some peace of mind as the British Ministry and however many other magical governments continue to work on their investigation. Although Dasha attended the Winter Festival in Hogsmeade shortly after her arrival in Britain, she was not there to witness the dragons descending upon the village.

Now, with the news of Hag's Fever spreading throughout the British Isles, Dasha’s concern has been heightened. She doesn't want to fall ill, but she knows that she doesn't have much choice in the matter. She had no plans to leave for Russia, anyway, so the situation could have been worse for her.

Of the most concern to her at present is the fact that she will be going to Hogwarts in September 2025. Realistically, she knows that there is a chance that something else could happen there, but the benefits of going to a real school and getting OWLs and NEWTs outweigh her concerns for her and her brother’s safety.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]@audrey[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]She/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]22[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]I don't even know anymore.[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]Current member![/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]@samira, @chrissy, @clarence, @parvati, @brody, @ezekiel, @penelope, @kaylee, @maxima, @muffet, @felix, @oona, @priscilla, @camila, @honey, @tamatha [/blockquote][/blockquote][/div][/div]