
[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt=" " style="max-width:100%;" src="https://64.media.tumblr.com/3634859ec189f535fd3214b2df2a36cf/tumblr_phlju0hY211xtaclho2_500.gif"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]caillen ailsa lancaster[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]kay-len isle-sa lan-cas-ter[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]cail, or cal.[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]sixteen | august 19th 2009.[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]half-blood.[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]straight.[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]apple, dragon heartstring, supple &amp; 10".[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]danielle rose russell.[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]cail looks almost identical to her playby. her hair while naturally dark, does get a little colour boost from the help of some magic. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling &amp; status[/b]
[blockquote]sixth year | ravenclaw.[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]student.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]quidditch, writing with a new quill, trying new things, friendly faces, animals, easy conversations, watching movies, walking through a forest in autumn, cooler weather, her family, listening to her grandparents stories, christmas, roasting marshmallows, camping, history, watching lightning.  [/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]failing, paper cuts, reptiles, getting sunburned, movies that last too long, music without meaning, nail polish, dull colours, when people try to understand, talking about her mother's death, her father (not really but she's angry).[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote][b][i]stubborn |[/i][/b] cail doesn't have a mind that's easily swayed from what she thinks, some might call her stubborn or obstinate but she knows it's much more than that. she's got courage in her convictions and how she things and she's confident enough in the morals she was raised with to be sure that she can usually make the right choices. she doesn't seek out the opinions of others often because she doesn't like people to assume that just because she's asked for their input she's going to change her mind. 

[b][i]impatient[/i][/b] | she's never really been what you could call a patient person. the world and the people in it often move far to slowly for cail. she doesn't like to wait and a lot of the time she'll find ways to get out of waiting but when she can't, she doesn't hold back from letting her annoyance be known. she does have a tendency to rush the things she does, though that shouldn't be mistaken for people thinking she's careless. she can take care and do things quickly. 

[i][b]focused[/b][/i] | when she's focused on a task, she's focused on it. it's not easy to sway her thoughts from what they're on when she enjoys what she's doing and when she's on a roll there's no pulling her attention away. she's goal driven and she strives to do everything she undertakes quickly, as best she can and to the satisfaction of whoever set her the task, whether that be her professors or herself. 

[b][i]quick temper[/i][/b] | she's got quite the temper and she doesn't hold back her bite. she might pull her punches here and there but her mouth is always quick, sharp and when she's angry she can be downright mean. she does often feel regret after she looses her temper but she's not one that's quick to apologize. a lot of the time she thinks that if someone's made her that mad that she snaps at them they they owe her the apology not the other way around. since recent events she's been finding it harder and harder to turn her back when someone angers her. 

[i][b]finicky[/b][/i] | she's something of a perfectionist and she likes things to be done a certain way. she knows that she has no control over how other people live their life or do things, but she can control how she does things and she does fight for control within her life. she doesn't like to feel like she doesn't have a grip and she'll fight tooth and nail to hold onto some sliver of control, regardless of what's going on in her life. 

[b][i]athletic[/i][/b] | cail could run before she could walk. she was always raring to go as a child and she channeled a lot of that energy into every sport she had the chance to play. over the years though she's settled into quidditch as the main sport she plays and she loves every moment of being in the air. she usually has some sort of ball close to her so she can throw it between her hands when she's thinking and she does like to run to clear her head when she needs it.  

[b][i]jumbled[/i][/b] | since the death of her mother she's felt like her brain is constantly spinning and she doesn't know how to stop it. everything changed in a moment and as much as she hates to admit it, she changed to. she's finding it harder to control her emotions, fighting back tears because she doesn't want her family to see her upset and trying to be as strong as she could for her brother and her father, the latter shut down after her mother's death and someone needed to try and keep their world from totally falling apart. she thinks she hates him for that but she doesn't really, she's just hurt, devastated and feeling like she lost both her parents in the same moment  [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]london | england.[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]frank edward lancaster | father | 37 | hogwarts professor.
catriona macleod-lancaster | mother | deceased.

--- --- lancaster | twin brother | 16 | hogwarts student. 

reginald edward lancaster | paternal grandfather | 68 | archaeologist.
ainsley elspeth macdougal | paternal grandmother | 60 | homemaker. 

malcolm james lancaster | paternal uncle | 42 | department of mysteries.
evanna jane lancaster | paternal aunt | 41 | quidditch player.
iona mary lancaster | paternal aunt | 36 | healer.  [/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]grey tabby cat called cricket.[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]cail was the first child of her parents. though that honour lasted all of five minutes before her brother came screaming into the world behind her. she was the only child for the first few moments of her life and she does at times still like to lord that over her brother's head when they're in the middle of an argument. both children were a welcome addition to the family they were born in, both of their little blonde heads so loved by their parents and their parents families. though cail didn't stay blonde. she grew up hearing from her family that her father had been so proud when the twins had been born blonde, that they looked like him rather than their mother. well it lasted a few months before, and these were her father's words, she had the audacity to start looking like her mother. her hair darkened as she grew older and eventually settled into a slightly duller version of the colour she has now. she does like to tease her father about it from time to time. her and her twin would be the only children of the couple but that suited cail just fine growing up. she had her brother and he was enough, she didn't need any other siblings to watch over, annoy when she was bored and protect when they needed. there was always someone to provide an alibi if she needed one and a person to lay the blame on when she could. not that it worked too often but no one could say she didn't try.

it was a happy childhood that she had and she loved every moment of it. there was always a pair of arms to hold her when she wanted and a person to talk to. it wasn't always her parents but that didn't bother her too much. she knew they had important jobs. the only time it was a problem was when she started learning about her father going on adventures with her grandfather. there were times she actively tried to sneak away with them because she hated being left behind while they were doing so many interesting things. she almost made it to the car in a suitcase one afternoon, before the latch had broken while her father had been lifting it into the trunk of her grandfathers car and she had tumbled to the ground, much to the adults surprise. needless to say she ended up staying at home. her childhood was filled with warm memories, of people who loved her and fun that she took a little too much for granted while she was growing up. 

it didn't take long for the twins to be old enough to go off to hogwarts and it seemed like no time at all between getting her letter and then standing on the platform of the hogwarts express with her luggage and eyes as wide as saucers as the reality of what was happening hit her. at least she had her brother, she wasn't going alone. she'll never admit that if she hadn't had her brother there she probably would have burst into tears and begged her parents to let her stay at home with them but she'd done what she could to keep it together for her brother. that's her story and she's sticking to it. she was quickly sorted into ravenclaw like her father before her and she had to admit there was a swell of pride when the hat called the house for her. she took her place among the sea of students and it was in the years that followed that really made her grow up. for the first few years her school years were good. she made friends, got good enough grades to make her parents happy and joined the quidditch team as soon as she was able to try out. then something shifted in the world at school and it would never be the same. there was death, deception and anger. students died, she lost friends she'd made and the school lost something she knew it would never be able to get back. no matter what was happening there was a feeling of something missing and it was something that no one would be able to replace. 

it was the summer before her sixth year started that she was finally able to go on one of those adventures with her grandfather. he took her along with him and she was thrilled at the chance to explore something she'd never seen before, to learn about things she'd never heard of and experience a place she'd only ever been able to read about. some might have thought it was just egypt that he'd taken her to but to her it was the most amazing place she'd ever seen. it was over all too quickly though and before she knew it she was back on her home soil and back to the life that offered just a little less excitment. little did she know that it would be the year that her own family changed for ever. it was the quidditch world cup. she had been desperate to go, to watch the action up close and experience the thrill of watching something so important up close and shile she'd thought her parents had decided not to, they surprised their children with tickets and they were off. of course their mother wouldn't be watching with them, she'd been invited to go to the ministers box. it's one of cail's biggest regrets that she didn't hug her mother before they'd parted ways but she'd never have guessed that that would be the last time she'd ever see her mother. 

hungry and desperate for food, her and her brother had begged to go get food and they'd been sent off with enough money to get the food and an instruction to say hi to their friends from their dad. it was while they were waiting in line for food with their friends that the stadium had exploded. dazed and confused from the chaos of what was happening around them, cail and her brother had been grabbed by their friends parents, though she fought her hardest to get back to where her parents were she eventually let herself be taken from the area and it would be hours before she reunited with her family. it was her grandparents at first. then their aunts and uncles but not their parents. it seemed like it took them forever to be told that their mother was dead and that their father had been injured but time stopped after that. cail felt like she couldn't breath, that the world had stopped spinning and nothing would ever be right again.

then her father came home from the hospital, only it wasn't her father. it was a shadow of the man he had been and it shocked cail. she knew it was unfair to expect him to be the same father she'd had before but she'd been holding onto the silly hope that when her father came home they would get back to some kind of normal. that he'd tell them things would be okay and that they'd all be okay. what came home was far from that. the next few weeks passed in something of a daze, her mother's funeral and her father's lack of life. it was like she was watching everything from somewhere else and no matter how hard she fought she couldn't find her way back to feeling like she was actually there. she took to escaping from the house into her mother's garden. her mother had been so proud of the garden and while cail hadn't inherited that love, she'd loved watching her mother while she'd been in there. being amongst the plants her mother had tended made her feel close to her. it was short lived though, as smart as cail was, gardening wasn't something that came naturally to her and slowly, no matter how hard she tried, her mother's garden slowly died before her eyes and it was like loosing her mother all over again. it was when the last flower finally died that cail let every emotion she'd been holding onto out into the world. she grabbed everything within reaching distance and thrown it at every surface she could, hearing the sounds echoing in the space around her. it hadn't been enough though, it wasn't enough. she'd grabbed her wand in her fit of despair and without thinking she'd set fire to the field of death around her and sunk back to her knees, watching everything in front of her burn. 

it was there her uncle found her, kneeling in the dirt, face red from the heat of the flames and the ferocity of her tears and he'd quelled the fire before it could take anything but the garden and he'd wrapped his arms around her and she found herself falling into them, holding onto him for dear life as she'd sobbed until she couldn't sob anymore. it was only when she'd calmed down that he helped her into the house and into the arms of her grandmother and then he'd left, saying something about frank needing a wake up call. she didn't know what he'd meant by that and she hadn't been able to see what her uncle had done because her grandmother had taken her to clean up. it was a few days after that that she went back to school. she couldn't be in the house anymore and she'd talked it over with her grandmother who thought the change might help too. she was assured that she could come home if she needed but being at school helped. it helped to get back into some normalcy and to have a routine and to know what was expected of her every day. she could focus on that, rather than being at home. 

she didn't know what to say when her father joined the teaching staff at hogwarts. the days between him bring a drunk on their couch and him becoming their professor were few and she couldn't help but think it wouldn't last. he'd done nothing in the last while to give her any faith that he would be different at school as he had been at home and as much as she loved the class he'd taught she dropped it. unable to face him when he first started teaching. things did slowly start to get better though, the longer he was at school the softer her heart started to get towards him. she still holds a lot of anger towards him, though she's not sure if she's even really angry at him or if he's just the scapegoat for everything she's feeling at the moment, she's not willing to admit that fully to herself just yet. so she's throwing herself into her studies, her quidditch and her extra curriculars to help her keep her focus and to keep her looking forward, because it hurts too much to look back. she needs to keep looking towards her future. it hurts less than her past. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]shadow.[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her.[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]a spring chicken.[/blockquote]
[/div][/div]