
[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="http://aroundmovies.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/Kristen-Stewart_What-Just-Happened_2008.jpg"][/div]

hello there, my name is [b]zenevieva novell[/b] but you can call me [b]zen[/b]. i'm a [b]ravenclaw student [/b]and [b]16 [/b] so that makes me a [b]sixth year[/b] at [b]hogwarts - previously ilvermorny[/b]. You could say I'm [b]intelligent, knowledgeable, & witty[/b] but I personally think that I am [b]quiet, warm-hearted and stubborn.[/b]. People say I look a lot like [b]kristen stewart (in her younger days pls)[/b], but I don't really see it...

[div align="center"][font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][i][b]zenevieva mira novell[/b][/i][/font][/font][/div]

[b][i]pronunciation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]zehn-ah-viy-vah ([a href="https://www.babynamespedia.com/pronounce/Zenevieva"]see here for guidance[/a]) // mir-ah // noh-vell[/blockquote]
[b][i]nickname:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]everyone around zenevieva calls her zen. considering her name is way too long. she's also open to nicknames people want to give her.[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]16.[/blockquote]
[b][i]date of birth:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]22nd feb 2008[/blockquote]
[b][i]gender & pronouns:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]female -- she/her[/blockquote]
[b][i]blood status:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]half-human/witch & half-vampire // Dhampyr[/blockquote]
[b][i]sexuality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]bisexual.

[/blockquote]
[b][i]schooling:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]Ilvermorny - Horned Serpent [formerly]
Hogwarts - Ravenclaw [currently]

[/blockquote][b][i]occupation:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]currently a student, but zen hopes to intern for the ministry within the department of regulation and control of magical creatures, with dreams to eventually lead a certain department in the near future.[/blockquote]
[b][i]wand:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]zen's wand is made of coffee wood and has a core of pegasus feather.  it is 11 and 1/2 inches long and is supple. it is darkly coloured and is roughly carved[/blockquote]
[b][i]playby:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]kristen stewart (in her younger days, like 2008 time...)[/blockquote]
[b][i]appearance:[/i] [/b]
[blockquote]zenevieva is very much like the younger version of her playby. she stands mid-height at 5'4 with long brunette hair and due to her mother being a vampire (once a half-blood witch), zen picked up her thin like appearance and remains like that to this very day. i.e, the novell girl struggles to put on weight at times. unlike most people zenevieva is extremely pale and struggles to tan as from her half-vampire nature - she becomes sunburnt instead. when zen was a newborn baby, a flicker of red would linger around her large green eyes but slowly dissolved / disappeared as she aged. during the one moment each month that zenevieva needs to feed, she develops small-like fangs, something that would be seen as baby fangs in comparison to her mother's. on her right wrist, zen always wears her mother's bracelet while her parent's wedding rings rest upon her neck; looped in a chain they gave to her as an early teen.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personality[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]likes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]books, music, school, movies, her aunt, moonlight, good dreams[/blockquote]
[b][i]dislikes:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]nightmares, the sun, her struggles with her weight and skin, the anniversaries of her parent's death, the fact she doesn't have cool powers like her mom did.[/blockquote]
[b][i]erised:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]as a current student, zenevieva strives to become the first half-human, half-vampire to work within the ministry. she wants to control the figures in which wizards and witches are attacked by other creatures, but knows she lacks the experience within it.[/blockquote]
[b][i]amortentia:[/i][/b]
[blockquote](strange but not uncommon) the smell of blood, the ocean air and the smell from the ocean overall.[/blockquote]
[b][i]boggart:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]zen has a few fears:
- fears she'll somehow attack her aunt
- somehow drink more blood than she needs
- burn alive

she also dislikes the smell of garlic, something natural within her nature.[/blockquote]
[b][i]overall personality:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]zenevieva has always been a quiet girl. even after her birth, her parents were left worried as the new-born novell barely made any sound. as she grew, zen felt it to be rather challenging when making friends. after all, who wanted to be friends with a vampire? because of this, zenevieva played close attention to her studies - being known as a rather intelligent student amongst her teachers.

though with positive attributes of a person came their downsides. because of her fears on what she could do with her vampiric abilities, zenevieva always avoided taking risks and would play out her life in a safe way which also led to her stubbornness. once her mind was settled on something, it would potentially take everything out of her parents to talk the novell girl out of it. she refused to give up things she had a passion for so easily.

while zenevieva is what most people call: awkward, she tries her best to remain kind, polite and warm-hearted. she sympathises with others easily, especially those who are/were being bullied or have problems of their own. while she's a good listener, zenevieva forgets that most times its okay to speak upon her own problems, but instead keeps the pain of her parents death and her non-stop struggle with pale skin and weight gain to herself.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]personal history[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]mother:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]lucienne novell (neé edwards), 41, deceased, half-blood turned vampire.[/blockquote]
[b][i]father:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]aleksei novell, 44, deceased, half-blood.[/blockquote]
[b][i]siblings / relatives:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]zenevieva has no siblings and very little family. after her parents death she lived with her aunt (mother's sister)

adèle edwards, late twenties, half-blood, hogwarts alum - hufflepuff, zen's legal guardian.[/blockquote]
[b][i]pets:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]as zenevieva is allergic to some animals, so she never obtained a pet until her 16th birthday. after turning 16 her aunt gifted her with a snowy owl which the novell girl later named after her father for a pet.[/blockquote]
[b][i]history:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]on a chilly day somewhere in north america, in late february of 2008, the quiet cries of the new baby novell were heard. named zenevieva mira novell based on her mixed background (british, american, french, russian) as well as for her parent's dying love of the ocean. (as zenevieva is claimed to mean 'white wave') - she grew up in a small household with just her father and mother. the two elder novell's had been trying for a baby for a long time - with complications coming from her mother: lucienne's side as she was once a half-blood witch turned into a vampire after being attacked one night in london. to zenevieva; who was later nicknamed zen, growing up with just her mother and father and no siblings was both a blessing and a curse. throughout her childhood they put all their attention onto her, but at times she felt rather lonely too. especially when she would watch muggle children run off to the school buses with their siblings.

while she was a half-blood, as a half-human, half-vampire, her parents feared for what their daughter could become. there was no line of other vampires within the edwards or the novell family, nor did either family want to provide help. once word got out of lucienne's attack and later pregnancy, the communication from each side of the family decreased drastically, with only her aunt adèle from her mother's side keeping in contact.

life was [i]normal[/i] enough for zenevieva. she was able to feed on human food around muggles while she attended muggle school and fed upon blood with her mother a couple times a month. when zenevieva turned 11, she shortly received an acceptance letter from [b]Ilvermorny School of Witchcraft and Wizardry[/b] - which left both her father and mother rather surprised as they were unsure of zenevieva's possible magical abilities. within a matter of a few short weeks zen was pulled out from muggle school and set off with her mother to prepare herself for the start of the new term.

upon her first night in Ilvermorny, zenevieva recalls being scared, her fingers fiddling with each other, her mouth closed while her eyes widened. zenevieva was already a quiet person but surrounded by other students who seemed to be [i]incredibly normal[/i] somehow increased her shyness. she would compare herself to the many other students, her skin extremely pale - almost sickly looking, and while young with a lot of growing still in need to complete, she felt rather small and frail. but, when her name was called to stand upon the symbol of the Gordian Knot set into the middle of the stone floor, zenevieva just chewed upon her bottom lip out of sheer nervousness. cheers from the upper balcony soon pulled her out of her own mind-set, leading zenevieva to look upon the enchanted carvings - she noticed that the crystal set into the forehead of the horned serpent had lit up, housing her into Horned Serpent. 

from her first year to her fifth, zenevieva tried to be the best student she could be. for herself and for her parents. she studied hard and tried to make friends at the best of her ability, even though her shy and quiet nature got the best of her at times. though within her fourth year, she suffered with small amounts of bullying from students in other houses. they picked upon the complexion of her skin and her strange nature as a vampire. considering zenevieva was only half - she didn't have all of the abilities her mother had been blessed with. the bullies had picked this up to, and would mock her for not turning into a bat or even biting them. she was teased for [i]being different.[/i]

every trip home between her fourth and fifth year was difficult for the novell girl as she would keep her secrets of being picked on a secret. though, eventually her mother discovered the teasing and later threatened the parents of the children to result to serious means - i.e. reporting to the school. although, considering most parents were afraid of zenevieva's mother, the children who were bullying zen soon stopped. but that didn't mean the tragedy that was to shortly follow had stopped.

after the final term of her fifth year, zenevieva returned home, greeted by her aunt and a few fellow lawful wizards. from her aunt's side of the story, zenevieva was told that both her mother and father were killed mysteriously meaning somebody had broken the strict laws placed to protect the different creatures within the magical realm. though, later on zenevieva soon discovered, her mother, while feeding upon her father - as he always offered at least a few times in a week to avoid increasing the numbers of injured muggles - had somehow lost her own control, draining him completely thus killing him. within the laws of the magical world, zenevieva knew that killing a human was punishable by death. resulting with the truth of her parents.

from her parents death came to the downfall of zenevieva as a person. after moving north america to live with her aunt in london, zen was soon transferred to [b]Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry[/b] where she was sorted into the [b]house of Ravenclaw[/b] to start her sixth year and finish her academics. living in a new place that she barely visited as a child and starting a new year in a new school was frightening for the novell girl, especially because she had no clue to how people would be around her, but as zenevieva soon discovered that many students were demi-humans like herself, zen became increasingly comfortable. although that doesn't mean she still isn't incredibly shy.

in the midst of moving from her home to london, news broke out of harry potter's disappearance and later on his tragic death - to zenevieva, who was grieving at the time, it didn't affect her completely; but instead tugged at her heart as a painful reminder for those she had just lost.[/blockquote]
[b][I]site events reaction:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]during the move and the settling in to hogwarts, zenevieva was disgusted around the events that surrounded england. the deaths of the ministers of magic and hogwarts frightened her the most as hogwarts would be her new [i]'home'[/i] while the ministry was a place zen dreamed to work within. but with the deaths of hogwarts students came along the student run-group that zen showed some interest but refused to join - as she hated taking risks / being involved in violence/chaos. 

along with this, she soon discovered the uprising of the group named the Purifiers. their attacks within Kings Cross, the Durmstrang ship and Beauxbaton's carriage only worried the novell girl even further. [i]why had she moved to england at such a horrible time?[/i] as a young student, zenevieva knew she couldn't do much, but potentially join the student run group. it's something she's still considering.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"]________________________________________________________[/div]

[font face="times new roman"][font size="6"][b][i]alias[/i][/b][/font][/font]

[b][i]name:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]haise or felly[/blockquote]
[b][i]age:[/i][/b]
[blockquote][s]18[/s][/blockquote]
[b][i]time zone:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]GMT[/blockquote]
[b][i]reference:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]uwu[/blockquote]
[b][i]other characters:[/i][/b]
[blockquote]@dana, @edrik[/blockquote][/div][/div]