
[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img alt="" src="https://66.media.tumblr.com/8aa5f0437140b05f55a2b605e561edb9/bb1442671e0c779a-99/s1280x1920/530936671b2a9cf10fa9ef86bde7b53b59a07d7a.jpg" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]Thursday Astrid Weekly[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]thruz-dei az-trid weak-lee[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b]
[blockquote]Thor - From the origin of Thrusday “Thors-day”
Russ
Astrid[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]16
March 17th[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Female She/her[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]half-blood, half-vampire[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Demi-Sexual[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]13 1/7th, Walnut, Phoenix[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]charlotte free[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Standing at a remarkable 5 feet tall, Thursday has a twiggy thin body type.  Being half vampire, she does have a naturally athletic physique. She has always had a sensitivity to bright lights, and therefore, always has a pair of sunglasses available.  Being the last girl of the family, and such a small petite figure, she was always her adoptive mother’s little doll.  Her mother would stock her closet with the girliest and poofiest clothing. As she grew older, she refused to wear the clothes, resorting to stealing her brothers clothes and wearing them instead.  They finally compromised by dying her hair from the natural dark brown, to a soft pink color.  Now she prefers to wear baggy pieces of clothing, but will also wear leggings and yoga pants.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling:[/b]
[blockquote]Ilvermorny - Horned Serpent 1-4th
Hogwarts - Ravenclaw 5th-6th
[/blockquote]
[b]schooling status:[/b]
[blockquote]6th year
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]Sweets of all kinds - dark Chocolate, Baked goods, pastries, candy
Video games
Singing in the shower
Her family
Most types of music
Nighttime 
Warm rain
Ancient runes class
technology/programing
Sunglasses
Bast her Kneazle[/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b]
[blockquote]Being alone
Being in big crowds
Eating - sometimes, depending on her mood
Garlic (she’s allergic to it)
Being asked if she is okay
Mornings
Everyones eyes on her
Being made to be super social
Bright sunny days - Her eyes are super light sensitive
Her dark moods[/blockquote]
[b]erised:[/b]
[blockquote]Design her own video game[/blockquote]
[b]amortentia:[/b]
[blockquote]Sweets
Oranges
The smell after it rains
Fire from a fireplace or campfire[/blockquote]
[b]boggart:[/b]
[blockquote]Witch hunters
Being left, lost or forgotten
Disappointing her adoptive family[/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Thursday has two main moods, one good and one that she considered being her dark mood. The first is her favorite.  And more common when she is around people who she is really close to, mostly just her siblings.  When that happens, she can get quite talkative, especially when it is about a subject she likes, such as technology or video games. Because of her natural resistance to injury, she tends to not realize that a situation, like climbing a tall tree, or running around on a tall roof is dangerous. Thursday is very light on her feet, and when not wearing shoes, usually doesn't make a sound.  She will try to make herself known around her siblings, especially around those who she knows to be on the jumpier side.

When in her dark mood, she is much less talkative, and would rather stay hidden in the background. It becomes harder for her to get out of bed, or even to do things that she normally enjoys.  During these times she can become quite cuddly, or curled inwards. It is also during these moods that she has less of a want to eat food.  If she is not in the mood to eat, she will usually just conveniently forget.  If she is at a meal with her family or friends she may eat a bite or two, but mostly just move her food around the plate.  The only food that she will rarely say “no” to during these moods, is sweets.  Something is better than nothing.

Thursday has an amazing singing voice, but doesn’t share it too often.  She also dabbles in a number of instruments, like the violin, drums, and mostly the guitar.  Unlike many of her siblings, Thursday is not a very social butterfly. Because of this, she has never been one to have many friends.  Aside from her siblings, she usually only has a small handful of close friends at one time. She does not like confrontation or take critique very well.  She internalizes what she did wrong and expands it until she cant take it any more.  And if she knows that she is right on something, but someone wants to debate it, she would rather agree that they are right, even if they aren’t, than fight about it.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Born in Anaheim California,  USA
Lives in Beverly Hills California, USA[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]Kieran Gray - Birthfather, vampire, died before birth
Zoe Ericson - Birthmother, muggleborn, died in childbirth
April Weekly – adopted mother, actress
August Weekly – adopted father, enchanted calendar exec
Monday Weekly – adopted sister age 17
Tuesday Weekly – adopted brother age 17
Wednesday Weekly – adopted sister age 17
Charlie Weekly - Adopted sister age 16
Friday Weekly – adopted brother age 16
Saturday Weekly - adopted brotherage 16
Sunday Weekly – adopted brother age 15[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b]
[blockquote]Kneezle named Bast who helps in an ESA capacity [/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Zoe Ericson was born to no-maj parents, and went to school at Ilvermorney. Shortly after graduation, she got a job at MACUSA and that was where she met the vampire Kieran. The two fell in love, but before the engaged couple could get married, he was murdered by witch hunters.  A few months later, Zoe gave birth to her little girl that she named Astrid.  The woman died shortly after that.  Her parents wanted to take the child, and raise her as their own, but the wizarding government forbad them from even seeing the tiny, pale little half vampire.

She started her life in the foster system, no one really wanted to keep her for too long.  While she doesn’t have many memories about this time, she was passed around enough that when she was adopted by the Weekly family, she was certain that they were just another in a long line of temporary residents.

At the age of 2, she and a boy around the same age were given to this family.  The word they used was “Adopted.” This word didn’t mean much to her. The arrived at a large house in Beverly Hills where there were already three kids there.  This didn’t come as a surprise, most foster houses had other kids.  It took a long time for her to realize that this was a permanent home. After she started to figure out that they wouldn’t be getting rid of her, she started to pay more attention to the other kids.  Two were older than she was, and one was around her age.  They started to call her Thursday, which was fine by her, and the other boy was Friday. After that, it didn’t take too long for her to get very attached to the others, finally speaking to them 6 months after being adopted. The best part about this new home, was that they were all different, like her.

Years later, the family adopted an additional 2 kids, naming them Saturday and Sunday. She did what she could to help them feel welcome, but being shyer than the others, she did it in her own way.  Namely by staying in the same room as them, trying to play with them, and not running away when they approached her. As the years moved on, she started to come out of her shell more, getting louder, and actually telling the others what she really wanted.

When she was 10 years old, Monday and Wednesday went away.  Mom and dad said that they were going to a special magical school, and that she would be joining them next year. This was hard on her.  And only constant letters and reasuances helped her through it.  Around this time, an eighth and final sibling was added to their family, an older boy named Tuesday.

A year later, Thursday, with most of her other siblings, went off to Ilvermorney.  She was sorted into her house, away from some of her siblings, and immediately developed a bad case of homesickness.  She was helped through it, and took to her classes.  She started to excel and fell in love with learning. After getting past some of these issues, she was determined to make friends.  She wasn’t too successful when she decided to start to learn how to program.

Her 5th year of school, Thursday, and the rest of the Weekly children were sent off to a European school named Hogwarts, where she was sorted into Ravenclaw house.
 [/blockquote]
[b]site events reaction:[/b]
[blockquote]Thursday isn’t one to pay much attention to the news, but when she learned about the vandalism at Ilvermonrey, she was upset.  She was used to the place now, and liked it, now she would have to get used to a new place with new people.  This time she was going to try to be social.  Though, she wasn’t as successful as her siblings were.

She only heard about the Azkaban break out from those around her.  It sounded scary, but also didn’t directly affect her, like her emotional issues that she was plagued with.

Now that they were stuck in this country, away from their family, unable to go home, she’s been having a rough time.  It was good that her adopted parents spent money to rent a penthouse for the kids, she heard that others were going to an orphanage.  She wouldn’t be able to handle it. She is happy that she can be close to her siblings and away from an orphanage. [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Sophi[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]she/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote]older every day[/blockquote]
[b]time zone:[/b]
[blockquote]Mountain[/blockquote]
[b]reference:[/b]
[blockquote]My roommate lives here[/blockquote]
[b]other characters:[/b]
[blockquote]More by the moment[/blockquote][/div][/div]
