
[div align="center"][div style="width:500px;font-family:georgia;font-size:10px;text-align:justify;color:black;padding:3px;"][div align="center"][img src="https://64.media.tumblr.com/12149216e65acfd79d8af62618d32626/d53d1b13296ac252-53/s500x750/9e606271afa983cf6d5159c558d6389cd3ddda1b.gifv" style="max-width:100%;"][/div]
[div align="center"][font size="5"]xena alice willowmoore[/font][/div][hr]
[b]pronunciation:[/b]
[blockquote]Zee-Na Al-ess Will-oh-more[/blockquote]
[b]nickname:[/b] 
[blockquote]Xen (Pronounced Zen)[/blockquote]
[b]age and birthday:[/b]
[blockquote]15
 February 1st 2011[/blockquote]
[b]gender and pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]Cis female - She/Her pronouns (but will respond to They/Them as well)[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]basic info[/font][/div][hr]
[b]blood status:[/b]
[blockquote]Muggleborn[/blockquote]
[b]sexuality:[/b]
[blockquote]Questioning[/blockquote]
[b]wand:[/b]
[blockquote]a simple birch wand. The length is twelve and three quarters inches long. The core consists of hippogriff heartstring.[/blockquote]
[b]playby:[/b]
[blockquote]Aislinn Paul[/blockquote]
[b]appearance:[/b]
[blockquote]Xen looks like her playby. She’s got a round face and dirty blonde hair. She’s around 5’4'' tall and has an average build. She usually wears her hair cut shorter and loosely curled.[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]education and jobs[/font][/div][hr]
[b]schooling &amp; status[/b]
[blockquote]Ravenclaw, 4th year @ Hogwarts 
[/blockquote]
[b]current occupation:[/b]
[blockquote]N/A[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personality[/font][/div][hr]
[b]likes:[/b]
[blockquote]reading, academics, staying out of trouble, butterbeer, snow, coffee, cookies, water (drinking and bodies of), lavender, plants, [/blockquote]
[b]dislikes:[/b] 
[blockquote]tea, carrots, travel (gives her anxiety), spice (hot sauce, etc), conflict,  [/blockquote]
[b]overall personality:[/b]
[blockquote]Xen is a good girl. Or at least she really wants to be. She spent her childhood wanting to get good marks in school and wanting to please her dad and step-mother. She wanted to give everyone around her a positive reason to pay attention to her. She wanted to prove her worth and prove she belonged in her family. She grew up with a lot of anxiety over the fact that their father chose to take her with him in her parents divorce and chose to leave Xan, her older sister, with their mother. The reason behind the custody agreement was never made clear to her.

Xen is friendly and happy, she likes to be known as someone who gets along well with everyone and fits in. She’s been known to mold her own personality based on those around her because fitting in is easier. As a ravenclaw she does consider herself fairly whitty and good in conversation, but she has her moments when talking at all is the last thing she wants to do. As a child, Xen found herself drawn to the world of books and she let that shape a lot of her personality. She’s imaginative and likes to see the color in the world around her as a character in a story would. 

Xen’s biggest worries are around her schooling. She aims high and studies hard and while she isn’t sure yet what she wants to do after school, she wants to get good grades all around so she can keep her options open. She’s most interested in plants and potions. Digging a little deeper, (which she doesn’t normally let herself do,) she worries about doing something to upset her father. She doesn’t have any reason to suspect he might disown her or cut her out of his life, as he’s been nothing but a loving parent to her, but seeing the way he distanced himself from her sister and mother left a scar on her that she doesn’t know how to heal. It’s left her feeling the need to be careful and watch herself subconsciously. 

 [/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]personal history[/font][/div][hr]
[b]origins:[/b]
[blockquote]Born and raised in Wales, moving to London soon with her family[/blockquote]
[b]relations:[/b]
[blockquote]
Jane Willowmore nee Bridges - Mother, muggle (Terminally Ill)
@xenon   &nbsp;- Father, 40, Police, Muggle
Amie Willowmoore - Step-mother, 35, Auror, Halfblood

----- - 16, Step-Brother, Hogwarts

The Trips
Christopher - half-brother, 3
Devin - half-brother, 3
James - half-brother, 3

@xantha   - Sister, Muggle, 19
[/blockquote]

[b]pets:[/b] 
[blockquote]no personal pets[/blockquote]
[b]history:[/b]
[blockquote]Xena was born the second child of Xenon and Jane Willowmoore on February 1st of 2011. She had a very normal childhood as far as she was aware. She spent most of her days reading books, attending muggle school, and wandering around the Welsh countryside with her friends. She was close to her old sister and idolized her growing up. Xan was older and cooler and everything Xen wanted to be. Xen began showing signs of magic young but neither of her parents seemed to notice, probably because at the time they didn’t know what to look for. It mostly had to do with books. Xen had a way of getting books to follow her wherever she went. The first time she noticed, she was 7. She was sitting out on the lawn on a rare sunny day and wished she had remembered her book on the coffee table in the den. And then there it was. That particular event only happened once and she was never able to replicate it again, but she couldn’t count the number of times books would fall off of herself when she was upset, or flip a few pages by themselves if she was confused. She never told anyone about any of this. She had read Matilda: everyone would think she was a freak. 

Xen noticed the distancing of her parents as she got older but she tried not to think much of it. She was young and she didn’t understand grown-up relationships and she didn’t really want to pretend to - they seemed so complicated. However, the last thing she expected in her life was for them to actually divorce, and not only that, but for her dad to remarry pretty soon after and leave the two girls with their mom. All this following the murder of their neghbors. Xen was young at the time of the murder and didn’t see the connection between the murder and the arrival of her future Mother-in-law, but looking back she understands that was the cause of the split.

The three of them were alright like that for a while, but when their mom fell ill and it was decided that she needed 24/7 care, the girls suddenly found themselves alone. There was a time when Xen thought it would just be her and Xan. She trusted her sister with her life. But then her dad showed up and brought her to live with him. Xen wasn’t sure why he had taken her and left Xan on her own, nor does she know anything regarding the details of this arrangement. She moved in with her new step-mom and step-brother, and when her hogwarts letter arrived less than a year later, things started to fall into place. She had been brought into the family because she was like them and Xan wasn’t. Xen understood the need to keep their world hidden from *most* muggles. But she couldn’t help but wonder why her father got to know but her sister didn’t. 

Xen kept up with her sister over the years as best as she could despite the separation. The two wrote letters to one another and were able to see each other on occasion, but it was tough to see them too often. Her dad was accommodating and never tried to keep her away from her sister and mother, but between family events and her own school it was tough to find time. Eventually it got easier and easier to be without them without Xen even realizing how much time went between visits. 

Her first three years were filled with drama but nothing that personally affected her, thank goodness. Between the explosions, the triwizard tournament (which was thought was really cool until the end), the arrival of the ilvermorny kids (which gave her a lot of new friends), and now dodging Hags Fever, she’s hoping that her last few years will be less eventful and she’ll be able to graduate without her school burning down first. Her goals include receiving O’s on all her subjects, and making prefect in the next year, and head girl in her seventh. 

[/blockquote]

[div align="center"][font size="5"]alias[/font][/div][hr]
[b]name:[/b]
[blockquote]Ali.[/blockquote]
[b] pronouns:[/b]
[blockquote]She/her[/blockquote]
[b]age:[/b]
[blockquote][s]old[/s] 25[/blockquote]
[/div][/div]
